{
	"catalog": [
	{
		"id":301,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Hijinx Studios", "Konami"],
			"synopsis":"On the continent of Sostegaria, two rival kingdoms stand on the brink of war. Caught in the tide of battle is young orphan Tobias Martin. Driven to defend his homeland, and to avenge those already fallen, Tobias enlists with his comrades to fight for peace. But all is not what it seems, and they face a threat far deadlier - and closer - than they know.<br><br>The rich storyline of Vandal Hearts: Flames of Judgment expands the universe, serving as the prequel to the original Vandal Hearts. Flames of Judgment combines the speedy RPG pace of the original with easily accessible user mechanics and sleek presentation design.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jlhOlJvlpRk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pa0JwQcHdtM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Vandal-Hearts/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/vandal-hearts-flames-of-judgment/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/vandal-hearts-flames-of-judgment"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Vandal Hearts Wiki",
				"url":"http://vandalhearts.wikia.com/wiki/Vandal_Hearts:_Flames_of_Judgment"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":302,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Arcade"],
			"synopsis":"Join Wordsworth the Owl in a series of fiendish and brain bending word games. Rearrange the letters to complete a variety of crossword-style games against the clock. Succeed, and you'll unlock challenging and exciting new games! With its beautiful presentation and pick-up-and-play appeal, KrissX is immediately accessible to everyone!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rq86TBy3-lU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Znr9Xy4stZ0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/KrissX/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/krissx/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/krissx"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":303,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Zoe Mode"],
			"synopsis":"Chime mixes up the addictive action of puzzle games like Tetris with elements of music synthesizing. You arrange note blocks on a grid which form patterns of sound, then secure them by surrounding them with other blocks, intensifying the audio and creating new melodies as you play. As you build larger block segments (quads) and cover the grid, the combo meter starts and the underlying song develops in full. But take care - if you build yourself into a corner, the blocks shatter and the music dies.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w2Cr9P0BLW8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aEwwGPyMq8I"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/977476-chime/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Chime/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/chime/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/chime"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":304,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Introversion Software"],
			"synopsis":"The world of Darwinia is a surreal and retro place, filled with epic fractal vistas and populated by iconic video game sprites from the past twenty years of computer games. The world is locked in warfare and on the verge of self-destruction, as the once peaceful Darwinians are besieged by a massive Red Viral onslaught. Against the backdrop of this war, this game within a game takes place.<br><br>This Xbox Live edition of the innovative and captivating action/strategy game by Introversion Software features both the original Darwinia and its follow-up multiplayer component, Multiwinia.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mxNPlx9vBWc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m6Ei9_SDpSM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Darwinia-Plus/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/darwinia/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/darwinia+"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":305,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["The Odd Gentleman"],
			"synopsis":"Enter a macabre and comical silent film world filled with mischief, time travel, and delicious pie. Record yourself and harness your time bending abilities to cooperate, compete against, and disrupt your past, present, and future selves. Winterbottom's debut misadventures present whimsical spin on the notions of time, space, and play.<br><br>Mr. P.B. Winterbottom is a villainous gentleman with a predilection for pies. Swiping the mysterious Cherry Chronoberry pie changed everything for our beloved Winterbottom... one bite made him more than an ordinary pie-grabbing humbug. That first taste changed him into something quite extraordinary, granting him the ability to break the rules of time. With these newfound time recording tricks up his cufflink, and with the help of his time clones, Winterbottom can now snatch pies with the greatest of ease. But on his journey to devour every pie, Winterbottom must mind the signs... the perils of being unstuck in time.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_AaCIe4d7Hs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jvu5ri6LEiA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/971669-the-misadventures-of-pb-winterbottom/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Winterbottom/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-misadventures-of-pb-winterbottom/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-misadventures-of-pb-winterbottom"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":306,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Pieces Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Rock on and harmonize the unity between music and 2D platformer! As you control your character through the artful stages, you play the game as if it were a jammin' rock song. Blast your enemies with riff combos and create your own soundtracks with each \"strum\" of a chord. You will have an ever-changing experience each time a stage is repeated.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cwI7hFFAEaI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lYfIdaTZuHk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fret-Nice/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fret-nice/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fret-nice"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":307,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["W!Games"],
			"synopsis":"In Greed Corp, you must find the delicate balance between harvesting the land for resources and preserving it to stay alive. Will you defend your territory or sacrifice it to keep it out of enemy hands? Manage the finite available resources to build your army and use the collapsing terrain to your advantage. Destroy your enemies, or destroy the very land they stand on, before they do it to you.<br><br>This game features a comprehensive single player campaign, introducing you to the four factions that inhabit the world. A large collection of unique maps is available outside of the campaign, specifically designed for 2, 3, or 4-player battles. Matches can be played with any combination of local, online and AI players, allowing for quick access to multiplayer action and offering multiple unlockables for a variety of challenges.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yqnC6_obOnY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T5mmLDb6Oco"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Greed-Corp/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/greed-corp/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/greed-corp"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":308,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sarbakan"],
			"synopsis":"Dr. Diggabone's getting too old for archaeological digs, or so he says. Truth be told, he's just plain lazy ... That's where you jump into Lazy Raiders and take control as you spin and flip mazes to send the Doctor or your Avatar on a gravity-defying quest for lost relics that would bring him instant fortune and glory. Of course you'll have to deal with greedy thieves, pesky minions, and ingenious traps along the way. If there weren't any challenges, you'd just grow lazy -- and we wouldn't want that, would we?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qZd6bz9teW8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sYMAr288prw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lazy-Raiders/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lazy-raiders/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lazy-raiders"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":309,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Signal Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Put your foot soldiers, snipers, cavalry, and fighter pilots to the test in Toy Soldiers. In this action-packed strategy-based game, players command antique WWI toy soldiers vying for control of the trench-filled battlefields of Europe. Deploy an exciting arsenal such as tanks, cavalry, biplanes, and flamethrowers in vintage WWI toy dioramas. Developed by Signal Studios exclusively for Xbox 360, Toy Soldiers allows you to take control of individual units or control the entire battlefield from a strategic view. Integrating multiple game genres and world-class visuals, Toy Soldiers is a unique and action-packed entertainment experience!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Kaiser's Battle",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/30",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Purchase The Kaiser's Battle and expand your Toy Soldiers experience. Enter the fray as the French Army in all new Single Player, Multiplayer, and Survival Mode Maps! Take on the new experimental boss, the fearsome K-Wagen! Earn three new achievements worth 50 gamer points and enjoy all new French inspired content!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Invasion!",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/29",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The British are bringing brand new secret weapons of tiny toy mayhem in 'Invasion!,' the second add-on to Toy Soldiers from Signal Studios! Put on your Kaiser's helmet and command the German Army against a mad menagerie of new antagonistic toys, including flying saucers, chivalrous knights, and the \"Rolls Royce of the Sky,\" the WWII Mustang. Defend Germany in a new Survival level, two new multiplayer maps, and a new mini-campaign topped by the most calculating, head-strong boss of all (batteries not included)! Raise your saber, soldier, and lead the charge against... is that a spaceman? The Invasion has begun!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3rTSQUEgQDo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4h0rS0dSe-0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/974789-toy-soldiers/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Toy-Soldiers/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/toy-soldiers/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/toy-soldiers"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Toy Soldiers Wiki",
				"url":"http://toysoldiers.wikia.com/wiki/Toy_Soldiers_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":310,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Slick Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"A top-down racer where you drift around corners while taking out that pesky competitor in front of you, fight your way to the top and defeat cunning track-bosses while collecting and upgrading awesome cars in your garage.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7K3A7mRsbu4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pYNRq0TRHWU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Scrap-Metal/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/scrap-metal/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/scrap-metal"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":311,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["4JStudios", "Rare"],
			"synopsis":"Released on Xbox Live Arcade, this is an Xbox 360 re-creation of the original N64 title.<br><br>In Perfect Dark you assume the role of Joanna Dark, a secret agent working for the secret Carrington Institute. Your mission is to rescue a kidnapped scientist and unravel the mystery of the dataDyne Corporation. Along the way you will get mixed up in alien conspiracies, government cover-ups with people trying to kill you at every turn!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U4fw0VvPg9w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BHgQ37m1fi0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960632-perfect-dark/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Perfect-Dark/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/perfect-dark/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/perfect-dark"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Perfect Dark Wiki",
				"url":"http://perfectdark.wikia.com/wiki/Perfect_Dark"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":312,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Capcom", "Inti Creates"],
			"synopsis":"The year is 20XX and a suspicious outbreak of Roboenza, a Robot Flu, has broken out. It spreads through the world like wildfire bringing down robots everywhere. Infected robots have rampaged out of control, destroying the city and holding it hostage! Who's behind this mess? It's up to Mega Man to take on this sinister threat and get to the bottom of this viral mystery.<br><br>Mega Man 10 once again brings back the nostalgic perfection of classic 2D Mega Man gameplay, embracing retro platform action and NES-inspired old-school graphics. Through-out Mega Man's adventure he'll take on the malfunctioning infected robots and classic-style bosses that can only found in Mega Man games. Each one has their own unique weapons and vulnerabilities. Great new additions to Mega Man 10 include the option to play as fan-favorite character Proto Man from the start, as well as an all new \"Easy Mode\" which will allow more fans to indulge in the challenges that make the series great. Additionally, \"Mega Man Challenges\" mode will allow players to practice their skills and prepare for the hair-raising adventures ahead of them.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cImYt-Ce8ss"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1ssokM3x134"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/982130-mega-man-10/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mega-Man-10/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mega-man-10/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mega-man-10"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Mega Man Wiki",
				"url":"http://megaman.wikia.com/wiki/Mega_Man_10"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":313,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Capcom"],
			"synopsis":"Final Fight: Double Impact is a dual release of two classic arcade side-scrolling beat-em-ups from Capcom.<br><br>First up is Final Fight, where players follow the heart-pounding adventures of Cody, Guy, and Haggar - three heroes fighting their way across crime-ridden Metro City in hopes of saving Haggar's daughter from the evil clutches of Mad Gear. There are 6 stages filled with perilous challenges where the only hope for justice is the unique fighting techniques mastered by each character.<br><br>In Magic Sword, users will take on the role of the The Brave One, a fierce warrior who bears the daunting responsibility of cleansing evil forces from an ancient tower. As a consequence of his actions, he will inevitably meet the source of this scourge upon humanity - the dark lord Drokmar. But fear not as the hero is accompanied by eight allies who will lend their assistance through out the game. All of them bring specific skills and talents to contribute to the fight. It's an amazing side-scrolling action illustrated in classic fantasy stylings, making a perfect pairing with Final Fight.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NImqD5A1ybo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ioxXt2XfQh0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/980766-final-fight-double-impact/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Final-Fight-Double-Impact/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/final-fight-double-impact/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/final-fight-double-impact"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":314,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Infinite Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Enter the dark and savage lands of the Ashurin Empire as you battle to avenge the atrocities the Empire brought upon your tribesmen in Puzzle Chronicles. On your heroic quest to topple the Empire, fight fierce beasts and battle-hardened warriors in this new puzzle/role-playing hybrid game. Featuring an active puzzle combat mechanic, deep story, and robust character development, Puzzle Chronicles brings you into the next era of puzzle RPGs.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BzXGuh9MbBo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BIgDgVpbVTo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/959349-puzzle-chronicles/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Puzzle-Chronicles/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Puzzle-Chronicles/walkthrough.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/puzzle-chronicles"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":315,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SEGA"],
			"synopsis":"The classic arcade flight action game After Burner has now returned for a new generation of gamers! After Burner Climax features fast and frantic feats, putting you in the cockpit of the world's top fighter jets. Players will dodge planes, rockets and bullets while trying to target multiple on-screen enemy aircrafts.<br><br>Square off against a plethora of AI opponents as they dodge, shoot, and barrel roll their way to victory in a variety of the game's environments. With the Climax Mode, players can activate slow motion, which makes avoiding rockets and bullets easier, and increasing accuracy whilst aiming for those harder to hit targets.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CXPDoFoauQ8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0JimxS9c5Fg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/After-Burner-Climax/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/after-burner-climax/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/after-burner-climax"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":316,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tecmo"],
			"synopsis":"The legend is back! Tecmo Bowl Throwback is a remake of the classic Tecmo Super Bowl, with the same rules and fast-paced gameplay as the original, but with the option to play it in brand new high-definition 3-D graphics. Switch it back to old school in real time with the same graphics and music from back in the day. Tecmo Bowl Throwback brings back the gameplay you loved, and stays true to the Tecmo Super Bowl legacy.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uoKeFjWNOq0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=spN_yb1zqi8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tecmo-Bowl/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tecmo-bowl-throwback/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tecmo-bowl-throwback"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":317,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["ACE Team"],
			"synopsis":"Zeno Clash is an action game with a strong focus on melee combat set in a punk fantasy world. Featuring up close and brutal combat in a first-person perspective, the game is played in battle scenarios where the adversaries are always dangerously close and the use of exotic firearms and artifacts is a commodity. The game features a new close combat mechanics designed as a deviation from traditional shooting in the FPS genre.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z2KuQAIlN0w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iK5-HLsr3Jw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/975437-zeno-clash-ultimate-edition/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Zeno-Clash/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/zeno-clash-ultimate-edition/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/zeno-clash-ultimate-edition"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":318,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Taito"],
			"synopsis":"A remake of the popular shooting game masterpiece, RayStorm HD combines the gameplay of the original RayStorm with all-new graphics updated for the present day. The gorgeous Lock-On Lasers that define the title, the engrossing audio tracks and the epic eight-stage game scenario will draw players back into the world of the feverish shoot-'em-up.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-HypeeN8kpk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k6JzE2se8oo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Raystorm-HD/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/raystorm-hd"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":319,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Climax Studios"],
			"synopsis":"In Rocket Knight, players take on the role of a fiery opossum named Sparkster who returns home to the Kingdom of Zephyrus after 15 years to find it in shambles. Using wits and a trusty rocket pack, players must steer clear and overcome a hostile wolf army looming to take the lives of the Zephyrus people.<br><br>A 2.5D action adventure title, Rocket Knight brings expansive new worlds, each with massive platform levels and a rocket flying level. As players navigate through the challenges, their rocket pack can be used to ricochet off walls, launch Sparkster through obstacles and enemies in his way, and rocket drill through weak walls to create new passageways. Along with burst projectiles that shoot from Sparkster's sword to attack distant foes, a burst vortex can also be created from players' rocket pack to repel enemy bombs back at them. If all else fails, players can use Sparkster's prehensile tail to hang from and slide down rails in order to avoid danger. With timed levels and leaderboards, dedicated players will also be able to show off their high scores and fastest times online.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pXOQ9JJF-wg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ldmAj2PtK4k"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/977248-rocket-knight/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rocket-Knight/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rocket-knight"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":320,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Load Inc."],
			"synopsis":"Things On Wheels is an arcade racing title that places players at the helm of radio-controlled vehicles as they compete on tracks set within a gigantic house.<br><br>A key innovation for Things On Wheels is its non-linear track design. Moving from room to room within an expansive virtual house, courses are constructed from routes that incorporate everyday items as hazards and obstacles. It's entirely possible that a championship could be won by taking the right path around a set of table legs, or cruelly lost by failing to avoid the searing heat of an electric heater.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"VrooM",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/16",
				"achievements":20,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"ToW VROOM contains 1 achievement and 5 new crazy tracks to race on: \"Magic Wheel\", \"Miami Rocket\", \"Speed Rush\", \"Rendez-vous\" and \"RC Master\"."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"RooAR",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/14",
				"achievements":20,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"ToW ROOAR contains 1 achievement and 5 new crazy tracks to race on: \"P.O.W.E.R.\", \"Need for Wheels\", \"Sprint Time\", \"Malo and Pablo\", and \"Slick Nicky G\"."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Cars",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/18",
				"achievements":10,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download 1 achievement and 3 new amazing race cars usable in all game modes: \"Namur\", \"Patriot\", and \"Cold Sweat\"."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yMm9Ak5GgAY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zPI43LzFEuQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Things-on-Wheels/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/things-on-wheels/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/things-on-wheels"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":321,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Games Distillery"],
			"synopsis":"In Aqua: Naval Warfare, the player takes control of an elite cruiser and steer into the middle of a raging naval war where masses of enemies and allies engage in real-time operations. Being attacked from above and below the water surface the player has to destroy masses of enemies' troops to be victorious. By unlocking new ship-types, weapons and upgrades, the player will have the opportunity to enhance his ship and gear up for the next fight.<br><br>Choosing from various tactics and forming special supporting squadrons, the player will also have the option to command offensive and defensive troops in order to overcome large enemy formations and defensive installations.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pcqSD7RC8bM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EVFScstmvrs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/994882-aqua/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Aqua/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/aqua-naval-warfare/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/aqua"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":322,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SNK Playmore"],
			"synopsis":"Six of the finest soldiers alive set out once again to brave a hellstorm of bullets in the seventh entry of Metal Slug, the popular run-and-gun videogame franchise! The story centers on the Peregrine Falcon Strike Force and the SPARROWS as they search once more for General Morden and his army. Their mission is to catch General Morden and stop his plans for attempting another coup d'&eacute;tat on the government. But as soon as Morden was defeated and failed, a strange army from the future came to his aid and strengthened his army. Now they must face Morden once again with his strengthened army and this time, put a stop to his plans once and for all.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Leona",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"To defeat the Morden's army, another ally from \"The King of Fighters\": Leona now joins the troop to break through everything which block her way."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FFlP8PLPHk0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Qh_yuPkNgo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Metal-Slug-XX/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/metal-slug-xx/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/metal-slug-xx"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Metal Slug Wiki",
				"url":"http://metalslug.wikia.com/wiki/Metal_Slug_XX"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":323,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Black Lantern Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Ben 10 Alien Force: The Rise of Hex is an action-puzzle platformer where gamers play as Ben Tennyson with the ability to transform into 10 different aliens. Utilizing the powers of the Omnitrix players will set out to battle a new threat to Earth.<br><br>Players transform into Swampfire, Brainstorm, Big Chill, Humongousaur, Echo Echo, Chromastone, Jetray, Spider Monkey, Goop and Lodestar to defeat Hex and his minions, with many surprises along the way. Players will have to utilize each alien during pivotal points in the game to take advantage of their special abilities and unique attributes. Players battle through 15 levels of fast-paced action and alien-specific puzzles to reach the final fight to save the Earth from destruction.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MlL-jianYm8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ben-10-The-Rise-of-Hex/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ben-10-alien-force-the-rise-of-hex/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ben-10-alien-force-the-rise-of-hex"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Ben 10 Planet",
				"url":"http://ben10.wikia.com/wiki/Ben_10_Alien_Force:_The_Rise_of_Hex"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":324,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Exkee"],
			"synopsis":"Roll the dice in a mystical world filled with exploration, puzzle solving, and adventure. Voodoo Dice is an innovative puzzler that challenges you to solve puzzles in unique and interesting ways in a quest to conquer the voodoo universe. Experience an endless variety of game play with 60 single-player levels, 20 multiplayer levels, and four multiplayer modes including Race Mode, Flag Mode, Tactic Mode, and Arcade Mode. Voodoo Dice will win you over with its immersive gameplay and countless hours of Voodoo fun!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0hS7Yrv1_V8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mPewcf-BFBI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Voodoo-Dice/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/voodoo-dice/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/voodoo-dice"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":325,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Nerve Software", "Id Software"],
			"synopsis":"To save Earth, you must descend into the stygian depths of hell in Doom II. Battle nastier, deadlier demons and monsters with your trusty Super Shotgun. Survive more mind-blowing explosions and take part in the bloodiest, fiercest, most awesome blastfest ever.<br><br>Recruit your friends and plow through nine all-new levels in the new episode, No Rest for the Living! Play solo or multiplayer over Xbox LIVE with up to four players. Doom II includes split-screen co-op over Xbox LIVE, game clips, 5.1 Surround Sound, enhanced graphics, and HD display support.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6cs9gar53sw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Speedrun (Original Game - 0:29:39)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8Q3QDmOMnNc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/971665-doom-ii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats (Original)",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/pc/197142-doom-ii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Doom-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/doom-ii/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/doom-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Doom Wiki",
				"url":"http://doom.wikia.com/wiki/Doom_II"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":326,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Smart Bomb Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"An adventure-filled flight game, this game once again follows Snoopy as his World War I Flying Ace alter-ego. With simple flight controls and a hangar full of customizable planes and weapons, all you need are nerves of steel to climb the Leaderboards and become a Flying Ace! Snoopy Flying Ace takes addictive, fast-paced airborne combat to new heights, with fantastic solo and co-op challenges testing your skills against the Flying Circus of the dreaded Red Baron. Remember, it ain't the size of the dog in the fight... it's the size of the fight in the dog!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Dogs of War Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/23",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"It was a dark and stormy night... with giant sky frigates, lightning storms, and a spooky old castle on a cliff! Here are two new multiplayer maps for Snoopy Flying Ace: \"Kaiser's Spike\" and \"Aces Airway\". Care for a game of armed Pigskin in the clouds, or perhaps some picturesque alpine CTF? Based on 100 percent authentically fictional battlefields of WWI, you'll feel like you were really there at the dawn of canine aviation."
			},
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Suppertime of Destruction Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/25",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"It's been called the greatest beagle-based air combat game ever made, yet somehow we still found room for more explosive features! TWO incredible new aircraft: the stealthy Woodstock Copter and Avatar-powered Spy Plane. Five, count 'em, FIVE new multiplayer game modes, with new Leaderboards to climb. THREE completely new weapons for your favorite plane! New costumes for all the Peanuts characters! Plus THIRTY new airplane skins that totally change the look of your warbird! Could we possibly cram any more cool stuff into this game??"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B2r_Vi1x1to"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RwqIdjGOvdI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Snoopy-Flying-Ace/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/snoopy-flying-ace/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/snoopy-flying-ace"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":327,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gameloft"],
			"synopsis":"The world's grooviest earthworm is blasting back into action in this reborn classic, now in HD! Rediscover the cult classic adventure with all the original levels plus new, never-before-seen locations, and brand new enemies. Team up with friends and combine your wormy powers in 4-player co-op locally or online.<br><br>Jim was an ordinary earthworm who did very earthworm-like things. One day, during a battle in outer space, a suit dropped to Earth and landed on Jim, mutating him into a large and intelligent (at least by earthworm standards) superhero. Play as the grooviest earthworm in the galaxy and explore a crazy universe that offers huge gameplay possibilities.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CrqaAidbkfo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iHA1OwMKqLI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats (Original)",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588302-earthworm-jim/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Earthworm-Jim-HD/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/earthworm-jim/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/earthworm-jim-hd"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Earthworm Jim Wiki",
				"url":"http://earthwormjim.wikia.com/wiki/Earthworm_Jim_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":328,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SNK Playmore"],
			"synopsis":"A special cast of NeoGeo characters bring their fight to competitive tag-team battles. In addition to original heroes and heroines, it features a host of unique characters that transcend time. Armed with weapons and robots, warriors from both old and new titles of the once dominant NeoGeo platform have been amassed under one roof in this new Xbox LIVE Arcade version, featuring both character and background graphics redone in high definition.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3SfcXbuMAME"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w3JrIN1qKFs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930010-neogeo-battle-coliseum/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NEOGEO-BATTLE-COLISEUM/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/neogeo-battle-coliseum"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"SNK Wiki",
				"url":"http://snk.wikia.com/wiki/Neo_Geo_Battle_Coliseum"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":329,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Strawdog Studios"],
			"synopsis":"A wandering black hole has passed through the galaxy destroying planets and leaving others damaged and desolate in its wake. The Arkonauts -- a team of space traveling animals -- have been dispatched in their Space Ark on a mission to bring life back to the shattered worlds. You must aid the Arkonauts in their quest by bouncing them into the air to collect DNA left in orbit by the previous inhabitants, transforming the planets back into vibrant habitats.<br><br>Space Ark is an homage to the bright and bouncy arcade games of the late 80s with an added mix of Pinball. The game features 180 levels of 'Arkonaut' bouncing entertainment split across 5 worlds, with 24 selectable Arkonauts, 5 mini games, bonus levels and a host of power-ups.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vChdsqWsWeI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SH9o1yJ7ko"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Space-Ark/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/space-ark/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/space-ark"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":330,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["3D Realms"],
			"synopsis":"Duke Nukem is back! New York City is being overrun by a mutant menace and it's time to de-worm the Big Apple. This explosive 3D action game features Duke Nukem defending the city that never sleeps, and its babes, from the evil Mech Morphix across 24 levels from Chinatown to Space. A super-sized collection of weapons, enemies and bosses await. As Duke would say, \"Babes, Bullets, Bombs. I love this job!\"",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fBSYI4gSrjQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gRF8mgXReCk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Duke-Nukem-Manhattan-Project/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/duke-nukem-manhattan-project/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/duke-nukem-manhattan-project"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Duke Nukem Wiki",
				"url":"http://dukenukem.wikia.com/wiki/Duke_Nukem:_Manhattan_Project"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":331,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Stainless Games"],
			"synopsis":"Risk: Factions offers innovative ways of experiencing the timeless turn-based board game in both objective-based and world conquest modes. Players will be able to engage as one of five playable factions, each with different strengths, as they wage war on new maps with dynamic terrain in their quest for missile silos in order to strategically dominate the game. Additionally, as rivals go head-to-head during unique, animated combat missions, enemies will be able to trigger \"Overkill\" moments, based on the roll of the dice, and unlock avatar awards while attempting global supremacy. With a special animated art style, kooky humor and a choice of five oddball factions, Risk: Factions is designed to challenge and captivate both new and seasoned Risk fans on their quest for world domination.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xhPCWvDiOdo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d7iQX7_ZrO8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Risk-Factions/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/risk-factions/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/risk-factions"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":332,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["J. Kenworthy Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"From the creators of Cloning Clyde comes a new epic adventure Ancients of Ooga! Eat, chant, and even puke your way through the highly comical, primeval land of Ooga. There's never a dull moment as you meet, befriend, and finally acquire seven zany Oogani tribes.<br><br>Uncover their lost ancient powers, and exploit their abilities and lead them in a revolt against the tyrannical Boolis. This is classic platforming and puzzle solving with a novel eat/carry/puke inventory management component. Over fifty amazing levels, excellent multiplayer, plus, narcotic slugs that make you loopy! Ancients of Ooga is sure to take you out of this world.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Forgotten Chapters",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/18",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"From the best selling Oogani game ever made comes seven amazing, all-new levels! Get them today!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g6Q-ImRVgzU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WrpxZ23J7-o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ancients-of-Ooga/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ancients-of-ooga/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ancients-of-ooga"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":333,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Infinite Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"A follow-up to the hit game Puzzle Quest: Challenge of the Warlords, Puzzle Quest 2 allows players to get closer to the action with an intimate viewpoint of the gem-studded match-3 video game. The sequel features the same hallmark blend of match-3 gem matching and fantasy, with a simple but meaningful role playing experience where players can choose any of four character classes; War Mage, Inquisitor, Barbarian or Assassin. Each character class provides interesting twists during multiple play-throughs as players reclaim the once peaceful village of Verloren from the evil clutch of the demon Gorgon. Players will be able to level up each character to progress through the adventure in Story Mode or even dive into Instant Action, Tournament Mode, or Mutliplayer Mode for a rich and diverse experience. With the entire Puzzle Quest world accessible on your fingertips in real-time action, players will be able to get a more streamlined experience for instant gratification.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qu6crdnO2Bc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iDIc68pohuw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/980488-puzzle-quest-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Puzzle-Quest-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/puzzle-quest-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/puzzle-quest-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Puzzle Quest 2 Wiki",
				"url":"http://puzzlequest2.wikia.com/wiki/Puzzle_Quest_2_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":334,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["LucasArts"],
			"synopsis":"Follows on the success of Special Edition release of The Secret of Monkey Island, Monkey Island 2 brings back the beloved sequel with exciting new features including high-definition graphics, a re-mastered musical score, full voiceover, and an in-depth hint system. Plus, experience all new unique special edition features that let you interact with the world of Monkey Island like never before.<br><br>Having defeated the evil ghost pirate LeChuck in his first adventure, pirate extraordinaire Guybrush Threepwood sets his sights on the treasure of Big Whoop. Legendary treasures however, come with legendary challenges and Guybrush will have to use his wits and humor to prove himself the greatest pirate in the Caribbean. Voodoo dolls, spitting contests and amusement parks are just some of the challenges Guybrush must overcome as he meets old friends, fights familiar enemies and uses every single ounce of his wits to become the most celebrated pirate ever.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vzs8_PilN54"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dnyyZ4GkCWA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/991338-monkey-island-2-special-edition-lechucks-revenge/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats (Original game)",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/pc/562680-monkey-island-2-lechucks-revenge/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Monkey-Island-2-Lechucks-Revenge/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/monkey-island-2-le-chucks-revenge/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/monkey-island-2-special-edition-lechucks-revenge"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Monkey Island Wiki",
				"url":"http://www.miwiki.net/Monkey_Island_2:_LeChuck's_Revenge"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":335,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Zombie Studios"],
			"synopsis":"In the near-future, the Blacklight Tango Team has been sent to find recently missing Colonol Klein and his personal Blacklight team in the city of Balik. The country has recently broken out in war after the assassination of the president. The rebel group that had killed the president The Order, is thought to have captured or killed the missing Blacklight team.<br><br>Tango Team prepares to attack The Order's headquarters when Blacklight command informs them that civilians have been infected with an unknown virus, causing them to attack everyone they encounter. As they engage the Order in combat, both sides are attacked by crazed civilians. Because the circumstances have changed, Tango Team is ordered to stop The Order at all costs...",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ACRSTJrxcg8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f_NETwX6mmo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Blacklight-Tango-Down/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/blacklight-tango-down/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/blacklight-tango-down"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Blacklight Wiki",
				"url":"http://blacklight.wikia.com/wiki/Blacklight:_Tango_Down"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":336,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Pipeworks Software"],
			"synopsis":"Deadliest Warrior: The Game is based on the the Spike TV series that regularly pits two of the most feared warriors civilization has ever known against each other in order to provide insight into what makes these combatants tick and determine which of these legends of the battlefield were truly the deadliest of all warriors.<br><br>Players can choose from history's greatest warriors, equip them with signature weaponry, and go head to head against the greatest fighters that ever lived. The game features five play modes, customizable warrior, and true to life action with interactive environments. This is a unique fighting game that is easy to play and hard to master. Sever limbs, decapitate heads, and taunt your enemy's lifeless corpse to build up ranking points and compete on a global scale to become \"The Deadliest Warrior\".",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Expansion Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/02",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"New DLC content featuring 3 new warriors, a new game mode, replays, titles and new taunts for all your characters!<br><br>Rajput: Rajput warriors were the fierce defenders of Northern India. They held personal honor and combat skill above all else. Rajput warriors believed that death in battle was their right. Because of their desire for glory, Rajput warriors were masters of one-on-one fighting. They also developed many unique weapons to dispatch their foes.<br><br>Zande: The Zande warriors were raiders in North Central Africa. Zande warriors filed their teeth to sharp points. This gave them a ferocious appearance. The Zande were very agile. They were adept at ducking and sidestepping attacks, as well as jumping over spears that were thrown at their legs.<br><br>Shaolin Monk: The Shaolin Monks are said to have been taught Kung Fu as a way to strengthen their bodies. Shaolin Kung Fu began as exercise, but was soon recognized as being effective on the battlefield. The addition of weapons to Shaolin Kung Fu, such as spears, iron staffs, and swords, was partly in response to raids from Japanese pirates. During the Ming dynasty Shaolin were frequently called on to repel these invaders.<br><br>Skirmish Mode: Select up to 4 warriors to fight in succession against each other. Warrior matchups consist of one round, with the loser being eliminated. The victor starts the next round with the same amount of health (and any injuries) they had at the end of the last round. Poison and severed limbs also carry over to the next round, meaning that in some cases a round will quickly end with a warrior bleeding out. The first player to have all of their warriors defeated loses the battle."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JMxTE38HpdQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tc9CERWNPk8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/995867-deadliest-warrior-the-game/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Deadliest-Warrior/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/deadliest-warrior/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/deadliest-warrior-the-game"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Deadliest Warrior Wiki",
				"url":"http://deadliestwarrior.wikia.com/wiki/Deadliest_Warrior:_The_Game"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":337,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Hothead Games"],
			"synopsis":"The game casts players in the role of DeathSpank, the Hero to the Downtrodden, a Vanquisher of Evil and Defender of Justice as he fulfills his life-long destiny and searches for a mysterious and magical item only known as \"The Artifact\". Along the way he'll rescue a few Orphans, defeat a local tyrant and tumble headlong into the even deeper mystery surrounding the legendary Thongs of Virtue in an epic adventure game that includes collecting loot, crazy puzzle solving, witty dialogue, collecting loot, over-the-top animations, fun, accessible action combat, and of course, collecting loot.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EAXzsc5aiKM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J4BJ8VdQdtA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Coop Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=njpLeOUaa_g"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/991035-deathspank/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/DeathSpank/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/deathspank/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/deathspank"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Deathspank Wiki",
				"url":"http://deathspank.wikia.com/wiki/DeathSpank_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":338,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["PlayDead"],
			"synopsis":"Limbo is a black and white puzzle-platforming adventure that puts players in the role of a young boy traveling through a hostile world in an attempt to discover the fate of his sister.<br><br>Limbo challenges players with traversing dark forests, trap-filled underground complexes, and stormy rooftops brought to life with hand-drawn visuals. They must be quick, clever, and fearless if they want to survive their journey and unravel the mysteries at Limbo's sinister heart.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kD5F54SZkMA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mrBDU6S1EME"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/991005-limbo/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/LIMBO/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/limbo/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/limbo"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":339,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Vector Unit"],
			"synopsis":"Featuring all-new, over-the-top themed environments, rocket-powered speedboats, lush visuals, and amazing dynamic water physics, Hydro Thunder Hurricane is the adrenaline-dripping sequel to Midway's legendary speedboat racing arcade game. The game includes eight \"theme park\" environments, each set in a different location around the globe. Each world is packed with animated surprises, destructible objects, and special events that players trigger in-game.<br><br>New game modes include Ring Master, Gauntlet and a series of multi-event Championships. Fan favorite speedboats from the original Hydro Thunder also make a return like Razorback, Cutthroat, and the flying saucer shaped Rad Hazard with redesigned models, multiple unlockable skins, and articulated boost animations with massive rockets folding out from hidden compartments. Each boat features unique handling characteristics. Hydro Thunder Hurricane introduces support for 8-player online racing on Xbox Live. The game also allows for local split screen multiplayer with up to 4 players - or any combination of local and online play. In addition to races, players can team up in the new Rubber Ducky game mode.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Tempest Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/27",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Fire up your boost rockets and shred the stormy waters of the Hydro Thunder Hurricane Tempest Pack, with all-new tracks, boats, challenges and achievements! Catch huge air off hurricane-force waves in the heart of the Bermuda Triangle. Blast through the lost city of Atlantis as it shakes with volcanic eruptions. Dodge exploding barrels and cannon-fire in the explosive Castle Von Boom. Take to the Leaderboards in two new super-fast Expert boats: the futuristic Whiplash and the slip-slidey Psyclone. Trick out new and existing boats with extra skins, including the winners of Vector Unit's Design-A-Skin Contest. Prove your mettle in all new Races, Gauntlet and Ring Master events."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FANeQRvkABc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xY9ssZ8z0Ic"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hydro-Thunder/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hydro-thunder-hurricane/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hydro-thunder-hurricane"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":340,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"Featuring the classic fast paced 2D, side scrolling action the series is known for, fan favorite vampire hunters from across the series will join forces to return Dracula, the Lord of Darkness, to his eternal slumber.<br><br>Designed by the legendary producer of the Castlevania series, Koji Igarashi, Castlevania Harmony of Despair allows up to 6 friends to play together via online co-op story mode or see who the best vampire hunter is in Survival Mode, which challenges players to fend off their friends while fighting for their very survival. Utilize your co-op skills to explore the levels with your friends in order to find hidden locations with special items and equipment or team up in battle to let loose destructive attacks on the hordes of attacking creatures.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Beauty, Desire, Situation Dire Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/29",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Explore and battle within an all-new map for Castlevania: Harmony of Despair inspired by psychedelic Egyptian art."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Music Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/13",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Five tunes for use in the game: Pitiful Scion, Pitch-Black Intrusion, Invitation of a Crazed Moon, The Hidden Curse, and An Empty Tome."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Julius Belmont Character Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/20",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Forget your past as Julius Belmont and reign a dawn of sorrow on the creatures of the night!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Yoko Belnades Character Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/20",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Manifest as this witch ally of the Belmont clan and inherit the powers of the magic seal!"
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Richter Belmont Character Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/27",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Feel the merciless power of the Vampire Killer whip in your own hands with Richter Belmont!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Maria Rendard Character Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/27",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Play as the petite vampire hunter and use her magical abilities to vanquish any monster in your path!"
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Music Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/10",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Five tunes for use in the game: Heart of Fire, Aquarius, Slash, Divine Bloodlines, and Simon's Theme."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Extra Stage: The One Who Is Many",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/12",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"An extra stage modeled after the underground section of Castlevania: Symphony of the Night. You'll face Legion, the boss that epitomizes \"All for one, one for all\"."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Extra Stage: Lord of Flies",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/19",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"An extra stage modeled after an above-ground section of Castlevania: Symphony of the Night. You'll face Beelzebub, Lord of Flies."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Extra Stage: Origins",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/26",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"A stage that goes back to the roots of Castlevania with 8-bit graphics. Do today's vampire hunters have what it takes to beat this blast from the past?"
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Simon Belmont Character Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Play as Simon Belmont, an extra character."
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Extra Stage: The Legend of Fuma",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/02",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"\"Getsu Fuma Den\", a Japan-themed action game, makes a cameo appearance in the Castlevania series. Enjoy the vintage graphics!"
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"Getsu Fuma Character Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Play as Getsu Fuma, an extra character."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d8g8lNgFxUo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0VVWMHRntpY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/997663-castlevania-harmony-of-despair/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Castlevania-Harmony-of-Despair/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/castlevania-harmony-of-despair/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/castlevania-harmony-of-despair"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Castlevania Wiki",
				"url":"http://castlevania.wikia.com/wiki/Castlevania:_Harmony_of_Despair"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":341,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Uber Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Monday Night Combat is a class-based, third-person shooter - and the most popular lethal sport of the future! It blends intense combat, finishing moves, and game show-like challenges and rewards to produce an action experience unlike any other. Why fight for \"honor\" or \"duty\" when you can fight for the real American dream: cash, fame and endorsements?",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Spunky Cola Special",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/14",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Spunky Cola Special DLC: The first DLC for Monday Night Combat that is completely free. Play Crossfire mode online in the new Spunky Cola Arena. Bring yourself and your closest friends into the new Super Sudden Death Blitz mode played in the amazing Suvivitol Arena. This DLC also features expanded private match options, updates to existing arenas, and many more features to make your Monday Night Combat gaming even better. Spunky Cola Special now with more arenas, more ProTags, more explosions, more awesome and churros!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HxMT8lZd5UM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n8O7C0rLvKs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/991788-monday-night-combat/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Monday-Night-Combat/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/monday-night-combat/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/monday-night-combat"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Monday Night Combat Wiki",
				"url":"http://mondaynightcombat.wikia.com/wiki/Monday_Night_Combat_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":342,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Crystal Dynamics"],
			"synopsis":"Lara Croft and the Guardian of Light follows Lara as she goes in search of the Mirror of Smoke, an ancient artifact located in a ruin known as the Temple of Light. When she finally reaches the mirror, she is ambushed by a mercenary army who takes the mirror and release an evil entity. Also awakened by the incident, Totec, The Guardian of Light joins Lara as her unlikely ally to save the world from never-ending darkness.<br><br>Lara Croft and the Guardian of Light showcases an isometric cooperative adventure that aims to deliver instant, intense action and bite-sized puzzles.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"All The Trappings Challenge Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/07",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Four new challenge maps filled with hordes of undead enemies and devious traps you must maneuver and exploit to survive."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"A Hazardous Reunion Challenge Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/08",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Four new challenge maps featuring mind-boggling puzzles, waves of intense combat action, and a fiery reunion with an old friend."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Raziel & Kain Character Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/15",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Grab a friend or go at it alone as Kain and Raziel from the Legacy of Kain games. The two iconic characters must work together to defeat a new threat in an unfamiliar world."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Kane & Lynch Character Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/29",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Grab a friend or go at it alone as gaming's most notorious criminals find themselves in Lara Croft's world and must work together to fight their way out."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wxtjg52-0pc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dL82Ilh4haY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/991065-lara-croft-and-the-guardian-of-light/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lara-Croft-Guardian-of-Light/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lara-croft-and-the-guardian-of-light/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lara-croft-and-the-guardian-of-light"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tomb Raider Wiki",
				"url":"http://www.tomb-raider.wikia.com/wiki/Lara_Croft_and_the_Guardian_of_Light"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":343,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Klei Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Featuring a unique art style inspired by graphic novels and golden age comics, Shank blends the intensity of classic 2D side-scrolling action games with a gripping and mature storyline. Betrayed by the only family he ever knew and left for dead it's up to Shank to seek revenge for the death of his beloved at the hands of the underworld's deadliest assassins. Utilizing his knowledge of gang warfare and weaponry Shank must battle his way through the criminal underground in order to seek revenge against the people responsible for bringing his world crashing down around him.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KOkV85ssM84"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gEesg1YJ_VQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Shank/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/shank/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/shank"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":344,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal", "Ubisoft Chengdu"],
			"synopsis":"This is the rock-n-roll action love story for the 8-BIT generation! Scott Pilgrim is a loveable loser whose life is turned upside down when a mind-blowing delivery girl named Ramona Flowers starts popping up everywhere, even in his dreams. Could she be his true love? But the path to Ms. Flowers isn't covered in rose petals. The League of Ramona's Evil Exes stands in the way. To get the girl, Scott must not only defeat the seven evil exes, but also take responsibility and become a better person.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Knives Chau Add-On Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/28",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Play as or play with your favorite characters - Team-up with up to 3 of your friends as Scott, Ramona, Stephen, Kim and now Knives, each with their own signature moves and attacks. Bonus Game Modes - Dodge Ball - take on enemies in everyone's favorite childhood game. Be the last one standing and you win! - Battle Royale - fight to the finish against friends in this multiplayer brawler mode Relive Scott Pilgrim's adventures in awesome 8-bit - 8-bit animations by the world-famous Pixel Artist Paul Robertson. - More than 30 original music tracks by chiptune heroes Anamanaguchi. - Tons of references to new and old cult games."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Online Multiplayer + Wallace pack",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/13",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Scott Pilgrim DLC: Online Multiplayer + Wallace pack will provide this long awaited online multiplayer experience, packed with a new playable character Wallace Wells."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yAY4vNJd7A8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nKjT1D93Nmk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/961765-scott-pilgrim-vs-the-world-the-game/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Scott-Pilgrim-the-Game/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/scott-pilgrim-vs-the-world/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/scott-pilgrim-vs-the-world-the-game"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Scott Pilgrim Wiki",
				"url":"http://scottpilgrim.wikia.com/wiki/Scott_Pilgrim_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":345,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blue Castle Games"],
			"synopsis":"Dead Rising: Case Zero is a downloadable chapter of the Dead Rising saga designed as a playable prologue for Dead Rising 2 that bridges the story between the first and second games. Any PP, clothing, and Combo Cards gained in Case Zero will carry over into your Dead Rising 2 game!<br><br>Chuck Greene and his daughter Katey have barely escaped the Las Vegas zombie outbreak with their lives. They arrive in the lonely desert town of Still Creek looking for some rest, but unfortunately there is no rest to be had as this sleepy town has become overrun with zombies. Chuck must kill zombies, rescue survivors and escape from the zombie nightmare that is Still Creek before time runs out.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ARP88JzbsEI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oroZymvlXcg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/989132-dead-rising-2-case-zero/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dead-Rising-2-Case-Zero/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dead-rising-2-case-zero/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dead-rising-2-case-zero"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dead Rising Wiki",
				"url":"http://deadrising.wikia.com/wiki/Dead_Rising_2:_Case_Zero"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":346,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["PopCap Games"],
			"synopsis":"Zombies are invading your home, and the only defense is your arsenal of plants! Armed with an alien nursery-worth of zombie-zapping plants like peashooters and cherry bombs, you'll need to think fast and plant faster to stop dozens of types of zombies dead in their tracks. Obstacles like a setting sun, creeping fog and a swimming pool add to the challenge, and with five game modes to dig into, the fun never dies!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VyggFQL-ghw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ztl2Fdv5rGk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/961689-plants-vs-zombies/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Plants-vs-Zombies/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/plants-vs-zombies/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/plants-vs-zombies"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Plants vs Zombies Wiki",
				"url":"http://plantsvszombies.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":347,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sonic Team"],
			"synopsis":"This downloadable game brings the classic Dreamcast game to the Xbox 360.<br><br>The hedgehog with an attitude makes his triumphant return to the world of videogames in Sonic Adventure. Sonic has been catapulted into the third dimension with style. Racing at supersonic speeds through nearly 50 gorgeous, fully 3D levels, Sonic will have to adapt to the new challenges and dangers invented by the evil Dr. Robotnik. Sonic knows when he's outmatched, though, so he's recruited five friends including Amy Rose, Tails, and Knuckles to help him put a stop to Robotnik's evil scheme. Each playable character features different abilities, playing through levels differently and seeing the story evolve from their own perspectives.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Sonic Adventure DX Upgrade",
				"releaseDate":"2012/09/11",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Upgrade your copy of Sonic Adventure to the Director's Cut version today and unlock 60 new missions, and Metal Sonic as a playable character!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CJc23pIK5yg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/997574-sonic-adventure/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sonic-Adventure/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sonic-adventure-dx-directors-cut/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sonic-adventure"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sonic News Network",
				"url":"http://sonic.wikia.com/wiki/Sonic_Adventure"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":348,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Moss Ltd."],
			"synopsis":"This bizarre top-down shooter uses characters from the tournament brawler franchise The King of Fighters as heroes shooting through space and blasting away at evil. Each character retains their own normal shots, as well as ultimate techniques. Each character's special move has 3 three levels at which they can be unleashed, depending on the amount of energy in your ultimate technique gauge. The biggest feature of this game is its brand new fusion of the play systems of the \"Shooting\" and \"Martial Arts\" genres.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vpzc-QABd7c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/KOF-Sky-Stage/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/king-of-fighters-sky-stage/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kof-sky-stage"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"SNK Wiki",
				"url":"http://snk.wikia.com/wiki/KOF_Sky_Stage"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":349,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Taito"],
			"synopsis":"Space Invaders, the game that defined video games for generations, is back with a new twist! The game starts off looking like the classic Space Invaders, but as you play through the game, it evolves. Unlock new stages, new power ups, and new features. The full game features a total of 143 stages from both Normal Mode and the breathtaking Challenge Mode where stages change with each playthrough. You can even blast your way through unique stages evolved from your very own music!<br><br>Compete against other players from all around the world in real time with the appropriately named Real Time Rankings! Space Invaders Infinity Gene is the pinnacle of outer space shooting action! The more you play, the more the game evolves!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WLttemu-Xx4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vonhADAAEmc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Space-Invaders-Infinity-Gene/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/space-invaders-infinity-gene"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Space Invaders Wiki",
				"url":"http://spaceinvaders.wikia.com/wiki/Space_Invaders_Infinity_Gene"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":350,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Krome Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Blade Kitten invites players into the world of Hollow Wish where they take on the role of Kit Ballard, one of the best bounty hunters in the business. With her pink hair and tail, Kit is part cat, part girl - and fully lethal. As one of the last of her species, Kit commands her unique \"Darque Blade\" hovering sword to defeat enemies. Also along for the ride is Skiffy, Kit's laid-back sidekick who lends a hand in collecting items, solving puzzles, and when needed, serves as Kit's protector.<br><br>Blade Kitten promises to deliver a strong narrative, with high-quality cinematics, and a colorful, frenetic visual style, that lends to the pick-up-and-play arcade action. Players will jump right in and easily begin exploring and fighting their way through 19 levels, including three exploration levels with Noot (a rideable alien mount).",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EjdK6QfIHBs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NC5yOKH9_Zk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/997381-blade-kitten/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Blade-Kitten/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/blade-kitten/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/blade-kitten"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":351,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Devolver Digital", "Croteam"],
			"synopsis":"Sam is back and with a bang like never before!! Help Sam take up the fight against his arch-nemesis Mental. Sam hijacks an alien aircraft to confront Mental but somehow crash lands in the South American Mountains. Now Sam is forced to battle his way towards Mental's fortress and put a stop once and for all to his plans of world domination but this is not easy as you have to face a stronger, meaner Mental army.<br><br>Following in the tradition of the first Serious Sam HD, The Second Encounter features all the insane action of the original game but with visuals vastly upgraded for more powerful plaforms. Serious Sam HD: The Second Encounter also features an all new Co-Op Tournament mode that will allow teams to compete with one another.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w-zgkKHB-eI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9io755PkM-E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Serious-Sam-The-Second-Encounter/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/serious-sam-hd-the-second-encounter/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/serious-sam-hd-the-second-encounter"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Serious Sam Wiki",
				"url":"http://serioussam.wikia.com/wiki/Serious_Sam:_The_Second_Encounter"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":352,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Hothead Games"],
			"synopsis":"Join DeathSpank in the hunt for the Thongs Of Virtue! Fight through war-torn battlefields, tame the High Plains and sail the savage seas. Experience fast paced action-RPG combat with over 150 quests and tons of weapons, armor and loot to collect. Wield exciting new weapons, slay unbelievable new creatures, and take DeathSpank on the ultimate quest to find and destroy the mysterious Thongs of Virtue.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Snowy Mountain Dungeon",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/22",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Be alert brave hero! A freezing yet terrifying dungeon has opened up in the Snowy Mountains! Horrible enemies of ice, flesh and terror await DeathSpank in this, the greatest expansion of all time!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Tankko the Warrior",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/22",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A new warrior is ready to join the battle for Justice! Tankko the warrior is half-man, half-monster, all awesome! Tankko inspires fear in enemies and slight discomfort among friends."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pjJTTqNcKd0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_77rBhDmsfo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/605420-deathspank-thongs-of-virtue/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/DeathSpank-Thongs-of-Virtue/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/deathspank-tov/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/deathspank-thongs-of-virtue"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"DeathSpank Wiki",
				"url":"http://deathspank.wikia.com/wiki/DeathSpank:_Thongs_of_Virtue"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":353,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Team17 Software"],
			"synopsis":"Alien Breed 2: Assault is the second chapter in the Alien Breed series, and is an explosive science fiction arcade-shooter with an epic story, swarms of highly intelligent alien enemies and highly detailed environments, developed using Epic Games' Unreal Engine 3. Assault finds the player taking control of Conrad, Chief Engineer aboard the dying ship Leopold and continuing his fight for survival across the fatally damaged space vessel. His only hope relies on reigniting the alien space craft's monstrous engines to rescue him from impending annihilation, but to do this he will have to survive wave after wave of relentless alien assaults. In addition to the thrilling single-player campaign and all new \"Survivor\" modes, the game also offers action-packed, two-player online co-operative battle modes.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RGMfeHNSoLY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YZCP_ruLlrk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Alien-Breed-Episode-2-Assault/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/alien-breed-2-assault"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":354,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Dark Energy Digital"],
			"synopsis":"Meet Kate Wilson, a reluctant hero who finds herself caught behind enemy lines when terrorists seize the Queen of the World, a new city-sized super ship. The terrorist attack takes place on the occasion of the first anniversary of the Queen of the World, and it's up to Kate to stop them.<br><br>Hydrophobia is an action/adventure survivor game utilizing the revolutionary HydroEngine technology to place you inside the flooding lower decks of the Queen of the World. Flowing water behaves completely realistically, creating a chaotic, dangerous and ever-changing environment. As systems engineer Kate Wilson, you must use every tool at your disposal to survive and escape the rising waters.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iZceJsTwdcg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WN1zfqIvCR0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939413-hydrophobia/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hydrophobia/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hydrophobia/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hydrophobia"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":355,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Twisted Pixel"],
			"synopsis":"This zany downloadable title is a comedy action game that draws inspiration from classic arcade-style action games. It stars The Captain, superhero extraordinaire and prima donna star of comic book adventures ... or, at least, he used to be. The Captain has discovered that his fans are losing interest in his comic books. Along with Star, the Captain's back-talking and foul-mouthed chest symbol, he obtains the assistance from his creator, Twisted Pixel, in order to \"jump\" into other comic books franchises and earn the love and respect he needs to re-launch his own series. Star and the Captain battle villains and help other heroes across four different comic books, each with varying takes on gameplay and their own distinct art style inspired by recognizable real-world comic genres.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=otE3lJ--nKo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lHE9pcvKjEs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/972659-comic-jumper-the-adventures-of-captain-smiley/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Comic-Jumper/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/comic-jumper/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/comic-jumper-the-adventures-of-captain-smiley"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":356,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sumo Digital", "Visceral Games"],
			"synopsis":"Hours before engineer Isaac Clarke begins his adventure on \"The Sprawl\" in Dead Space 2, a Necromorph outbreak occurs - but how did the events unfold? Players witness the horror first-hand in Dead Space Ignition, a downloadable game that takes place on the Sprawl and challenges players to survive the initial Necromorph outbreak.<br><br>Dead Space Ignition combines an interactive comic-style story with three unique hacking mini games; Hardware Crack, Trace Route and System Override. Each game offers a fun and satisfying arcade experience that will challenge players with puzzles and twitch gameplay. Dead Space Ignition features a unique \"Choose Your Own Adventure\" type narrative, allowing players to survive the horrific Necromorph outbreak in multiple ways. The game offers four unique endings and upon completion of each one, players will be rewarded with unlocks including an exclusive suit, all of which can be used by Isaac Clarke in Dead Space 2.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=283_ZwjFw2s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2zaoJ3bNP-g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dead-Space-Ignition/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dead-space-ignition/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dead-space-ignition"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dead Space Wiki",
				"url":"http://deadspace.wikia.com/wiki/Dead_Space:_Ignition"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":357,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sonic Team"],
			"synopsis":"Available exclusively via download, Sonic the Hedgehog 4 Episode I brings back the addictive side scrolling action that Sonic fans love in an all-new 2D adventure. Played from the traditional side-scrolling perspective, the game offers classic Sonic moves that fans love including Spin Dash and Rolling Attack and will also feature Homing Attack, all in stunning CG rendered environments.<br><br>Packed with special stages, Sonic the Hedgehog 4 Episode I will take players through a variety of different Zones, inspired by the Genesis-era style. And, of course, expect intense boss battles against everyone's favorite villain -- the always devious and evil -- Dr.Eggman!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ebyps1CKpG4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DRs1BqezP-I"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/972791-sonic-the-hedgehog-4-episode-i/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sonic-the-Hedgehog-4-Episode-1/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sonic-the-hedgehog-4-episode-1/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sonic-the-hedgehog-4-episode-i"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sonic News Network",
				"url":"http://sonic.wikia.com/wiki/Sonic_the_Hedgehog_4"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":358,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Team Meat"],
			"synopsis":"Super Meat Boy is a tough-as-nails platformer where you play as an animated cube of meat who's trying to save his girlfriend (who happens to be made of bandages) from an evil fetus wearing a tux who lives in a jar.<br><br>Leap from walls, jump over seas of buzz saws, and run through crumbling caves and pools of old needles. Super Meat Boy relives the old school difficulty of classic retro platformers and streamlines it down to the essentials, no BS, just straight-forward twitch reflex platforming, and all while sacrificing his own well-being to save his damsel in distress.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=snaionoxjos"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0kIGueVqD_0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iayxzN7QJg0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/990836-super-meat-boy/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Super-Meat-Boy/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/forum/showthread.php?t=270106"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/super-meat-boy"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Super Meat Boy Wiki",
				"url":"http://supermeatboy.wikia.com/wiki/Super_Meat_Boy_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":359,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["PlayFirst"],
			"synopsis":"Welcome to the Dream Chronicles, where the lines between reality and fantasy no longer exist. Follow subtle clues to help Faye find her missing husband and escape the mysterious sleeping spell that has taken over the town of Wish. Stay sharp and focused and you may unravel this intriguing, dreamy mystery!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VXVA8a5bihQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dpxk3Hwu-48"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/988777-dream-chronicles/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dream-Chronicles/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dream-chronicles/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dream-chronicles"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":360,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Double Fine Productions"],
			"synopsis":"A childhood dream come alive created by Double Fine's lead animator, Tasha Harris, Costume Quest follows the adventure of a group of young friends who must rid their neighborhood of monsters using only their wits, their bravery, and their home-made costumes. Players go door-to-door collecting candy, points, cards, battle stamps and quest assignments as they prepare themselves for Combat Mode -- where they transform into larger-than-life versions of their costumes. Each costume that comes-to-life provides its own unique set of superpowers that players will need to battle Halloween's worst monsters. Explore the various neighborhoods, complete quests, discover hidden areas and trick-or-treat your way through this spooky Halloween night.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Grubbins on Ice",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/08",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Continue the Costume Quest adventure by exploring the monster world, Repugia. Face new enemies while collecting additional quests, costumes, battle stamps and creepy treat cards. Help the monsters overthrow Araxia to bring peace back to Repugia! Unlock now!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IJcVECLkHvg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pWHwa-6R_Ic"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/604987-costume-quest/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Costume-Quest/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/costume-quest/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/costume-quest"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Costume Quest Wiki",
				"url":"http://costumequest.wikia.com/wiki/Costume_Quest_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":361,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Wanako Games"],
			"synopsis":"In 3D Ultra MiniGolf Adventures 2, players are challenged to navigate their ball beyond obstacles using the help of secret shortcuts, game-changing power-ups and traps to sabotage the competition. Players can also manipulate the game by using special pick-ups to destroy course obstructions or even interfere with competitor's shots.<br><br>Gamers can bring their A-game as they play in matches of up to four players locally or online. The sequel also offers an intuitive Map Editor tool, allowing full customization of virtual courses and the strategic placement of power-ups and traps. Putt through over 50 fun-filled holes in diverse locations, such as a Haunted Manor, a Manic Museum and a Winter Wonderland. As an added bonus, players can choose from up to four customizable animated characters and are invited to play using their own Xbox 360 Avatars and watch as their personalities unfold in every course.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UzNxZ3hskWY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VTQ00P1Wwdc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/3D-Ultra-Minigolf-Adventures-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/3d-ultra-minigolf-adventures-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/3d-ultra-minigolf-adventures-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":362,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Zen Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Pinball FX 2 offers a host of features for novices and experts alike: a state-of-the-art physics model, Operators Menu with custom settings and advanced play info, automatic in-game challenges against your friends, and split-screen local multiplayer mode.<br><br>Players can download the Pinball FX 2 application and choose from an a la carte menu offering a variety of pinball tables to download.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Core Collection",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/13",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Biolab, Pasha, Rome, Secrets of the Deep, Pinball FX is back, and it is better than ever! Pinball FX2 offers improved graphics and a host of new features for novices and experts alike! Full backward compatibility for Pinball FX owners: download Pinball FX2 for free and play all your Pinball FX tables within Pinball FX2! Browse all available tables and try them out for free before buying. Split-screen local multiplayer mode - a first in video pinball history! Own your pinball game: Operators Menu lets you tune practically every aspect of each table. Special features include online competitions, worldwide scoreboards, periodic Tournaments, and live video chat via the Xbox 360 Live Vision Camera."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Street Fighter II Table",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/13",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Enter the World Warrior Championship and fight your way up to challenge M. Bison himself!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Excalibur Table",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/13",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Earn your seat at the Round Table amongst the greatest knights in King Arthur's court! The Arthurian legend is reborn on a lively pinball table with several unique features. See the tales of each of the Knights of the Round Table unfold before you. Participate in duels or jousting tournaments for honor and defend Camelot against the robber knights!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Earth Defense Table",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/13",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Hordes of hostile aliens are attacking Earth! Lead the united forces of Earth against the gigantic Flip-Bot and its minions. The fate of the world is in your hands!"
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Classic Collection",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/13",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Speed Machine, Extreme, Agents, and Buccaneer pinball tables. This classic Pinball FX table pack includes the four original tables which made Pinball FX one of the most popular titles on XBLA. These tables combine the arcade thrills of traditional pinball with enhanced gameplay and exciting, innovative features not found in any other pinball game."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Nightmare Mansion Table",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/13",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The old mansion on the hill has been abandoned for decades. Most people say it's haunted, and on some nights screams can be heard coming from within. What evils have taken up residence there? Do you dare enter and find out?"
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Marvel Pinball",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/01",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Your favorite Marvel Super Heroes are coming to Pinball FX2! Join Spider-Man, Wolverine, Iron Man, and Blade on four brand new Pinball FX2 tables. Use your pinball wizardry to save the world from the most notorious Super Villains, and relive the greatest moments of the classic Marvel Universe in an epic pinball adventure!"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Mars Table",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/13",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The mysteries of Mars, the red planet, have enthralled the human race for millennia. And today, you can be part of the first manned mission to uncover its secrets."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Fantastic Four Table",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/18",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The shadow of the mighty Galactus approaches Earth! His herald, the Silver Surfer, has discovered our lush planet and called the ruler of the Power Cosmic, who is already on his way. A menace to the entire galaxy, Galactus wants to consume the Earth by converting it into pure energy. Only the Fantastic Four can face this challenge, as only they have enough power to obtain the Ultimate Nullifier and with it coerce the ruler of the Power Cosmic to depart. But before the Fantastic Four can meet with Galactus, they have to deal with Doctor Doom and his Doombots, invading Skrulls, and much more."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Captain America Table",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/29",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Engage Cap, Bucky and members of the Howling Commandos in an all-out assault on Baron Zemo's castle. Destroy the fearsome Sleeper robot, face the Red Skull in a series of battles, and recover the omnipotent Cosmic Cube from his grasp!"
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Ms. Splosion Man Table",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/31",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Splosion Man captured! The World is safe... At least, that's what they thought! Straight from the science lab, Ms. Splosion Man is out of control, even more dangerous...and pinker than her better half. She's on a mission to save Splosion Man from the grasp of the giant robot, the Mighty Eternal. The Scientists will try anything to stop her during this perilous quest. Ms. Splosion Man will Splode herself through Energy Walls, Electric Beam Hazards, Rollerbots, and hundreds of barrels and Zip lines to reach her goal and save Splosion Man."
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Sorcerer's Lair",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/12",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"For centuries, the forbidding stone structure has stood outside the village, undisturbed. Until two children decided to venture inside to uncover its secrets. Guide Jake and his sister through an ever-changing labyrinth of twisting corridors, secret passageways, and terrifying encounters with the castle's denizens."
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"Paranormal Table",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/02",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"As a paranormal detective, your job is to investigate mysterious and supernatural phenomena. You'll have your hands full with hauntings, weird creatures, and inexplicable lapses in the laws of nature! Even the silver ball is not immune to the erratic forces at work within this table."
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"Marvel: Vengeance and Virtue",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/14",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Marvel Pinball returns with Vengeance and Virtue in four brand new pinball tables: GHOST RIDER: Outwit Lucifer's insidious villains, and ride through Hell with Johnny Blaze! MOON KNIGHT: Eliminate Morpheus, Midnight, Black Spectre and Bushman, culminating in an epic battle with the god of evil and death! THOR: Wield the hammer Mjolnir to fend off Loki, the Destroyer, Ymir the Frost Giant, Surtur and others! X-MEN: Help Xavier and Cyclops defeat Magneto, Juggernaut, Mystique and the Blob."
			},
			{
				"id":15,
				"name":"Epic Quest Table",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/15",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"It is the sworn duty of every knight to seek out evil, defeat it, and take its stuff. One such knight is Max, whose enthusiasm for combat is surpassed only by his love of rare and valuable loot. Join Max as he battles hordes of evil (or just evil-looking) monsters, rescues a wealthy princess, and accumulates the loot and xp that make good worth doing. If Max suffers a defeat, never fear! He will return in the next game with all of his hard-won loot and experience levels intact."
			},
			{
				"id":16,
				"name":"Marvel: Avengers Chronicles",
				"releaseDate":"2012/06/20",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Marvel Pinball: Avengers Chronicles takes the critically acclaimed pinball series to uncharted territory. Each of the four tables in this brand new pack chronicles a blockbuster event in the Marvel Universe: Marvel's The Avengers (based on the 2012 film from Marvel Studios), Fear Itself, The Infinity Gauntlet and World War Hulk. Avengers Assemble!"
			},
			{
				"id":17,
				"name":"Plants vs. Zombies Table",
				"releaseDate":"2012/09/05",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Mmmm....pinball! Based on PopCap's hit title, Plants vs. Zombies, Zen Studios is bringing the zombie invasion to the pinball playfield! Plant your defenses and prepare your flippers for a Plants vs. Zombies pinball adventure!"
			},
			{
				"id":18,
				"name":"Civil War Table",
				"releaseDate":"2012/11/20",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The controversy over the Superhuman Registration Act has led to the unfathomable Super Hero Civil War. Choose between Iron Man, who leads the SRA's supporters, and Captain America, who sees it as a threat to personal liberties, as you assemble your team and experience one of the most dramatic conflicts in the Marvel Universe."
			},
			{
				"id":19,
				"name":"Zen Classics",
				"releaseDate":"2012/12/12",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Zen Pinball Classics features a dazzling collection of four Zen Studios original pinball designs all upgraded for Pinball FX2. Shaman, El Dorado, Tesla and V12 have been re-mastered with updated graphics, superior ball physics, and a host of new features."
			},
			{
				"id":20,
				"name":"Star Wars Pinball",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/27",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Feel the power of the Force in Star Wars Pinball! Set in a galaxy far, far away, each of the three tables in this brand new pack lets you interact with the most iconic characters, and relive the greatest moments of the Star Wars universe: Star Wars: Episode V The Empire Strikes Back, Star Wars: The Clone Wars, and Boba Fett. May the Force be with you!"
			},
			{
				"id":21,
				"name":"Star Wars Pinball: Balance of the Force",
				"releaseDate":"2013/10/16",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Feel the disturbance in the Force in Star Wars Pinball: Balance of the Force, featuring three brand new Star Wars pinball tables. The pack includes Star Wars: Episode VI Return of the Jedi, Starfighter Assault, and a table dedicated to Darth Vader."
			},
			{
				"id":22,
				"name":"Doctor Strange",
				"releaseDate":"2013/12/18",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The Master Of The Mystic Arts needs your help stopping the two dimension rulers, Dormammu and Nightmare, and their foul ally, Baron Mordo, who are trying to conquer our dimension. Our fate is in your hands! Table features: Increase the Sorcerer Supreme's abilities and skills, including: Arcane, Alchemy, Wisdom, Spirit and Intellect. Test your wisdom on the Eye Of Agamotto special mini playfield. Defeat Baron Mordo and retake The Book Of The Vishanti. Enter the Dark Dimension and defeat its ruler Dormammu. Save the world by entering the Dream Dimension and defeat its ruler Nightmare."
			},
			{
				"id":23,
				"name":"Super League - A.C. Milan",
				"releaseDate":"2014/02/19",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Lead A.C. Milan to glory against the world's finest football clubs! Guide them in their quest to become Super League Champions. Save your progress between games, filling your Trophy Cabinet, and bringing ultimate glory to your team!"
			},
			{
				"id":24,
				"name":"Super League - Juventus",
				"releaseDate":"2014/02/19",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Lead Juventus to glory against the world's finest football clubs! Guide them in their quest to become Super League Champions. Save your progress between games, filling your Trophy Cabinet, and bringing ultimate glory to your team!"
			},
			{
				"id":25,
				"name":"Super League - Zen Studios F.C.",
				"releaseDate":"2014/02/19",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Lead Zen Studios F.C. to glory against the world's finest football clubs! Guide them in their quest to become Super League Champions. Save your progress between games, filling your Trophy Cabinet, and bringing ultimate glory to your team!"
			},
			{
				"id":26,
				"name":"Super League - A.S. Roma",
				"releaseDate":"2014/02/19",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Lead A.S. Roma to glory against the world's finest football clubs! Guide them in their quest to become Super League Champions. Save your progress between games, filling your Trophy Cabinet, and bringing ultimate glory to your team!"
			},
			{
				"id":27,
				"name":"Super League - FC Barcelona",
				"releaseDate":"2014/02/19",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Lead FC Barcelona to glory against the world's finest football clubs! Guide them in their quest to become Super League Champions. Save your progress between games, filling your Trophy Cabinet, and bringing ultimate glory to your team!"
			},
			{
				"id":28,
				"name":"Super League - Liverpool F.C.",
				"releaseDate":"2014/02/19",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Lead Liverpool F.C. to glory against the world's finest football clubs! Guide them in their quest to become Super League Champions. Save your progress between games, filling your Trophy Cabinet, and bringing ultimate glory to your team!"
			},
			{
				"id":29,
				"name":"Super League - Real Madrid C.F.",
				"releaseDate":"2014/02/19",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Lead Real Madrid C.F. to glory against the world's finest football clubs! Guide them in their quest to become Super League Champions. Save your progress between games, filling your Trophy Cabinet, and bringing ultimate glory to your team!"
			},
			{
				"id":30,
				"name":"Super League - Arsenal F.C.",
				"releaseDate":"2014/02/19",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Lead Liverpool F.C. to glory against the world's finest football clubs! Guide them in their quest to become Super League Champions. Save your progress between games, filling your Trophy Cabinet, and bringing ultimate glory to your team!"
			},
			{
				"id":31,
				"name":"Star Wars Pinball: Heroes Within",
				"releaseDate":"2014/04/30",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Celebrate your favorite characters with Star Wars Pinball: Heroes Within featuring four brand new pinball tables including Han Solo, Star Wars Pinball: Droids, Star Wars Pinball: Episode IV A New Hope, and a table dedicated to the Masters of the Force."
			},
			{
				"id":32,
				"name":"Deadpool Table",
				"releaseDate":"2014/06/25",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Hi, fellas - welcome to Deadpool Pinball. As in, Me Pinball. As in, I'm in it... What else do you need? It has ramps, me, multiballs, me, pinball, me, and a whole lot of bangs and booms. Oh, and did I say that I'm in it?"
			},
			{
				"id":33,
				"name":"Guardians of the Galaxy Table",
				"releaseDate":"2014/07/30",
				"type":8
			},
			{
				"id":34,
				"name":"The Walking Dead Table",
				"releaseDate":"2014/08/27",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Zen Studios, Telltale Games, and Skybound Entertainment partner to create an all-new table based on the 'Game of the Year' winning series."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VtWOULvl-PE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_5Vl2h9-HtA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pinball-FX2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pinball-fx-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":363,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Imaginengine"],
			"synopsis":"Enter the Haunted House, if you dare. The terrifying fun that lies within Graves Mansion is back in this spooky game inspired by Atari's classic groundbreaking original, now reimagined for a new generation of gamers with rich 3D environments, interactive objects, suspense filled challenges, new chilling environments and more frightful enemies than ever before! Players fight for their lives in Graves Mansion as the grandchildren of the original character that disappeared without a trace in the evil mansion over 30 years ago. Chased by pesky poltergeists, haunted by scary skeletons and exhausted from battles with creepy creatures, players are in a goosebump-educing fight to explore the dark and creepy depths of Graves Mansion in search of the four lost pieces of the magical urn. The player's goal is to reassemble the urn and defend their family's legacy with the aid of mystical tomes, powerful light sources and multiple keys.<br><br>The pick up-and-play arcade-style adventure allows players to jump right in and begin battling for their family's legacy and explore the dark and mysterious levels. An eerie, 3D rich environment of towers, basements and catacombs draws players into the haunted world and cursed story. Find hidden treasures, solve puzzles, fight bosses, and navigate through the spooky mansion and multiple levels on the way to a showdown with Zachary Graves.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1qoyJndfUwE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/998584-haunted-house/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Haunted-House/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/haunted-house/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/haunted-house"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":364,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Outerlight"],
			"synopsis":"Bloody Good Time takes a new and irreverent approach to multiplayer shooters by putting players on a Hollywood set, where they get to choose their thrill. From a spring-break beach house, to a horrifying Vegas hotel, players will discover the merciless world of movie studios where anyone can star in a scary Hollywood blockbuster film. There is an option link up to eight players online in this first-person shooter and to have a multiplayer experience like no other.<br><br>In the game, players can be as devious as possible by killing other competitors in nasty and unexpected ways. Players can use an arsenal of wacky weapons including guns, a frying pan and even an exploding remote-controlled rat to transform the movie set into real mayhem. In addition, players will be able to choose from a variety of stereotypical B-movie characters, such as the bikini beach babe, the creepy clown and the super jock.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EDseppt_CGM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6qz5F0QboYs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bloody-Good-Time/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bloody-good-time/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bloody-good-time"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":365,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"Torn from the immensely popular animated series Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Live gives fans the opportunity to battle with cards from the original series, GX and 5D's against some of the most popular characters in a race to the Fortune Cup.<br><br>Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels allows players the ability to compete with up to 4 friends in tag duels or compete in single duel matches through 3 modes of play. Rank matches allow players to compete against other XBLA players of the same rank, Quick match allows players to compete against anyone on XBLA and Custom match allows players to compete against their friends while completely customizing the rules. Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels provides the ability for total customization of gameplay rules, the ability to purchase new decks, deck construction and recipes while offering the ability to text and voice chat with a players tag duel partner.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Card Pack 001",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Card Pack 002",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Card Pack 003",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Card Pack 004",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Card Pack 005",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Card Pack 006",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Card Pack 007",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Card Pack 008",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Card Pack 009",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Card Pack 010",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Starter Deck 01",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Starter Deck. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Starter Deck 02",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Starter Deck. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"Starter Deck 03",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Starter Deck. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"Starter Deck 04",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Starter Deck. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":15,
				"name":"Starter Deck 05",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Starter Deck. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":16,
				"name":"Card Pack 011",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":17,
				"name":"Card Pack 012",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":18,
				"name":"Super Pack 01",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Super Pack 01 - A Super Pack for Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Easily strengthen your deck by applying this powerful Super Pack."
			},
			{
				"id":19,
				"name":"Structure Deck 01",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this Structure Deck. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":20,
				"name":"Card Pack 013",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":21,
				"name":"Card Pack 014",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":22,
				"name":"Structure Deck 02",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this Structure Deck. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":23,
				"name":"Super Pack 02",
				"releaseDate":"2013/02/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Super Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":24,
				"name":"Card Pack 015",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":25,
				"name":"Card Pack 016",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":26,
				"name":"Structure Deck 03",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this Structure Deck. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":27,
				"name":"Super Pack 03",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Super Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":28,
				"name":"Card Pack 017",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/12",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":29,
				"name":"Card Pack 018",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/12",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":30,
				"name":"Structure Deck 04",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/12",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this Structure Deck. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":31,
				"name":"Super Pack 04",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/12",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Super Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":32,
				"name":"Card Pack 019",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":33,
				"name":"Card Pack 020",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Card Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":34,
				"name":"Structure Deck 05",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this Structure Deck. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":35,
				"name":"Super Pack 05",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Strengthen your deck with this powerful Super Pack. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":36,
				"name":"Pieces of Exodia Deck",
				"releaseDate":"2013/12/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A deck with Exodia and other alternate win cards. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":37,
				"name":"Release the Iron Core Deck",
				"releaseDate":"2013/12/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A deck fueled by the Iron Core of Koa'ki Meiru. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":38,
				"name":"Syncing Dragon Deck",
				"releaseDate":"2013/12/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A deck with legendary Synchro Summoning Dragons. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":39,
				"name":"Chance for Gold Deck",
				"releaseDate":"2013/12/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A deck with the coin flipping Arcana Force. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":40,
				"name":"Worm Unity Deck",
				"releaseDate":"2013/12/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A deck with crafty Worms and Fusion monsters. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":41,
				"name":"Silent Levels Deck",
				"releaseDate":"2014/01/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A deck with powerful Leveling monsters. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":42,
				"name":"Reflection Destruction Deck",
				"releaseDate":"2014/01/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A deck with damage reversing traps and Synchro monsters. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":43,
				"name":"Ritual Victory Deck",
				"releaseDate":"2014/01/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A deck with powerful Ritual Summon Monsters. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":44,
				"name":"Returning to Mist Valley Deck",
				"releaseDate":"2014/01/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A deck with the winged beasts of Mist Valley. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			},
			{
				"id":45,
				"name":"Weapons of Power Deck",
				"releaseDate":"2014/01/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A deck with dangerous equipment cards. (Compatible with Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D's Decade Duels Plus and Yu-Gi-Oh! Millennium Duels)."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YzYpptoYVcc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/995075-yu-gi-oh-5ds-decade-duels/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Yu-Gi-Oh-5D-Decade-Duels/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/yu-gi-oh-5ds-decade-duel/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/yu-gi-oh!-5ds-decade-duels"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Yu-Gi-Ho! Wiki",
				"url":"http://yugioh.wikia.com/wiki/Yu-Gi-Oh!_5D's_Decade_Duels"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":366,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Spiders"],
			"synopsis":"In Faery: Legends of Avalon, the player plays as an elf or a fairy that will evolve during the story, through numerous quests and epic turn-based battles.<br><br>Throughout the adventure, the player will customize his avatar thanks to a unique system changing not only the whole look of the character in every detail, but also its spells and special abilities! The player will recruit various companions during his journey to assist him in his mission, and he will be given the chance to explore mythical places full of magic such as the World Tree, the famous 'Flying Dutchman' ghost ship, and many others, in order to try to understand why the Kingdom of Avalon is dying.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5Lf_PYzAEzk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6otavc33gE8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Faery/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/faery-legends-of-avalon/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/faery-legends-of-avalon"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":367,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cave"],
			"synopsis":"Set in the Muromachi period of Japanese history, Guwange tells the tale of the \"Shikigami users\", hosts to ghostly avatars called Shikigami. Unlike other Cave shooting games, known for their fighter craft and destructive machinery, the heroes of Guwange walk across the demonic landscape on their quest to rid themselves of the Shikigami curse, cutting a swath through their enemies.<br><br>The Xbox Live Arcade release of Guwange includes an Arcade Mode, ported directly from the arcade, an Arrange mode, featuring a more accessible design for new players, and a \"Blue\" version, previously shown only at Cave fan events.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RySQ6wAPY7k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Guwange/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/guwange/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/guwange"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":368,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Vitamin-G"],
			"synopsis":"Offering a puzzle exploration experience designed for gamers who have an affinity for solving new-style puzzles, The UnderGarden is a casual zen-like game that challenges players to explore beautiful underground caverns filled with strange life forms; physics based puzzles and plenty of hidden secrets. The world comes alive and music evolves as players get deeper into the world of The UnderGarden. With local co-operative gameplay, players can chill out,work together to solve puzzles and explore the world. The UnderGarden offers 20 different levels of modern exploration filled with brain teasing physics and eco-friendly puzzles that evoke an emotional response to the beauty and calm of this underwater oasis.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Ludwig Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/23",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GTs5fxLQj3g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s2AW-144UA8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-UnderGarden/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-undergarden/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-undergarden"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":369,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Team17 Software"],
			"synopsis":"With the Leopold and its unwanted attachment breaching the surface of an imposing ice planet, you have only a few hours to wade your way through flooded corridors and locate the origin of the threat that has so far laid waste to your once proud space ship. For the first time Conrad can venture outside of the ship in the breathtaking hull walk set pieces, and for those trigger-happy shooter fans there are vicious new enemies to fight, including the Electro-Shocker alien and the awe-inspiring final bosses. New armaments are also available in Descent, with the Electro-Link gun allowing for shockingly good crowd control whilst the formidable Project X weapon will tear through anything in its path.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ea9SFZOsmdE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P_jlMo4ehXQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Alien-Breed-Episode-3-Descent/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/alien-breed-3-descent"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":370,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bandai Namco Games"],
			"synopsis":"Celebrating the 30th anniversary of Pac-Man and following up on the 2007 award winning title, Pac-Man Championship Edition DX bolsters the beloved arcade formula by offering even more sophisticated mazes, modes, and enhancements. It'll be a celebration for fanatics and a new generation of players alike. Building upon Pac-Man Championship Edition's original six courses, the new game features more than 100 varied and mind-boggling mazes to navigate. Several new modes will also be available to test a player's pellet-munching aptitude. In Time Attack Mode, players will vie for the quickest clear time. Fulfill a series of objectives in Mission Mode or compete to devour the most number of ghosts gobbled in Ghost Mode.<br><br>With brand new visual variations and music, plus all the great features found in the first Pac-Man Championship Edition including mazes that dynamically change shape during gameplay, Pac-Man Championship Edition DX is a game worthy of the rotund hero's 30th birthday.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Mountain Course",
				"releaseDate":"2013/09/25",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Go mountain climbing while watching out for ghost trains that suddenly close in! Blazing through this technical mountain-like route requires advanced control technique. But beware ghost trains that take a shortcut and suddenly close in on Pac-Man if you pull too far ahead. Be one of the first to beat this new course and then try your hand at getting the highest score in the world! This add-on includes 8 modes: Score Attack (5 Minutes), Time Trial, and six different Time Trial (Short) games! Add-on included in the All You Can Eat Add-on Pack and Edition."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Big Eater Course",
				"releaseDate":"2013/09/25",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Greed can be fatal! Try this new concept with more than three times the usual number of sleeping ghosts appearing again and again. Power up frequently and gobble up those ghosts like crazy. Eat as many ghosts as you can, but never become too greedy and forget to secure an escape route while you're still powered up! You'll quickly realize that it's next to impossible to eat all the sleeping ghosts on a map with just one power-up! Try this new challenge for advanced players and get the highest score in the world! Add-on included in the All You Can Eat Add-on Pack and Edition."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Dig Dug Skin",
				"releaseDate":"2013/09/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Transform all your Pac-Man courses into complete Dig Dug Adventures! Dig Dug tries it Pac-Man style with the Pookas, but beware that infamous monster that will surely make an appearance as well... Dig it your way and enjoy the specially arranged version of the original Dig Dug music. This add-on includes characters, visuals, and BGM from the hit '80s arcade game Dig Dug! Add-on included in the All You Can Eat Add-on Pack and Edition."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Pac Steps BGM",
				"releaseDate":"2013/09/25",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Time to update your Pac-Man Championship Edition DX techno and trance music tracklist with drum 'n' bass music. The first half of the game has more organic sounding music centered on real instruments, while the second half is electronic music built around distorted synth tracks. Oh, and the double melody of Pac-Mania is also included somewhere, so make sure to hunt it down! Add-on included in the All You Can Eat Add-on Pack and Edition."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Pac is Back Skin",
				"releaseDate":"2013/09/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The characters from the computer-animated TV show \"Pac-Man and the Ghostly Adventures\" have invaded Pac-Man Championship Edition DX+ in a reckless celebration of the show's debut! Play using the characters and visuals from the show and transport all your courses into the world of \"Pac-Man and the Ghostly Adventures\"! Characters from the show even appear in visuals. Add-on included in the All You Can Eat Add-on Pack and Edition."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Rally-X Skin",
				"releaseDate":"2013/09/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Pac-Man gets an automotive makeover! Embark on a frantic Pac-Man-style car chase in Rally-X universe. From the pesky ghosts to the juicy fruits, all your courses now turn Rally-X-style! Even the BGM is a specially arranged version of the original Rally-X music. Get swept away by that nostalgic melody as you enjoy Pac-Man Championship Edition DX+ as you've never seen or heard it before! This add-on contains the characters, visuals, and BGM from the hit '80s arcade game Rally-X! Add-on included in the All You Can Eat Add-on Pack and Edition."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Reentrance BGM",
				"releaseDate":"2013/09/25",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Pac-Man Championship Edition DX main menu \"ENTRANCE\" is back in an extended version that can now be selected to play with. While the original version was more laid-back, in the long version, the tempo has been increased to match the game's frenetic pace. The track's simple phrase unexpectedly expands in a grandiose fashion at the end. Add-on included in the All You Can Eat Add-on Pack and Edition."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Championship III and Highway II Courses",
				"releaseDate":"2013/09/25",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Two Course Special Deal! Highly popular Championship II and Highway maps redesigned from square one to ramp up the fun factor to the max! Using bombs strategically will be the key to success even in advanced-player strategies to establish top scores. Try beating this ultimate challenge designed for the best players and chomp your way to the highest score in the world! This add-on contains a total of four modes, including Score Attack (5 Minutes) and Time Trial in Championship III and Highway II! Add-on included in the All You Can Eat Add-on Pack and Edition."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lnJ9Op7c_w4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0dLol1BM5bY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/997762-pac-man-championship-edition-dx/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pac-Man-Championship-Edition-DX/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pac-man-championship-edition-dx/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pac-man-championship-edition-dx"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Pac-Man Wiki",
				"url":"http://pacman.wikia.com/wiki/Pac-Man_Championship_Edition_DX"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":371,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sega"],
			"synopsis":"This downloadable game brings the Director's Cut of the arcade classic Crazy Taxi to Xbox 360.<br><br>Buckle up - it's sheer asphalt anarchy! Crazy Taxi screeches offers one wild and hilarious joy-riding jaunt. As a fearless cabbie with attitude, you're driven by a single goal: to rack up the mega-bucks in fares and tips before your shift ends. It's a race against the clock as you pick up passengers and white-knuckle it through busy streets and back alleys to their various destinations.<br><br>To keep that meter collecting cash, you've gotta take the fastest route possible, even if it means bending the traffic laws - just a little. Drive the wrong way down a one-way street, catch air as you sail over rooftops, swerve between oncoming traffic, or plough through a pavement cafe. But beware - the city is full of obstacles that are guaranteed to slow you down. And time is money! So get a grip on the wheel, sharpen your senses, and don't lose your cool.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_dzL-0FwT7M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TxGny9VtAGY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/997576-crazy-taxi/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Crazy-Taxi/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/crazy-taxi/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/crazy-taxi"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":372,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Vogster Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Unbound Saga is a 3D side-scrolling brawler based on the comic book by Dark Horse Comics. The game is set in a satirical comic book universe, where enemies are drawn onto the screen and madcap battles travel from panel to panel through a twisted, post-apocalyptic landscape. Break off a weapon and rage off the page!<br><br>You are Rick Ajax or Lori Machete, two fighters with their own style and a unique set of skills. As you journey through the futuristic wastelands of Toxopolis in search of your nemesis, \"The Maker\", you will encounter a wide range of bizarre creatures, colorful characters, and brutal bosses, most of whom will try their best to prevent you from reaching your goal.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3a0FYpXGJ0E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fvJ23yJuebc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Unbound-Saga/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/unbound-saga/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/unbound-saga"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":373,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Pi Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Ready for more? The second game in the Bomberman Live line of explosive action games features the same frantic action with 8-person online multiplayer that the series is known for, as well as a wealth of additional features, including teams, new modes, new arenas, new power-ups, new costumes, and even the ability to use an avatar as a playable character.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Bomb-Up Pack I",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/29",
				"achievements":10,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Craving more Bomberman action? Put on your Power Glove and go low-gravity with the all-new Asteroid arena! Bomb your opponents into traffic in Intersection! Dress up in two new costumes, the mighty Bombzilla and the heroic Firebomb!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Bomb-Up Pack II",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/12",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The Bomberman action never ends! The new Charger arena boosts your bombs bigger than ever! Go retro with Future, where the teleporters will take anything you throw at them! Dress for the occasion by terrorizing your opponents as a werewolf or playing nice as the nurse!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Bomb-Up Pack III",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/26",
				"achievements":25,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"A true Bomber never stops, and neither will you! The action continues in two new arenas -- Dodge spears like a true ninja in the Dojo, and take advantage of an extra life in Resurrection! Show up your opponents with the classy Matador costume or ready yourself for the field as Farmer Bomb!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d31LBU6SCkQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hRAzwVdfb3U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bomberman-Battlefest/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bomberman-live-battlefest/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bomberman-live-battlefest"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Bomberman Wiki",
				"url":"http://bomberman.wikia.com/wiki/Bomberman_Live:_Battlefest"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":374,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Wanako Games"],
			"synopsis":"This game was one of three finalists in the Unlock Xbox project, a promotion where amateur game designers competed to have their visions brought to life as actual game titles.<br><br>Doritos Crash Course is a fast-paced, funny, obstacle course game show for your Avatar to compete against your friends and family over Xbox Live. Play through 15 exciting platformer levels across 3 different countries. Compete against your friends and family up to four players over Xbox Live and local split-screen.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"City Lights",
				"releaseDate":"2013/01/02",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Doritos Crash Course returns with new level pack featuring 10 new courses filled with unique challenges and puzzles. Bounce above the glitz and glamour of Las Vegas and sprint through the historic sights of London to prove once more, who is the fastest in the world's leaderboards. As well as new achievements for even more gamerscore, we also include new versions of the Japan levels so you get even more chance to unlock all the achievements."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YuCFgaI_qEA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sGhiped9wYY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Doritos-Crash-Course/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/doritos-crash-course/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/doritos-crash-course"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":375,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bongfish GmbH"],
			"synopsis":"This game was one of three finalists in the Unlock Xbox project, a promotion where amateur game designers competed to have their visions brought to life as actual game titles.<br><br>Harms Way is a fast paced, action packed race with both drivers and snipers pairing up. As the sniper, help your driver win by any means necessary. Destroy the opponents, block their path, pick off their sniper, or even create shortcuts and earn nitrous for your driver! As the driver, you will want to be aggressive and ram the other cars. Don't stick too close for too long though, or your sniper won't have many options. There are various game modes so everybody can find a mode that is right for them! The sniper campaign has you trying to help your driver through various scenarios. You will need to have fast reflexes and a steady aim to complete the later missions. In singled out, everybody is a sniper except for one target car. If the target finishes the race, they can earn upgrades like bulletproof windshields. If somebody stops the target, they get to be the target next round. Call your shot mode is only racers, but allows you to call for race changing shots.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GOwSCJWF4jQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wOX2AW1bhrQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/615371-harms-way/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Harms-Way/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/harms-way/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/harms-way"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":376,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Microsoft Research"],
			"synopsis":"Discover the ancient board game of Go and take your Avatar on an unexpected HD adventure full of challenge with The Path of Go! Learn the basics and test your abilities using cutting-edge AI from Microsoft Research. Pit your skills against the world on Xbox Live. The ultimate Go experience for players of all skill levels: Dare you walk The Path of Go?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6bMnIw1vqjQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Path-of-Go/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-path-of-go/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-path-of-go"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":377,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Pi Studios", "Id Software"],
			"synopsis":"Quake Arena Arcade rumbles onto Xbox Live Arcade, introducing the challenge and adrenaline rush of THE definitive, competitive first-person shooter to a new generation of gladiators. Frag up to 15 of your best friends, closest enemies or complete strangers in 6 game types over Xbox LIVE, including Deathmatch, Capture the Flag and Harvester. Humiliate your opponents with 12 brutal weapons including the Lightning Gun, the Chain Gun and the time-honored Rocket Launcher. With 33 classic maps, 12 Xbox-exclusive arenas, HD and Widescreen support, and a brand new Single Player campaign, players will experience Quake like never before.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1fGFLup_lQ0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Quake-Arena-Arcade/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/quake-arena-arcade/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/quake-arena-arcade"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Quake Wiki",
				"url":"http://quake.wikia.com/wiki/Quake_Wikia"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":378,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Backbone Entertainment", "Konami"],
			"synopsis":"Wolverine, Storm, Cyclops, Dazzler, Colossus and Nightcrawler must battle through Brotherhood of Evil Mutants in this action-packed beat 'em up based on the comic book franchise. A massively popular brawler from Konami in its time, the original X-Men: The Arcade Game featured six X-Men characters (all of which could be playable at a time on the massive 6-player kiosks) brawling through millions of Sentinal forces and evil X-Men opponents.<br><br>For the first time ever, the arcade action comes home in a complete reproduction of the original hit! The double-screen action has been conformed for more modern widescreen HDTVs, allowing all six mutant heroes to be on-screen at one time, and Xbox Live integration allows all your friends to join you in a cooperative strike on Magneto's armies.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3id4s5YYljA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7efbpwf8PQA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/610419-x-men-the-arcade-game/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/X-Men-Arcade/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/xmen-arcade/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/x-men-the-arcade-game"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":379,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["NinjaBee"],
			"synopsis":"Once again, players can build a Kingdom for the Keflings that live in a little valley in this follow-up to the hit XBLA title A Kingdom for Keflings.<br><br>In Kingdom for Keflings, players will meet a Kefling pirate, a witch, a princess and an inventor just to name a few characters. They'll also travel between exotic Kelfing lands, assemble a robot, build an airship, and more. Players can even use their Xbox Avatars to put themselves into the game. In addition, A World of Keflings features a dynamic split-screen local multiplayer mode.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"It Came From Outer Space",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/26",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Aliens have crash-landed in A World of Keflings! Return to the Kefling world and help your new, little green friends repair their ship and return home! Get hours of added gameplay, explore a new kingdom and build an alien city! Meet bizarre new characters! Complete new quests and earn new achievements! Salvage wreckage, harvest sulfur crystals, and discover the haunting secrets of Scoobs' garbled past! Repair the alien spacecraft and send the marooned visitors back to the stars."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Sugar, Spice and Not So Nice",
				"releaseDate":"2012/10/10",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The chocolate volcano, caramel lake, cotton candy forest and gingerbread Keflings are in danger of being devoured when a sinister wizard and his evil nephew try to snatch control of Candy Peak! Help the Gingerlings of this mountaintop candy kingdom rebuild the sweet, sugary paradise. Harvest candy, bake building pieces and assemble edible buildings to create a beautiful, tasty kingdom. Save the Gingerlings and drive the wizard from their kingdom! This add-on requires the latest title update."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"The Curse of the Zombiesaurus",
				"releaseDate":"2012/10/17",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Put a horde of spooklings to work gathering bones, brimstone and ectoplasm in this macabre, amusing, night-time, graveyard kingdom! Build an eerie graveyard town for Wilhelm the grave keeper, Count Kefula and the other creepy Kefling residents of this chilling land. Horrifyingly strange creations await you as you create your spooky kingdom and work out how to deal with the largest, most horrifyingly strange creation of all... the Zombiesaurus! This add-on requires the latest title update."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=83phVz2NZOI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NlPfKQDS0Ng"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/A-World-of-Keflings/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/a-world-of-keflings/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/a-world-of-keflings"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":380,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blue Castle Games"],
			"synopsis":"Following up on the events of Dead Rising 2, Case West brings Frank West back into action in an epilogue to the harrowing story of the zombie assault on Fortune City. Dead Rising 2: Case Wet sees Frank West team up with Chuck Greene for some serious co-op action. In co-op mode, players will see the two protagonists delve deeper into the reasons behind the Fortune City outbreak and provide further links to the Willamette incident.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L9Dt56-9CJU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0N0VFmrCw3A"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/605976-dead-rising-2-case-west/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dead-Rising-2-Case-West/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dead-rising-2-case-west/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dead-rising-2-case-west"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dead Rising Wiki",
				"url":"http://deadrising.wikia.com/wiki/Dead_Rising_2:_Case_West"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":381,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Naked Sky Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"MicroHexon Research thought they had revolutionized medical technology when they invented the MicroBot, a microscopic robot specifically designed to assist the immune system in fighting a variety of health ailments. Unfortunately, due to a disastrous malfunction, their technology is now working in tandem with the viruses and bacteria and attempting to take over the host body. Now it is up to you to stop the biotechnical infestation before it's too late.<br><br>Pilot a prototype cutting-edge MicroBot that has the capability to be customized and upgraded mid-mission in order to cure the infected host. Improve your weaponry, movement, defensive options and special attacks using data fragments harvested from eradicated enemies. Travel through blood, bone, breath and brain as you track down and eradicate the cause of the infection. But are you the ultimate cure... or the disease?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bQIwChUvX-c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pBjpcMGTR_A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MicroBot/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/microbot"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":382,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Halfbrick Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Raskulls is an entirely original puzzle platformer with a rich single-player campaign and addictive online multiplayer component. Gameplay blends platforming, puzzle and racing. With hundreds of blocks arranged in Tetris-style fashion throughout each world, players must use a block-smashing wand to find their way through the level in the most efficient way possible. Some levels are simple point-to-point or lap footraces, while other modes involve diffusing bombs and conserving block-bashing \"ammo\". Up to four players can race with heaps weapons and powerups in a huge variety of levels and modes.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Reinforcements 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/26",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Raskulls is expanding in the first Reinforcements pack with the addition of four new playable characters and a new Grand Prix! Meet Spaceman, with a heart of gold and lust for adventure - Viking, whose pillaging tendencies have made him none too popular - Kitten, who never forgets to purr - and Barney, the lovable yet entirely incompetent henchman of the evil Turncoat. Take your new Raskulls to race on 4 entirely new tracks that even take you inside King's castle! Download this pack and turn the heat up in your Grand Prix matches!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Reinforcements 2",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/13",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"It's round two for Raskulls Reinforcements, with four new characters stepping up to race against the best. General Battlebones, proving that seniority means superiority - Robot, who is some twisted scientist's bizarre creation - Witchdoctor, with more curses that you can shake a voodoo doll at and Scurv, the final and dumbest of all the evil henchmen. Race over 4 awesome new tracks and brave through the storm! Collect the final four characters to complete your full Raskulls roster!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N44t-H93tHE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JRZxy_xFieA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Raskulls/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/raskulls/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/raskulls"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":383,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Southend Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Ilomilo is a puzzle game where the player controls two fellows named ilo and milo. The two friends always seem to get separated from each other in the surrealistic and ever changing world they inhabit, and the goal of each level is to reunite them.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Autumn Tale",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/09",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Ilo and milo have decided to go for a nice autumn stroll. While wandering through the autumn landscape, they discover a trail of leaves. The two friends excitedly follow the trail, hoping to find something new and exciting. Before they know it, the trail has split in two and they have once again lost each other! This new ilomilo adventure features 25 brand new levels played in a new beatiful autumn setting. Naturally, there are also more safkas to find, unlocking the most challenging bonus levels yet!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_9cFP37Opko"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wpXWyWj2p04"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/605744-ilomilo/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/ilomilo/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ilomilo-wp7/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ilomilo"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":384,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Brightside Games"],
			"synopsis":"Zeit 2 is an arcade shoot'em up built around an innovative time travel feature. Assist your mission and co-op with your prior self playing by traveling back in time. Blast away countless enemies and get the high score in 6 challenging game modes.<br><br>Zeit 2 is a Independent Games Festival 2009 Student Showcase Finalist and Microsoft Dream Build Play 2008 Finalist",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nqmo63Sg-_0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zC8rkVZsf2k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Zeit/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Zeit/walkthrough.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/zeit-squared"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":385,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Bright Light"],
			"synopsis":"In this online action adventure, players join courageous robots Mar-T and Chip as they find themselves dumped with the trash on a strange planet. Working together in co-op mode, the mechanical duo must find a way to repair their ship and escape the planet before nefarious Lord Krung can dispatch his henchmen to destroy them. Mar-T and Chip will need to collect upgradable action parts to unlock new abilities that will aid them as they battle countless enemies including the evil Krofax, hostile spider monkeys and even a Super Huge Mega Laser! Can our heroes rescue their other stranded robotic friends and unearth all of the spare parts they need to make their escape?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9vXVwv4qXCs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DYh9wtUsGHA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Spare-Parts/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/spare-parts"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":386,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Atomic Games"],
			"synopsis":"Breach is a first-person multiplayer shooter which utilizes the innovative Hydrogen Engine to give players inventive ways to use destruction so they can stun, manipulate, and eliminate their opponents with a new toolbox of tactics. Virtual warriors can punch holes through floors to get the drop on enemies below, breach both interior and exterior walls, crush enemy fighters by collapsing ceilings and balconies, and even shoot away individual bricks to create \"shooter's holes\".<br><br>Players will take on the roles of some of the most elite field operatives in the US. CIA Special Activities Division officers are the teams sent in on real-life black operations when no one can ever know the US was involved. This secret world of black operations is brought to life with accurate weapons, gear, and real-life spy gadgets which virtual operators can use with real world tactics to defeat the enemy.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ict4wH-avGg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uRAJOAkgk6I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9a4VF2s6kH4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Breach/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/breach/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/breach"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":387,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Fatshark"],
			"synopsis":"Nathan Spencer returns as the daring elite soldier equipped with special bionic abilities. Spencer will have to face his greatest challenge yet as General Sabio, a new technologically sophisticated foe, is on the brink of launching a deadly missile attack.<br><br>Nathan Spencer will make use of his trademark tool - his bionic grappling hook - to grab, swing and leap through series of lush new environments. He'll be met by plenty of gun-toting soldiers and mechanized threats ready to give him a hostile greeting. Bionic Commando Rearmed 2 improves upon the visual achievements of its predecessor with the addition of more detailed character models, textures, and vibrant colors. New player mechanics will add another strategic layer of platforming to the overall experience and the famous bionic arm will be getting a major makeover delivering a more dynamic bionic experience to the player.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oWSh7h1VJoE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fn8KgmSPo18"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bionic-Commando-Rearmed-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bionic-commando-rearmed-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":388,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Double Fine Productions"],
			"synopsis":"Set in a diorama world, Stacking is a third person adventure puzzle game where you play as Charlie Blackmore, the world tiniest Russian stacking doll. He is all too accustomed to being overlooked and dismissed--too small to be of any consequence. But Charlie's size turns out to be his greatest strength after all.<br><br>Explore a vintage world inhabited by living Russian stacking dolls as you jump into more than 100 unique dolls and use their special abilities to solve a wide variety of puzzles & challenges.Embark on an adventure to rescue Charlie's family from the nefarious industrialist known only as the \"Baron\". This imaginative 3rd person puzzle adventure game will take you on a journey from a bustling Royal Train Station to a high-flying Zeppelin as you collect unique dolls and matched stacking sets to display in Charlie's secret hideout, where you chronicle your adventures.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Lost Hobo King",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/06",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"In the Lost Hobo King, the first downloadable expansion for Double Fine's Stacking, players once again assume the role of Charlie Blackmore, the world's smallest Russian stacking doll. Charlie travels with his hobo friend Levi to the mysterious kingdom of Camelfoot, the mythical resting place of lost hobo king and his crown. Charlie must help Levi's uncle, Rufus Ryken, reclaim his rightful throne by solving three tests of valor and reawakening the hobo blacksmiths of old. Only then can the crown be reforged, enabling Rufus to become king and unite the fractured hobo people under one sardine. The Lost Hobo King features a complete adventure with several new challenges, each with multiple solutions, an all new assortment of unique dolls with engaging abilities, and a new round of hi-jinks to discover and make trouble with. Only the worthy can reclaim the crown of Camelfoot!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YsrAIe2xWpU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gWh2o2pM5e4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/614182-stacking/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Stacking/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/stacking/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/stacking"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":389,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Keen Games"],
			"synopsis":"Have you got what it takes to outrun your rivals? TNT Racers is a multiplayer racing game full of variety, combining fast as lightning race action with brand new features. The Shadow Race feature lets every player stay in the race even if a driver is clearly in an inferior position. But the best things are the wicked pick-ups which will ultimately decide about victory or defeat. TNT - Tracks N Tricks - cool tracks and snappy gadgets! One powerful adrenaline kick is guaranteed. Grab yourself TNT Racers today and let your competitors eat the dust!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Drift Package",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/26",
				"achievements":25,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"You're looking for new challenges in TNT Racers? How about the exclusive Speed Class: Drift! With 2 brand spanking new vehicles, 4 additional demanding tracks and Drift Challenges galore. With TNT Racers, the thrills just keep on coming. May the most explosive driver win."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Formula TNT Package",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/23",
				"achievements":25,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"TNT Racers is taking it to the next level! Experience an even faster Speed Class: Formula TNT! It comes with 2 new crazy fast cars and another 4 awesome circuits. Stacks of Formula TNT Challenges are waiting to be mastered. What are you waiting for? So get going: Hit the gas and have fun!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a1guSiTgXxY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NVYRc1Z59k0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/TNT-Racers/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tnt-racers"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":390,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["ARC System Works"],
			"synopsis":"As homage to the legacy of Konami's run-and-gun games, Hard Corps: Uprising brings an exciting new look to a traditionally retro genre, all the while keeping with the frenetic gameplay that defines the shooter category. The game follows the soldier Bahamut as he begins to rise in strength and write his legend. Multiple game modes allow seasoned pros to show off their skills and enable genre neophytes to reach victory. Rising Mode affords new players the opportunity to earn points by overcoming enemies while under the protection of the life gauge system. This new system allows them to team up with advanced players cooperatively on or offline without the threat of sudden death.<br><br>Superior players will feel right at home in Arcade Mode, modeled after the classic run-and-gun aesthetic. Playing solo or co-op, players will have to prove their expertise by finding numerous achievements and avoiding sudden death. Players all over the world can also link up via Online Co-Op Mode to view rankings, achievements and leader boards.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Harley",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Harley Daniels is a mercenary for hire who wears the dog tags of his many fallen enemies as medals. He has the upbeat attitude of a man who has seen it all and is a survivor. Although he's never one to abandon a friend, he's fine with taking the easy way out. Base Attributes: Extra tough (4 health), but slower movement Available Attributes: Rising Mode store discounts on weapons and extra health."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Sayuri",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A lone woman with incredible strength, Sayuri is a mysterious samurai assassin from the Republic Tribe. She has joined the Rebellion's mission to defeat Tiberius, but her motives are murky. Base Attributes: Samurai blade attack, Quick movement Available Attributes: Launch Attack, Homing Jump, Dunk Attack."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Leviathan",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Bahamut's defection to the Rebellion stunned everyone, no one more than his chief rival in the Empire's army, Leviathan. Beneath the bitter rivalry was a deep respect, and so the questions gnawed at him: Why did he leave? How could he betray us? Why did he choose that path? Base Attributes: Only one weapon slot Available Attributes: Moonsault (backflip), Grenade Throw, Sliding Attack."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZDOrp_TMGfA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0jHu4GNYwwQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hard-Corps-Uprising/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hard-corps-uprising/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hard-corps-uprising"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Contra Wiki",
				"url":"http://contra.wikia.com/wiki/Hard_Corps:_Uprising"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":391,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["PopCap Games"],
			"synopsis":"Take on friends in the brilliant gem-matching action of Bejeweled Blitz Live! Bejeweled Blitz LIVE offers Xbox 360 players the same fast paced 60-second action found in the popular Facebook variant of Bejeweled Blitz, but with all new modes, including 16-player simultaneous Party mode and head-to-head Battle mode over Live.<br><br>Beyond crystal-sharp, high-definition graphics, Bejeweled Blitz LIVE for XBLA boasts two styles of play: classic and an all new twist. In addition to real-time leaderboards driving up-to-the-minute scores from you and your friends, the game also provides the all new Friendscore. Friendscore allows you to combine your score with the scores of your Xbox LIVE friends for the highest weekly and all-time totals.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R0chEm5a2ow"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-Zoed4obbkg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bejeweled-Blitz-LIVE/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bejeweled-blitz-live/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bejeweled-blitz-live"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":392,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Piranha Games"],
			"synopsis":"Days of Thunder: Arcade teams players with Rowdy Burns as the latest recruit to hit the high-octane racing circuit. With Rowdy as their coach, players will learn to drop the hammer, hit the pit and trade paint with other cars. Rowdy Burns is voiced by Michael Rooker, known for his roles in \"Mallrats\", \"Eight Men Out\", \"Cliffhanger\", and of course, \"Days of Thunder\". As players advance, they'll compete against the characters from the film, each with AI designed to match their driving style and personality seen in the film.<br><br>Players will need to watch for Cole Trickle's reckless, aggressive driving, Rowdy Burns' ruthless, veteran skills and Russ Wheeler's hot head. To steer clear of otherwise unavoidable crashes, gamers can take advantage of the focus feature, which temporarily puts surroundings into slow-motion. The adrenaline soon kicks back into gear as players drop the hammer by drafting behind other cars and whipping past them to get an extra burst of speed.<br><br>Days of Thunder: Arcade features road tracks for both single and multiplayer challenges. Road tracks allow players to race outside the speedway for an added challenge and variation in turning and car control. Up to twelve players can race online, pushing the limits to log the fastest times on the leader boards. There are four different modes -- Quick Race, Time Trial, Career, with circuits of varying difficulty, and Derby Mode, where players are encouraged to deal as much damage as they can.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nLkJn8J_oKk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Days-of-Thunder/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/days-of-thunder-arcade/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/days-of-thunder-arcade"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":393,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft"],
			"synopsis":"One of Ubisoft's most beloved classics comes to HD consoles in this refreshed edition of Beyond Good & Evil. Use your camera to uncover the dark secrets of your government in this story-driven action-adventure.<br><br>Meet Jade. She's a brunette beauty with an eye for mystery and a camera to uncover it. When the would-be heroine's futuristic planet is threatened by aliens, Jade finds herself thrust into the heart of a vicious conspiracy that could stretch to the very top of her government.<br><br>Jade can explore a huge, water-covered world by hovercraft or take to a variety of islands and interact with merchants, or tackle assignments to earn money and advance the surprisingly deep and intriguing storyline that surrounds her quest. She can also gain a number of items and weapons that are integral to advancing and a lot of fun to wield. Packed full of twists and turns and even a talking man-pig, Ubisoft has crafted yet another big adventure series.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wg4CDpo0aw0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bG1Lwy5hXLE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/609596-beyond-good-and-evil-hd/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Beyond-Good-and-Evil-HD/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/beyond-good-and-evil/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/beyond-good-evil-hd"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Irish Network - The Beyond Good and Evil Wiki",
				"url":"http://beyondgoodandevil.wikia.com/wiki/The_IRIS_Network_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":394,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Runic Games"],
			"synopsis":"From the creators of Diablo and Fate, Runic Games presents a fresh take on action RPGs with Torchlight. The discovery of a rich vein of powerful but dangerous magic ore has turned the sleepy village of Torchlight into a thriving boomtown. Players risk their lives to explore randomly arranged dungeons in a variety of treacherous and exciting settings, learning spectacular skills and finding the most exquisite and powerful treasures.<br><br>In its Xbox 360 incarnation, combat is more exciting with revamped controls and mechanics, new armor and quests! There's even an exclusive new pet for your character. Send a select goodie or two to your friends on Live to share the fun for the first time.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_tbzlLLHdPw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dEYU1KSOp94"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/618630-torchlight/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Torchlight/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/torchlight/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/torchlight"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Torchlight Wiki",
				"url":"http://torchlight.wikia.com/wiki/Torchlight_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":395,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Saber Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Battle: Los Angeles gives players the opportunity to relive the thrill of the movie as they fight alongside characters from the film to defend the city of Los Angeles from attacks from unknown forces in fast and frantic first-person shooter gameplay. Players assume the role of Corporal Lee Imlay, a Marine fighting against a worldwide alien invasion that has the city of Los Angeles as the major battleground and focal point for the game. Battle unique and varied enemies, using an arsenal of weapons throughout the game like an assault rifle, sniper rifle, rocket launcher, frag grenades, and a turret gun. Navigate the streets of Los Angeles avoiding fierce and relentless attacks. Aside from high-caliber fire fighting combat, destructible environments have been included using the Havok Destruction Module, which will allow players to destroy scaffolding structures, vehicles and overpasses to eliminate enemy forces. With unlockable content, trophy support, and 5.1 surround sound, Battle: Los Angeles will pull players deep into the heart of the battle to save mankind.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OoidaoqBFB8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C8G7tDZ2F3Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Battle-Los-Angeles/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/battle-los-angeles/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/battle-los-angeles"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":396,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Krome Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Go all-in with Full House Poker! Play Texas Hold 'Em against your friends and thousands of players worldwide, and bring your personality to the table with unique tells and unlockables galore. Play a quick two-player game for some lightning action, join a big 30-player tournament, or play a round of Texas Heat, our live poker game show where you play with thousands of players worldwide and have 30 minutes to bluff, bet, and raise your way to the final table! You can also build your bank roll on the go with a companion game on Windows Phone 7 handsets. Save your player progression and winnings between sessions as you increase the stakes and make your mark as a Full House Poker pro!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Texas Heat, Spring 2011 Season",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/15",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Texas Heat, Summer 2011 Season",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/03",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Texas Heat, Summer 2012 Season",
				"releaseDate":"2012/07/26",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Texas Heat, Fall 2012 Season",
				"releaseDate":"2012/09/22",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Texas Heat, Winter 2012 Season",
				"releaseDate":"2012/12/20",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Texas Heat, Spring 2013 Season",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/27",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lgj3vkcr_Ao"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j8cAmG7hteo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/618628-full-house-poker/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Full-House-Poker/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/full-house-poker/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/full-house-poker"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":397,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Behaviour Santiago"],
			"synopsis":"Ghostbusters: Sanctum of Slime is a four player, ghost-busting adventure that will take players on a brand new paranormal experience. Gamers will suit up with their proton packs and assume the role of a rookie hired by the Ghostbusters to save New York City from a disaster of ghoulish proportions.<br><br>The action-packed gameplay progresses as players complete jobs as fearless rookies who explore a series of haunted environments that must be cleared of any ectoplasmic threats. The gripping adventure rages on as players encounter gigantic bosses that require a concentrated effort to defeat using a medley of highly destructive weapons including the Proton Stream, Plasma Inductor, and the Fermion Shock. Rookie Ghostbusters will face the dangers of the eerie world alone or with a ghostbusting team of friends both locally or online through the game's multiplayer capability.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y5bZzIfrdlA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E4rhSHq6Yjg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/614910-ghostbusters-sanctum-of-slime/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ghostbusters-Sanctum-of-Slime/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ghostbusters-sanctum-of-slime/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ghostbusters-sanctum-of-slime"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Ghostbusters Wiki",
				"url":"http://ghostbusters.wikia.com/wiki/Ghostbusters:_Sanctum_of_Slime"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":398,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Hothead Games"],
			"synopsis":"Swarm lets the player take control of 50 utterly fearless Swarmites and drive them through an intense, entertaining and often suicidal battle for a greater good. Run, bash, huddle, boost, stack, jump, push and throw your way through gauntlets of death and destruction in an attempt to collect valuable DNA and ensure that at least one Swarmite survives. With a unique combination of mass character control and fast action, the resulting brutal aftermath will make players want to play Swarm over and over again.<br><br>Featuring innovative swarm control and imitate mechanics, Swarm is a hilarious romp through a desolate and dangerous world that offers players gameplay they've never experienced before.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bc6kIgDIO64"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ywj9FFGSKN0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Swarm/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/swarm/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/swarm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":399,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ankama Studio"],
			"synopsis":"Islands of Wakfu is an action/adventure game set in the universe of the world-famous DOFUS and Wakfu MMORPGs. Gameplay revolves around the complementarity between the two principal characters: Nora, the young Eliatrope, and her brother dragon, Efrim. Nora is a close combat fighter, relying on her fists, feet, combos, and dimensional powers. Efrim is a long-distance shooter who is able to fly. They breathe the Wakfu in and out, bloom Wakfu flowers, and harvest Wakfu honey that can be used to buy upgrades for both characters. Control the third playable character, the Platypus, to pick up items, interact with the environment, and find secret passages.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RApH3yxd3ZM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n_0CI6Je_iU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Islands-of-Wakfu/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/islands-of-wakfu/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/islands-of-wakfu"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dofus Wiki",
				"url":"http://dofuswiki.wikia.com/wiki/Islands_of_Wakfu"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wakfu Wiki",
				"url":"http://wakfu.wikia.com/wiki/Islands_of_Wakfu"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":400,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Vatra"],
			"synopsis":"In Rush'N Attack Ex-Patriot, a clandestine struggle exists between Russia and the United States for military intelligence during the shadows of the Cold War.<br><br>When the CIA discovers that the Russians have found a never-before-seen material used to create devastating nuclear missiles, they form a secret branch called \"Harvest\" to infiltrate and investigate the Soviet weapons program. The Cold War soon ends without a bang and the operation is discontinued. Decades later, new operative Sergeant Sid Morrow, call sign \"Wolf Spider\", is tasked with retrieving an abandoned member of Harvest, re-evaluating the missile threat, and sabotaging it if necessary.<br><br>Rush'N Attack Ex-Patriot takes players through three massive environments of a Siberian prison complex, a bio-weapons laboratory, and a nuclear weapons base. In each location, gamers will have to complete a variety of mission and survive encounters with a variety of Russian soldiers from prison guards to elite paratrooper, snipers, and more.<br><br>Players choose their own gameplay style by moving through each level loud and fast or silent and deadly. As they find themselves almost always outnumbered, players must avoid constant detection from the vigilant guards and the unblinking eyes of security cameras. Armed with a little more than a knife, the players will have to scrounge for weapons and supplies to survive as they are truly behind enemy lines.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=znsIzJBULU0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=deRmx1o9yTE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rushn-Attack-Ex-Patriot/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rushn-attack-ex-patriot/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rushn-attack-ex-patriot"
			}]
		}
	}]
}