{
	"catalog": [
	{
		"id":201,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Arcade"],
			"synopsis":"Get ready for high-octane, shooting action with PowerUp Forever. Space and time are irrelevant in your search for evil forces as you fight a relentless horde of enemies across an endless spatial battlefield. Destroying elite enemies allows you to absorb their energy, transforming your ship's size, shape and power. As your ship evolves and grows your world and its enemies shrink to insignificance, revealing even more massive and powerful enemies that were previously too large to see.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xueAmzV7Y8A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/PowerUp-Forever/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/powerup-forever/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/powerup-forever"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":202,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["NinjaBee"],
			"synopsis":"Doritos' Dash of Destruction is a free game packed with action as a promotion for Dorritos snack chips.<br><br>Dash your way through the city as a hungry Tyrannosaurus Rex in search of a Doritos delivery truck, or as a terrified truck zooming in and out of the T-Rex's path of destruction in search of its drop-off points. Enjoy the fast-paced action as a single player or join with friends!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fZ696qybV0E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=soviF3Xx7Po"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/955192-dash-of-destruction/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dash-of-Destruction/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dash-of-destruction/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dash-of-destruction"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":203,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Say Design", "CTXM"],
			"synopsis":"Puzzle Arcade is a jigsaw puzzle game for the Xbox 360. The game features a number of puzzle settings and features (including Picture Puzzles, Dynamic Puzzles Weekly Puzzles, Challenge Puzzles and Xbox Live Vision Puzzle) as well as multiplayer modes and leaderboards.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Space",
				"releaseDate":"2008/01/08",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Explore the universe, from planet Earth to distant galaxies with this collection of fascinating space images."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sLpWdt_Wgoc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Puzzle-Arcade/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/puzzle-arcade/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/puzzle-arcade"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":204,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Pipeworks Software"],
			"synopsis":"Merv Griffin's Crosswords is a fast-paced, new generation Q and A game in which players compete against each other and the clock in a unique way to solve a crossword puzzle.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=urudE2ZIu5s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Merv-Griffins-Crosswords/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/merv-griffin-xwords/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/merv-griffins-crosswords"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":205,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["TikGames"],
			"synopsis":"Track down the evil and destructive fugitive Dr. Chaos, as you hunt down clues in the exciting seek and find game Interpol: The Trail of Dr. Chaos. As an elite agent for Interpol, it is your mission to eradicate his trail of corruption as it takes you around the world from one international city to the next. Use your investigative skills to quickly gather the evidence needed to bring him to justice.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o51WvAE9rV4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=csBBdj77n_U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Interpol-The-Trail-of-Dr-Chaos/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/interpol/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/interpol-the-trail-of-dr-chaos"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":206,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Twisted Pixel"],
			"synopsis":"In this full featured 3D action adventure, players take control of Frank, a simple alien that must partner up with The Maw, a cute little blob with an insatiable hunger that makes him the most dangerous creature in the galaxy. Players will need to harness The Maw's unstoppable growth and the incredible powers he earns, in order to help Frank find his way home.<br><br>The Maw features a lengthy, full scope, single-player experience filled with hundreds of 3D character animations, intense cinemas, cutting-edge graphics technology, a professionally composed soundtrack, and much more.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Deleted Scene - Brute Force",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/18",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"In this \"deleted scene\" from The Maw, the Bounty Hunters have sent in members from their new elite strike force, the Brutes, to stop Frank and Maw. The two must use powers from the Beetull and Gastro creatures to avoid capture. This part of the story occurs between the Bulb Valley and Chaindown levels."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Deleted Scene - River Redirect",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/11",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"In this \"deleted scene\" from The Maw, raging fires block Frank and Maw's way, but with the powers of the Gastro and Puff-tor creatures, they change the course of a river and reopen their path. This part of the story takes place after the Looferland level."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Deleted Scene - Speeder Lane",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/29",
				"achievements":20,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"In this \"deleted scene\" from The Maw, Frank steals a Bounty Hunter Speeder and uses it to break through their blockade. This part of the story takes place before the Mesas level."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-KJbUeXmEq8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xnE7M_HZD1s"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/949624-the-maw/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Maw/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-maw/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-maw"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":207,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FunTown World Limited"],
			"synopsis":"This version of the traditional Chinese tile game is made for the whole family to play! It includes the ability to compete against your friends on Xbox LIVE or against AI opponents. You can also earn achievements, aim for the top of the leaderboards, and enjoy tons of exciting Mahjong variations!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Chinese Festival",
				"releaseDate":"2009/01/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Visit the temple and play Mahjong during the Chinese New Year to bring good luck for the whole year."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Moon Festival Theme",
				"releaseDate":"2009/10/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Celebrate the Moon Festival in Sci-Fi style! Play Mahjong on the Moon with a Space Station, the Moon Bunny, and a flying spaceman."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Zen Garden Theme",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Play Mahjong in a Japanese garden surround by red and white Sukura blossoms and the springtime vista of Mount Fuji Mountain."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Cool Summer Theme",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/04",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Enjoy a cool summer by playing Mahjong at the South Pole. Have a great Mahjong party surrounded by floating icebergs. It's cool!"
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Merry Christmas DLC",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The holidays are the time for Mahjong! Family reunions, Christmas trees and gifts make everyone happy. Santa Claus comes down the chimney while you play."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iGPhHFum45M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/FunTown-Mahjong/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/funtown-mahjong"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":208,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Southend Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"R-Type Dimensions combines the genre-defining coin-op classics R-Type and R-Type II, with a twist. Although classic gameplay remains untouched, R-Type Dimensions elevates the experience to greater heights with brand-new additions and enhancements. For the first time, R-Type Dimensions allows multiplayer co-op play locally or over Xbox LIVE for up to two players. Fight through all 14 Bydo-infested stages in the original 2-D or all-new 3-D graphics with the ability to swap back and forth between the two seamlessly. Strike down the evil Bydo Empire and save the earth in R-Type Dimensions.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3UhUzM7fJOs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qjj_cJBfQvM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/R-Type-Dimensions/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/r-type/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/r-type-dimensions"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"R-Type Wiki",
				"url":"http://rtype.wikia.com/wiki/R-Type_Compilations"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":209,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"An all-new downloadable hockey experience from EA Sports, 3 on 3 NHL Arcade promises to provide a lightning-paced, no rules hockey experience that gamers of all ages and ability levels can enjoy. With no rules to hinder the action, gamers can enjoy the sport without the having to worry about adhering to icing, checking and other cumbersome regulations. And the all-new physics engine that was introduced in NHL 09 is back, but with one small adjustment -- now each hit is specifically designed to be absolutely huge. Now gamers will be able to hit the opposition with such bone-crushing checks that his victim will literally be blasted clear over the boards and off the rink.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vRO240ch_GA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G1ou31V564I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/3-on-3-NHL-Arcade/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/3-on-3-nhl-arcade/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/3-on-3-nhl-arcade"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":210,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["TikGames"],
			"synopsis":"A version of the popular Minesweeper puzzle game for Xbox Live Arcade. Find and flag all the bombs by searching spaces around the explosives, using the numbered clues to zero in on the bombs. Just don't tap the bombs themselves or you'll go up in a bang.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajvzkC9bhXE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Minesweeper-Flags/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/minesweeper-flags/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/minesweeper-flags"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":211,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Snowblind Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Enter the ever-changing \"Death Tank\" arena and unleash your destructive power in multi-player, next-gen combat. Equip your futuristic tank with earth shattering weapons and roll on over to Xbox LIVE to join in epic battles between friends.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i7yoVTsCDc4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DghcuZfsGfI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cvwz7wRWtl0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lv8go2hgAEA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Death-Tank/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/death-tank/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/death-tank"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":212,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Taito"],
			"synopsis":"Mr. ESC returns in the sequel to the puzzler Exit. The second adventure places a greater emphasis on challenging puzzle elements. In turn, the game's control scheme has been changed in order to deemphasize action and place the emphasis on puzzles -- you now input actions in order to make Mr. ESC move rather than directly control him. Among other gameplay refinements, you can now change your direction when climbing up a ladder. The game also adds new obstacles, like ropeways and escalators. You'll also find new types of survivors, including a dog, whose capable of making long jumps and swimming, and a \"macho\", a male or female character who, as the name suggests has tremendous strength.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"DLC",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/22",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"XBLA Original Stage Pack Add Situations 23 to 25 - 3 exclusive Xbox LIVE Arcade Situations (30 stages)."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E75TZRiAy1c"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958334-exit-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Exit-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/exit-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":213,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Deadline Games"],
			"synopsis":"This action-brawler acts as the prequel to the story in the Watchmen graphic novels and movie. Taking place in an alternate history of the 1980s, the game stars the two masked vigilantes Rorschach and Nite Owl, and features a co-operative mode so that players can team up to beat down the bad guys. Watchmen: The End is Nigh will go beyond the film and delve into the characters, rivalries and challenges in a mature action-brawler.<br><br>Part 1 takes place more than a decade before the film's main story, delving into the partnership of urban vigilantes Rorschach and Nite Owl before the hero-banning Keene Act. The game features bloody, visceral combat in rich settings while it explores the crime-fighting partnership of urban vigilantes Rorschach and Nite Owl.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QoEaqi-Zep4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i_FkjQzE6-g"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/951551-watchmen-the-end-is-nigh/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Watchmen/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/watchmen-the-end-is-nigh/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/watchmen-the-end-is-nigh"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Watchmen Wiki",
				"url":"http://watchmen.wikia.com/wiki/Watchmen:_The_End_Is_Nigh"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":214,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Square Enix"],
			"synopsis":"Featuring jobs and locations from the popular Final Fantasy Tactics series, this unique defensive simulation game requires players to strategically deploy units to fend off encroaching enemy hordes and prevent them from stealing their party's crystals.<br><br>The Xbox LIVE Arcade for Xbox 360 version includes several improvements to the interface and a new design optimized for consoles. A worldwide ranking system allows players to upload their scores to leaderboards and see how they stack up against other players around the globe. These and other new features are sure to increase excitement and enhance replayability.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fiLk0_vpGJI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ll9G9lcsQtU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/957925-crystal-defenders/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Crystal-Defenders/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/crystal-defenders/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/crystal-defenders"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Final Fantasy Wiki",
				"url":"http://finalfantasy.wikia.com/wiki/Crystal_Defenders"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":215,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"Fans can replicate the NCAA Division I Mens Basketball Championship bracket and play with all the schools in the NCAA Basketball 09: March Madness Edition, available to download just in time for the start of the NCAA tournament. The game initially features teams from last year's tournament, and beginning on March 18, the stats update to feature the just-announced official Selection Sunday brackets and accurate teams with updated ratings.<br><br>NCAA Basketball 09: March Madness Edition re-creates all the atmosphere and intensity of NCAA March Madness by enabling fans to authentically replicate the entire NCAA Tournament and play through the \"virtual bracket\" with their favorite team under the same conditions they'll face throughout March Madness. Take on the challenge of leading any of the 65 schools competing on the road to the Final Four, from the opening round right through to a virtual reproduction of the Final Four on the authentic Ford Field court in Detroit, where one team will be crowned NCAA Division I Men's Basketball National Champion on April 6, 2009.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Bracket Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/18",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Update your tournament bracket with the latest teams and seedings and take your team to the Final Four! NCAA Basketball 09: Bracket Pack lets you replicate the 2009 NCAA Tournament with an authentic field of teams including updated teams ratings for all tournament teams. This update is compatible with NCAA Basketball 09: March Madness Edition."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SU_WrhkQiak"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NCAA-Basketball-March-Madness/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ncaa-basketball-mme/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ncaa-basketball-09-march-madness-edition"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":216,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["PopCap Games"],
			"synopsis":"Wield mystifying Magic Powers, rack up huge bonus points and make shots you'll smile about for weeks. Amidst all this fevered action, only one question remains: Can you become a Peggle Master?<br><br>This Xbox 360 version of Peggle is the complete package for fans of the original game. Bonus features include online and offline multiplayer as well as downloadable content features.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Peggle Nights",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/12",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Stay up late with the next episode of PopCap's peg-busting phenomenon and meet the Peggle Masters' nighttime alter egos. Enter a dreamscape world featuring 60 new Adventure levels, 75 new challenges, and befriend a new Peggle Master. Wield 11 Magic Powers, score new style shots, and rack up tons of bonus points. Stock your Trophy Room and prove your Peggle prowess in four game modes including four-player Xbox LIVE multiplayer play. It's Extreme Fever under the silver moon... catch it in Peggle Nights today!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hGXvCmHgXCo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IzKJOpQX1po"
			},
			{
				"type":"Peggle Nights Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NAWDbKrJ3nQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/954814-peggle/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Peggle/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/peggle/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/peggle"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":217,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bright Light Productions"],
			"synopsis":"Join your host Mr. Potato Head for fun and games in Hasbro Family Game Night, a package that allows you to play classic games that you know and love, such as Connect Four, Battleship, Yahtzee, Boggle, Sorry! and Sorry! Sliders. Or get into your favorite games in a brand new way, with new games such as Connect 4 Power Chips, Boggle Portal Cubes, Reverse Yahtzee and Battleship Barrage! Quickly build a custom Party Game - just choose: favorite games, number of players and time you have to play.<br><br>Hasbro Family Game Night is an a-la-carte release -- gamers can download the main Hasbro Family Game Night application and then pick which one of the many Hasbro games they wish to download and play. The initial download is free, and users can play trial versions of the digital board games to help find the ones they want to buy.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Battleship",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/18",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This DLC pack adds Battleship to the Family Game Night client."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Yahtzee",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/18",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This DLC pack adds Yahtzee to the Family Game Night client."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Connect Four",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/18",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This DLC pack adds Connect Four to the Family Game Night client."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Scrabble",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/18",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This DLC pack adds Scrabble to the Family Game Night client."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Sorry!",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/18",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This DLC pack adds Sorry! to the Family Game Night client."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Boggle",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/18",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This DLC pack adds Boggle to the Family Game Night client."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Sorry! Sliders",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/18",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This DLC pack adds Sorry! Sliders to the Family Game Night client."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Connect 4x4",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/18",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This DLC pack adds Connect 4x4 to the Family Game Night client."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Pictureka",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/18",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This DLC pack adds Pictureka to the Family Game Night client."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Jenga",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/18",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This DLC pack adds Jenga to the Family Game Night client."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZbJnx9D-JFs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Family-Game-Night/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/family-game-night/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":218,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Carbonated Games"],
			"synopsis":"Uno Rush is a challenging and exciting party card game for up to four players. Developed by the same team that brought the original, best-selling Uno to Xbox LIVE Arcade, Uno Rush boasts a wide range of gameplay and social features - multiple variants, house-rule options, local and Xbox LIVE multiplay, camera support, avatar support, and more -- plus fast-paced gameplay to keep the party going.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lItMdcoLElE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Uno-Rush/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/uno-rush/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/uno-rush"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":219,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ska Studios"],
			"synopsis":"An independent project designed using the XNA development suite and rewarded with a publishing contract on Xbox Live Arcade Marketplace via a win at the Gamefest 2007 Dream-Build-Play contest.<br><br>The Dishwasher: Dead Samurai is a 2-D stylistic action platformer showcasing fast action, deep gameplay, and a unique visual style. An undead samurai dishwasher in a dystopian universe is on a quest for revenge against the evil cyborg army. To dispatch hordes of zombies, cyborgs, and robots, the Dishwasher has at his fingertips a devastating array of attacks using ancient blades, disturbing machinery, and screen-obliterating Dish Magic. Compete with the rest of the world in a variety of speed run and high score challenges to become the most formidable Dishwasher yet!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9dPj0mQaRqU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BBBkw0hLYnE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942778-the-dishwasher-dead-samurai/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Dishwasher/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-dishwasher-dead-samurai/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-dishwasher-dead-samurai"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":220,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Proper Games"],
			"synopsis":"Look! Up in the sky! It's a bird! It's a plane! It's a ... lovable animal-herding UFO! In Flock, players take control of an alien UFO that is tasked with herding animals to its mothership through a variety of interactive levels. Players will have to overcome the stubbornness of the temperamental beasts (this may require the use of fear, or amorous yearnings, etc.), as well as a series of environmental puzzles that must be solved using Flock's physics-based gameplay. By finding or making a passable route, players can herd the animals safely toward the ship. Solving the puzzles within the suggested time limit yields exciting rewards. But players can also take their time to find more hidden bonuses.<br><br>Flock uses a sophisticated physics engine that drives the challenging puzzle elements of the game. Whether it's using the Tractor beam to move obstacles out of the way, or the Depressor beam to stamp out crop circles to guide your herds, being an extraterrestrial has never been this addictive. Friends can also join in through co-op play. And when all the levels have been completed, users can make their own with the level editor that comes with the game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=579idPwVT74"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LburmsWBIc4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Flock/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/flock/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/flock!"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":221,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Infinite Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"In Puzzle Quest: Galactrix a horrifying scientific accident has provoked another race to attempt extermination of humankind; players will create a persistent pilot who gains skills, crafts items, maneuvers among the universe's political factions, and upgrades the ultimate space fleet as they attempt to end the genocide. An innovative hexagonal puzzle board allows for a wide range of strategic depth as it heeds to gravity according to a player's location in the game universe. A rich and detailed storyline and fresh gameplay elements make the world of Puzzle Quest: Galactrix a captivating new adventure to explore and conquer.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mKL643yIQ34"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942613-puzzle-quest-galactrix/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Puzzle-Quest-Galactrix/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/puzzle-quest-galactrix/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/puzzle-quest-galactrix"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":222,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sumo Digital"],
			"synopsis":"Test your time, speed and handling ability as you race through vibrant, colourful stages and rediscover the 15 glorious OutRun courses. From the steep streets of San Francisco to the beautiful beaches of California, it's mile after mile of unrelenting acceleration, thrills and action. Feel the kick as you put your foot to the floor in one of the 10 high-performance, fully licensed Ferrari cars as you race your way across the U.S. to a killer soundtrack. Which route will you choose on your drive for the highest possible score?<br><br>OutRun Online Arcade delivers online multiplayer racing for up to 6 players, with fast paced OutRun, Heart Attack and Time Attack modes, the draw to the open road has never been so appealing. OutRun Online Arcade on Xbox Live will feature achievements and voice; and on PlayStation Network will include trophies, voice over IP and leaderboards.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z_y_Ydrso_M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Szjy4JLg0vs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/OutRun-Online-Arcade/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/outrun-online-arcade/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/outrun-online-arcade"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":223,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Southend Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"It's an all-new Lode Runner gold mine -- 3-D graphics, frenzied 2-D action, lodes of modes, 220 levels, multiplayer options, puzzles, a level editor and more! Run, climb, blast blocks, outsmart enemies and grab the gold on your own or with a partner. It's classic action with \"lodes\" of new twists.<br><br>Battle up to three friends on Xbox Live in a frantic game of tag, where the first to die is the first to avenge ... as an enemy. Survive endlessly spawning foes to earn medals. Create devious levels to challenge the Community. For long-time fans or first-time runners, this is the mother lode.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Skill Expansion Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/08",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Play and post scores on 8 new Hang On levels, and solve a slew of new master puzzles! Professional Lode Runners needed! The Skill Expansion Pack for Lode Runner adds 1 new achievement."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Journey Expansion Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/13",
				"achievements":35,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The Journey Expansion for Lode Runner adds 8 single player stages and 8 co-op stages! Both new adventures progress through simple to challenging levels and award an achievement upon completion."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dngd53hktjI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944469-lode-runner/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lode-Runner/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lode-runner/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lode-runner"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":224,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["4JStudios", "Rare"],
			"synopsis":"Colossal, immense, and gigantic; beautiful, gorgeous, and grandiose -- these are the words one thinks of when describing Rare's 2000 follow-up adventure to Banjo-Kazooie. Keeping consistent with the attitude found in this title, Rare has wittily named it Banjo-Tooie. Explore eight giant worlds, solve puzzles and help game characters to unearth jiggys, play as Mumbo, a T-Rex, Submarine, Money-Van, Washing Machine, and more, and learn more than 40 new moves on the way.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WDA72kdmRjw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TZat7uX5GQA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/954756-banjo-tooie/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Banjo-Tooie/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/banjo-tooie/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/banjo-tooie"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Banjo-Kazooie Wiki",
				"url":"http://banjokazooie.wikia.com/wiki/Banjo-Tooie"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":225,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SEGA"],
			"synopsis":"A remake of the Dreamcast entry in Virtual-On, the renown mech combat game. Oratorio Tangram is an update to the original Virtual-On and features two new mechs and revised play mechanics. Although the arcade version saw limited distribution in the U.S., it was an instant classic on both sides of the Pacific.<br><br>Virtual-On Oratorio Tangram isn't the typical fighting game by any stretch of the imagination. You pilot a giant Gundam-like machine in a 3-D arena armed with three different weapons which can have altering effects depending on the situation their employed and the movement of your mecha.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=34cht0xbJGc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=20B2puOSqzs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ku_KfhJpiSs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats (Arcade)",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/arcade/564860-cyber-troopers-virtual-on-oratorio-tangram"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cyber-Troopers-VirtualOn-OT/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cyber-Troopers-VirtualOn-OT/walkthrough.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/virtual-on-oratorio-tangram-ver566"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":226,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Taito"],
			"synopsis":"First appearing in the 1980's as a new style block-breaking game, Arkanoid appears on Xbox Live Arcade having accomplished even further evolution. Enjoy Arkanoid in high-definition with beautifully choreographed background movies and background music. Loaded with 120 stages in all and colorful cooperative and versus modes. As part of \"TAITO's Collection Series\", in which Taito's masterpiece games are remade, Arkanoid is remade with even cooler background movies and sound and loaded with colorful game modes. Within the simplistic block-breaking game element, and beyond effects incurred by items and the appearance of enemies, several kinds of new bosses appear in the final stage.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Episode Add-on Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/17",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Arkanoid Live! Episode Add-on Pack 1"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Episode Add-on Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/17",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Arkanoid Live! Episode Add-on Pack 2"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3p1585Mqs7g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Arkanoid-Live/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/arkanoid-live/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/arkanoid-live!"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":227,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Backbone Entertainment", "Taito"],
			"synopsis":"As part of the series' 30th anniversary celebration, Taito has reinvented the classic in many ways while keeping the old-school charm of the game we all know. New design features maximize performance and play on the console. For the first time, experience Space Invaders in fully immersive sound and vivid high-definition on the next-gen system, with visuals that will excite your senses!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Expansion Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/17",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"You'll be able to enjoy the original Space Invaders and the now legendary Part II with this action-packed purchasable content!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jd5aOyxOtbU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=34q-Qzk8mjc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Space-Invaders-Extreme/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/space-invaders-extreme/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/space-invaders-extreme"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Space Invaders Wiki",
				"url":"http://spaceinvaders.wikia.com/wiki/Space_Invaders_Extreme"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":228,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Frozen Codebase"],
			"synopsis":"Be very, very quiet... we're wrangling Zombies!! Save the city of Potters Field from an infestation of zany zombies in the quirky and comical Zombie Wranglers! Armed with a trustworthy Wrangler-Pack and your own unique special abilities, play as one of the four gallant apprentice Wranglers and rescue your neighborhood before it's too late!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zfvs8GNDg_4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LXTpYQcr8UA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Zombie-Wranglers/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/zombie-wranglers/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/zombie-wranglers"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":229,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Naked Sky Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Star Trek: D.A.C. is a top-down space shooter be based on the 2009 J.J. Abrams movie reboot of the Star Trek franchise.<br><br>Star Trek: D-A-C allows fans to directly control a variety of ships and pitch battles between Starfleet and the Romulan Empire. Up to 12 players can compete in thrilling team combat. There are three game play modes - single player, online multiplayer and online co-op. For each mode, there are three different game types - Team DeathMatch, Assault and Conquest. Players can choose from three ship types for each faction, including the new U.S.S. Enterprise featured in the \"Star Trek\" film. Each ship - the powerful Flagship, the nimble Fighter and the devastating Bomber - offers its own unique capabilities for players to master and manipulate as they fight for victory. In addition to featuring the new U.S.S. Enterprise, Star Trek: D-A-C incorporates music and signature sounds taken directly from the new \"Star Trek\" film.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Deluxe Edition",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/03",
				"achievements":35,
				"type":8
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TyeOROXulmk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NjRdkB1WczA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Star-Trek-DAC/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/star-trek-d-a-c/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/star-trek-d-a-c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Memory Alpha",
				"url":"http://en.memory-alpha.org/wiki/Star_Trek_D-A-C"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Memory Beta",
				"url":"http://memory-beta.wikia.com/wiki/D-A-C"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":230,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Wideload Games"],
			"synopsis":"Texas Cheat 'Em is a new take on the classic Texas Hold 'Em rules, turning an average online poker table upside down by layering party games and other gambling minigames on top of the basic rules, and allowing players to cheat to win! Gamers of all levels can hoodwink their opponents in Texas Cheat 'Em; novice competitors who craft good cheating strategies by using x-ray vision, pre-cognition, chip stealing, card swapping and more can defeat more veteran card players.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WrmzWdS0w-I"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/955743-texas-cheat-em/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Texas-Cheatem/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/texas-cheat-em/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/texas-cheat-em"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":231,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Vector2"],
			"synopsis":"An independent project designed using the XNA development suite and rewarded with a publishing contract on Xbox Live Arcade Marketplace via a win at the Gamefest 2007 Dream-Build-Play contest.<br><br>Compete in the sport of robot badminton in Blazing Birds. Challenge sixty computer controlled opponents over three levels of difficulty. Invite your friends to play multiplayer matches or round robin tournaments with up to twenty players. The unique control scheme allows for blazing fast action and quick responsiveness. Score points using smash, drop, and clear shots with either manual or automatic aiming. Unleash seven deadly power shots including Meteor Strike, Firecracker, Hyperspace, Lightning Bolt, Dragon Flight, Hunting Season, and Wormhole. Only the best will face Signum IV.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s8U-r152W8w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Blazing-Birds/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/blazing-birds/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/blazing-birds"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":232,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gastronaut Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Gel is a puzzle game in which players use a small character to move colored blocks and arrange them into formations. Players can also customize their characters with a variety of zany costumes.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PJbMmPjUXZ8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Gel-Set-and-Match/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/gel/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/gel-set-match"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":233,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Telltale Games"],
			"synopsis":"Join Wallace and his dog Gromit in a series episodes of of grand adventures create by Telltale Games, the minds behind the Sam & Max game series and Strong Bad's Cool Game for Attractive People.<br><br>The inventor and his loyal pooch are faced with a big problem. They need 50 gallons of honey by tonight - far more than their bees can handle! When Wallace's plans to step up production go horribly awry, it falls to Gromit to fight off the angry swarm. Featuring a brand new story with the same slapstick humour, cinematic visuals, and charm fans of the Wallace & Gromit films have come to love, Fright of the Bumblebees kicks off this four-episode series in cracking style!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ACo09CSIeUI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gJcDa5TgZRM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=joWaSdXVfMQ&list=PL5B46E645EBDD4D68&index=1"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/pc/951720-wallace-and-gromits-grand-adventures-episode-1/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wallace-and-Gromit-Fright-of-the-Bees/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wallace-and-gromit-episode-1/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wallace-gromits-grand-adventures-episode-1-fright-of-the-bumblebees"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wallace and Gromit Wiki",
				"url":"http://wallaceandgromit.wikia.com/wiki/Wallace_%26_Gromit%27s_Grand_Adventures"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":234,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Square Enix"],
			"synopsis":"Yosumin Live is a puzzle game by Square Enix that involves finding 4 pieces that can be made into a perfect rectangle or square. The game is a deceptively simple yet fiendish challenge, and it's not just about solo play -- there are online battle modes to enjoy as well!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Yosumin Adventure",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/24",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"A puzzle adventure where you must travel the world to recover the pieces of a beautiful stained-glass window. Play your way through stage after stage, using the Treats given to you by the Grand Goldmin to help you on your way!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V174KTZ1_WI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MA3jf-fQLvY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Yosumin-LIVE/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/yosumin-live/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/yosumin!-live"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":235,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Immersion Games", "Timeline Computer Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"CellFactor: Psychokinetic Wars is a fast-paced first-person multiplayer shooter that puts players in the center of the battle of technology vs. humanity. Complete with next-gen graphics and robust gameplay, CellFactor: Psychokinetic Wars allows players to wage war by using their choice of gunfire and/or telekinetic superpowers. Players can use telekinetic energy to rip objects from the surrounding environment and hurl them at enemies or draw on their powers to create a bullet-proof energy shield that protects against gunfire. Flying, teleporting and accelerated speed abilities give players countless ways to fight the good fight with plenty of intense combat action.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GOBk8hyLohE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cQWbSpOHK5s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/CellFactor-Psychokinetic-Wars/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cellfactor-psychokinetic-wars/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cellfactor-psychokinetic-wars"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":236,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Nerve Software", "Id Software"],
			"synopsis":"Deep in World War II, you are B.J. Blazkowicz, the Allies' bad boy of espionage, a terminal action seeker built for abuse with an attitude to match who has been captured by Nazis, tortured, and imprisoned beneath the floors of Castle Wolfenstein where you await an inhumane execution. Now, you must do anything and everything to escape from the belly of the Nazi dungeon... or die trying.<br><br>The famed title that created an entire video game genre, Wolfenstein 3D offers players a chance to experience the intensity of escaping from Castle Wolfenstein all over again. Classic enemies like Hans Grosse and Mecha-Hitler await players in the six episodes that span 60 levels. Gamers taking the challenge to defeat the twisted Nazi regime also will earn accolades and be awarded gold for customizable weapon upgrades in id Software's all new, Wolfenstein.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zghBNK52toE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Speedrun (Original Game - 0:27:14)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MbnpEJ11ANk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960483-wolfenstein-3d/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wolfenstein-3D/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wolfenstein-3d/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wolfenstein-3d"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wolfenstein Wiki",
				"url":"http://wolfenstein.wikia.com/wiki/Wolfenstein_3D"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":237,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Backbone Entertainment", "SEGA"],
			"synopsis":"When Zeus, the legendary Greek God, brings you back to life, set forth on a mission to rescue Zeus' daughter Athena from the underworld in Altered Beast. Along the way, collect the Spirit Balls dropped by enemies to increase your strength and transform into a variety of mythical creatures with powerful attacks.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LxXMpHn4mN8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960799-altered-beast/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Altered-Beast/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/altered-beast/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/altered-beast"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Altered Beast Wiki",
				"url":"http://alteredbeast.wikia.com/wiki/Altered_Beast_(Sega_Genesis)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":238,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Backbone Entertainment", "SEGA"],
			"synopsis":"A downloadable version of the 1995 Genesis/MegaDrive game.<br><br>Sketch Turner is an artist in New York City. One day while Sketch is drawing, there is a huge thunderstorm and a bolt of lightning hits Sketch's image, bringing it to life. That image is Mortus, a megalomaniac mutant who wants to become real and rule the earth. Mortus magically transports Sketch into the pages of his comic book so that he can end his creator's life and become real. Inside the comic book, Sketch meets General Alissa Cyan, who believes he is a superhero that came to save their post-apocalyptic world from the evil brought by Mortus' hand. Now Sketch must save the comic book world and get back to his own...",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b7NbAEx0_tQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960800-comix-zone/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Comix-Zone/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/comix-zone/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/comix-zone"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":239,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Treasure"],
			"synopsis":"A downloadable version of the classic 1997 Genesis/Mega Drive game.<br><br>The Gunstar 9 planet was peaceful for many years until the vicious dictator, Colonel Red, kidnapped the Gunstar twins' older brother and used mind control to make him his slave. You'll face many different enemies and bosses as you battle to stop the dictator from unleashing \"Golden Silver the Destructor\" with apocalyptic consequences.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KAIbS4RszaE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960485-gunstar-heroes/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Gunstar-Heroes/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/gunstar-heroes/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/gunstar-heroes"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":240,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SEGA"],
			"synopsis":"A downloadable version of the classic 1989 Genesis RPG.<br><br>In the vastness of space, the Algo Star System floats like a dust fleck in a sunbeam. Cruise closer. See its three twinkling planets? The middle one gleams like an emerald. This is Mota, a beautiful, beckoning jewel... gripped by madness.<br><br>Tour scenic Mota - and experience weird research labs, creepy dungeons, catastrophic floods and exploding planets! Thrill to Mother Brain blowing her circuits! Chill to Climatrol in chaos! Sweat when the killer lurks in the tunnel!<br><br>Travel light -- in Knife Boots and a Carbonsuit - as you stalk boldly into the unguarded wilds armed with magic. As you planet-trot with your friends - Hugh the Biologist, Shir the Thief and Kain the Wrecker - you must solve a twisted riddle. And be ready to die!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZWujBvyG4Oc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960801-phantasy-star-ii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Phantasy-Star-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/phantasy-star-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/phantasy-star-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Phantasy Star Wiki",
				"url":"http://phantasystar.wikia.com/wiki/Phantasy_Star_II"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":241,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Backbone Entertainment", "SEGA"],
			"synopsis":"As the ninja Shinobi (Joe Musashi) you must stop the criminal organization known as Zeed, who have kidnapped the children of the Oboro clan. Test your ninja skills through five missions of increasing difficulty, and make your way to Zeed's headquarters to free all the hostages. The Ring of Five, the leaders of Zeed, are determined to stop you as you face off against one of them at the end of each stage.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VHZDxjMdduY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960797-shinobi/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Shinobi/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/shinobi/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/shinobi"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":242,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Backbone Entertainment", "Sonic Team"],
			"synopsis":"A downloadable version of the 1994 Genesis/Mega Drive game.<br><br>Sonic and Tails are back for another adventure as they again battle the evil Dr. Eggman (AKA Dr. Robotnik), who is desperately trying to collect all the Chaos Emeralds in order to rebuild his Death Egg. Our heroes must find the Chaos Emeralds before Dr. Eggman does, but winning the race won't be easy -- a new adversary, Knuckles the Echidna, has arrived on the scene and will do whatever he can to keep Sonic and Tails from reaching their goal. Grab all the golden rings, find various bonus zones, and overcome Knuckles and Dr. Eggman as you rocket through the third chapter in Sonic's adventures.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=njQQuiy7yw0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960798-sonic-the-hedgehog-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sonic-The-Hedgehog-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sonic-the-hedgehog-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sonic-the-hedgehog-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sonic Wiki",
				"url":"http://sonic.wikia.com/wiki/Sonic_the_Hedgehog_3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":243,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Stainless Games"],
			"synopsis":"Duels of the Planeswalkers takes players on a journey through a Multiverse in which they take on the roles of Planeswalkers, powerful wizards who battle others for glory, knowledge and conquest. Throughout their journey, Planeswalkers battle with, or against each other in lush interactive 3D environments. Similar to the Magic: The Gathering trading card game, Planeswalkers are equipped with an arsenal of spells and creatures that if used wisely will help advance the Planeswalker through the game.<br><br>Extending the game experience beyond the confines of the traditional card game, players can opt to battle real life opponents online. Also available are a variety of strategic single-player game scenarios.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Player Personas",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Give yourself a new look! Choose from 10 new personas for Magic: The Gathering - Duels of the Planeswalkers. Show a new side of yourself in local matches and on Xbox LIVE."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Game Tables",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Throw down in style! Add 3 new playfields to your Magic: The Gathering - Duels of the Planeswalkers matches. This in-game content pack includes the perfect playing surfaces for blue, red, and green decks."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Backgrounds",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/11",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Need a change of scenery? Add 3 new backgrounds to your Magic: The Gathering - Duels of the Planeswalkers menus. This in-game content pack includes an ethereal blue, a macabre black, a blazing red, and a savage green setting."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Expansion Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2009/10/21",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The legendary dragon Planeswalker Nicol Bolas has come out of hiding and now he's more powerful than ever! This expansion pack features new cards and new decks to add to your arsenal. Now you can wield the power of Tezzeret's \"Relics of Doom\" deck, unlock three new cards for each of the eight original decks, or defeat the new single-player campaign to unlock Jace Beleren's \"Mind of the Void\" and Sarkhan Vol's \"Cries\" of \"Rage\" decks. This expansion pack also contains four new Two-Headed Giant co-op levels as well as three new puzzling challenge levels to test your Magic skills."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Expansion Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2010/05/12",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The vampire Planeswalker Sorin Markov has walked the Multiverse for thousands of years. His thirst is eternal, and bloodless victims litter his wake. Expansion Pack 2 features new cards and new decks from the latest Magic: The Gathering trading card game sets. Wield Nicol Bolas's \"Eons of Evil\" deck, unlock three new cards for each deck you already own, and defeat eight new campaign levels to unlock Rhys's \"Heart of Worlds\" and Chandra Nalaar's \"Heat of Battle\" decks. This expansion pack also contains four new Two-Headed Giant co-op levels as well as five new puzzling challenge levels to test your Magic skills."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Expansion Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/03",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The ancient evil dragon Planeswalker Nicol Bolas commanded Sarkhan Vol to guard Zendikar's mysterious Eye of Ugin. In the Eye's chamber, the dragon-worshipping shaman slowly spiraled into madness. Expansion Pack 3 features new cards and new decks from the latest Magic: The Gathering trading card game sets. Wield Sorin Markov's \"Master of Shadows\" deck, unlock three new cards for each deck you already own, and defeat eight new campaign levels to unlock Gideon Jura's \"Rally of Righteousness\" and Niv-Mizzet's \"Root of the Firemind\" decks. This expansion pack also contains four new Two-Headed Giant co-op levels as well as five new puzzling challenge levels."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XgV6f3B0rRw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/956484-magic-the-gathering-duels-of-the-planeswalkers/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Magic-The-Gathering-Duels-of-the-Planeswalkers/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/magic-the-gathering-duels-of-the-planeswalkers/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/magic-the-gathering---duels-of-the-planeswalkers"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"MTG Salvation",
				"url":"http://mtgsalvation.gamepedia.com/Duels_of_the_Planeswalkers_(2009)"
			},
			{
				"type":"Magic The Gathering Wiki",
				"site":"Magic Wiki",
				"url":"http://mtg.wikia.com/wiki/Magic:_The_Gathering_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":244,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Codeglue"],
			"synopsis":"Rocket Riot is an action-packed side-view shooter featuring a bazooka-wielding jetpack soldier. With a highly stylized 8-bit era feel, players blast their way through the environment against enemies or multiplayer foes online. Navigating through a completely destructible environment, players can uncover special power ups or even burrow into different areas of the map.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3f_Q-yQX1xI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k9lrt62tTTY&index=7&list=PLECF09607A4040D4B"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rocket-Riot/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rocket-riot/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rocket-riot"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":245,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Telltale Games"],
			"synopsis":"Sam & Max are finally back with their hilarious and critically-acclaimed first season of the Sam & Max adventures -- and now, all six episodes of the first season are here on Xbox Live. Experience why the game's bizarre humor, crazy characters, vivid 3D graphics, and exciting gameplay make Sam & Max: Season One the funniest game in years!<br><br>It's a vile world out there. Get too complacent and all sorts of weirdos start coming out of the woodwork. Good thing Sam & Max are here to hose down the sleaze and keep some kind of peace. Violently, if possible. Who are these irreverent crime fighters? Sam's a six-foot tall canine shamus with a love of justice. Max is a hyperkinetic rabbity-thing with a taste for mayhem. Together, they're a team of freelance police officers, on a mission to take down a bizarre mind-control conspiracy. And they're bringing you along for the fun.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YQFlFF-FuR8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960924-sam-and-max-save-the-world/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sam-and-Max-Save-the-World/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sam-and-max-save-the-world/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sam-max-save-the-world"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sam & Max Wiki",
				"url":"http://samandmax.wikia.com/wiki/Sam_%26_Max_Season_One"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":246,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Arcade"],
			"synopsis":"Can a game be too addictive? Find out with Droplitz, an engaging and intuitive game that will captivate players for hours at a time. Rotate the dials to create paths for the Droplitz to reach the collectors. Making multiple paths simultaneously earns score combos and generates even more Droplitz! As the speed of the game increases, settle into the zone and enjoy the sights and sounds of this atmospheric and challengingly addictive game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ViJ_ukl_X6c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NazO7L89CKw&list=PL600446DA217233B2&index=2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Droplitz/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/droplitz/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/droplitz"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":247,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SNK"],
			"synopsis":"It's been 10 years since the death of Geese Howard. However, Howard's skills have been passed to his son, Rock. The new hero is joined by cast of 12 new characters plus one returning fighter, Terry Bogard for this tournament of champions.<br><br>Representing the world's best, the maulers gather once again to crown the \"King of Fighters\". Fatal Fury: Mark of the Wolves improves on the Fatal Fury system by adding three new battle formats, creating fights more furious than before.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=de7PinSqZKc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/961060-garou-mark-of-the-wolves/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Garou-Mark-of-the-Wolves/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/garou-mow/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/garou-mark-of-the-wolves"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Fatal Fury Wiki",
				"url":"http://fatalfury.wikia.com/wiki/Fatal_Fury_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":248,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SNK Playmore"],
			"synopsis":"The King of Fighters '98 Ultimate Match comes to Xbox Live Arcade! The KOF '98 fighting game has fascinated game fans all over the world, and now it's powered up and ready to be on Xbox LIVE Arcade. Additional characters have been added from the King of Fighters universe, and new battle systems and moves have been implemented. Extend the fight to opponents all over the world. Face off against others to prove who is the real King of Fighters. Use Practice Mode to learn, Challenge Mode to improve your skills, then go to battle to show what you've got!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N9M8tFNVq4Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats (Arcade)",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/arcade/944206-the-king-of-fighters-98-ultimate-match/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/KOF-98-UM/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/king-of-fighters-98-ultimate-match/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-king-of-fighters-98-ultimate-match"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Shoryuken",
				"url":"http://wiki.shoryuken.com/The_King_of_Fighters_'98:_Ultimate_Match"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"SNK Wiki",
				"url":"http://snk.wikia.com/wiki/The_King_of_Fighters_'98"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":249,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Team17 Software"],
			"synopsis":"The turn-based mayhem and destruction continues! Worms 2: Armageddon is the most fully-featured digital version of the game yet. This game is exploding with features -- four player online and offline multiplayer, voice support, a raft of new weapons (including the return of some iconic weapons from the brand's past), all new high-definition landscape themes, new play modes, hats, skins, speech-banks, loads of other customization and to top it all off, a highly-involving single player experience with tutorials, deathmatches, races, fort games and puzzles!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Battle Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/07",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Incoming! Say hello to the Worms 2 Armageddon Battle Pack. This downloadable content package greatly adds to Worms 2 Armageddon with the addition of 6 new weapons, 30 new single-player missions, an all-new game mode called Body Count, 10 all-new Forts, new speechbanks, Player Titles, leaderboards and much, much more. It's a package high on content & explosive goodness, a must for all Worms fans out there."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/24",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The Worms 2: Armageddon \"Puzzle Pack\" features 20 mind-boggling single-player puzzle missions, designed to test even the most cunning Worms players. The \"Puzzle Pack\" also includes 3 new hats, 3 new speech banks, 3 new gravestones, a new \"puzzle\" landscape theme and 5 new Achievements."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Forts Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/31",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The Worms 2: Armageddon \"Forts Pack\" features 20 addictive and challenging single-player levels, based upon a variety of fort-based mission objectives. The \"Forts Pack\" also includes 10 brand new forts for multi-player battles, 3 new hats, 3 new speech banks, 3 new gravestones, and a new \"Fort\" landscape theme."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Time Attack Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/07",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The Worms 2: Armageddon \"Time Attack\" pack features 20 new heart-pounding single-player race missions designed to test players' Rope and Jet Pack skills to the limit! The \"Time Attack\" pack also includes 3 new hats, 3 new speech banks, 3 new gravestones and a new \"Time Attack\" landscape theme."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Mayhem Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/14",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Worms 2: Armageddon \"Mayhem Pack\" is a free downloadable content pack released to celebrate the launch of Worms: Ultimate Mayhem. The \"Mayhem Pack\" features 3 new landscape themes, 3 new hats, 3 new speech banks and 3 new gravestones, all based upon some of the great content from Worms: Ultimate Mayhem."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Retro Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/21",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The Worms 2: Armageddon \"Retro Pack\" features 20 single-player missions that have been hand-picked from the classic Worms: Armageddon game and re-worked exclusively for this downloadable content pack. The \"Retro Pack\" also includes 3 new hats, 3 new gravestones, a new landscape theme and 5 new Achievements."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z5VFA7ErgKU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Worms-2-Armageddon/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/worms-2-armageddon/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/worms-2-armageddon"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Worms Wiki",
				"url":"http://worms.wikia.com/wiki/Worms_2:_Armageddon"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":250,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["DICE"],
			"synopsis":"Using the acclaimed Frostbite engine, Battlefield 1943 takes players back to WWII to re-experience some of the legendary battles that kicked off the Battlefield franchise. The game offers endless hours of 24 player multiplayer action over three classic and tropic locations; Wake Island, Guadalcanal and Iwo Jima. Delivering the award-winning through-the-gun and vehicle warfare online experience DICE is best recognized for, Battlefield 1943 will have players battling in ruthless aerial dog fights and intense trench combat.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jcoLS1dM7E0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer Wake Island",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bym2UkfjMkQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer Guadalcanal",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t2ftVwZOYsI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer Iwo Jima",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gwlGZ2ZhgPM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer Coral Sea",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6TgsCgWsHW0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PoXyKoBttmA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/957940-battlefield-1943/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Battlefield-1943/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/battlefield-1943/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/battlefield-1943"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Battlefield Wiki",
				"url":"http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Battlefield_1943"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":251,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Play Brains"],
			"synopsis":"Madballs: Babo Invasion is a fast-paced multiplayer game where armed ball-like \"Babos\" navigate maze-like worlds in a free-for-all firefight or team-based combat. The game offers an arcade-style single-player mode and the optional depth of multiplayer team and class-based gameplay. It also features top-down and chase cam views, new weapons, and lush 3-D environments. Multi-player Competitive Mapping, a first-of-its-kind game feature, supports the Invasion game mode, adding a major strategic and competitive element to gameplay.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Obsidian Magmor",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Jazz up your line-ups with cool new character skins. This pack includes one skin: Obsidian Magmor Skin."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Versus Weapons",
				"releaseDate":"2009/10/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Expand your arsonel with the latest in Babo and Scorched technology! New versus mode weapons - Slicer and Striker. "
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Yvf_Ut0NEU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jnk9iyZEuXQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Madballs-Babo-Invasion/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/madballs-in-babo-invasion/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/madballs-in-babo-invasion"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":252,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["LucasArts"],
			"synopsis":"The Secret of Monkey Island: Special Edition is a completely re-imagined version of the first game in the series that adds updated high definition graphics, a re-mastered musical score, and full voiceover.<br><br>Welcome to the Port of Melee, Mr. Guybrush Threepwood. So ya think you've got what it takes to be a swashbucklin', bloodthirsty pirate, do ya? Ya think a young swabby like yourself's gonna be the first to tame mysterious Monkey Island? Well, laddy, there's more to bein' a buckaneer than just swingin' a sword and swillin' gallons of Grog. First ya got to pass the seadog test. Good luck to ya, mate... yar gonna need it.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SZHBGVblNJA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yd5scM3dzog"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960369-the-secret-of-monkey-island-special-edition/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Monkey-Island/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-secret-of-monkey-island-special-edition/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-secret-of-monkey-island-special-edition"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Monkey Island Wiki",
				"url":"http://www.miwiki.net/The_Secret_of_Monkey_Island"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":253,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cyanide"],
			"synopsis":"Pro Cycling Manager: Tour de France 2009 is a balanced mix of both management and sport simulation. Choose one of the 18 official teams and lead it through 2009 edition's 21 official legs by interacting directly on you riders. Early breakaways, fights for jerseys, sprints are some of the possible behaviors that are particularly specific to the sport. Race up to 4 players, wheel to wheel, on Live Arcade to lead your team to the highest step on the podium.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rgiwCJmQa14"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tour-de-France-2009/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tour-de-france-2009/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/pro-cycling-manager-season-2009-le-tour-de-france"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":254,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Twisted Pixel"],
			"synopsis":"Born of plasma and flame in an underground military lab, 'Splosion Man can 'splode at will, propelling himself around a side-scrolling world and destroying everything in his way.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Prologue to Ms. Splosion Man",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/28",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"This new level is available FREE as a Prologue to Ms. Splosion Man. See what happens to Splosion Man after he emerges victorious from his original adventure. See how Ms. Splosion Man is created and what she must do in order to save her beloved from the clutches of those evil scientists at Big Science Labs!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qq52w4AijkU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ennmNmg5lbM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/959210-splosion-man/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Splosion-Man/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/splosion-man/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/splosion-man"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":255,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Backbone Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"A downloadable edition or the classic fighter, Marvel VS Capcom 2 pits some of Capcom's familiar faces against a host of Marvel Comic's biggest names in explosive three-on-three team battles. The game features the biggest roster of challengers to ever square off in a Capcom fighting game, a total of 56 combined brawlers from both the Capcom and Marvel universes. Players can mix and match from both worlds in order to create their own ideal three man/woman/robot/monster team-up.<br><br>Offering both offline and online battles, Marvel vs. Capcom 2 is designed to be a gateway for new players to experience the fun of fighting games while providing a deep system for hardcore fighting fans to dig into. Action is based around colorful, exaggerated attacks that include gigantic projectile attacks and high-flying aerial moves.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlnfIy_3zNg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/959864-marvel-vs-capcom-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Marvel-vs-Capcom-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/marvel-vs-capcom-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/marvel-vs-capcom-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Marvel vs Capcom Wiki",
				"url":"http://marvelvscapcom.wikia.com/wiki/Marvel_vs._Capcom_2:_New_Age_of_Heroes"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":256,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Singapore"],
			"synopsis":"One of the best games in the TMNT franchise returns with this downloadable 3D remake.<br><br>The Turtles have come up against some tough stuff in the past, but there's no comparison to what they're about to encounter. While sitting around the sewer watching television, Raphael, Donatello, and the crew witness a giant android ripping the Statue of Liberty from the ground, terrifying hundreds of tourists. Use pizza power-ups and huge body slams to make your way backwards and forwards through history in an attempt to restore peace to the Big Apple.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uTVkeX7-K68"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5XIdm22lPUc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960528-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-turtles-in-time-re/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Turtles-In-Time-RS/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tmnt-turtles-in-time-reshelled/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-turtles-in-time-re-shelled"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Turtlepedia",
				"url":"http://turtlepedia.wikia.com/wiki/Teenage_Mutant_Ninja_Turtles:_Turtles_in_Time"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":257,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["RedLynx"],
			"synopsis":"Put on your helmet, and rev your way through Trials HD, a fully-featured, physics-based motorcycle racing game in stunning HD graphics. Tear up more than 50 tracks and test your metal in two unique game modes: Race and Skill. Create, share and download an unlimited number of free tracks with the level editor, and customize your rider to fit your personality.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Big Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/21",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"This Big Pack introduces 35 completely new tracks: 23 racing tracks and 12 skill game tracks. Five new tournaments include all the new tracks. For level designers the Big Pack provides more than 50 new crazy physics objects: car, rocket turbine, gravity field, wind, motor and many others! Three new fun achievements to unlock worth 50 extra gamerscore. Fasten your helmet and prepare for serious bruises!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Big Thrills",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/01",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Thrill for more Trials HD! This second DLC for the award-winning Xbox LIVE Arcade game includes 40 all new tracks, including the 10 best user-created tracks from the Big Thrills contest. There are also 3 new achievements you can unlock for 50 more Gamerscore. With more than one million copies sold, it's time to try Trials and see why this was voted the number one Xbox LIVE Arcade game by Xbox 360 fans just like you!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8EGkbQN8FQw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JTX1VCPG5S0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7QAJumpwjpE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Trials-HD/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/trials-hd/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/trials-hd"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Trials HD Secrets Wiki",
				"url":"http://trialshdsecrets.wikia.com/wiki/Trials_HD_Secrets_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":258,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Chair Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Shadow Complex is set in the compelling universe of Empire, Orson Scott Card's best-selling novel outside of the famed Ender's Game series. The game provides a fresh twist on classic side-scroller action by delivering an original single-player adventure that unfolds across a range of non-linear levels. Gameplay centers around exploration and fast-paced combat as players gather power-ups to overcome obstacles, thwart enemies, and delve into a mysterious and challenging world.<br><br>Shadow Complex propels lost hiker Jason Fleming into the hollows of government conspiracy, dark politics and military upheaval. When Jason and his girlfriend, Claire, accidentally stumble upon a rogue paramilitary group called the Restoration, it soon becomes clear that the faction's intent is to set in motion a chain of events that will cause America to collapse into a civil war. Assumed to be a government agent, the Restoration captures Claire, and while this initially fuels Jason's motivation to find justice, he soon discovers the magnitude of what the sinister offshoot has planned. Along the way, Jason acquires many high-tech \"toys\" the Restoration is developing, and eventually becomes a super-powered engine of destruction.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WhJsQTw0cOk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nJNbf0E1oKo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3CLvC5z5Ns4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960508-shadow-complex/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Shadow-Complex/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/shadow-complex/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/shadow-complex"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":259,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Arcade"],
			"synopsis":"Han Tao, General of a Thousand Victories, has pledged his life to protect the legendary Star of Destiny, a mysterious artifact recently stolen by the Evil Overlord. Han Tao will face a cavalcade of enemies, ranging from standard grunts to undead horrors in his quest to recover the sacred Star. Luckily he is well versed in intense combos, slick counter-moves, the art of deadly weapons, and mystical Zen attacks.<br><br>A hand-to-hand action game, Invincible Tiger: The Legend of Han Tao allows players to pick up weapons, acquire different combos and learn various finishing moves. The game also features co-op multiplayer modes so players can enjoy the game at home with a friend or online with people around the world.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cvVFhmYwxNo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZL4RPpc9N0I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Invincible-Tiger/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/invincible-tiger-the-legend-of-hand-tao/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/invincible-tiger-the-legend-of-han-tao"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":260,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"NBA 2K10: Draft Combine is a download-only title that provides pre-season fun for basketball fans leading up to the fall launch of NBA 2K10. The game allows fans to create their own custom player with the utmost detail and, for the first time in the NBA 2K series, begin their career by experiencing the on-court life of an NBA hopeful going through the NBA Draft Combine at the world-renowned, ATTACK Athletics gym in Chicago.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i0I4odYB1Z8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mWoX5oe--Yg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-2K10-Draft-Combine/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-2k10-draft-combine/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-2k10-draft-combine"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":261,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Deadline Games"],
			"synopsis":"Rorschach and Nite Owl team up to solve the case of the missing Violet Greene in Watchmen: The End Is Nigh Part 2.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ibKcjAIQ_s8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ujMYof5HxgU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Watchmen-Part-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/watchmen-the-end-is-nigh-part-2/overview/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/watchmen-the-end-is-nigh-part-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Watchmen Wiki",
				"url":"http://watchmen.wikia.com/wiki/Watchmen:_The_End_Is_Nigh"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":262,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Hidden Path Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Defense Grid: The Awakening is designed to be the definitive tower defense game experience designed specifically for Xbox LIVE Arcade. The role-playing game lets let up to four players hack, slash and smash their way together through a hand-drawn landscape.<br><br>Defense Grid: The Awakening has 20 unique environments, each with a different placement of roads, tower build locations, and open areas to plan a strategy around. Each level encourages a different strategy, such as trying to find an optimal path to redirect enemies, making the best use of limited space, and breaking up individual enemy waves to avoid being overwhelmed, all while planning ahead for future waves.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Map Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/02",
				"achievements":10,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Map Pack 1 contains two new maps: Service Interruption and Height of Confusion. Includes one new achievement."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Map Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/09",
				"achievements":10,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Map Pack 2 contains two new maps: Risk Exposure and Roundabout. Includes one new achievement."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Map Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/16",
				"achievements":10,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Map Pack 3 contains two new maps: Urban Planning and Tactical Diversion.  Includes one new achievement."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Map Pack 4",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/23",
				"achievements":20,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Map Pack 4 contains two new maps: Kill Zone and Overflow. Includes two new achievements."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"You Monster",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/07",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Portal's GLaDOS invades the world of Defense Grid in this first full-story expansion to the award winning game. Eight new maps break all the rules, and 35 additional challenge missions provide 15+ hours of new gameplay. Purchase this new chapter in the story of Defense Grid now!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sSq83CAieLo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NTumcXp8MBA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945048-defense-grid-the-awakening/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Defense-Grid/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/defense-grid-the-awakening/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/defense-grid-the-awakening"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":263,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Canalside Studios"],
			"synopsis":"An independent project designed using the XNA development suite and rewarded with a publishing contract on Xbox Live Arcade Marketplace via a win at the Gamefest 2007 Dream-Build-Play contest.<br><br>In Yo-Ho-Kablammo you must navigate your ship around the sea priming mines, collecting power-ups and treasure in order to defeat your opponents. You can always use your cannons to blast them straight to the depths! If fast frantic fun is what you're looking for then this game is for you. This is a small taste of Yo-Ho-Kablammo; buy the full version for many more features including Maps, Ships, Game Modes, Custom Game Rules, Characters, Championships and much, much more!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9NFSd4CraQo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=usX2uzwEBfk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/YoHo-Kablammo/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/yo-ho-kablammo/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/yo-ho-kablammo"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":264,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sproing"],
			"synopsis":"The stage is shrouded in dry ice, spotlights gradually focus on the centre of the stage, the curtain rises and with the first move a fantastic show explodes around you: this is your first performance! You will be dancing with the world's best. Select one of the 6 available characters, style your character using around 300 accessories and perform at 8 spectacular venues. Dance the hottest moves using the Controller or on the Dance Mat. Use the cool dance routines to show off your skills in 20 tracks that have been created exclusively for the game! In Multiplayer you can play with up to 4 players and dance against your friends, and you'll soon be looking down at your rivals from the top of the online leaderboard; the stage is yours!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YFXbKR8t1aw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=18SUczRY_dc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dance-Its-your-Stage/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dance-its-your-stage/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dance!-its-your-stage"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":265,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sonic Team"],
			"synopsis":"The blue hedgehog and the red echidna were sworn adversaries in Sonic 3, but in the platform adventure Sonic & Knuckles, Knuckles realizes that he's been just a pawn in the schemes of Dr. Eggman (aka Dr. Robotnik). Knuckles, the former adversary, now supports Sonic to chase the common enemy, and each must use their strengths to acquire the priceless Master Emerald and save Angel Island.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uXQeq-u6-6o"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/971809-sonic-and-knuckles/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sonic-and-Knuckles/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sonic-knuckles/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sonic-knuckles"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sonic News Network",
				"url":"http://sonic.wikia.com/wiki/Sonic_%26_Knuckles"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":266,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Taito"],
			"synopsis":"The action game classic Bubble Bobble returns as an Xbox Live Arcade game in Bubble Bobble Neo! Encase your enemies in bubbles with the bubble-spitting dragon Bub! Learn the various techniques of the game and clear all the rounds in multiple game modes, including offline co-op play.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Extra Map 1",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/30",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Adds Extra Map 1 (50 rounds) to the game."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Extra Map 2",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/30",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Adds Extra Map 2 (50 rounds) to the game."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PWWfQ2O9Bc8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bubble-Bobble-Neo/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bubble-bobble-neo/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bubble-bobble-neo"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":267,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Los Angeles"],
			"synopsis":"Comrades, the Red Alert 3 battle rages on! This entry in the Command & Conquer series challenges players to take on the world's toughest commanders and conquer the globe in 50 unique challenges. The Commander's Challenge throws the player into intense battle challenges against a set of nine different commanders, including 16-time world champion \"Nature Boy\" Ric Flair. Each challenge features its very own over-the-top and distinctive twist, confronting players with everything from giant Soviet war bears and an entire army of psionic Japanese school girls to massive satellite orbital bombardments. As players progress throughout the gauntlet, they gradually unlock more units, technology and new challenges. Additionally, each challenge is equipped with a par time set by the dev team that is up to the most competitive players to beat.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dubL0oZynFQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nx4isQExt-Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Red-Alert-3-Commanders-Challenge/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/red-alert-3-commanders-challenge/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/command-conquer-red-alert-3---commanders-challenge"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Command & Conquer Wiki",
				"url":"http://cnc.wikia.com/wiki/Command_%26_Conquer:_Red_Alert_3:_Commander's_Challenge"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":268,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Coreplay"],
			"synopsis":"In 2183 humanity discovers an energy source that facilitates travel into new regions of space. Gigantic mother ships collect the newly discovered fuel from the distant energy fields and transport it to Earth. When the fleet is destroyed in an alien attack, the player sets out on a perilous journey home in a small harvester.<br><br>In Ion Assault, instead of conventional weapons, players use the free energy particles that are abundant in space to fend off swarms of aliens. The particles are bundled and the player is able to shoot them at asteroids and enemy ships. The particles are not destroyed in this process, but are redistributed in space, ready to be magnetically attracted again and re-used. Their random distribution makes for dynamic gameplay and calls for a more strategic approach.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZZxNMOk24bc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iVQSj0h5TIc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ion-Assault/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ion-assault/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ion-assault"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":269,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["CTXM"],
			"synopsis":"Available on Xbox LIVE Arcade, The Warriors: Street Brawl features six missions of three levels each for a total of 18 arcade-style battles. Staying true to the movie, The Warriors: Street Brawl begins at the gang summit in Van Cortland Park and continues as players fight hordes of notorious rivals in a life or death battle to their home turf. Players can become one of the iconic Warriors, including Swan, Cochise, Vermin or Rembrandt, as they try to uphold the gang's reputation as one of the toughest factions in New York. The tension builds until the epic beach showdown against Luther, devious leader of The Rogues.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=53CVcI9RDGQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Warriors-Street-Brawl/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-warriors-street-brawl/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-warriors-street-brawl"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":270,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Nihilistic Software"],
			"synopsis":"As heavily equipped gunslingers, Zombie Apocalypse sets players on a mission to destroy as many zombies as possible in order save the last remaining human survivors.<br><br>Using an array of up to 11 lethal weapons including assault rifles, flame throwers and a teddy bear filled with C4 explosives, up to four players can play locally or via the Internet to stop the zombie attacks and rescue survivors as they compete for the highest scores. Players can use a chainsaw to melee zombies and protect themselves against becoming one of the undead. As an added line of defense, players can also use environmental hazards to crush, burn, slice, or cause other types of destruction on the masses of zombies.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YjRVuTJss6U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x_WVS3G18p4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Zombie-Apocalypse/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/zombie-apocalypse/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/zombie-apocalypse"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":271,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["I-Imagine"],
			"synopsis":"Football Genius: The Ultimate Quiz incorporates more than 3,500 different questions and six football packs with reference to football leagues around the world including, English, French, German, Italian, and Spanish. The quiz allows for up to four players to compete for the best score with subjects ranging from general football trivia to true insider questions, testing players' knowledge of all things related to the vast world of football.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gfemgQPLhS4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/971402-football-genius-the-ultimate-quiz/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Football-Genius/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/football-genius-the-ultimate-quiz/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/football-genius---the-ultimate-quiz"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":272,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Hudson Soft"],
			"synopsis":"Military Madness, the classic turn-based strategy game, returns at last for the modern generation of consoles. This 2009 entry in the strategic combat simulation franchise includes an all-new graphical barrage, a regiment of new units, online co-op and vs. multiplayer and a platoon of other new features.<br><br>With new features such as the commander unit, four person online multiplayer gaming and a 3D view of the battlefield, Miltary Madness has been modernized to meet the needs of today's gamer without straying from the strategic elements that earned the original version awards and accolades.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=77_7H4qh10c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h3N0gqmJbOM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Military-Madness-Nectaris/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/military-madness/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/military-madness-nectaris"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":273,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Taito"],
			"synopsis":"Bust-A-Move, sometimes known as Puzzle Bobble, returns in Bust-A-Move Live!, with all of its exciting pick-up-and-play gameplay intact. Dazzling graphics and a surreal soundtrack create a unique fantasy world enhancing the ultimate Bust-A-Move experience!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"1P Puzzle Pack-1",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/11",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Take a trip to the past with these stages from Bust-A-Move 2. Also includes a brand new \"ZONE ?\"!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"1P Puzzle Pack-2",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/11",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Enjoy some classic, hand-picked stages from Super Bust-A-Move and Bust-A-Move 3DX. Also includes a brand new \"ZONE ?\"!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a91wefQT9GE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Puzzle-Bobble-Live/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/puzzle-bobble-live/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bust-a-move-live!"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":274,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["LucasArts"],
			"synopsis":"Lucidity is an addictive puzzle platformer set in the surreal dreamscapes of a little girl named Sofi. In Lucidity, players take a trip into the imagination of Sofi, a young girl who is filled with a persistent desire to explore new worlds and overcome all obstacles in her way. In this challenging puzzle platform game, players are tasked with keeping Sofi safe as she drifts deeper into the strange new world of her dreams. Through quick reaction and placement of randomly generated puzzle pieces, players must create a path through beautifully detailed dreamscapes to keep Sofi in perpetual motion and deliver her to safety.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xKfGSQWc29Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gbjBmOhUCoo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lucidity/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lucidity/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lucidity"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":275,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Doublesix"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the Emmy- and Peabody-award winning show, this South Park game is exclusive to Xbox LIVE Arcade. In this fast-paced action/strategy game, you play to save the town of South Park. The game combines snowball-throwing action with tower defense strategy, and is designed for players of all skill levels. Unlock special content and new characters throughout the game for your in-game scrapbook. Play locally with up to four players or team up on Xbox Live in the story-based campaign or the extra-demanding Challenge levels.Unlock the full game of South Park to access all the great gameplay features, including challenge levels and all 15 un-lockable playable characters. The full game features fast-paced and intense action/strategy with local and Xbox Live multiplay, leaderboards, achievements, and more!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_tiBcGYvtS0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fAcciZOT3-E"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/961649-south-park-lets-go-tower-defense-play/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/South-Park/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/south-park-lets-go-tower-defense-play/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/south-park-lets-go-tower-defense-play!"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sout Park Archives",
				"url":"http://southpark.wikia.com/wiki/South_Park_Let's_Go_Tower_Defense_Play!"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":276,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Silver Wish Games"],
			"synopsis":"Axel & Pixel tells the story of Axel the artist and his dog Pixel as they embark on a fantastic journey through the surreal and dangerous Dream World. Combining simple point-and-click gameplay and a beautiful hand-drawn environment, the game is truly unique.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7pFMzETP8XI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xK9kDxWdiHk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Axel-and-Pixel/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/axel-and-pixel/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/axel-pixel"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":277,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Telltale Games"],
			"synopsis":"Sam & Max are on the job again in Season Two of their infamous adventure series! This downloadable package features five Sam & Max episodes chock full of adventure, crime-fighting, and chaos. The season starts with a giant battle robot attack and never lets up, taking our valiant crime-fighters on a gut-wrenching mission from the North Pole to Easter Island, from outer space to Hell and back.<br><br>Special features! Experience hours of special features and behind-the-scenes goodies that rival any TV series boxed set on the market today. Hear commentary from the team who made the games. Peek behind the scenes at the game design process through concept art and designer notes. And if you're a savvy viewer, you may even uncover some surprises...",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DJWUJ6nv5YY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay (PC)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GQIMzGXlkI0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960925-sam-and-max-beyond-time-and-space/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sam-and-Max-Beyond-Time/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sam-and-max-beyond-time-and-space/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sam-max-beyond-time-and-space"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sam & Max Wiki",
				"url":"http://samandmax.wikia.com/wiki/Sam_%26_Max_Season_Two"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":278,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Petroglyph"],
			"synopsis":"A combination between a board game and a card battle game, Panzer General: Allied Assault is a single and multiplayer digital card game that takes place during the last phase of World War II, from 1944 to 1945. The dramatic events of D-Day finally gave the Allies a foothold on Fortress Europe, allowing them to push the Germans back to Berlin. Players can recreate actual battles such as Utah Beach, Operation Market Garden, and the infamous Battle of the Bulge in the hopes of turning back the German tide. Build, customize and fight with your personalized deck of 60 digital cards. History is in your hands.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FWOZ6y5aXYA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Panzer-General/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/panzer-general-allied-assault/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/panzer-general-allied-assault"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":279,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Chocolate"],
			"synopsis":"Get Tower Bloxx Deluxe and discover 6 massive game modes of this addictive smash-hit! The action-puzzle phenomenon is played by millions on the web, but Xbox players get the full HD experience with revolutionary social scoring, avatar support, power ups, and even multiplayer. Get ready for edge of your seat action that'll have you creating swaying, tipping and tumbling towers sky-high.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CvSu53CjUl8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SIAqcw6IUXo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tower-Bloxx-Deluxe/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tower-bloxx-deluxe/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tower-bloxx-deluxe"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":280,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Dark Energy Digital"],
			"synopsis":"Inferno Pool is a revolutionary arcade Pool/Billiards game where 1-4 local or online players battle to clear their tables while firing potted balls at opponents. Players can stockpile balls for a later onslaught, nominate their victims, and unleash devastating ball streaks and outrageous skill shots to trigger the punishing Inferno Mode. Alliances will be formed, friends will be betrayed, and the battle isn't over until the stat screen appears. The game also includes classic 8 ball and 9 ball modes for 1-2 players, and the addictive, Inferno-fueled, race against the clock Endurance Mode.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ac9vFfgA-Y8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Inferno-Pool/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/inferno-pool/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/inferno-pool"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":281,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Taito"],
			"synopsis":"See our twin heroes in their human forms of Bubby and Bobby as they embark on another adventure climbing to the top of Rainbow Tower. Bubby and Bobby borrow the mystical powers of Rainbow magic as they ward off the attacks of the pesky Dr. Crescent and aim for the top of Rainbow Tower to meet Holly's Comet, who will make any dream a reality.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ULCGiikP-1I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rainbow-Island/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rainbow-islands-towering-adventure/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rainbow-islands-towering-adventure!"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":282,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Telltale Games"],
			"synopsis":"Join Wallace and his dog Gromit in a series episodes of of grand adventures create by Telltale Games, the minds behind the Sam & Max game series and Strong Bad's Cool Game for Attractive People.<br><br>Will the perfect holiday turn into the perfect crime? When unrelenting rain ruins their holiday plans, Wallace & Gromit bring the beach to 62 West Wallaby with a makeshift resort - in their basement. Keeping customers satisfied is tricky business, especially when one of them is clocked on the head by an unknown assailant. Whodunnit? Find out... with a little help from Wallace's latest invention, the Deduct-o-matic!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ACo09CSIeUI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gJcDa5TgZRM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kk4hHKUgrNE&index=2&list=PL5B46E645EBDD4D68"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/pc/958991-wallace-and-gromits-grand-adventures-episode-2-the/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wallace-and-Gromit-The-Last-Resort/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wallace-and-gromit-episode-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wallace-gromits-grand-adventures-episode-2-the-last-resort"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wallace and Gromit Wiki",
				"url":"http://wallaceandgromit.wikia.com/wiki/Wallace_%26_Gromit%27s_Grand_Adventures"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":283,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Telltale Games"],
			"synopsis":"Join Wallace and his dog Gromit in a series episodes of of grand adventures create by Telltale Games, the minds behind the Sam & Max game series and Strong Bad's Cool Game for Attractive People.<br><br>Monty Muzzle, a newcomer in town, is holding a grand fundraiser to rebuild the local dog shelter. Gromit soon realizes that Muzzle's intentions aren't exactly charitable and he must foil the huckster's plot to save the town's investment and rescue his canine friends.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ACo09CSIeUI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gJcDa5TgZRM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fNC25NI1RHE&index=3&list=PL5B46E645EBDD4D68"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/pc/958993-wallace-and-gromits-grand-adventures-episode-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wallace-and-Gromit-Muzzled/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wallace-and-gromit-episode-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wallace-gromits-grand-adventures-episode-3-muzzled!"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wallace and Gromit Wiki",
				"url":"http://wallaceandgromit.wikia.com/wiki/Wallace_%26_Gromit%27s_Grand_Adventures"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":284,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Telltale Games"],
			"synopsis":"Join Wallace and his dog Gromit in a series episodes of of grand adventures create by Telltale Games, the minds behind the Sam & Max game series and Strong Bad's Cool Game for Attractive People.<br><br>Wallace has been admitted to Prickly Thicket, the oldest country club in Lancashire. Wallace and his faithful caddie Gromit get wrapped up in a decades-old club dispute that threatens to destroy their peaceful West Wallaby lifestyle, and the duo must fight to save the neighborhood they hold dear!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ACo09CSIeUI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gJcDa5TgZRM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nFctmjp_wNQ&list=PL5B46E645EBDD4D68&index=4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/pc/958995-wallace-and-gromits-grand-adventures-episode-4-the/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wallace-and-Gromit-The-Bogey-Man/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wallace-and-gromit-episode-4/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wallace-gromits-grand-adventures-episode-4-the-bogey-man"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wallace and Gromit Wiki",
				"url":"http://wallaceandgromit.wikia.com/wiki/Wallace_%26_Gromit%27s_Grand_Adventures"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":285,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cyclone Zero"],
			"synopsis":"The fusion of rhythm and puzzle gaming is here! Tap your foot to the music and attack your opponent while you strategically pile up your pieces like a normal puzzle game to score some points. Let the rhythm guide you and the right moves will follow!<br><br>The game includes 2 Player Versus (fight another player locally or over Xbox Live), a single-player mode, 21 types of background and blocks to choose from, and more.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Blaz Blue Special Skin and BGM Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Blaz Blue comes to 0D Beat Drop! It's the collaboration of your dreams! This first DLC pack contains new skins and music for three of BlazBlue's lovely ladies: Noel, Nu and Tsubaki. When you purchase this DLC, a new [Planet Quest +] option will be added to the [Single Player Game] menu, where you can play with the new skins and music. This DLC also adds a new DLC-only leaderboard!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7oVlRMYDybE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pH5o_kZkJ_Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/0D-Beat-Drop/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/zero-d-beat-drop"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":286,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Arcade"],
			"synopsis":"Join the brilliant and eccentric Professor Ivor Question in his funky lab for a variety of fun and fast-paced challenges testing memory, reflexes, and dexterity. Response time and accuracy are rewarded with Noodles, the in-game currency. The game's challenge is to accumulate Noodles, but out-braining your friends is fun, too.<br><br>In the single-player Take-a-Test Mode, players take the Professor's five-round tests in mathematics, pattern recognition, reactions, and memory. Players can track their improvements over the previous 30 tests to see how much their brains have become \"enclevered\". To test your encleverment against others, Game Show Mode allows multiple players to complete the Professor's challenges as quickly as possible, with top honors going to the first player to answer correctly. Players can challenge randomly generated quizzes or design their own \"Home-made Games\" with the easy-to-use Editor feature, which can create game shows up to 30 rounds long. The last round is always the \"Score Stealer Game\" - the first person to answer correctly gets to steal points from the fellow contestant of choice. Winners are rewarded with Noodles which are used to purchase up to 60 collectible Mascots to show off their gaming prowess.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QQpiKLMo0PM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FD01z041lKU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Encleverment-Experiment/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/enclevermentexperiment/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/encleverment-experiment"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":287,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["A.C.R.O.N.Y.M. Games"],
			"synopsis":"Paying homage to the old school look and feel of classic arcade games, NBA Unrivaled brings to the table a contemporary retro design to this generation of high definition gaming. Sporting the full NBA license and the 2009 NBA season's team and player rosters, the game also includes current stats, logos and jerseys. Ball your way up to the top of the league and play to your fullest to get the crowd pumped.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M7J16IG5vYg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R57vYjeeqtU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-UNRIVALED/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-unrivaled/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-unrivaled"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":288,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Coresoft, GameLab"],
			"synopsis":"Welcome to Diner Dash, the action-puzzle that brings out the entrepreneur in all of us! Poor Flo! Sick and tired of pushing paper in the dreary, bleary-eyed world of finance, she ditched her desk job and now she's rolling up her sleeves and setting out to build her very own empire of high-class, five-star restaurants. It won't be easy, though! Flo's on her own now, and heading for the top! To get there she'll have to start on the ground floor-and she needs your help to survive and thrive. Diner Dash blends the best in fast paced-action puzzles with a build-your-restaurant-empire theme that encourages players to serve their way from a two-table diner to the top of the restaurant ladder - starting with a run-of-the-mill greasy spoon and ending in a dream restaurant.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-mhwkNR2nrk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Diner-Dash/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/diner-dash/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/diner-dash"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Diner Dash Wiki",
				"url":"http://dinerdash.wikia.com/wiki/Diner_Dash_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":289,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Square Enix", "PopCap Games"],
			"synopsis":"Rivel, leader of the rebel faction Temperance and sorcerer vessel of the Godseye, follows Qraist, the countslayer, into the enchanted Aldemona Wood. The wood whispers to the two. For Rivel, the wood holds the key to his locked memories. For Qraist, the wood holds his calling -- to be its master. Unbeknownst to either, the nefarious Everett watches quietly from the shadows. Within this enchanted wood, severed from the outside world by ritual, lie mysteries and answers, knowledge and wonder. Each enters in search of something -- but what is it they will find?",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/18",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Add three additional stages to Gyromancer. These stages are accessible once you've reached the middle stages of the original game. Includes new beasts that will pose a challenge for even seasoned players."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iSQyXlj8XS0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HwRPQ8KSVkQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/974793-gyromancer/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Gyromancer/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/gyromancer/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/gyromancer"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":290,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Endemol"],
			"synopsis":"From the makers of Deal or No Deal, Endemol, the world's largest independent production company, brings the popular television game show 1 vs. 100 to Xbox LIVE Primetime. The exclusive game pits one Xbox LIVE member against 100 others from around the world with a live host and great prizes. The goal of \"the One\" is to eliminate all the opposition by correctly answering questions, hoping that the opponents will answer incorrectly and be eliminated from the game. And stay tuned for 1 vs. LIVE, where one lucky winner will have a chance to compete against the entire Xbox LIVE community.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c3WwnUGH4B8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e0BXdgz8Ipg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/1-vs-100/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/1-vs-100/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":291,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"Madden NFL Arcade is a fun, pick-up-and-play, 5-on-5 football game from EA Tiburon. Madden NFL Arcade is pure adrenaline football for both casual and diehard NFL fans, featuring a unique art style that brings your favorite players to life like never before.<br><br>Madden NFL Arcade is the perfect video game for gameday, allowing up to four players to play co-op on a single console. You can also take on the world online in head-to-head matches and track your performance via interactive leaderboards. If you like to commemorate your gridiron success, Madden NFL Arcade will also provide a host of achievements and trophies to boost your gamer score.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UbPmyZRUuRc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bAtnRoOdn50"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Madden-NFL-Arcade/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/madden-nfl-arcade/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/madden-nfl-arcade"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":292,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Aspyr", "Infinity Ward"],
			"synopsis":"For the first time ever, Infinity Ward's 2003 award-winning game that launched a franchise comes to consoles. Experience the cinematic intensity of World War II's biggest conflicts including D-Day, Stalingrad and the Battle of Berlin. Play through 24 epic single-player missions across four interconnected campaigns. Complete in online multiplayer on the battlegrounds that decided the history of the world.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YUrUDrjOFYY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0zGhIrvdjlk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats (Original game)",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/pc/914586-call-of-duty/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Call-of-Duty-Classic/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/call-of-duty/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/call-of-duty-classic"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Call of Duty Wiki",
				"url":"http://callofduty.wikia.com/wiki/Call_of_Duty"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":293,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Taito"],
			"synopsis":"Inheriting the style of the renowned arcade title, QIX++ allows you to take up the fight again in a variety of different ways. With customized weapon improvements, a technique-based scoring system, and events triggered by opening Item Containers, the evolution of the series has truly come a long way.The object of the game is to defeat the QIX using the marker. When the total area cut off by the marker reaches a percentage equal to the Threshold, your final attack begins and you have cleared the stage.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Expansion Pack 1 \"Float\"",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/30",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Through this downloadable content, you can enjoy the new game mode \"Float\", in addition to four extra QIX."
			},
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Expansion Pack 2 \"Hunt\"",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/30",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Through this downloadable content, you can enjoy the new game mode Hunt Mode, in addition to four extra QIX."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nkviLaYYIRk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/QIX-Plus-Plus/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/qix/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/qix++"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":294,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Team17 Software"],
			"synopsis":"One of the true classics from the Team17 vault comes back in this next-generation take on Alien Breed. Alien Breed Evolution marks the rebirth of a gaming legend that has laid dormant for years. While the core gameplay remains intact, the technology, online component, and production values have improved immeasurably for your pleasure. The first episode of three has you battling alone or partnering up against the \"breed\", offline or online over five action-packed single-player levels and three multiplayer levels.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=laQOwfRbAAQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=54xIHKCpQMI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Alien-Breed-Episode-1-Evolution/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/alien-breed-evolution/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/alien-breed-evolution"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":295,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Pieces Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Set in an array of galaxies, Puzzlegeddon features a clever mix of puzzle, action and strategy for gameplay that is fast-paced and addictive. Compete for the top spot on the planet by creating multiple combos for the quickest way to gather enough resources to blast your enemies out of this world! Or, if you find yourself on the perilous poisonous planet, solve brainteasers to rapidly get your way back onto the battlegrounds. You can battle up to five players in a variety of galaxies in this stylish and quirky puzzle brawler.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NZE72yhldiw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wzg6qflIiB0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Puzzlegeddon/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/puzzlegeddon"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":296,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gulti"],
			"synopsis":"Earth is under attack by massive creatures from outer space. With a huge arsenal of heavy-power artillery at your disposal, climb into your fighter jet and wage fierce battles against these gruesome aggressors. 0 Day Attack on Earth gives you full range of motion and attack while you engage in air strikes over real-world cities, such as Tokyo, New York and Paris. Team up with-or battle against-players from around the world in online co-op. Only you can save Earth from complete annihilation!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"London Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/13",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The struggle to protect Earth and prevent the end of humanity continues. After defending New York's Manhattan skyline, freeing the mammoth metropolis of Tokyo, and rescuing the historic and beautiful Paris, your next mission awaits in London. Seven new stages to clear! The battles over the Thames are intense with new, huge enemies swarming the skies. This map pack is for use only in Single Player Mode and Co-op Mode for 2-4 players. Maps are not playable in Capture the Flag or Control Point modes for 2-8 players."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Night Missions Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/03",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The hardest version of 0 Day is here. Revisit New York, Tokyo and Paris, where the enemy only comes out after sunset and are much stronger and harder to defeat. Must play for gamers that enjoyed the original version! This map pack is for use only in Single Player Mode and Co-op Mode for 2-4 players. Maps are not playable in Capture the Flag or Control Point modes for 2-8 players."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=19jr8ejNqBY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hNLuHFVLmXU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/0-day-Attack-on-Earth/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/0-day-attack-on-earth/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/0-day-attack-on-earth"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":297,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eiconic Games"],
			"synopsis":"In Polar Panic, players control a bear named Polar who pushes and destroys snow and ice blocks around a grid-based environment in order to kill trapper enemies, activate switches, earn bonus points and gather powerful pickups, such as 'Time Freeze' or score bonuses and extra lives. In story mode, players battle against a series of enemies in a variety of Arctic environments that include an icy wasteland, a logging area, the back of a giant logging truck, and the decks of a ship rocked by icy seas. Players can vary the difficulty levels, which change gameplay elements, such as speed of movement, and reaction and decision time. In puzzle mode, players push or destroy the blocks in order to open a door or reach an exit.<br><br>With 50 levels of single-player madness in story mode, and 50 mind-numbing puzzle levels, along with single and multiplayer survival modes, Polar Panic will heat up gaming for players during the Holiday season and beyond.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r-jPyBAxGuw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MV9lZBARC5s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Polar-Panic/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/polar-panic/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/polar-panic"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":298,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Vicious Cycle"],
			"synopsis":"General Neutronov, one of Matt's nemeses has reactivated all of Hazard's greatest enemies from the past. Matt has no time for a stroll down memory lane as he chases Neutronov through the games of the past in order to save his future.<br><br>Matt Hazard: Blood Bath and Beyond is a flood of carnage that the classic 8-bit side-scroller era didn't want gamers to see. Recreated today with next-gen 3D graphics, it's nonstop run-and-gun action at its finest. Take a suspenseful ride in single player or co-op through a pirate hideout, an ancient Japanese castle, the Old West, Siberian ice mines, and even the moon and relive some of the most classic and violent moments in Matt Hazard's videogame history.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C1QNkBUfaYw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pQPlue_MoeY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Matt-Hazard-Blood-Bath-and-Beyond/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/matt-hazard-blood-bath-and-beyond/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/matt-hazard-blood-bath-and-beyond"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":299,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Devolver Digital", "Croteam"],
			"synopsis":"Monsters spawned from another dimension are trying to make The Milky Way their personal trash can. As attempts to defend the solar system fail, the fate of the Earth, and even the universe, rests with one man. YOU are Sam 'Serious' Stone, a legend in your time. Sam is our only hope against these mischievous miscreants and their evil leader, Mental. In practice, this translates into adrenaline-pumping, non-stop alien blasting action, as Serious Sam throws whole waves of monsters at the player.<br><br>Bring back the onslaught, Serious Sam HD is not your mother's generic, large-scale, orchestral scored, Space Marine-themed epic FPS with dialog that pretends it's an RPG... instead, Serious Sam HD is a grab you by the jibblies run and gun, twitch FPS: big guns, tons of enemies, 4-Player Online Co-Op and HD graphics.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SjKDjiV-ktM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k5iBOwBQXb4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/961109-serious-sam-hd-the-first-encounter/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Serious-Sam-The-First-Encounter/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/serious-sam-hd-the-first-encounter/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/serious-sam-hd-the-first-encounter"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Serious Sam Wiki",
				"url":"http://serioussam.wikia.com/wiki/Portal:SS1"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":300,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Premium Agency"],
			"synopsis":"LEO is a robot, one who awakes to find that he has lost his memory. All he knows is that he must reboot the heroine robot SELSIE, so he sets forth on a mission hoping to regain his memory. To his surprise, he finds the world is now filled with battalions of enemy robots, drenched in bright red oil, and shooting bullets every direction.<br><br>Death by Cube is an exhilarating action game in which you must take out endless hordes of enemies, while avoiding the rapid barrage of their fire that envelopes the screen. Take advantage of your shooting, as well as \"dash\" and \"shield\" abilities in order to clear each level and gain the medals which are awarded according to the score you achieve. By using the chips gained from completing levels, you can upgrade your character and focus on shooting, or on other abilities. Upgraded characters can also be used in the multiplayer modes, where up to 8 players can battle it out at the same time. Death by Cube has 3 types of multiplayer mode -- Death Match, Base Battle and High Score Scramble -- so you can compete with your friends using whichever rules you like.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9MQxKqQ5B0E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ek-1hLJvVTA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Death-By-Cube/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/death-by-cube/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/death-by-cube"
			}]
		}
	}]
}