{
	"catalog": [
	{
		"id":101,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Carbonated Games"],
			"synopsis":"Building on the success of Hexic HD, Hexic 2 brings all-new pieces to the board and a new multiplayer mode, so you can compete with friends in your living room or over Xbox LIVE.<br><br>The basic gameplay is straightforward, familiar, and addictive. Just spin a trio of hexes to create a group of three or more matching colors, or build a formation of hexes to create more advanced pieces. Whether you want a relaxing puzzle break or a frantic race against the clock, Hexic 2 has you covered!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZzuFqf8ZNSw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hexic-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hexic-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hexic-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":102,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Llamasoft"],
			"synopsis":"Another trippy shooter concept from videogame vet Jeff Minter, this 3D FX-a-thon has you as the star-assembled Space Giraffe flying through a warped void of space, firing shots from your \"hooves\" as it crawls along the edge of the void, trying to destroy enemies and keep its tail growing (the tail can be sacrificed for Smart Bombs) while trying not to be knocked off into the void outside of the void. Very similar in concept and play to Minter's own classic Tempest.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EAJ5texZVyM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938955-space-giraffe/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Space-Giraffe/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/space-giraffe"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":103,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gaia Industries"],
			"synopsis":"Grab a custom hover-board and lay trail across the urban sprawl, racing through abandoned streets and battling in war-torn arenas. It is an adrenaline pumping action game that combines both arena combat and racing.<br><br>Meet the cast of rebel 'Tracers' and trick-out your board and weapon through cash and pickup tournaments. Then race, shoot, and grind your way to victory, taking on the circuit champions in single player mode or compete in split screen multiplayer with friends. Take it to the next level and go live, competing against fellow Tracers from around the world. Gain ranking supremacy across a range of over 40 leader boards!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nak2RUvDaVA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9ilBUv-8Oks"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Street-Trace-NYC/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/street-trace-nyc/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/street-trace-nyc"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":104,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SEGA"],
			"synopsis":"To celebrate their defeat of the Syndicate exactly one year before, Blaze, Adam and Axel met for drinks. The next morning, Axel received a frantic phone call from Eddie \"Skate\" Hunter, Adam's younger brother, whom he was living with on the edge of the city. Blaze and Axel found Adam and Skate's house wrecked, and a picture showing Adam chained up at the feet of Mr. X.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b6ZSrGT20IA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Video walkthrough",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TWmnVtDOIFk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942662-streets-of-rage-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Streets-of-Rage-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/streets-of-rage-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/streets-of-rage-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Streets of Rage Wiki",
				"url":"http://streetsofrage.wikia.com/wiki/Streets_of_Rage_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":105,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Backbone Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Super Puzzle Fighter II Turbo HD Remix downloads Capcom's incredibly popular puzzle game into the new generation. The new version of the game features newly created 1080p HD graphics, several new game modes, improved game balance, new stage backgrounds courtesy of Udon Entertainment and online play.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9sBOxNOtklk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939074-super-puzzle-fighter-ii-turbo-hd-remix/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Puzzle-Fighter-HD/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/super-puzzle-fighter-2-hd-remix/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/super-puzzle-fighter-ii-turbo-hd-remix"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Street Fighter Wiki",
				"url":"http://streetfighter.wikia.com/wiki/Super_Puzzle_Fighter_II_Turbo"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":106,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software"],
			"synopsis":"Take control of your robotic team, and call the plays to move your team downfield for a touchdown. But watch out, the ball gets hot if you don't keep moving! Keep your eye on the ball to make sure it doesn't go critical before you can score.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CW8VL2VhLDM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cyberball-2072/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cyberball-2072/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cyberball-2072"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":107,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Mine Loader Software"],
			"synopsis":"The grandmother of all fighting games is here, with FATAL FURY SPECIAL, a unique adaptation of the original 1993 arcade smash Garou Densetsu Special. Experience all the great fighting game action, with added network play and high-definition display, now available on Xbox LIVE Arcade. Fifteen fighters (plus a special guest), gather for the match of the millennium.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aKmLHClx6ns"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935217-fatal-fury-special/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fatal-Fury-Special/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fatal-fury-special/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fatal-fury-special"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Shoryuken",
				"url":"http://wiki.shoryuken.com/Fatal_Fury_Special"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"SNK Wiki",
				"url":"http://snk.wikia.com/wiki/Fatal_Fury_Special"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":108,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sonic Team"],
			"synopsis":"Dr. Eggman (AKA Dr. Robotnik) is back to continue his zealous search for the Chaos Emeralds needed to fuel his new Death Egg contraption. Now Sonic must thwart the doctor's plans at all costs, but this time he isn't alone as a peculiar two-tailed fox named Miles Prower (AKA Tails) decides to aid him in the battle. Together they must locate the Chaos Emeralds before Dr. Eggman does, and put an end to his diabolical scheme.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tYAffR_7irs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Video walkthrough (Original)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8cr1rqVcIhA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943242-sonic-the-hedgehog-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sonic-The-Hedgehog-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sonic-the-hedgehog-2-arcade/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sonic-the-hedgehog-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sonic Wiki",
				"url":"http://sonic.wikia.com/wiki/Sonic_the_Hedgehog_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":109,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Strawdog Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Geon: Emotions is a psychedelic, pick-up-and-play game of rapidly changing tactics. Playing as one of eight emotions players must race to collect pellets and score goals, using power-ups and their emotional strengths and weaknesses.<br><br>There are three single player modes: Duel, Time Attack and Mini Games, and three multiplayer modes for up to four players: Duel, Team Geon and Last Man Standing and a huge selection of different arenas to get pulses racing.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K2t7JRWXpww"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=69EoqIbqGDE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Geon-Emotions/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/geon/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/geon-emotions"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":110,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tetris Online America"],
			"synopsis":"The most popular electronic game of all time is back, with new variants, enhanced graphics, and beautiful aquatic playscapes in Tetris Splash. Now, with new modes and team play, Tetris Splash introduces even more exciting, enjoyable ways to play this classic favorite. As easy to learn as it is addictive, it's equally fun for the casual player and the seasoned Tetris pro. Three different modes of play including Tetris, T-Spin, and Combo, plus a unique screensaver mode.<br><br>Playable solo, competitively or in teams, with an online multiplayer mode via Xbox LIVE for up to six players. New, enhanced graphics, and beautiful aquatic backscapes add a real splash to the fun of Tetris. Exciting downloadable content will be made available including themes and background aquatic creatures. Twelve new achievements to master and conquer.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Triggerfish Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Download the triggerfish bundle to add to your collection of salt water themed fishes. The triggerfish pack include the clown, reef and picasso fish."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Angelfish Bundle",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Want to add some of your favorite fish to Tetris Splash? This fresh water Angelfish pack includes pearl, black, zebra, and marble fish."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Tetra Bundle",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Want to add some of your favorite fish to Tetris Splash? This fresh water Tetra pack includes bloodfin, neon, glowlight, and black neon fish."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Marine Angelfish Bundle",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Want to add some of your favorite fish to Tetris Splash? This salt water Marine Angelfish pack includes pygmy, emperor, and flame fish."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Fresh/Salt Water Graveyard Theme",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Looking for a change of underwater scenery? Download this fresh/salt water theme for Tetris Splash and customize your game with a snazzy Graveyard background and d&eacute;cor!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Tang Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Download the tang bundle to add to your collection of salt water themed fishes. The tang pack include the yellow, purple, and sailfin fish."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Fresh/Salt Water Atlantis Theme",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Looking for a change of underwater scenery? Download this fresh/salt water theme for Tetris Splash and customize your game with a snazzy Atlantis background and decor!"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Discus Bundle",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Want to add some of your favorite fish to Tetris Splash? This fresh water Discus pack includes blue diamond, red marlboro, red turquoise, and royal blue fish."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Butterflyfish Bundle",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Want to add some of your favorite fish to Tetris Splash? This salt water Butterfly pack includes raccoon, oval, and vagabond fish."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Arowana Bundle",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Want to add some of your favorite fish to Tetris Splash? This fresh water Arowana pack includes red, golden, redtail, and silver fish."
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Fresh/Salt Water Pirate Theme",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Looking for a change of underwater scenery? Download this fresh/salt water theme for Tetris Splash and customize your game with a snazzy Pirate background and decor!"
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Fresh/Salt Water Scuba Theme",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Looking for a change of underwater scenery? Download this fresh/salt water theme for Tetris Splash and customize your game with a snazzy Scuba background and decor!"
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"Fresh/Salt Water Coral Theme",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Looking for a change of underwater scenery? Download this fresh/salt water theme for Tetris Splash and customize your game with a snazzy Coral background and decor!"
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"Guppy Bundle",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Want to add some of your favorite fish to Tetris Splash? This fresh water Guppy pack includes albino, full red, blue delta, and moscow fish."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jBWGp-BkowA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tetris-Splash/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tetris-splash/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tetris-splash"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tetris Wiki",
				"url":"http://tetris.wikia.com/wiki/Tetris_Splash"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":111,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Infinite Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Puzzle Quest: Challenge of the Warlords challenges players to create, develop and customize the ultimate hero in order to save the land of Etheria from evil Lord Bane. To advance their character, players battle in turn-based, head-to-head \"match-three\" style puzzle games in one of three gameplay modes. Single-player allows gamers to battle against the AI as they embark on over 150 quests. Instant Action allows gamers to jump in and immediately play continuous battles to level-up characters without participating in quests. Multiplayer allows gamers to battle live opponents - victory will advance the player's hero, magical arsenal, creature companions and more, ultimately rewarding gamers at nearly every turn.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Revenge of the Plague Lord",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/23",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Battle against the minions of Lord Antharg, Master of Plague, with four new professions and hundreds of new items and spells."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IDnmsnhwI9s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JDEpHwj7Okk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939313-puzzle-quest-challenge-of-the-warlords/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Puzzle-Quest/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/puzzle-quest-challenge-of-the-warlords/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/puzzle-quest-challenge-of-the-warlords"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Puzzle Quest Wiki",
				"url":"http://puzzlequest.wikia.com/wiki/Puzzle_Quest:_Challenge_of_the_Warlords"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":112,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Backbone Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Yaris is a quick, fast and easy-to-learn game that puts players behind the wheel of a customizable Toyota Yaris to destroy enemies, avoid obstacles, and finish the course before it finishes them. Players will enjoy customization options and an arsenal of weapons while they attack enemies and advance to the next level. Yaris features online multiplayer over Xbox LIVE, allowing gamers to challenge each other for the best time and score. Developed by Backbone Entertainment, Yaris is the first free brand-supported game on Xbox LIVE Arcade and is available for download in the U.S. and Canada for one full year.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X2BzEhTMmt8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943627-yaris/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Yaris/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/yaris/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/yaris"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":113,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Q Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"The latest creation from Q Entertainment, \"Every Extend Extra Extreme\", or E4, is a unique action-packed shooter where the goal is to perfectly time your self-destruction to create chain reactions that explode surrounding enemies. With outrageous visuals and the ability to play your own favorite music, E4 puts a new twist on puzzle shooter games.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7dHqU7HPqt4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Every-Extend-Extra-Extreme-E4/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/every-extend-extra-extreme/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/every-extend-extra-extreme"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":114,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bitmap Brothers", "Razorworks"],
			"synopsis":"In the year 2326, rival gangs form an ultra-violent streetsports league called Speedball to settle their deadly disputes. Get your steel ball into the opponent's goal. That's it, there are no other rules, and anything goes. The sport becomes quite popular, but it is also extremely dangerous. Ten years later, Speedball becomes the national sport with sponsors, professional teams, and insanely brutal action.<br><br>A brutal, fast-action, futuristic sports game, Speedball 2: Brutal Deluxe is completely remastered for Xbox LIVE Arcade. Play the fast-paced and utterly brutal game with its classic 2-D graphics, or go full on with the new super-enhanced high definition 3-D visuals. Smash your way to the top of the league in the solo game or go head to head locally or on Xbox LIVE. The game features 32 teams, 4 leagues, cup and knockout competitions, team enhancements, management and training options, and Ranked Preset or Ranked Career games.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ME5vq0tT7YU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Video walkthrough (Original)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iyX4BPU-Bao"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Speedball-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/speedball-2-brutal-deluxe"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":115,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Auran"],
			"synopsis":"Battlestar Galactica is a top-down space combat game set in the universe of the hugely popular sci-fi television show. Sign up to defend the Galactica, or play as the ruthless Cylons as they seek to remove the human menace from existence. Take part in enormous multiplayer space battles - up to 8 players online - or play through the single-player campaign.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hMueCu81oEU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Battlestar-Galactica/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/battlestar-galactica"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":116,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Taito"],
			"synopsis":"An addictive, frenzied puzzle game, Exit has players using their decision-making skills and quick wit to escape numerous obstacles while rescuing people from more emergencies in over 220 levels. The game stars Mr. ESC, the escape artist who goes wherever he's needed to get people out of the worst predicaments you've ever seen. When it comes to escape, nothing's impossible for Mr. ESC.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Additional Stage Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/28",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Add stages from Situations 13 to 17. \"WINTER FESTIVAL\", \"THE LABYRINTH AREHOUSE\", \"FIRE IN THE HOLE\", \"DON'T PANIC!\", and \"SPACE SOLDIER\" will become playable."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Additional Stage Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/12",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Add stages from Situations 18 to 22. \"WITHIN CELLPHONE RANGE!\", \"FOR EXPERTS ONLY\", \"CAN YOU SEE?\", \"CODE BLUE\", and \"INTO THE AIR\" will become playable."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer (PSP)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JBME7cSFiug"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZwibdxlvcvU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Exit/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/exit"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":117,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["PomPom Games"],
			"synopsis":"Mutant Storm Empire is packed with sci-fi action as players crush gangs of robots, smash swarms of UFOs and demolish massive enemy bosses. Mutant Storm Empire features 16 unique levels spread over four richly detailed and varied worlds. Players move from room to room without having to enter a loading screen, in addition to offline co-op and multiplayer LIVE support for two people.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4nidzLO8j4s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WZZ0sS1GkRk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mutant-Storm-Empire/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mutant-storm-empire/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mutant-storm-empire"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":118,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Atomic Elbow"],
			"synopsis":"Switchball is a puzzle game set in a fully-realized 3D world. Control an ever-changing ball along a narrow winding course suspended in midair. Solve your way through challenging levels jam-packed with obstacles, traps and mazes. Morph the marble ball with metal, electric and lighter-than-air properties to more easily get through each area.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5vc5bgStJg4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Switchball/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/switchball/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/switchball"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":119,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["InterServ International"],
			"synopsis":"The traditional pen and paper word search game is taken to a whole new level in World Puzzle. The game features 3D boards, exploding word bombs and a whole host of synapse melting challenges and special effects. World Puzzle also has five game modes, Live support for up to four players and Xbox Live Vision Camera support.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oCodDMkiN_Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Word-Puzzle/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/word-puzzle/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/word-puzzle"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":120,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Frozen Codebase"],
			"synopsis":"Freefall into the depths of the chaotic underworld as a Screwjumper, and drive the aliens back to their home world by destroying their precious mining equipment. Demolish structures in freefall as you increase your destructive power by increasing your velocity. Use dynamite to pick off hazards and high value targets. Destroy the mine core and jetpack out alive. Dead screwjumpers don't get paid!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bpLtSnCRWdQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LiEGXPYOJPk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Screwjumper/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/screwjumper/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/screwjumper!"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":121,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Backbone Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Gamers join Shrek, Fiona, Donkey, Puss in Boots and 20 other twisted fairy tale friends in this puzzle game designed for ogres of all ages.<br><br>Navigate through 16 challenging mazes across four unique environments in Far Far Away's newest competitive tournament. Test your tilting and rolling skills in Single Player mode, challenge others in Versus mode, or work together with friends and family in 2-player local Co-op mode.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay (Minute 2:30)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wTD6C9QdNuE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/ShreknRoll/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/shrek-n-roll/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/shrek-n-roll"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":122,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Chair Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Based in an alternate world where earth has been completely flooded and several factions are vying for supremacy, Undertow is an underwater shooter featuring a complex multiplayer component. Undertow features a complete campaign mode that can be played either solo or co-operatively with a friend, and also boasts a battle mode that supports up to 16 players at once in an online contest. The goal is to destroy your enemies and take control of their bases, with victory coming from a traditional flag-and-ticket system found in online conquest modes, but the gameplay here is faster and easier to play than other online titles thanks to the simple dual-analog control scheme.<br><br>Each faction in battle has its own look and feel -- the Atlantians are a magical race that fight by riding creatures and attack with magic, the Nemodians are a lost and once peaceful race living under the sea for over a hundred years and led by Captain Nemo, and the Iron Marines are a militant group of humans that took to the seas when the world flooded. None of these groups necessarily wants this battle, but with the planet in ruins, civilization is not an option.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Path of the Elect",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/05",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Download the first expansion to Undertow! Play as the Elect through their ALL NEW five level campaign! Includes four awesome new multiplayer maps, and adds the Elect as a playable race!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=99hHos6Zv38"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nOIJ9ZFmJJs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Undertow/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/undertow/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/undertow"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":123,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Stainless Games"],
			"synopsis":"Thrust through space blasting a path for survival, in this two-pack of the classic arcade game Asteroids, each edition with Original and Evolved game modes. Released as a tandem set of Asteroids and its sequel Asteroids Deluxe, enhancements for both include support for both 4:3 and 16:9 aspect ratios. Full-screen anti-aliasing and Dolby Digital surround sound complete the gaming experience.<br><br><b>ASTEROIDS</b>: Originally released in 1979 by Atari, the simple black and white game Asteriods was a masterpiece of vector graphics game design, and had millions of arcadegoers entranced by its simple mechanic of controlling a spaceship firing at and destroying asteroids.<br><br><b>ASTEROIDS DELUXE</b>: Originally released in 1980 by Atari, the sequel to the legendary arcade phenom Asteroids featured the same classic gameplay but added a new shield feature and dangerous satellite enemies.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SbJ3bGTU-3U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Asteroids-and-Deluxe/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/asteroids-asteroids-deluxe/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/asteroids-asteroids-deluxe"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":124,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Wanako Games"],
			"synopsis":"Define your legacy... Awaken your inner-beast... Fight with one of three powerful warriors to the ultimate confrontation with Gorgon herself. Spanning treacherous dungeons consisting of countless enemies, heinous and powerful bosses, your warriors will embark on a trek of unimaginable proportions.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=srTPzh-3EwE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942874-arkadian-warriors/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Arkadian-Warriors/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/arkadian-warriors/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/arkadian-warriors"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":125,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sidhe"],
			"synopsis":"A re-mixed version of GripShift, the award-winning racing/puzzle game from Sidhe Interactive, speeds onto Xbox Live Arcade with a complete set of upgrades and new features. In this definitive version of the game, players will enjoy improved controls, enhanced HD graphics, additional single player courses and intense, friend-fragging Deathmatch arena battles. A full set of achievements and TrueSkill Leaderboards give Xbox 360 players even more of a reason to jump, blast and speed their way past the competition to become the true GripShift guru.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Turbo Boost Expansion Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/13",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"More GripShift fun - 8 new race tracks, 8 new deathmatch arenas, Multiplayer Reverse Tag, 3 wacky mini-games - Penguin Bowling, Snaker, Playground - plus 18 additional music tracks. Standard Edition required."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vb1d88gY4es"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R58c0QqoI3E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/GripShift/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/gripshift/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/gripshift"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":126,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Atari"],
			"synopsis":"In 1981 Tempest introduced the gaming world to an extra-sensory visual and futuristic play experience that went beyond any video game concept ever developed. With never-before-seen QuadraScan Color video graphics, Tempest set new standards for 3D animation and challenge, and became the first arcade game to be a guaranteed hit. Play an interdimensional guardian tasked with defending the spacelanes from marauding alien monsters. The unique spinner controller merged well with the vector graphics to create a truly well known classic.<br><br>This XBLA version of the classic features a full suite of 12 achievements, support for all Xbox 360 high definition resolutions up to 1080p as well as full-screen anti-aliasing and digital surround sound.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6BTixCQ8l90"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tempest/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tempest"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":127,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Codemasters"],
			"synopsis":"Alongside the usual mix of management and fast-paced field action, the special Live Arcade edition of World of Sensible Soccer will take the game online, offering head-to-head matches, friendlies, tournaments and custom leagues. If you'd rather be a billy-no-mates, World of Sensible Soccer's offline mode features the classic twenty-season career mode, offering up the chance to play as thousands of different teams.<br><br>The Xbox 360 game includes both hi-def visuals up to 720p and the ability to switch to the original game's retro graphics.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gTqn4zCxl2U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WocqSLAzRqg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935845-sensible-world-of-soccer/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sensible-World-of-Soccer/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sensible-world-of-soccer/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sensible-world-of-soccer"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":128,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Arcade"],
			"synopsis":"In SpongeBob SquarePants: Underpants Slam!, players collect Lord of the Sea Neptune's underpants that have been spread across the sea bottom by a powerful storm current. The game features key locations from the series such as the Krusty Krab, the Flying Dutchman's ship and the depths of the new Treasure Room of Atlantis, where players will search for the bronze, silver and gold medallions. Players can gain special powers from pick-ups that allow movement at super speed, invincibility or the ability to steal pants from other players.<br><br>Game modes include single-player Quest and Time Trial Modes, as well as multiplayer Slam and Tag Modes.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xj99F6-xoKM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LcPGThlQuWE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/SpongeBob-UnderPants/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/spongebob-squarepants-underpants-slam/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/spongebob-squarepants-underpants-slam!"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":129,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SNK Playmore"],
			"synopsis":"Xbox version of the classic sidescrolling 3D shooter. The evil General Morden is back... as is his depraved plan to establish a new world order. Join Marco, Tarma, Eri and Fio on their mission to stop this madman. Little do they know of what's in-store for them lurking behind the unfolding chaos. The action builds in momentum with every level and leads to a climax of an unprecedented blaze of firepower.<br><br>This Xbox edition features Xbox Live Leaderboards as well as the same bulletting 2D action across 5 stages as seen in arcades.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e3T1qmPeb4I"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats (Arcade)",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/arcade/577440-metal-slug-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Metal-Slug-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/metal-slug-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/metal-slug-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Metal Slug Wiki",
				"url":"http://metalslug.wikia.com/wiki/Metal_Slug_3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":130,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Natsume"],
			"synopsis":"Face your enemies with a hail of bullets in Omega Five, a high-definition shooter. As you fly through entirely dangerous 3D environments in this side-scroller, enemies come at you from all sides, even the background. Grab an extra controller, choose your merc, and engage in 2-player local co-op, too.<br><br>The gameplay follows the tradition of past side-scrolling shooters: as the screen scrolls from right to left, you move your character in two dimensions, either shooting or dodging enemies and their attacks. As you proceed, you can collect both weapon upgrades for your normal attacks and chips to power-up your special attacks.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nt2zdUp6WbY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K6s4V1DmSOg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Omega-Five/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/omega-five/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/omega-five"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":131,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Backbone Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the Disney movie of the same name (TRON, 1982) Tron has players assume the role of some hapless script and are run through the game grid in various exercises. Those too young to play the arcade game can now experience it on the Xbox Live Arcade.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J9addUn6ltY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tron/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tron/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tron"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tron Wiki",
				"url":"http://tron.wikia.com/wiki/TRON_(arcade_game)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":132,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Artech Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Boogie Bunnies is the next evolution in match-3 puzzle games. Match bunnies from three different sides - left, right and from the bottom. The longer you take, the further the bunnies march to the bottom of your screen where dangerous pitfalls await. Save the bunnies by matching them quickly. Score chain combinations and watch them get their groove on. Let's get the party started.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m2jBmNHP4ig"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Boogie-Bunnies/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/boogie-bunnies/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/boogie-bunnies"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":133,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Sofia"],
			"synopsis":"A downloadable version of the master's game, Chessmaster Live allows players to connect online to players of all skill levels as well as test their skills against AI opponents. The game features five original chess variants, including the all-new Message Chess option, which will allow players to engage in a match over the course of days, weeks or even months. Players can tune their skills by competing against hundreds of AI opponents to play in ELO-ranked matches. Online, gamers can go head-to-head in matches that allow voice-chat and LIVE Vision picture display. New 3D chess sets are added inspired by luxury board designer, House of Staunton.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CCRumR-ORDw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Chessmaster-Live/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/chessmaster-live/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/chessmaster-live"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":134,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["HexaDrive", "Q Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"If you like a little style and originality in your first-person shooters, look no further than REZ. Brought to the Xbox 360 in an all-new HD incarnation, this classic game takes the genre to its most viscerally extremes. The game gets most of its luster from its incredible storyline: The information age comes to a deadly halt when the core of society's technological memory an AI unit called Eden begins to feel the strain of too much data. Struggling to keep up, the technology actually begins to question its own existence and goes into a futuristic freak out. Now, you must journey deep into the realm of 3D cyberspace in order to fix the system, a task that will require hacking codes and battling fierce creatures. Your goal is to get all the way to the system's core, but that's a journey that only the bravest and most dedicated adventurers will be able to survive. The game features an incredible array of music samples (you can actually create your own sounds and rhythms to accompany to you on your trip), a plethora of stages, and a list of modes that includes: Score Attack, Beyond, Boss Rush, and Trance Mission. In addition, there are more than 20 hidden features that can be unlocked.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gaY7cvtG1xM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HDdz21ZhZaY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats (Original)",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/dreamcast/534915-rez/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rez-HD/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rez/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rez-hd"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":135,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Void Star Creations"],
			"synopsis":"An action packed puzzle game with next-gen 3D graphics, Poker Smash is a blazing fast puzzle game with a poker twist.<br><br>In Poker Smash, players rush to clear rows of cards by arranging them into poker hands. To keep things interesting Poker Smash offers card-blasting bombs and a super slow-motion trigger for players caught in a bind.<br><br>The game features over 30 minutes of original music set against stunning visuals, and contains seven unique game modes, including: action, timed, puzzle, practice, custom playlist, split screen head-to-head and multiplayer tournaments. For the Achievement junkies, Poker Smash contains 12 Achievements with a total of 200 points, including: Score of the Gods, which requires gamers to reach 1,000,000 points; The Thinker, which requires gamers to unlock all puzzle groups; and Pack Rat, which is awarded after gamers unlock all 11 in-game themes.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Environment Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2008/04/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Pack includes 2 new table environments for action mode with original music and next-gen 3D graphics."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2008/09/03",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Pack includes 15 additional puzzles and solutions."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Environment Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2008/04/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Pack includes 2 new table environments for action mode with original music and next-gen 3D graphics."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fR5IpmvkImc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wT9KEaqtV1k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Poker-Smash/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/poker-smash/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/poker-smash"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":136,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Southend Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Commanders: Attack! is a turn-based tactical game with a combination of strategic troop placement and entertaining head-to-head warfare. Featuring a 1930's art deco look and feel, players will use missile launchers, bombers and infantry to amputate the enemies' defenses and conquer the land. Players can choose to challenge the computer AI in a 15-mission campaign across three different landscapes or battle against three friends either locally or online in four intense multiplayer modes - Versus, Team Play, Player vs. CPU or same-system Skirmish.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nvN4mt6cu1Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=seTiifExV5I"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/941958-commanders-attack-of-the-genos/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Commanders-Attack-of-the-Genos/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/commanders-attack/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/commanders-attack-of-the-genos"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":137,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Backbone Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"In Discs of Tron, players face off in a three-dimensional arena against the film's villain, Sark, as they throw discs to try to knock him off of a platform or \"derezz\" him with a disc while he counters. The game, which includes both classic and enhanced modes, gets increasingly more difficult as players progress. A player's advancement through the game includes multiple platforms of different altitudes, a barricade between the two combatants and chasers, which are secondary weapons from Sark.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zHApQ40bYYg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Discs-Of-Tron/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/discs-of-tron/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/discs-of-tron"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tron Wiki",
				"url":"http://tron.wikia.com/wiki/Discs_of_TRON"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":138,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Slick Entertainment", "Metanet Software"],
			"synopsis":"In a futuristic world of inadvertently homicidal robots, a daring ninja must use deft acrobatic skill and guts of steel to survive. N+ is a peerless action-puzzle platformer with more than 300 levels in which to hone your ninja reflexes, plus a built-in level editor for when you're hungry for more. N+ also features unique, physics-based controls, stylish graphics, unlimited lives, competitive and cooperative multiplayer, plenty of gold, and several flavors of sweet, sweet action. Running, jumping, and dying in an unpleasant-yet-comical manner has never been more fun!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Level Pack #1",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/23",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This pack is bursting with 150 Easier Single Player maps and 50 juicy co-op multiplayer maps for you to dominate. It's not easy, but it's easier."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Level Pack #2",
				"releaseDate":"2008/09/10",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This pack boasts 150 Harder Single Player levels, 50 Multiplayer Race and 25 Multiplayer Survival maps you can really sink your teeth into. Enjoy a challenge? This one's for you!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Level Pack #3",
				"releaseDate":"2008/10/22",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This pack contains a smattering of classic N levels, revisited and restyled for N+. You get 150 Single Player, 50 Multiplayer Co-op and 50 Multiplayer Race - we tried to tone down the difficulty, but they've still got plenty of bite!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OWKVcAzd0uY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/N-Plus/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/n+"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":139,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Warashi"],
			"synopsis":"A vertical shooter based on the NAOMI arcade board title (and last seen on the Dreamcast before this Xbox 360 version), featuring intense single-player shooting through realtime 3D worlds and AI-adjusted boss challenges. The game is a vertical scrolling shooter that makes use of a three button system - one button for shooting, one for releasing a bomb, and one for using an \"anchor shot\". The anchor shot allows you to capture enemies in the air and lock on to enemies on the ground. When you've captured an enemy, you enter \"capture mode\", and can move it around and release it as a special type of bomb.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D1nWXyTLR1Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Triggerheart-Exelica/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/triggerheart-exelica/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/triggerheart-exelica"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":140,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["A.C.R.O.N.Y.M. Games"],
			"synopsis":"WizKids' popular constructible strategy game comes to the videogame world with Rocketmen: Axis of Evil. In this arcade shooter, players will join the heroes of the Alliance of Free Planets in their white-knuckled, frenzied struggle to free the Solar System. Up to four players will be able to cooperatively shoot their way through multiple levels, powering up their weapons, picking up bonuses and laying waste to anything that moves.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"It Came From Uranus Expansion Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/05/14",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Saturn is in the clutches of the Legion of Terra and it's up to YOU to stop them! Continue the story with your original saved characters. New powerful guns and secondary weapons! Explore the planet Saturn in three glorious levels. Buy the exciting new expansion for the Rocketmen universe!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n9JQHt-97_I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f1nZSn_Y1_U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rocketmen-Axis-of-Evil/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rocketmen-axis-of-evil/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rocketmen-axis-of-evil"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":141,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["PomPom Games"],
			"synopsis":"Explore Bliss Island as Hoshi the Zwooph, a mystical blue creature that emits precise puffs of air to create clouds. Help Hoshi become the Bliss Island champion by winning over 25 unique challenges across nine intense levels. Better yet, challenge friends online for more competitive gameplay or focus on topping the Leaderboard charts.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0yTVUBki0EM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IIVglK99-Ko"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bliss-Island/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bliss-island/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bliss-island"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":142,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gameloft"],
			"synopsis":"An entertaining brain training program, Brain Challenge boosts brain activity and helps players develop stress-management skills thanks to a wide variety of games. A personal coach helps players develop their abilities in several areas of cognitive function, including logic, math, memory and visual thinking, in a fun and entertaining way.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K9ba_glVEjc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Brain-Challenge/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/brain-challenge/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/brain-challenge"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":143,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Slapdash Games"],
			"synopsis":"An addictive new puzzler, TiQal takes players on an epic journey to save an ancient Mayan village. Players demolish enemy block walls by matching squares of the same color and building them up to unleash massive combo points and mind-blowing power-ups. Partner with a friend over local or LIVE co-op play to rescue the village, while enjoying sumptuous graphics, pulse-pounding sound effects and an awe-inspiring musical score.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vEXatAar5qs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/TiQal/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tiqal/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tiqal"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":144,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bandai Namco Games"],
			"synopsis":"Players take on the role of a driller moving through levels of colorful blocks, avoiding the threat of being crushed by falling blocks, all while keeping their air supply from running out.<br><br>Mr. Driller Online features single player modes including Standard Driller and Quest Driller, as well as online multiplayer support for up to four players on Xbox LIVE. In online multiplayer mode, players can participate in a split screen Solo Battle, where the best score wins, or in Tag Battle, where friends team up in pairs to beat the game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A68Zp697pc0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mr-Driller-Online/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mr-driller-online/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mr-driller-online"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":145,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Treasure"],
			"synopsis":"The popular shooter comes to the Xbox Live Arcade. As pilot Shinra, players must battle their way through 18 stages, move swiftly and act rationally in a new war, a space crusade of frighteningly intense firepower and hypnotic beauty. Take control of the ship Ikaruga -- alter your energy field, evade epic maelstroms of fire and terminate enemies with a nearly limitless arsenal -- all to protect an aging, exiled people. Find calm amid the chaos and reap the rewards, in this perfect combination of beautiful, manga-style storytelling and refined, ultra-challenging arcade heroics. Developed by Treasure, Ikaruga is quick-paced shooter with strong strategy elements and two-player co-op gaming.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F1W6GBA0h8w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Perfect Play",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kIxKjmrCrS4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943282-ikaruga/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ikaruga/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ikaruga/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ikaruga"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Ikaruga Wiki",
				"url":"http://ikaruga.wikia.com/wiki/Ikaruga_(game)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":146,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Atari"],
			"synopsis":"Using vector-based, Battlezone was the first fully 3D game of all time. That alone would probably be enough to earn it a slot in the list of the Top 100 games of all time, but not only was it the fore-father of 3D, but it was also danged fun. With a unique dual-stick control system, a porthole window and wrap-around speakers to immerse you into the action, Battlezone sucked many a quarter out of our pockets in the 80s. Simple shapes made out of green lines really can be amazing.<br><br>This XBLA version of the classic features a full suite of 12 achievements, support for all Xbox 360 high definition resolutions up to 1080p as well as full-screen anti-aliasing and digital surround sound. On the multiplayer side, the game feature online multiplayer and support for the Xbox Live Camera, enabling players to watch live video of their opponents.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9_L0x8y5ROc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats (Original)",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/pc/196737-battlezone/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Battlezone/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/battlezone/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/battlezone"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Battlezone Wiki",
				"url":"http://battlezone.wikia.com/wiki/Battlezone"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":147,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Zen Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the highly popular cartoon series of the same name, \"Rocky and Bullwinkle\" on Xbox LIVE Arcade is a fast and fun party experience packed with over 100 micro-games and decked out in an authentic retro art style. All your favorite characters are coming straight out of Frostbite Falls and into your living room: Rocky, Bullwinkle, Boris, Natasha, Dudley Do-Right and many more. Plus, players with an Xbox LIVE Vision camera can control 25 of these games using fun gestures.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vDckc8Tar1c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9IxXm1kP6P8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rocky-and-Bullwinkle/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rocky-and-bullwinkle/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rocky-and-bullwinkle"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":148,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sierra"],
			"synopsis":"True to the original adventurous card game, Lost Cities transports players to exotic destinations where riveting adventures await. Before players embark on their trips they must choose how much to invest in the expedition in hopes of increasing their investment. Players then play their cards with the goal of amassing the most points and making prosperous expeditions through the various lost cities: the Himalayas, the Brazilian rain forest, the ever-shifting desert sands, ancient volcanoes and the mystifying depths of the oceans.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WhUe1eMtD5w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lost-Cities/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lost-cities/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lost-cities"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":149,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Hidden Path Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Party and trivia fun! Even if trivia isn't your thing, the first trivia and party game to hit Xbox Live Arcade is one in which players can win by making educated guesses, playing the odds or just knowing the interests of other players, whether they are local or online. Break out the Big Button Pad controllers or play couch vs. couch on Xbox LIVE for a trivia party extravaganza.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Question Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/02",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Energize your Wits & Wagers experience with 280 new questions and fun facts. Purchase this pack for use in all local and selected online games. Online, packs are automatically used if owned by all participants in a game."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qmCFvMs9YGc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wits-and-Wagers/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wits-and-wagers/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wits-wagers"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":150,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Vivendi Games"],
			"synopsis":"Re-envisioned for an even more action-packed arcade shooter experience, Assault Heroes 2 expands its horizons into outer space. New features also include hi-jackable enemy vehicles, more levels and enhanced on-foot and co-operative gameplay modes. Whether attacking on foot or piloting all-new spacecraft, players will enjoy optimum mobility in the most dangerous situations.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jeVBQLd-S6Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pOwaWPrl_PM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AeneO3oqln4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aMivlnVf_84"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Assault-Heroes-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/assault-heroes-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/assault-heroes-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":151,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Hothead Games"],
			"synopsis":"An RPG-adventure game set in a highly stylized 1920s universe filled with bizarre characters, outrageous combat and adult humor. The game is based on the characters and universe of the popular videogame-oriented web comic Penny Arcade.<br><br>On the Rain-Slick Precipice of Darkness: Episode One is the first title in the downloadable series",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gWKQ4CyhZxk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nIONWMp4ebQ&index=4&list=PLwE_FjQpKcvGBYZpkRena00xxzWcssfq9"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943006-penny-arcade-adventures-episode-one/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Penny-Arcade-Episode-1/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/penny-arcade/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/penny-arcade-adventures-episode-one"
			},
			{
				"type":"Web Comic",
				"site":"Penny Arcade",
				"url":"http://www.penny-arcade.com/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":152,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Absolutist"],
			"synopsis":"Experience the excitement of the world's hottest number game sensation. Buku Sudoku takes the pen-and-paper puzzler high-tech with HD graphics, helpful tutorials, single- and multiplayer game modes, multiple grid sizes, and the option to display hints, highlight errors, undo moves, and even solve puzzles. 1,200 puzzles give you plenty of opportunity to challenge your own brain, play cooperatively with friends, race head-to-head to see who can complete a board first, or compete in the new battle mode, where completing a line, row, or square will remove numbers from your opponent's board. It's Sudoku however you like to play it.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2008/06/04",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/16",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2008/09/10",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 4",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/17",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 5",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/11",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 6",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/20",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 7",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/09",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 8",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/09",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 9",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/09",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 10",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/09",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 11",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/03",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 12",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/03",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 13",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/03",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 14",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/14",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":15,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 15",
				"releaseDate":"2010/05/26",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":16,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 16",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/14",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":17,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 17",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/18",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":18,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 18",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/29",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			},
			{
				"id":19,
				"name":"Puzzle Pack 19",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/19",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Extend your Buku Sudoku experience with 1200 new Sudoku puzzles!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uFZyu1KVemY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Buku-Sudoku/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/buku-sudoku/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/buku-sudoku"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":153,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Stainless Games"],
			"synopsis":"An endlessly addictive multiplayer variation of block-busting/ball-bouncing games such as Pong, Warlords became a classic with its simple and challenging four square structure. Each competitor in the game is in charge of defending a castle (represented as a wall of bricks at each corner of the TV screen) from volleying fireball attacks let loose by a war dragon. Your bounce shield will send the fireball hurtling at your foes based on the angle of incident and speed of deflection, and by holding down the game button, you can \"catch\" the fireball to aim it where you want to attack and release it at super-speed. The game becomes heated the more you play, but the real fun is when other players take up arms in multiplayer play! Deflect the attacks as best you can as more and more fireballs appear and don't let any one of your three crafty opponents get the best of you -- some might even strike up an alliance with one castle to double up against their most hated rival, but don't forget that only one may stand at the end!<br><br>This XBLA version of the classic features a full suite of 12 achievements, support for all Xbox 360 high definition resolutions up to 1080p as well as full-screen anti-aliasing and digital surround sound. On the multiplayer side, the game feature online multiplayer and support for the Xbox Live Camera, enabling players to watch live video of their opponents.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1XrCU3zcaiM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Warlords/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/warlords/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/warlords"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":154,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Artech Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Take control of the gun turret on an AI-driven spaceship aiming the reticule to vaporize waves of enemies. Featuring pick-up-and-play game play with optional co-operative multiplayer, the user is thrust into epic space battles in the ultimate struggle to survive.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W5wTjlXc9ss"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BYaMhYvMqJE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Aces-of-the-Galaxy/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/aces-of-the-galaxy/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/aces-of-the-galaxy"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":155,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Spidermonk"],
			"synopsis":"Roogoo tasks players with guiding meteors in the form of shaped blocks though a series of rotating disks as a means of saving the planet Roo and the entire Roogoo race. If aligned correctly, the disks allow the blocks to reach the ground and scores are awarded. However, it's not as easy as simply rotating the disks to form a neat tunnel. Various obstacles and enemies will impede the blocks' transit and with the flow of meteor blocks steadily increasing as the game progresses, players will have to think on their feet to save the Roogoo and rack up seriously high scores.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IZURthcpDSY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ti7bIapYQXs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Roogoo/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/roogoo/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/roogoo"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":156,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Voltex"],
			"synopsis":"Hop along with Frogger 2 as you travel through more than fifteen challenging levels filled with new enemies and obstacles. Each of the five exotic environments provides a new set of challenges, but beware of the bosses that try to thwart your progress. Compete with up to four friends in two different online multiplayer modes, and hop your way to victory.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fa1ovpiNeHk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Frogger-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/frogger-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/frogger-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":157,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Backbone Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Reviving the classic arcade shooter franchise (which was previously followed up in the heavy-gunning game known as Mercs), Wolf of the Battlefield: Commando 3 is a co-operative shooter, which sees up to three players, either online or offline, blasting the evil Zalestad soldiers with a range of rocket launchers, grenades and shotguns. At the player's disposal is a huge arsenal of weaponry, controllable vehicles, and a rag-tag group of specialized soldiers, each with their own unique characteristics. Thankfully, players aren't alone in this mission, as up to three players can enjoy the classic arcade-style experience together on a single console or online.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8JnypT3j7Fk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZBmRD4gvh78"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943724-wolf-of-the-battlefield-commando-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wolf-of-the-Battlefield-Commando-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wotb-commando-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wolf-of-the-battlefield-commando-3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":158,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Frozen Codebase"],
			"synopsis":"You are a force of nature. Move and manipulate Mother Nature to your design. The world is yours to control and destroy using forces of nature of your choosing. Each scenario offers unique locations, challenges and goals that cause the player to use the forces of nature in different ways.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Ueo2yih7U4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Elements-of-Destruction/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/elements-of-destruction/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/elements-of-destruction"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":159,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["WildTangent"],
			"synopsis":"Say, how big does a lobster get? How fast can a turtle swim? Take a deep sea dive into a colorful world with 3D characters in jaw-dropping environments. Swim alongside creatures like: Bannerfish, Banded Shrimp, Purple Tang, Barracuda, and more! The old professor needs your photographs to help further his research. Prove to the world that fish have personality too! Enjoy in-game tutorials, keep logs, search for special items, and receive stars. Print your priceless photos and share with friends. It's an exciting, inviting world inside the Sea.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q_yE578tJvw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b4_x0LvwtAQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945955-sea-life-safari/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sealife-Safari/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sealife-safari/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sea-life-safari"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":160,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Stainless Games"],
			"synopsis":"The internet video phenomenon about cute, cuddly, giggly, and adorable animals who are often gruesomely shredded and skewered in ultra-violent displays of comedic anarchy. Now, it's a videogame for multiple consoles, so you can enjoy not only watching the whole gang get torn from limb to limb, you can be a part of it!<br><br>Happy Tree Friends False Alarm is an action-puzzle game with a unique physics-based reactive environment. The game enables players to control one of three characters: Flippy the emotionally tattered war-torn bear, Lumpy the dim-witted blue moose, and Handy the amputee beaver carpenter always eager to lend a helping limb. Using resources such as concrete, ice, gasoline, and nitroglycerin to augment the dynamic 3D environments, your goal is to save the Happy Tree Friends from hilarious disaster situations and their own bad luck. Play in 10 diverse levels designed exclusively for the Happy Tree Friends False Alarm game including mine shafts, candy factories and a museum, all of which are filled with outrageous outcomes and plenty of accidental mayhem!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pGYBWaU7THQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9MJ9e_QEly4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Happy-Tree-Friends/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/happy-tree-friends-false-alarm/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/happy-tree-friends-false-alarm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Happy Tree Friends Wiki",
				"url":"http://happytreefriends.wikia.com/wiki/Happy_Tree_Friends:_False_Alarm_(videogame)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":161,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Playful Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Developed by Playful Entertainment, Ticket to Ride challenges players to plan cross-country rail routes across North America and visit all the city stops in-between, racking up points as they race to reach the most destinations. The game supports play with up to five people on Xbox Live or four people on the same console and supports the Xbox LIVE Vision Cam for hours of family-friendly fun.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Europe",
				"releaseDate":"2008/08/01",
				"achievements":30,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Ticket to Ride Europe will include a new map (Europe) as well as add new gameplay elements to the base game."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"USA 1910",
				"releaseDate":"2008/09/17",
				"achievements":20,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Ticket to Ride USA 1910 uses the North America map from the base game and adds new Destination Tickets as well as a new Bonus Card. This expansion leverages this new content into three new game types for players to enjoy: 1910, Big Cities and Mega Game."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WeZWv_9-BUs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ticket-to-Ride/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ticket-to-ride/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ticket-to-ride"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":162,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Project Soul"],
			"synopsis":"The highest rated console fighting game ever is back again for a new generation! Sharpen your blades and relive old grudges against classic adversaries in high definition. Prove your mettle against the world with a variety of leaderboards spanning every character and mode. Match your wits and fighting instincts in Arcade, Training and Survival modes, or challenge a friend in local-play Versus mode.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tXul0190UpA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945861-soulcalibur/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/SoulCalibur/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/soul-calibur-arcade/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/soulcalibur"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"SoulCalibur Wiki",
				"url":"http://soulcalibur.wikia.com/wiki/Soul_Calibur_(game)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":163,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Housemarque"],
			"synopsis":"Hit the sweet spot with Golf: Tee It Up! Pick up and play a few quick holes on your own or compete with friends in a full 18-hole multiplayer tournament. With zany customizable characters, both beginners and experienced golfers can easily join the fun on beautiful panoramic and challenging courses. Need that special touch for your hacked shot? With the unique Focus feature, read the green or control the ball's spin in flight to achieve amazing precision! A huge combination of game modes awaits including stroke, cup, or match play with local or multiplayer modes over Xbox LIVE.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Desert Course",
				"releaseDate":"2008/09/03",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Tee it up on an exquisite desert oasis course set against incredible mountain views, treacherous ravines, and luxurious casinos. The Desert Course is a must play for all golfers!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Clothing Pack #1",
				"releaseDate":"2008/09/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Express your own style. Grab the Hip Hop themed outfit for male golfers and Goth style outfit for female golfers before they're all gone!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Clothing Pack #2",
				"releaseDate":"2008/09/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Need a fresh look on the green? Download the new Kung Fu set for male golfers and the Western-themed set for female golfers now!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NiK8fWJALR8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Golf-Tee-It-Up/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/golf-tee-it-up/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/golf-tee-it-up!"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":164,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Torpex Games"],
			"synopsis":"Cooperative gameplay is redefined in the fast-paced and unique Schizoid! Control red and blue ships, ramming them into enemies of the same color to destroy them. But be careful, because if you hit the opposite color, you will be destroyed. Quick thinking and quicker reflexes help you seize victory, but sharp teamwork provides the best chance of earning gold medals along the way. Schizoid offers more than 120 levels of challenge, playable in either single-player or co-op mode, plus the brain-melting Uberschizoid hardcore mode, in which one player controls both ships!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NcxGZQs6mkQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Schizoid/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/schizoid/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/schizoid"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":165,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Voltex"],
			"synopsis":"Prepare for a true crossword challenge as you test your skills in Coffeetime Crosswords. Try for the high score as you progress through more than 150 crosswords developed by Penny Press. Play together with a friend in co-op mode and help each other solve the crosswords. Gather your wits, prepare yourself to be entertained, and challenge your crossword prowess.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R5DhOUpySo4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Coffeetime-Crosswords/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/coffeetime-crosswords/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/coffeetime-crosswords"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":166,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Yuke's Media Creations"],
			"synopsis":"Relive the good old days of playgrounds and coin-ops! Double D Dodgeball turns the classic childhood sport into a fast-paced, retro arcade experience. With frenetic eight person multiplayer action, grab seven of your friends and go four-on-four via Xbox LIVE to see which team has the ultimate bragging rights. Choose between a host of arcade-themed characters each with their own unique abilities. Select either East or West rule sets, switch up the playing surfaces, change the ball type, and more. No need to risk injury, just blast your friends from the comfort of your couch.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ljqAZB-QAAA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Double-D-Dodgeball/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/double-d-dodgeball/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/double-d-dodgeball"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":167,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"If you've ever wanted to test your fantasy team against others in the Madden NFL franchise, EA Sports Fantasy Football now gives you the opportunity. Players designate which fantasy team will be imported into Madden NFL 09. This fantasy team is a fully-functional created team and can be played in all areas available to created teams, including online head-to-head games, providing the ultimate football gaming experience.<br><br>Based on the web-based service previously available to PC users, gamers will have the ability to download the EA Sports Fantasy Football Live Draft Tracker application and experience a fantasy draft that includes all of the fanfare and presentation of an authentic professional football draft. The days of paper draft boards are over and gamers can view video clips and hear the EA Experts team provide commentary on top players. Moreover, gamers will be able to track their EA Sports Fantasy Football teams and leagues through the EA Sports Fantasy Football Live Score Tracker app. The fantasy scores can be viewed in two ways: full screen mode with complete rosters and details or picture-in-picture mode which allows gamers to keep an eye on scoring updates while watching live football action.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Fantasy Football Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y0bfmkKqYkk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Live-Draft-Tracker/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/live-draft-tracker/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":168,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Backbone Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"1942: Joint Strike takes inspiration and influence from the 194X series of Capcom vertical shooters. The art, sound and gameplay give the players hints of the classic historical shoot-em-up franchise, but this entry stands out as its own entry in the franchise and utilizes a full 3D engine along the traditional 2D top-down perspective.<br><br>The action takes place during an alternate timeline of World War II. Locales, vehicles and weapons have the same look and feel of the classic battleships and planes, but the battles over the Pacific were never this hot or this insane -- your single fighter will turn the tides of history, but only if you survive!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IG23dqcVq18"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945395-1942-joint-strike/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/1942-Joint-Strike/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/1942-joint-strike/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/1942-joint-strike"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":169,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Little Boy Games"],
			"synopsis":"Take on DJ Scruffy and his Beatniks in the \"All City Break Steady Tournament\". The debut title from independent developer Little Boy Games, Go! Go! Break Steady combines music breakdancing and puzzle gameplay for crazy block-rocking play beats. Break it down in all 30 rounds of the Break Steady Tournament. Play solo, cooperate with friends, or challenge the world with your rhythm and smarts!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RqG9es6ZSek"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NSPXKVK6IVo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Go-Go-Break-Steady/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/go-go-break-steady/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/go!-go!-break-steady"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":170,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bizarre Creations"],
			"synopsis":"Following the amazing success of the 2005 blockbuster Xbox LIVE Arcade launch title Geometry Wars: Retro Evolved, Bizarre Creations thrusts players back into the pilot's seat and introduces Geometry Wars: Retro Evolved 2. Featuring all the signature eye-popping visuals, lightning-quick action and mesmerizing music that fans have come to know and love, gamers can now test their skills and prove their prowess in up to six different gameplay modes. Providing a complete package, Geometry Wars: Retro Evolved 2 offers an all-new adrenaline rush to gamers of all shapes and sizes with the opportunity to compete either head-to-head, or blast enemies cooperatively with up to four players in multiplayer pandemonium.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AL2rIVuwhmQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zdL-l10XJ68"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/950901-geometry-wars-retro-evolved-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Geometry-Wars-Evolved-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/geometry-wars-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/geometry-wars-retro-evolved-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":171,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Number None Inc."],
			"synopsis":"Braid is a platformer/puzzle game with unique elements that aim to provide a mind-expanding, filler-free experience. The player journeys across seven worlds to rescue a princess; in each world, time behaves in its own peculiar way. The player must cleverly manipulate the flow of time to solve puzzles.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uqtSKkyJgFM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WCyWDIUQJSY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943284-braid/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Braid/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/braid/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/braid"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Braid Wiki",
				"url":"http://braid.wikia.com/wiki/Braid_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":172,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["GRIN"],
			"synopsis":"Classic side-scrolling gameplay is reporting back for duty with Bionic Commando Rearmed, a remake of the classic NES game. 20 years after the 8-bit classic was released, Bionic Commando Rearmed recreates the world of the original with a complete \"2.5D\" visual revamp. Bionic Commando Rearmed preserves the original's mix of swinging and shooting in an intense 2D side-scroller, all to the tune of a brand-new soundtrack based on the classic 8-bit music from the NES masterpiece.<br><br>But Rearmed is far more than just a remake - it features all-new modes such as the 2-player co-op play and also a special combat multiplayer mode, smarter enemy AI, new bionic arm abilities, new weapons, bigger bosses and online rankings. Faithfully sticking to the original story, Bionic Commando Rearmed tells the story of Nathan \"R.A.D.\" Spencer's first mission, sent in to retrieve captured agent Super Joe from the hands of the Imperials. Fans of the original story can expect to see all the characters from the NES version, as well as the memorable moments that made the title so popular with fans.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ARysBx2PrQ8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uBwMhCEUhBY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944602-bionic-commando-rearmed/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bionic-Commando-Rearmed/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bionic-commando-rearmed/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bionic-commando-rearmed"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":173,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Lionhead Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Fable II Pub Games includes three casino-style games -- Spinnerbox, Fortune's Tower, and Keystone. The download also includes a Shell, which is a tutorial of all three games. Each game has multiple variants, plus the ability to earn and transfer gold and unique items to your character in Fable II. You'll also get access to minigames, leaderboards, achievements, and all the fun of these backroom games of chance!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9YPhKK6A_ts"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/951203-fable-ii-pub-games/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fable-2-Pub-Games/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fable-2-pub-games/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fable-ii-pub-games"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Fable Wiki",
				"url":"http://fable.wikia.com/wiki/Fable_II_Pub_Games"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":174,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Namco"],
			"synopsis":"The arcade shooter Galaga has captivated players all over the world, and now the legend lives on with Galaga Legions. Featuring table-turning game dynamics, updated graphics and vast waves of ferocious enemies, Galaga Legions was created by the same team that developed the best-selling Pac-Man Championship Edition for Xbox Live Arcade.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wacotRdCLxs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cGRvbBT6r2A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Galaga-Legions/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/galaga-legions/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/galaga-legions"
			},]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":175,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["The Behemoth"],
			"synopsis":"This four player RPG adventure will let you hack, slash, and smash your way to victory. Featuring hand-drawn characters, Castle Crashers delivers unique hi-res illustrated visuals and intense gameplay action. Play with up to three friends and discover mind-boggling magic and mystery in the amazing world created just for you!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JUkcCHl-fLA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BsLHvg93bX4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AfcremAuaTs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/934458-castle-crashers/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Castle-Crashers/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/castle-crashers/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/castle-crashers"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Castlepedia",
				"url":"http://castlewiki.castlecrashers.com/Castle_Crashers"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Castle Crashers Wiki",
				"url":"http://castlecrashers.wikia.com/wiki/Castle_Crashers"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Behemoth Wiki",
				"url":"http://thebehemoth.wikia.com/wiki/Castle_Crashers"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":176,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"If you've ever wanted to test your fantasy team against others in the Madden NFL franchise, EA Sports Fantasy Football now gives you the opportunity. Players designate which fantasy team will be imported into Madden NFL 09. This fantasy team is a fully-functional created team and can be played in all areas available to created teams, including online head-to-head games, providing the ultimate football gaming experience.<br><br>Based on the web-based service previously available to PC users, gamers will have the ability to download the EA Sports Fantasy Football Live Draft Tracker application and experience a fantasy draft that includes all of the fanfare and presentation of an authentic professional football draft. The days of paper draft boards are over and gamers can view video clips and hear the EA Experts team provide commentary on top players. Moreover, gamers will be able to track their EA Sports Fantasy Football teams and leagues through the EA Sports Fantasy Football Live Score Tracker app. The fantasy scores can be viewed in two ways: full screen mode with complete rosters and details or picture-in-picture mode which allows gamers to keep an eye on scoring updates while watching live football action.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Fantasy Football Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y0bfmkKqYkk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Live-Score-Tracker/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/live-score-tracker/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":177,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sierra"],
			"synopsis":"A downloadable version of the classic card game, Gin Rummy features a number of different modes, including classic, 100, Hollywood, three-hand and Oklahoma varieties. Players will need to strategically select the right cards to complete combinations of sets and runs, minimizing the risk of getting caught with a poor hand in all 6 of the challenging variations of the game. Knock out your opponent with high scores and bonus points, and video chat with players from around the world for endless hours of casual card game fun.<br><br>This version of Gin Rummy isn't just a deck of cards... 6 Popular Game Modes come packed in the game including, Classic Gin Rummy, Speed Gin Rummy, Oklahoma Gin, Hollywood Gin, Three-Hand Gin. You can event customize your own rules. And with 4 player multiplayer matches and Xbox LIVE Vision support, you'll never go back to the normal card game again.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Theme Deck",
				"releaseDate":"2008/09/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download 7 additional Gin Rummy game skins featuring themed backgrounds, serene animated graphics, and 3 all-new card decks to play with! \"Go Gin\" in style and customize your game today!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZROEcG4cjlc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Gin-Rummy/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/gin-rummy/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/gin-rummy"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":178,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blazing Lizard"],
			"synopsis":"The first game in the Pirates vs. Ninjas series allows up to 8 players to choose from 5 unique teams and compete against one another in the ultimate sport of champions - Dodgeball. However, this is no ordinary Dodgeball game. Teams aren't restricted to one side of the court, instead they roam freely around 6 detailed arenas. In addition, characters are equipped with combat moves and special abilities to deliver a more action-packed experience than could ever be found on the playground.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3-B8ZYS_OuE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pirates-vs-Ninjas-Dodgeball/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pirates-vs-ninjas-dodgeball/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pirates-vs-ninjas-dodgeball"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":179,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["CrunchTime Games"],
			"synopsis":"Shred Nebula combines the best elements of arcade space-shooter action with free-roaming exploration and multiplayer excitement. Pilot the experimental R.I.P. Rocket through the galaxy in search of the Lost Expeditions... no ship has ever returned from the vastness of interstellar space!<br><br>This top-down, fast-paced ship-combat game features three loaded modes of play-Adventure, Score Attack, and Multiplayer. Play co-op with your friends, or go head-to-head in a deathmatch dogfight. No one knows what lies in the center of the galaxy. Will you be the first to discover the secrets of the gravitational region known as The Shred and make it home alive?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eQ4rkhnwKXs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dICz7T9_zX0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Shred-Nebula/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/shred-nebula/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/shred-nebula"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":180,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Large Animal", "21-6 Productions"],
			"synopsis":"A twist on a classic sport, RocketBowl offers a 50' style retro-futuristic vibe, out-of-this-world courses and rocket-powered bowling balls. Players will compete in tournaments, challenge their friends in multiplayer, test their bowling skills and more!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qjkZFnSwOzU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/RocketBowl/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rocketbowl/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rocketbowl"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":181,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SNK"],
			"synopsis":"The classic fighting game Samurai Shodown II comes to Xbox Live Arcade in all its action-packed glory! Haohmaru is attacked by a sinister assailant. This would-be assassin has been clearly manipulated by an evil force, and promises with his last breath to own Haohmaru's soul. Haohmaru's mentor and fencing master insists that Haohmaru stay away from the evil forces and avoid confrontation, but this he cannot do. The two share a few drinks to celebrate their reunion after a long separation, but at dawn, Haohmaru slips out unannounced to embark on his journey. An audacious smile plays on his lips.<br><br>You are the supreme samurai warrior. As such, you must face demons from Hell who unleash their fury on you through an assortment of special moves and unique abilities. Samurai Shodown 2 lets you be the supreme samurai, but do you have the ability?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5jaZRM4XAK4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943402-samurai-shodown-ii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Samurai-Shodown-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/samurai-showdown-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/samurai-shodown-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"SNK Wiki",
				"url":"http://snk.wikia.com/wiki/Samurai_Shodown_II"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":182,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rubicon Development"],
			"synopsis":"Experience a new kind of shogi, Japan's top board game, which encourages complex tactical play and strategic sacrifices. Set in an elegant Japanese room, this beautifully rendered game features 16 challenging artificial intelligence opponents as well as an online multiplayer mode. For beginners, Shotest Shogi on Xbox LIVE Arcade also offers an advanced tutorial that guides and tests players as they progress through the game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i3na6Nz7uhU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NTkGCNb5GHk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-ILjAYH9NSg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Shotest-Shogi/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/shotest-shogi"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":183,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["TikGames"],
			"synopsis":"It's dominos with all the bells and whistles in Domino Master. Play solo or against friends and family in any of five exciting game variations including Mexican Train, All 3's, All 5's, Straight Dominos, or Bergen. See if you have what it takes to move up the ranks and score the coveted spot at the top of the Leaderboards or grab the exciting achievements in this great family game sure to please all ages.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Bone Slammin'",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Domino Master goes hip hop, mixing classic with cool. Check out five new backgrounds and three new Dominos sets."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Chillin'",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Domino Master puts the freeze on. Shiver with five new backgrounds and three frosty bone sets."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Baseball",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Baseball Themed Backgrounds for the playfields + new sports-themed music."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Basketball",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Basketball Themed Backgrounds for the playfields + new sports-themed music."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Rap",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Music Themed Backgrounds for the playfields + gold dominoes + new music."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Football",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Football Themed Backgrounds for the playfields + new sports-themed music."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oIFpumUpb7Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Domino-Master/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/domino-master/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/domino-master"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":184,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sprout Games"],
			"synopsis":"In Feeding Frenzy 2, you start as a tiny fish striving for ocean supremacy in a sea full of predators. Eat your way to the top of the food chain, from tiny butterfly fish to a great white shark. A new storyline finds the ocean in chaos, with some fish species missing and others out of place. Assume the role of six different fish on your mission to discover the cause of the problem and defeat it in order to save the sea. A wide range of new creatures (both friendly and unfriendly), power-ups, super abilities and food provide surprises around every coral.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DrrcvsFXJHo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UaXZD19QWv4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Feeding-Frenzy-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/feeding-frenzy-2-shipwreck-showdown/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/feeding-frenzy-2-shipwreck-showdown"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":185,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["3D Realms"],
			"synopsis":"Note: Atomic Edition is included in this version.<br><br>Duke Nukem on Xbox 360? Bring it on, baby. In this classic game, you assume the role of Duke Nukem, arguably the most recognized and most beloved character in the 3d game genre! Travel in deserts, duke it out in movie theaters, and toughen it up (in all senses) in the red light districts! Shoot, blow up, shrink, or freeze your enemies, and bring them their ultimate destruction!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NExBO-QOdIU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0fPHkpkeABQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Speedrun (Original Game - 0:12:43)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RxdUFOKG3r4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944795-duke-nukem-3d/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Duke-Nukem-3D/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/duke-nukem-3d/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/duke-nukem-3d"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Duke Nukem Wiki",
				"url":"http://dukenukem.wikia.com/wiki/Duke_Nukem_3D"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":186,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Capcom", "Inti Creates"],
			"synopsis":"This latest Mega Man title brings the series back to its old school roots with retro action platforming gameplay and classic 8-bit NES-style graphics and sound. Relive the Mega Man experience with classically inspired bosses, each with their own unique weapons and weaknesses.<br><br>The story of Mega Man begins in the year 200X, as the advanced science of the era has created industrial robots that co-exist with humans. However, an evil genius, Dr. Wily, plots for world domination and creates his own robot army to take over mankind. Luckily for humanity, Dr. Light outfits one of his domestic robots \"Rock\" to fight Dr. Wily's creations. Mega Man is born.<br><br>Set after the events of Mega Man 8, multiple riots have sprung up all over the world. Whilst many people suspect that this is another plot from Dr. Wily, Dr. Light is stunned to recognize that some of the robots rioting on the TV screen are his own creations. Even more stunning, Dr. Wily appears on television to proclaim that Dr. Light is the evil mastermind behind these latest catastrophic incidents and it's up to Mega Man to clear his creator's name!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Proto Man mode",
				"releaseDate":"2008/10/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Play the game as Proto Man. You can use the shield while jumping. Some of Proto Man's abilities may differ from Mega Man's. There is no story for Proto Man. Not compatible with Leaderboards, Achievements, or Challenges."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Endless attack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/10/08",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Test your skills on a stage without end. Try to break the record for getting the farthest.Results will be displayed in the Leaderboards. Not compatible with Achievements or Challenges."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Special stage",
				"releaseDate":"2008/10/22",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Gives you another Time Attack Stage to try, including a new Boss at the end!Results will be displayed in the Leaderboards. Not compatible with Achievements or Challenges."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Hero mode",
				"releaseDate":"2008/10/22",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Play the game with a more difficult level of enemy distribution. Not compatible with Leaderboards, Achievements, or Challenges."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Superhero mode",
				"releaseDate":"2008/10/22",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Play the game with a super difficult level of enemy distribution. Not compatible with Leaderboards, Achievements, or Challenges."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zsgtDJmlqFc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mOVBhVKhdr8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Speedrun (0:32:56)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JpZSdvRPcG4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/950952-mega-man-9/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mega-Man-9/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mega-man-9/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mega-man-9"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Megaman Wiki",
				"url":"http://megaman.wikia.com/wiki/Mega_Man_9"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":187,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Third Wave"],
			"synopsis":"Imagine a planet dedicated just to the art of war. War World throws players directly into combat on the battlefield of a war-torn planet. This third-person shooter combines both single-player and multiplayer into one action-packed downloadable game. Control one of 10 different Mechanoids, each with special abilities, and wreak havoc throughout the 100-level single-player campaign. The game boasts four multiplayer game modes for up to eight players (Capture the Flag, Bomb Assault, Death Match, and Team Death Match).",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B-sfQHK5FL4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/War-World/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/war-world"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":188,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Voltex"],
			"synopsis":"Feel the rhythm in Beat'n Groovy as the pulse of the music moves you and the energy of competition drives you to get the high score. Play as one of seven characters through a collection of music that spans many different genres such as electronic, instrumental, and pop. Use your Xbox Live Vision camera to interact with the game seamlessly as you flow with the beat in Xbox Live Vision mode. Challenge a friend in local VS Mode or take on the world via Xbox Live.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nRgCRhubrj8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Beatn-Groovy/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/beatn-groovy/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/beatn-groovy"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":189,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["2K Sports"],
			"synopsis":"In MLB Stickball, gamers can buy and collect packs of Topps Big Head major league baseball cards. Each time a pack is opened, those players are unlocked and added to each major league team to play! Part of the fun of stickball is the custom rules for each city, just like the rules kids create when they play in their own neighborhoods! MLB Stickball can be played on the streets of a number of big cities, including New York, San Francisco, and Boston. In addition to scoring runs in the stickball game itself, there will be objects scattered throughout each environment that serve as targets or hazards for the batter. If you smack the ball off the fire hydrant and get it to spray water into the street, your team will be richly rewarded; break a window, though, and youre out!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cAAwOJLpIDg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MLB-Stickball/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mlb-stickball/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mlb-stickball"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":190,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FromSoftware"],
			"synopsis":"Experience the Tenchu universe like never before in Shadow Assault Tenchu! Play single-player or with up to three other players in unique Japanese-themed environments as you employ stealth and strategy in an effort to take out your enemies.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bYvaGR7HpAE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RKfoHiqZbI4&list=PLO8Vchj9SjzyEsu0JXJjHdLGmfSmTW15N&index=4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Shadow-AssaultTenchu/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/shadow-assault-tenchu/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/shadow-assault--tenchu-"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tenchu Wiki",
				"url":"http://tenchu.wikia.com/wiki/Shadow_Assault:_Tenchu"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":191,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Certain Affinity"],
			"synopsis":"Age of Booty is a casual , real-time multiplayer strategy game that puts players at the helm of their own pirate ship with the goal of sending your enemies to the briny deep, and looting and capturing towns for your pirate faction.<br><br>In the game, players team up with other online players or AI-controlled pirate ships to raid, pillage, sink, and destroy their way to dominance on the high seas. Spoils of war and booty are used to upgrade and customize pirate ships to make them even more deadly as players take on 25 unique challenges and seven of the most devious Pirate Alliances on the high seas. Gain notoriety and fame by climbing the online leader boards. Create and share custom maps using the intuitive map creation system",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x3VLiBjXjgc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7apAn-D9Zvk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945392-age-of-booty/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Age-of-Booty/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/age-of-booty/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/age-of-booty"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":192,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ultizen Games"],
			"synopsis":"In this 32-level game, the player guides a mouse-a gastronomist (a connoisseur of fine food) -through a vibrantly-colored maze, attempting to grab and eat food, run, dodge and score, depending on the level. On a trip seeking the legendary gourmet, the player meets many challenges and battles against his opponents until he finally enters the place where the gourmet is found. To win the game, the player must overcome the gourmet's guards to find out who the gourmet is.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pKSU_CBg1-U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/CrazyMouse/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/crazy-mouse/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/crazy-mouse"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":193,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Valve"],
			"synopsis":"Portal: Still Alive features the full award-winning Portal single-player game from Valve plus a new challenge mode.<br><br>A unique take on puzzle gameplay by the makers of Half-Life. Portal is unique that changes how players approach, manipulate, and surmise the possibilities in a given environment in a manner similar to how the Gravity Gun changed our approach to how an object may be leveraged in any given situation. Solve physical puzzles and challenges by opening portals to maneuvering objects, and yourself, through space.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tGNR3bIOTno"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yRbqTbkViY4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/950903-portal-still-alive/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Portal-Still-Alive/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/portal-still-alive/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/portal-still-alive"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Portal Wiki",
				"url":"http://theportalwiki.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Half-Life Wiki",
				"url":"http://half-life.wikia.com/wiki/Portal"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":194,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Games"],
			"synopsis":"Join Mr. Foxworthy's class and take the Are You Smarter Than A 5th Grader? trivia game where every question is based on grade school curriculum and the answers are, well... elementary. This Xbox Live Arcade version of the hit show features over 6,000 grade school question across 21 subjects as well as multiplayer for your friends on the couch or your online rivals from all across the globe.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VSaMUNK_KVw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Are-You-Smarter-than-a-5th-Grader/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/are-you-smarter-than-a-5th-grader/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/are-you-smarter-than-a-5th-grader-make-the-grade"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":195,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Hothead Games"],
			"synopsis":"The madcap Penny Arcade experience continues in Episode Two of the RPG-adventure game series Penny Arcade Adventures: On the Rain-Slick Precipice of Darkness! Jump right in with a fresh character and new customization options or carry over your look and stats from Episode One. Plus, there are more puzzles, areas to explore, levels to gain, and new difficulty settings to make the journey more insane than ever before. Rejoin Gabe and Tycho to go crazy with a whole new episode, moving ever closer to solve the mystery in the heart of New Arcadia. Your hoe awaits!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LetJQxt5zms"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w_a9X3kAA5k"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/952841-penny-arcade-adventures-episode-two/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Penny-Arcade-Episode-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/penny-arcade-episode-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/penny-arcade-adventures-episode-two"
			},
			{
				"type":"Web Comic",
				"site":"Penny Arcade",
				"url":"http://www.penny-arcade.com/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":196,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Isopod Labs", "Luxoflux Corp."],
			"synopsis":"Vigilante 8: Arcade is a brand new re-imagining of the original themes and gameplay, engineered from the ground up for today's hardware by the original founders of Luxoflux and V8 developers. Players will rediscover the joys of weapon-based off-road car mayhem on five newly-designed, highly interactive arenas that players can demolish in eight highly varied '70s vehicles. In addition to local split-screen mode, multiple players will be able take their car-crushing skills online, competing and/or teaming up with other V8 players the world over!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"High Octane Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/04",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Rev up with 3 new crazy cars and 2 never-before-seen arenas in this groovy pack! Grab the Strider buggy (Sheila), Towmaster tow truck (Houston), and the Groundhog 6-wheel armored car (Loki), each with its own ultra cool special weapon. You also get a tricked-out Stunt Track arena and an explosive miniature Garage environment - both fine-tuned for some high octane multiplayer action!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7nnFe9-YZ4w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6hEWclwx_KE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vEHuiQCG5NM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Vigilante-8-Arcade/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/vigilante-8-arcade/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/vigilante-8-arcade"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Vigilante 8 Wiki",
				"url":"http://vigilante8.wikia.com/wiki/Vigilante_8:_Arcade"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":197,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["NinjaBee"],
			"synopsis":"A Kingdom for Keflings puts players in the shoes of a giant who has the ability to design and construct an intricate city for the local Keflings. Each giant starts out with a small handful (literally!) of helpful Keflings who follow the giant's every command. These Keflings can be trained to become lumberjacks, miners, transporters, sheep shearers, scholars, and various other professions as they help build the kingdom from the ground up.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Kingdom Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/09",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This Kingdom Pack brings a fresh perspective to the original game with brand new Kingdom layouts. The Orchard Kingdom puts some new and interesting twists on the Classic Kingdom, and Kingdom Crossroads gives a new pace to your game. Luckily, the Keflings are still just as nice in both Kingdoms. "
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Kingdom Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/09",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The new layouts in this Kingdom Pack are not for the faint Giant at heart. The mysterious Relic Kingdom will force you to explore every inch of the map to find your way around, and the challenging Central Kingdom is definitely meant for the more advanced player. Previous Kefling management experience is a plus."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EI8ahuJkvZ4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DdKWnWQXDPU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/946839-a-kingdom-for-keflings/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/A-Kingdom-for-Keflings/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/a-kingdom-for-keflings/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/a-kingdom-for-keflings"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":198,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Backbone Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"The Capcom arcade classic receives a whole new look with Super Street Fighter II Turbo HD Remix. Capcom maintains the integrity of the popular game by utilizing the original game code while upgrading the graphics with new artwork and high resolution 1080p images -- all of the art, from character animation to stage backgrounds, will be completely redrawn by Udon Entertainment, the company responsible for the official US Street Fighter series of comics. Super Street Fighter II Turbo HD Remix includes both online and offline competition for one to two players.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Py9kemu8CIo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EHuWkNzpThw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939066-super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-hd-remix/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Super-Street-Fighter-2-Turbo-HD-Remix/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/super-street-fighter-2-turbo-hd-remix/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/super-street-fighter-ii-turbo-hd-remix"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Shoryuken",
				"url":"http://wiki.shoryuken.com/Super_Street_Fighter_II_Turbo_HD_Remix"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Street Fighter Wiki",
				"url":"http://streetfighter.wikia.com/wiki/Super_Street_Fighter_II_Turbo_HD_Remix"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":199,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["4JStudios", "Rare"],
			"synopsis":"Rare's classic adventure game is now available on Xbox Live Arcade!<br><br>You are Banjo, a honey bear on the hunt for your kidnapped sister, Tooty. By your side or actually on your back is your trusty friend, the red gull Kazooie. You'll have to travel through 10 different worlds, but to unlock the doors to those worlds, you'll need to find jigsaw puzzles and musical notes. Banjo and Kazooie each have different abilities to help you on your quest, and you can switch between the two in order to get the job done.<br><br>This Xbox Live Arcade version of Banjo-Kazooie is a special treat for fans of the franchise, as it incorporates the lost \"Stop 'N' Swop\" feature, which was built into the original release of the game and would have allowed gamers to connect together play sessions with this game and its sequel. That feature was lost in development, but now players can finally take advantage of Stop 'N' Swop with the Xbox debut of Banjo -- collecting Mystery Eggs in the original game will gamers gamers secret bonuses in Banjo-Kazooie: Nuts & Bolts!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sst0clZ6g0Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/951686-banjo-kazooie/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Banjo-Kazooie/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/banjo-kazooie/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/banjo-kazooie"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Banjo-Kazooie Wiki",
				"url":"http://banjokazooie.wikia.com/wiki/Banjo-Kazooie"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":200,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Q Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Take a ride through this intergalactic journey where you slide, stack and ignite your blocks to blast away the world-ending meteors! Only you can stop them from falling and crushing your planet. Master the combo links and power-ups to challenge your friends in intense multiplayer sessions!<br><br>Meteos Wars features several gameplay modes and tons of unlockables with a focus on both single and multiplayer play. The game has received an audio and visual facelift and picked up a few new features along the way, keeping the Meteos experience fresh and creating hours of excitement.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Planet Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/01/21",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Can't get enough of Meteos Wars? Challenge yourself and your opponent to more planets! The Planet Pack features 9 planets, each with its own visual and audio style as well as gravity effects. Find the planet that best fits your style of play in Meteos Wars! Simply slide, stack and ignite your blocks to blast away the world-ending Meteos. Only you can stop them from falling and crushing your planet. Master the combo links and power-ups to challenge your friends in intense multiplayer sessions. This fast-paced action puzzler is nothing but one explosive adventure!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Galaxy Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/25",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Challenge yourself and your opponent to an out-of-this-world experience with even more planets in Meteos Wars!  The Galaxy Pack features 9 planets, each with its own visual and audio style as well as gravity effects.  Find the planet that best fits your style of play in Meteos Wars and show off your alien invasion defense system! Simply slide, stack and ignite your blocks to blast away the world-ending Meteos. Only you can stop them from falling and crushing your planet. Master the combo links and power-ups to challenge your friends in intense multiplayer sessions. This fast-paced action puzzler is nothing but one explosive adventure!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=32yBMTXLooc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Meteos-Wars/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/meteos-wars/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/meteos-wars"
			}]
		}
	}]
}