{
	"catalog": [
	{
		"id":1,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Halfbrick Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Chop and strike to deliciously slash and splatter fruit like a true ninja warrior with this Kinect-enabled version of Fruit Ninja. But be careful of the bombs, which are explosive to the touch and will put a swift end to your juicy adventure!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Storm Season",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/24",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Feel the wrath of Mother Nature! Storm Season contains: Lighting Bolt BladeeLIGHTNING BOLT BLADE - Feel like Zeus as you throw thunderbolts from the heavens! THE STORM CASTLE BACKGROUND - A storm is brewing above the ancient castle. THE RAIN MAN SHADOW - Anyone got an umbrella? All are immediately available in Sensei's Swag."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Space Capsule",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/07",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Explore the final frontier! Space Capsule contains: THE COMET BLADE - Steer comets through the heavens and create cosmic collisions. THE STAR CHART BACKGROUND - Never leave home without it. THE STELLAR SHADOW - There's a universe within you. All are immediately available in Sensei's Swag."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Art Box",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/21",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Discover your creative side! Art Box contains: THE CALLIGRAPHY BRUSH - The pen is mightier than the sword. THE PARCHMENT BACKGROUND - A blank canvas just for you. THE INK SHADOW - Leave your mark with grace. All are immediately available in Sensei's Swag."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Christmas Present",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/14",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Merry Christmas! It's a FREE gift just for you! This Christmas Present will enhance your Fruit Ninja Kinect experience like never before! Christmas Present contains: THE CANDY CANE - It's made of candy! SANTA'S WORKSHOP THEME - I can almost see the elves. THE SNOW GLOBE SHADOW - Shake it up! All are immediately available in Sensei's Swag."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"8-bit Cartridge",
				"releaseDate":"2012/08/31",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Be transported to the golden age of gaming with the 8-bit cartridge! This pack will give the game a super retro feel with the Mega Sword blade, Super Retro Land background and Game Man shadow! We even pixelated the fruit and menus for that 1980s feel. Radical!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Trick or Treat Bag",
				"releaseDate":"2012/10/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Scare the pants off your friends with this delightfully spooky Trick or Treat Bag! This pack includes the Slasher blade, Haunted House background and Ghostly Apparition shadow - even Sensei is all dressed up and ready to party!"
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Flower Power",
				"releaseDate":"2012/11/14",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Take a trip to the summer of love with the Flower Power pack! Includes The Rainbow blade, Flag of Peace background and Psychedelic Dream shadow. Groovy!"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"High-Tech Vault",
				"releaseDate":"2012/11/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Beam yourself up with the High-Tech Vault! This pack includes the Energy Sword blade, Airlock background and Cloaking Device shadow! Don't let our future be destroyed by the fruit of tomorrow!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UzsmDfKzk7M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y7X1AAT7aXM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fruit-Ninja-Kinect/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fruit-ninja-kinect/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fruit-ninja-kinect"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":2,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ludia"],
			"synopsis":"The Hole In The Wall game brings all the wild and crazy fun of the international TV phenomenon straight to your Xbox 360 Kinect to play solo or with friends. You become a human puzzle piece as you contort to fit through wacky shapes that are cut out into themed walls hurtling towards you. Try to pass your body through the wall to boost your score, or you'll be pushed straight into the water below!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7oIag7dTup0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hole-in-the-Wall/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hole-in-the-wall/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hole-in-the-wall"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":3,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"Your body is the controller is in this whimsical and dreamlike game. Guide the Leedmees, a mysterious population of small and creatures, home, using your limbs and head as bridges and walkways. Lift them up, toss them about, and slip them past treacherous obstacles, but be careful and don't let them get hurt!<br><br>Lose too many of them and the game will be over.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YOBPKKBjLyo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Rz9DkZ_wxKc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Leedmees/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/leedmees"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":4,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Criterion Games"],
			"synopsis":"In Burnout Crash, players are rewarded for causing traffic chaos by crashing into cars, triggering explosions and destroying everything in sight!<br><br>Burnout Crash packs countless hours of reckless chaos into an easy to pick up, but difficult to master gameplay experience. There are three explosive game modes available across 18 crash junctions in six unique locations, each requiring different skills and strategies to maximize damage and destroy everything in sight. With a variety of player vehicles to unlock, high-value targets to seek and destroy, and crazy surprise features to discover, players will be hooked on an adrenaline-fueled rampage to the top of the Crashwall.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3ISO9aWJAt0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IedyDtG_kRo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Burnout-Crash/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/burnout-crash/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/burnout-crash!"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Burnopedia",
				"url":"http://burnout.wikia.com/wiki/Burnout_CRASH!"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":5,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Nana On-Sha", "Zoe Mode"],
			"synopsis":"Haunt is a horror game based around Kinect and designed by Masaya Matsuura (of Parappa the Rapper fame.) This first-person perspective horror game uses a cartoony art style and a fun, spooky atmosphere to draw players into the story of a haunted mansion. Players will use a flashlight to point at objects as they explore this mysterious abode.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YAA1N7_Tzo0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6hQlwYJaOuA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Video walkthrough",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IZYqG9-fUTE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Haunt/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/haunt/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/haunt"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":6,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Double Fine Productions"],
			"synopsis":"Are you annoyed at how little magic you are able to shoot from your fingers? Have you ever tried to get grandma to do the worm, but all she would do is just stand there? Have you ever noticed how your living room doesn't have any hot lava in it? And who designed this living room anyway?! It doesn't even have any buildings to smash! Well, Double Fine Happy Action Theater can solve all of these problems and more! You will also be able to clone yourself or hang out in a plate of jelly if you want. And when you're done with that, maybe you will want to feed some pigeons or have a snowball fight. There are 18 amazing ways that Double Fine Action Theater will enhance your life! And up to 5 of your friends lives too!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ab64djRW_gA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vPIZ5EuTRJo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Double-Fine-Happy-Action-Theater/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Double-Fine-Happy-Action-Theater/walkthrough.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/double-fine-happy-action-theater"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":7,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"Rhythm Party is a rhythm action game developed exclusively for Kinect. Brought to you by the \"Dance Masters\" development team, it transforms your entire body into a controller. No need for choreography anymore. You're the choreographer and the dancer!<br><br>Game play is simple: Use your arms and legs to hit the Ripples in time with the rhythm while you create an original performance. Your performance skills are the key! With a soundtrack recorded largely in collaboration with top international artists, and different special effects for every song, this game is guaranteed to get your body moving and your blood pumping!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Song Pack No. 1",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/15",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"New songs and stages have been added. \"Keep it Real\" by NAOKI feat. Tiffany, \"DM Star\" by NAOKI, \"Unbelievable (Sparky remix)\" by jun feat. Sarah-Jane."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Song Pack No. 2",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/15",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"New songs and stages have been added. \"Activation\" by jun feat. Kathy Sledge, \"Pharaoh Love\" by Des-ROW, \"Diamond Night\" by Tomosuke feat. Alexa Slaymaker."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Master Level Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/15",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"This Master Level Pack adds new master level songs to the game."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Song Pack No. 3",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/29",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"New songs and stages have been added. \"All Around The World\" by Stacey Q, \"Evolution\" by TERRA, \"El ritmo te controla\" by Jeanette Herrera."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Song Pack No. 4",
				"releaseDate":"2012/03/14",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"New songs and stages have been added. \"Inside your mind\" by Limahl, \"The Sunbeam\" by Des-ROW + XX, \"bag\" by RevenG."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Song Pack No. 5",
				"releaseDate":"2012/03/28",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"New songs and stages have been added. \"Lame by Monday\" by Des-ROW, \"-Flowers- (2nd EDITION)\" by TEERA, \"Love is the power -Re:born-\" by NM."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TUT2amQ7R4w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xf6xhc2htrw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rhythm-Party/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rhythm-party/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rhythm-party"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":8,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Grasshopper Manufacture"],
			"synopsis":"An unusual, unique and wacky pitching action game is coming to Kinect and the name of the game is Diabolical Pitch.<br><br>A former pitcher now outfitted with an incredibly powerful bionic arm finds himself in a run-down, dark, and twisted amusement park. The night gets strange and intense quickly as you must use your pitching skills to survive the game of your life. Charge up your diabolical pitch to wipe out all the enemies crowding towards you. Power-ups give your throwing arm insane abilities that will give you the edge against huge mobs of enemies or even the mostfearsome boss. Kinect turns your room into a playing field and your Diabolical Pitch is the main attraction.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W8H-DgAZGpg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7hE4jytZqjA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Diabolical-Pitch/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/diabolical-pitch"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":9,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Leisure"],
			"synopsis":"A downloadable version of the classic FMV videogame. In this single-player action game, you play as heroic knight Dirk the Daring as he journeys to a mysterious castle filled with danger, in order to save the fair Princess Daphne from the forces of evil and the towering dragon Singe. Dragon's Lair features full-motion animation directed by Don Bluth, the man behind animated films such as the Secret of Nimh and Titan AE. It takes fast reflexes and a good memory to remember the safe way through each section of the deadly castle. Do you have what it takes to guide Dirk to the end and save Princess Daphne?<br><br>For the first time, Dragon's Lair can now be enjoyed from the comfort of your couch. This fully arcade authentic version is fully playable with Kinect so you can really show how well you wield Dirk's sword. The game is also fully playable with standard Xbox controllers. Included with this ultimate edition are bonus Avatar items, Gamerpics and even a full watch feature to sit back and enjoy Don Bluth's stunning animation.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Oz-ZziFK-dg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a65u5zU4bPE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dragons-Lair/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dragons-lair/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dragons-lair"
			},
			{
				"type":"Original game's Wiki",
				"site":"Dragon's Lair",
				"url":"http://dragonslair.wikia.com/wiki/Dragon%27s_Lair"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":10,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Mando Productions"],
			"synopsis":"In Babel Rising, gamers play as God, preventing humans from building the tower of Babel. Gamers can use their divine powers by hurling bolts of lightning, summoning massive earthquakes or unleashing gigantic floods upon the Babylonians.<br><br>Mando Productions, the developer of Babel Rising, has built upon their original mobile release of Babel Rising by creating new 3D environments and integrating competitive and cooperative multiplayer modes.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Sky's the Limit",
				"releaseDate":"2012/07/11",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The Humans are defying you once more! Embody a vengeful god and get it over with the waves of heretics who try to build two new towers. Let's unleash your mighty powers and confront new vicious types of units in exciting exclusive levels."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pigHqFtw5sM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IRN7oLDDfl0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Babel-Rising/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/babel-rising/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/babel-rising"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":11,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Side Kick"],
			"synopsis":"Calling all ninjas! Get ready to swipe, kick and battle your way through 21 levels of intense ninja action as you help Hiro rescue his master and fellow ninjas from the clutches of the evil Samurai Warlord. Be prepared to face a multitude of enemies that will push your skills to the limit and test your ingenuity. So pack your ninja stars, sword and more and get ready for adventure ...a Mini Ninjas Adventure!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UI27uhUjOIU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kxV7_e4FmtE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mini-Ninjas-Adventures/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mini-ninjas-adventures/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mini-ninjas-adventures"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":12,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Iron Galaxy Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Wreckateer uses Kinect for Xbox 360 to put you in control of a massive castle-wrecking ballista. With the help of Wreck and Tinker, travel the land and destroy sixty goblin-infested castles using six magical projectiles. Aim and fire each shot and then control it in mid-air, motion-activating special powers and guiding them toward their target. Utilize an arsenal of Flying, Explosive, Splitting, and rocketing Speed shots to explore the infinite ways you can wreak havoc with Wreckateer's fully-dynamic destruction.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Mt. Adalmant Level Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/11/14",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Wreck 6 brand new levels in Wreckateer! Demolish castles in the frosty region of Mt. Adalmant while ridding the region of the terrible goblin infestation!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Callonburg Level Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2013/01/12",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Wreck 6 brand new levels in Wreckateer! Wreck and Tinker discover a new region to smash. Crush your way through the long lost foul fortresses of Callonburg!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=td7BNhe8qow"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IkAJM9eb_qQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay (with commentary)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tOyYdn9hdTA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wreckateer/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wreckateer/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wreckateer"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":13,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Wahoo Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Do you have what it takes to be a superstar? Get schooled by Chris Evans on the secrets of the action hero. Get styled and learn how to work the runway with Chanel Iman. Rock the party with Redfoo of LMFAO. Live video play puts you in the action: punch, jab, kick, jump - pose, smile - surf the crowd. Pass these celebrity tests and you'll be slated for stardom. Share the custom movie poster of you and Evans, and your magazine cover shot, with your friends.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bJv1wFLeCzY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Discovered/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/discovered/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/intel-discovered"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":14,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Smoking Gun Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Step up to the plate and swing for the fence in Home Run Stars, featuring Avatar Fame Star! Progress through the League mode through all three unique stadiums! Each one features a vast number of spectacular targets to aim for and earn big points. Compete with your friends in multiplayer for the highest score. Use your device supported by SmartGlass to compete in a Duel with a friend!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gDhp3LQRpi8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Home-Run-Stars/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/home-run-stars/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/home-run-stars"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":15,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bongfish"],
			"synopsis":"Red Bull Crashed Ice Kinect is a Sports game, developed by Bongfish and published by Microsoft Game Studios, which was released in 2012.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lg9LwSj_7XQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xDbdyR89COw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Red-Bull-Crashed-Ice-Kinect/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/red-bull-crashed-ice-kinect"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":16,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Double Fine Productions"],
			"synopsis":"Transform your living room into the ultimate Kinect Party! Immerse yourself and up to 5 friends in this augmented reality playground as Kinect Party presents 36 mind-bending channels - each overflowing with outrageously unique, motion-controlled fun. Wield nunchucks, grow fairy wings, dodge hot lava, harness electricity, dig for treasure, launch fireworks, become a fire breathing dragon and more! Be sure to download the free Game Add-On \"Kinect Party - Full Unlock\" to take advantage of the inclusion of this game in the \"Countdown to the Holidays Promotion\".",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Full Unlock",
				"releaseDate":"2012/12/18",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Unlock all 36 mind-bending channels - each overflowing with outrageously unique, motion-controlled fun. Wield nunchucks, grow fairy wings, dodge hot lava, harness electricity, dig for treasure, launch fireworks, become a fire breathing dragon and more!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=buBCZG2xMi4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e4o-uSHlsd0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kinect-Party/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kinect-party/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kinect-party"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":17,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Lima Sky"],
			"synopsis":"Jump, jump, jump to the top, top, top with Doodle Jump Kinect! Guide the Doodler on a springy journey up the never-ending sheet of graph paper to see how far you can climb. Leap from platform to platform, finding your way higher and higher using brilliant contraptions such as springs, propeller hats, and jet packs. Avoid broken platforms, menacing black holes, UFOs, and baddies. Blast them with your nose balls!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b8ivIaGkhLs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yas8OUMAHn4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Doodle-Jump-for-Kinect/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/doodle-jump-kinect/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/doodle-jump-for-kinect"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":18,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Smoking Gun Productions"],
			"synopsis":"Freefall Racers is an XBLA exclusive Kinect racing game featuring flying squirrels.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4bLqoLndqKg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PAF_qzUWQAQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Freefall-Racers/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/freefall-racers/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/freefall-racers"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":19,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Voxler Games"],
			"synopsis":"Let's Sing and Dance uses Kinect to bring music games to the next level, combining singing and dancing at the same time. Using Kinect, the game scores the players' dance moves as well as their singing performances. Unlimited number of players can take the stage at the same time and chose between 12 hits from major artists -- recent hits and all time classics.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pO71zyQ-gAc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C53YtceCMbI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lets-Sing-and-Dance/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lets-sing-and-dance"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":20,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gaijin Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Skydive: Proximity Flight lets players fly through the air by simply waving their arms and maneuvering their bodies using accurate and immersive motion controls. Realistic graphics, precise sounds, and stunning aerial landscapes provide exhilarating skydiving experience.<br><br>Skydive players can learn the mid-air tricks of professional skydivers and also make up their own tricks, either solo or with friends. Best of all, Skydive: Proximity Flight makes it possible for wide audience to enjoy the intense adrenaline rush of wingsuit flying-without the real-world safety risks.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XZeLhcsmhuw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PwRe3HbIc30"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Skydive-Proximity-Flight/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/skydive-proximity-flight"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":21,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Krome Studios", "Float Hybrid"],
			"synopsis":"Step into the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle lair and train to become a ninja. In this action-packed Kinect driven experience, use your skills to complete various missions using different Ninja Turtle weapons. Unlock photo backgrounds and pose with your favorite Ninja Turtle to share photos with your friends on Facebook.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dcFQsmOwdd4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/TMNT-Training-Lair/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-training-lair"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":22,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["PopCap Games"],
			"synopsis":"Discover the ancient secrets of Zuma Deluxe! Deep in the jungle lie hidden temples bursting with traps and trickery. It will take a quick hand and a sharp eye to unlock their treasures. Explore more than 20 realms in Adventure mode and put your skills to the test in the Gauntlet. Fire magical balls from the stone frog idol to make color matches, then collect coins and powerups to clear the path. But watch out! If the stream of spheres reaches the golden skull, it'll be the end for you!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d366k7yYEmo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930860-zuma-deluxe/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Zuma/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/zuma/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/zuma-deluxe"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":23,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["PixelStorm"],
			"synopsis":"Prepare to release your inner pool shark! Bankshot Billiards 2 improves upon the original with nine different game styles: classic 8-Ball, 9-Ball, Cutthroat, Euro 8-Ball, 14.1 Continuous, 3-Ball, Trick Shots, Time Trial, and Golf. Turn on the Aiming Aid option and practice your shots against the computer. When you're ready, challenge your friends in your own living room or take on the world over Xbox Live. Earn achievements such as Trick Shot Mast er, Speed Freak, or Ultimate Hustler!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tN9PCjncC6Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930852-bankshot-billiards-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bankshot-Billiards-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bankshot-billiards-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bankshot-billiards-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":24,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["PopCap Games"],
			"synopsis":"An Xbox Live Arcade game (built for the Xbox 360 system.) With four unique and entrancing ways to play, explosive new game pieces and awe-inspiring planetary backdrops, Bejeweled 2 is more wildly addictive than ever before!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m9IEwF8rAuQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930837-bejeweled-2-deluxe/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bejeweled-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bejeweled-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bejeweled-2-deluxe"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Bejeweled Wiki",
				"url":"http://bejeweled.wikia.com/wiki/Bejeweled_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":25,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software"],
			"synopsis":"An Xbox Live Arcade game (built for the Xbox 360 system) based on the classic arcade game. Gauntlet is back! The original role-playing arcade game lets four adventurers explore together as a warrior, valkyrie, wizard, and elf. Traverse the darkest of mazes, destroying vile beasts and claiming gold. Consume food to regain your strength, collect keys to journey deeper, and seek out potions to defeat your most powerful foes.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5dYw91jKw9k"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930856-gauntlet/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Gauntlet/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/gauntlet/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/gauntlet"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Gauntlet Wiki",
				"url":"http://gauntlet.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":26,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bizarre Creations"],
			"synopsis":"An Xbox Live Arcade game (built for the Xbox 360 system), also part of PGR3.<br><br>Blast away at enemies with 360 degrees of movement and targetting (via the dual stick control set-up on the Xbox pad) in this throwback shooter game. Return to the farthest reaches of the galaxy, where hordes of evil, neon shapes await! Green squares evade your fire; purple ones divide into smaller clones. Snake-like lines leave behind a venomous trail, and red circles morph into black holes. Conserve your bombs-they destroy all enemies, but quantities are limited.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kijt1dH1u2g"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930851-geometry-wars-retro-evolved/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Geometry-Wars-Evolved/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/geometry-wars-evolved/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/geometry-wars-retro-evolved"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":27,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Microsoft Game Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Included free with every Xbox 360 System, this Xbox Live Arcade puzzle game is designed by Alexey Pajitnov, the internationally-known creator of Tetris. You will spend your time rotating groups of different colored hexagons, attempting to group them together and wipe them from the board. Special blocks add points in the equation. Bombs make an appearance, and if you don't clear them in a specified number of turns, the the game is over. This makes for a tense and entertaining experience. Even the music changes to a gripping song ala \"Who Wants To Be A Millionaire?\" when a bomb drops in.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zx28ArANC0w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hexic/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hexic-hd/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hexic-hd"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":28,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software"],
			"synopsis":"An original game (for play on the original Xbox system), designed for play from a download from Xbox Live Arcade.<br><br>Mount thy noble ostrich and ride forth into battle in the classic arcade game Joust. Defeat enemy knights and capture the resulting eggs before they hatch or you're in for an even bigger fight with stronger foes!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KL8olv282QM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930838-joust/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Joust/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/joust/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/joust"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":29,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["PomPom Games"],
			"synopsis":"Mutant Storm Reloaded features the official training grounds for those who wish to master Blastikkidoo--the Art of Blasting. Just as in martial arts, you begin with a white belt and earn higher belts as you progress. As you move to higher belts, the difficulty increases, which in turn hones your skill. Your goal is simple: Blast through 89 levels inhabited by an array of nasty beasties and live to brag about it. Survive, and you could earn the elusive black belt.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f9_gIL9SIcs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mutant-Storm-Reloaded/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mutant-storm-reloaded/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mutant-storm-reloaded"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":30,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["NinjaBee", "Wahoo Studios"],
			"synopsis":"An Xbox Live Arcade game (built for the Xbox 360 system).<br><br>Outpost Kaloki X combines a very simple interface with the game play of a deep strategy game. Each space station has a number of \"spokes\" that you can build attachments to. Each attachment fulfills a specific need, such as social interaction, business, energy production, maintenance, and defense. Most objects are designed to produce revenue, but some, like solar collectors and repair bays, are designed to keep your station functioning. If you can meet the demand of your customers while maintaining all your structures and energy production you will be on your way to victory.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Fireworks Scenario",
				"releaseDate":"2005/11/01",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Help direct Superstar Fishy McFisherson's fireworks extravaganza in this scenario for Outpost Kaloki X."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Bounty Hunter Scenario",
				"releaseDate":"2006/01/10",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Earn fame and glory as a destroyer of nasty evil alien robots in this scenario for Outpost Kaloki X."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Love Story Scenario",
				"releaseDate":"2006/01/10",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Choose a sweetheart and win her heart in this romantic 5-part story for Outpost Kaloki X. "
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Challenge of the Gods Scenario",
				"releaseDate":"2006/02/07",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Please the Greek gods of your choice without angering the others in this challenging extra scenario for Outpost Kaloki X."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"The Swarm Scenario",
				"releaseDate":"2006/02/07",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Defend your station as long as you can against an increasing swarm of nasty evil alien robot attackers!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=97MFsRfhoY0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930854-outpost-kaloki-x/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Outpost-Kaloki-X/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/outpost-kaloki-x/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/outpost-kaloki-x"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":31,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software"],
			"synopsis":"An Xbox Live Arcade game (built for the Xbox 360 system), based on Midway's arcade blaster.<br><br>Win cash and prizes in this deadly game show in a full-tilt assault against massive numbers of enemies, shooting at them with 360 degree targetting and movement (using the Xbox's double control stick set-up on the gamepad.)",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x5AIJSTj1vI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Smash-TV/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/smash-tv/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/smash-tv"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":32,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Silver Creek Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Play a game of Hardwood Backgammon against the computer, against a friend on a single console, or against on online opponent over Xbox Live on Xbox 360.<br><br>Move all of your checkers onto your home board, and then bear off before your opponent does. Roll two of a kind to double your number of moves. Catch your opponent with a vulnerable checker, and send him to the bar. And once you're sure you're going to win, use the doubling cube to bring you even closer to ultimate victory!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eT_TV6h7i2g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hardwood-Backgammon/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hardwood-backgammon/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hardwood-backgammon"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":33,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Silver Creek Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Your mama told you not to go around breaking hearts. But in the classic card game Hardwood Hearts, that's what it's all about! Try to take as few points as possible ... unless you want to shoot the moon. If you take all the points in a moon shot, the points go to your opponents!<br><br>Up the stakes even more with Spot Hearts, where heart cards are worth their face values, the queen of spades is worth 50, and a moon shot earns your foes a whopping 150 points! And don't forget to congratulate your friends (or irritate your opponents) with a clever Foom!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hdv4WIe_3b4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hardwood-Hearts/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hardwood-hearts/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hardwood-hearts"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":34,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Silver Creek Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Welcome to Hardwood Spades... the game where a trick IS a treat! Bid on how many tricks you can take, then work with your partner to make it happen. Don't overbid, or you'll be set. But don't underbid either, or you'll be stuck with a bag! If you think you can duck all the tricks, go for a nil bid... just make sure you're not holding the Ace of Spades!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mdRM9KyUIRQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hardwood-Spades/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hardwood-spades/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hardwood-spades"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":35,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Reflexive Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"An Xbox Live Arcade game (built for the Xbox 360 system).<br><br>As the wild and unlikely hero Wik, you collect shiny coins, precious gems, green grubs and slimy bugs in a bizarre fantasy world with this wild action/platform/puzzle game. Wik's abilities stem from use of his super strong frog-like tongue. Wik can swing his body around by latching his tongue to things. He can also spit harder and much more accurately than a 3rd grader with a straw and a wad of paper!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rG72gK588C8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wik-Fable-of-Souls/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wik-fable-of-souls/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wik-the-fable-of-souls"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":36,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software"],
			"synopsis":"An Xbox Live Arcade game (built for the Xbox 360 system), based on Midway's arcade blaster where you are in a full-tilt assault against a screenful of enemies, shooting at them with 360 degree targetting and movement (using the Xbox's double control stick set-up on the gamepad).<br><br>In 2084, man creates a species of super-advanced cyborgs known as Robotrons. Recognizing the imperfect nature of their creators, the Robotrons conclude that the inefficient human race must be exterminated.<br><br>In Robotron: 2084, only you and a single family of clones remain. If mankind is to survive, you must destroy the Grunts, Brains, Enforcers, and Tanks--but avoid the indestructible Hulks at all cost. Can you withstand wave after wave of android invasion and rescue Mommy, Daddy, and Mikey... before it's too late?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ro4ZX1QKsnE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930762-robotron-2084/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Robotron-2084/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/robotron-2084/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/robotron-2084"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":37,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Garage Games"],
			"synopsis":"Marble Blast Ultra is the latest in the classic Marble Blast series. Get ready for an arcade action masterpiece with stay-up-all-night gameplay and an insane level of visual polish.<br><br>Marble Blast Ultra is an online multiplayer arcade action game, expanding on the original to take advantage of the Xbox 360 system. Suitable for players of any age, the game takes place in a futuristic 'astrolab' arena suspended high in the clouds where players compete against each other by navigating their marbles through moving platforms and dangerous hazards, while collecting rare gems and power-up enhancements, in an effort to complete each course in record time. To add to the fun, players will compete head to head in ultra blast multiplayer mode where racing to collect gems will combine with full on marble bashing action to see who ultimately wins all the marbles.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pwNJKE8XQxk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930825-marble-blast-ultra/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Marble-Blast-Ultra/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/marble-blast-ultra/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/marble-blast-ultra"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":38,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Stainless Games"],
			"synopsis":"The 1987 classic, Crystal Quest, returns with updated graphics, enhanced special effects, and Dolby sound! Pilot your ship through 60 waves, collecting crystals and evading the Nasties. These unique baddies-each one different-emerge from portals on each side of the screen.<br><br>Fire your weapon at them, or deploy a smart bomb to vaporize every Nasty on the screen. Grab all the crystals to open the gateway at the bottom of the screen. And don't forget to gather up the goodies in each wave... you can find bonus points, extra smart bombs, and even an occasional mega-crystal for massive points!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Sketch Graphics Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/02/10",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Complete graphics reskin that gives the game a cool \"handcrafted by draftsman\" look. Nothing else looks anything like it. Amaze your friends. Stun your mom. Confuse your dog. "
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Nano Graphics Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/02/10",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Complete graphics reskin that turns the game into an achingly good-looking view through an electron microscope into a bizarre world of semi-transparent critters and X-ray weirdness. Spooky!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Super Synth Sounds Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/02/10",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"This spiffy set of novelty noises turns your quest for crystals into a whirling wonderland of swooping synthesizer sounds. Tune in, turn up, and freak out!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Animal Madness Sound Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/02/10",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Insane sounds from the animal kingdom. Player must be sitting down for play due to possible injuries caused by excessive laughing. Apply generously. Not to be taken internally."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Xtreme Scenario",
				"releaseDate":"2006/02/10",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"So, you think you're a Crystal Quest Pro player? Are you ready for the challenge of Crystal Quest Xtreme? All scores are doubled, so scoring opportunities are huge. You may need to lie down after play. Sissies need not apply."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gQ6agKk6X78"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Crystal-Quest/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/crystal-quest/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/crystal-quest-2006"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":39,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["iWin"],
			"synopsis":"Jewel Quest is a unique new take on the classic-style matching game. Explore the ancient ruins of Mayan civilization while discovering hidden treasures and priceless artifacts. Rearrange valuable relics to turn sand tiles into gold. Watch out, though... as you venture deeper into the jungle, you will encounter increasingly difficult puzzles containing secret twists, cursed items, and buried artifacts.<br><br>Earn the respect of your fellow archaeologists and collect oodles of treasures and jewels. Your quest is complete when you have solved every puzzle, uncovered all the gold statues, and proven yourself a Chief Explorer.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8ENxfvKNFxA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Jewel-Quest/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/jewel-quest/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/jewel-quest"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":40,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["PopCap Games"],
			"synopsis":"Slurp, gulp, and crunch your way all along the Frenzy Coast in Feeding Frenzy! The rules here are simple: Eat anything that's smaller than you and swim clear of everything else. The more you eat, the bigger you get, and the bigger you get, the closer you come to taking on the fearsome Shark King.<br><br>Starfish bubbles don't help you grow, but they're an easy way to boost your score. Oysters offer up bonus points in the form of pearls, but be quick or the shell could snap shut with you inside! Nibbling on the tail of a patrolling barracuda is a risky way to earn extra pointshe can turn on you in an instant. And the jellyfish well, it's best to swim clear of them altogether.<br><br>Did you know that tuna can swim up to 50 miles per hour? Or that a parrot fish can change its gender? Feeding Frenzy includes more than four dozen fascinating fish facts like these one between each game level.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uy5gLclr_TQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/931334-feeding-frenzy/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Feeding-Frenzy/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/feeding-frenzy/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/feeding-frenzy"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":41,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["PopCap Games"],
			"synopsis":"Fire your rockets and blast off to fast-paced, arcade-puzzle action! Astropop blends fast twitch challenge with an offbeat, fun storyline. Choose from four space pilots, each with unique abilities and weaponry. Then grab, group, and blast bricks to create combos and clear a path to the stars.<br><br>As you progress, a mysterious link between the pilots unfolds against a backdrop of spectacular graphics, captivating sound effects, and myriads of scoring opportunities. Astropop's two different gameplay modes coupled with 33 challenging bonus rounds offer hours of extraordinary replay value for players of all ages and skill levels.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GnT0A5NiAAU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Astropop/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/astropop/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/astropop"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":42,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Carbonated Games"],
			"synopsis":"Downloadable Xbox Live Arcade version of the popular party card game. UNO is the classic party card game that's number one for family fun! Compete against three other players to match colors and symbols, go Wild with special command cards such as Skip and Reverse, and be the first to play all your cards. Gamers will be able to compete against three other cross-platform players on the Xbox 360 or Windows Vista platforms to match colors and symbols and be the first to play every single card. Add-on theme decks offer new art and new card effects, keeping the game fresh and challenging. So connect with friends, choose your favorite house rules, and get ready to shout \"UNO!\"",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"35th Anniversary Theme Deck",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"It's UNO's 35th anniversary, and we're celebrating with new cards, rules, music, and background art!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Project Gotham Racing 3 UNO - Theme Deck",
				"releaseDate":"2006/09/06",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Life begins at 170... take a spin through London, New York, Las Vegas, and Tokyo in Project Gotham Racing 3 UNO!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Kameo UNO - Theme Deck",
				"releaseDate":"2006/11/01",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Harness the power of the Elemental Warriors in Kameo UNO! New game rule card allows exchanging hands with another player. New card art, music, and sound effects add to the immersive experience of the classic Xbox 360 game, Kameo: The Elements of Power!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Street Fighter UNO",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"UNO meets the World Warriors in glorious HD! Download this Street Fighter theme deck now, and enjoy the new cards, music, and background art, anytime!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WWzxKZ3Y3ZY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932361-uno/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Uno/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/uno/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/uno"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":43,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software"],
			"synopsis":"Enjoy the classic game Frogger, revitalized and brand spanking new on your Xbox 360. With enhanced artwork building on the original title's style, modernized sound and music, and all new play modes, this is an Xbox Live Arcade title you won't want to miss out on.<br><br>Whether you've had your hands on the original or not, Frogger's fast paced and addictive gameplay is ready for it's latest incarnation on Xbox Live.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q9otgIgeJ3s"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933056-frogger/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Frogger/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/frogger/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/frogger"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":44,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["NinjaBee"],
			"synopsis":"Cloning Clyde is a completely unique 3D adventure and puzzle game that may bring new meaning to the word \"schizophrenic\". In addition to a single-player story and individual challenging scenarios, enjoy multiplayer split-screen or online play, both co-op and vs. modes, with friends from all over the world.<br><br>Clyde was an ordinary (but slightly dim) guy before Dupliclone Inc. paid him $20 to take part in a cloning experiment. Now he's multiple ordinary dim guys trapped in the nefarious Dupliclone Lab. To escape his diabolical captors, Clyde is going to have to get a little creative with himself and those around him. Lucky for him, Dupliclone left a whole lot of strange technology laying around, and it's up to Clyde to clone, combine, and mutate his way out of the evil Dupliclone trap. As Clyde adventures and meets new inhabitants of the Dupliclone labs, he'll combine with apes, frogs, chickens, and more.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WUvJOSkX4lc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932518-cloning-clyde/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cloning-Clyde/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cloning-clyde/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cloning-clyde"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":45,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Namco"],
			"synopsis":"The classic arcade shooter comes to Xbox Live Arcade, with exact replication and added features. Included additions are high-resolution borders and score leaderboards.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lE5gH28QdD0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932516-galaga/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Galaga/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/galaga/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/galaga"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":46,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sensory Sweep", "Capcom"],
			"synopsis":"With this Xbox 360 Arcade release of Capcom's classic, players can play the forever-the-champ fighting game online with players anywhere. In addition to being a full playable version of the classic game (based on Street Fighter II Hyper Fighting, with all 12 playable characters and bosses) downloadable to your Xbox 360 over Xbox Live, but it also packs exclusive online modes including Quarter Match (a spectator-based system allowing players to put a \"quarter\" down on the machine of a 2-player match you are watching to play winner, just like everybody did in arcades back in the '90s), Quick Match and Optimatch, Create Game (for customizing invites and skill levels), choice of casual or competitive matches (for determining whether win/loss stats are counted), and voice chat for both players and spectators. Also includes VS Mode, Training Mode, CPU mode, leaderboards and full single-player tracking, fully customizable control, and 5.1 surround sound.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kfc5_JNqcks"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/931283-street-fighter-ii-hyper-fighting/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Street-Fighter-2-Hyper-Fighting/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/street-fighter-ii-hyper-fighting/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/street-fighter-ii-hyper-fighting"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Street Fighter Wiki",
				"url":"http://streetfighter.wikia.com/wiki/Street_Fighter_II%27:_Hyper_Fighting"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Shoryuken",
				"url":"http://wiki.shoryuken.com/Street_Fighter_2:_Hyper_Fighting"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":47,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Namco"],
			"synopsis":"Gobble, gobble, gulp! Who's munching Power Pellets? Who's zipping around the maze at top speed, chomping up ghosts and scoring big points? It's Pac-Man, the world's hungriest character! And he's got the munchies! Devour a fruit treat and get a big bonus score. But if you're caught by the spooky hunters roaming the maze, you're ghostflakes! Use the warp tunnel for a quick escape, and swallow up a Power Pellet to temporarily make Pac-Man an unstoppable eater!<br><br>The classic arcade game comes to Xbox Live Arcade, exactly replicated and with added features. Included additions are high-resolution borders and score leaderboards.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=39XVcglCOP0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932517-pac-man/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pac-Man/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pac-man/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pac-man"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Pac-Man Wiki",
				"url":"http://pacman.wikia.com/wiki/Pac-Man_(game)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":48,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["TikGames"],
			"synopsis":"Whether you're a beginner or a pro, enjoy the thrill of the perfect hand or the perfect bluff. Test your skills in ring games and tournaments, or fine-tune your skills playing the scenario you always wanted to be in. Customize the game however you want. The comprehensive help provides details on each aspect of the game.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Environment: Jungle Party",
				"releaseDate":"2007/07/11",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Liven up your Texas Hold 'em game with some new scenery. Take the party to the jungle and play on jungle-themed tables with a fun new card deck."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Environment: Casino",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Liven up your Texas Hold 'em game with some new scenery."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Environment: Hip Hop",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Liven up your Texas Hold 'em game with some new scenery."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GlokaKmbU9E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Texas-Holdem/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/texas-hold-em/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/texas-hold-em"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":49,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software"],
			"synopsis":"With \"Time Pilot\", Xbox Live Arcade gamers can step back in time and fix the future for the safety of all mankind. Gamers will pilot a futuristic fighter jet with the capability to travel through time to destroy wave after wave of enemies; starting in 1910 and gunning down biplanes and UFOs through to the 21st century. Online multiplayer, high-definition graphics and achievements make this shooter hit Mach-3 like only an Xbox Live Arcade game can.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XEV_9nFyRPE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933057-time-pilot/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Time-Pilot/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/time-pilot/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/time-pilot"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":50,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software"],
			"synopsis":"Scramble your fighter and take on the enemy base in this newly enhanced version of the arcade classic. The base is heavily guarded and you must guide your ship through five levels of enemy defenses before you can destroy your objective.<br><br>Featuring brand-new graphics and sounds for Xbox 360, take your skills online and challenge the new \"Versus\" and \"Co-op\" modes. List your high score on the Xbox Live leaderboards and prove you're the best in the world!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L-2fZIZQeAU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933058-scramble/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Scramble/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/scramble/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/scramble"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":51,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Id Software"],
			"synopsis":"Note: Ultimate Doom is included in this version.<br><br>Go to Hell and back in Doom, as you battle through hellish levels of infernal action. Use pistols, chainsaws, shotguns, chain guns, rocket launchers, plasma rifles, and the BFG-9000 to blast demons, mutant spiders, possessed marines, and other creatures of the night. Take a trip to Hell and keep the demons from taking over the Earth in Doom.<br><br>A downloadable version of the classic shooter, this game includes the original four-episode, single-player game, four-player split screen (cooperative and deathmatch) and four-player cooperative and deathmatch.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RQvmPb6bFKE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oWHm0YvMW8U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Speedrun (Original Ultimate Doom - 0:16:05)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M6PK9bd_uUs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935829-doom/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Doom-XBLA/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/doom/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/doom"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Doom Wiki",
				"url":"http://doom.wikia.com/wiki/Doom"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":52,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Freeverse", "Strange Flavour"],
			"synopsis":"When the ancient Ptolmec tribe simultaneously discovered gunpowder and barbeque, the explosive results scattered their musical totems across the jungle! Now Pterry the Pturtle must roll over mountains, cross islands, scale pyramids, and battle giant pinball games to retrieve the lost totems and bring music back to the party.<br><br>Totemball is a musical platform adventure game for the Xbox Live online entertainment network, designed specifically for use with the Xbox camera so that you can play the game with your body.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z7Pu4M6Cn4g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/TotemBall/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/totemball/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/totemball"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":53,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bandai Namco Games"],
			"synopsis":"The classic arcade action title Dig Dug is now available for play on your Xbox 360 through Xbox Live Marketplace. Experience the fast-paced action of this quarter-cruncher from 1982 as you take control of Dig Dug himself and vanquish Pookas and Fygars.<br><br>Using your trusty pump, inflate your enemies until they pop, or squash them under rocks. Don't hesitate, or you could get squashed yourself. Drive your high score up by taking out enemies further underground, or making more difficult kills.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FM3xzHWifmM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933061-dig-dug/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dig-Dug/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dig-dug/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dig-dug"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":54,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Q Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Frenetic puzzle action! Dazzling background videos! A fresh installment to the original blockbuster puzzle series has landed on Xbox Live Arcade: Lumines Live! Harnessing the power of Xbox 360, Lumines Live! is a deep and entertaining game experience, enhanced with vibrant music and newly designed skins that you can custom-select in Skin Edit mode.<br><br>Lumines Live! even features full multiplayer mode on Xbox Live, unleashing leaderboards, achievements, gamer scores, online competitive modes, and more on Xbox Live gamers. Expand your Lumines Live! experience with additional downloadable content via Xbox Live Marketplace, including new puzzles, skins, and music.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Advance Challenge Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/01/24",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Feeling feisty and up for a new challenge? The Advance Challenge Pack for Lumines Live! adds some edge to the Standard Edition with more challenging gameplay and 20 all-new skins! After clearing your favorite skins in Skin Edit mode, customize your gameplay experience! Don't miss out on your chance to own these fresh, cool skins!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"VS CPU Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/01/24",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Here's your chance to rage against the machine with 9 new opponents! Challenge the CPU and show that box who's boss with the VS CPU Pack for Lumines Live! With each stage, you get some stylin'-themed skin and character designs. And if you can walk your talk, a special bonus skin awaits you at the very end of the challenge!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Puzzle/Mission Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/01/24",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Lumines Live! is not just about dropping blocks. In Puzzle mode, you have to use just the right blocks to create a certain shape. In the brand new Mission mode, you'll have to clear all blocks in a tightly limited number of moves. With 90 additional puzzles to solve 40 new missions to clear, you won't want to miss this Pack!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Booster Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/03/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Lumines addicts, are you ready for next challenge? Presenting the latest addition to the Challenge Mode, this Booster Pack features 20 stylish skins including some brand new, never before seen designs. A must-see is the unique collaboration between Lumines and \"Bloomy Girls\", a colorful and lively piece created by striking Japanese video artist/musician Masakatsu Takagi. You can also customize your Lumines experience by selecting your favorite skins once you have cleared them and line them up with your favorites from other packs! Good luck in clearing all of the skins!"
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Tokyo Club Mix Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/03/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Feel the beats and see the visuals from four of the hottest DJs, artists and VJs, with Tokyo Club Mix Pack! Fast-emerging Japanese DJ Sugiurumn is already making it big on the international scene, funky DJ unit TECHRIDERS keeps it fresh with their mix of audiovisuals, rising DJ Malo and his unit Muku are dropping the beats and the Tetsuya Mizuguchi-produced hybrid group Genki Rockets presents a special \"Heavenly Star SOS Remix\"."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Rockin' Holiday Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/03/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Introducing the first seasonal, themed pack for Lumines Live! A collection of 20 brand new skins featuring Halloween spookiness to snowflake wonderland, this Rockin' Holiday Pack is the newest addition to the Challenge Mode. The stylish skins come alive with tracks from genres never seen in the Lumines series - from heavy metal, UK rock to gabber, the pack features a little something for everyone! Amazing artist collaborations including Keiichi Sugiyama (Rez, Area 1), h ueda (Every Extend Extra Extreme), and Takayuki Nakamura of Brainstorm (Lumines series)."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lIrEOppA3PI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lumines-Live/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lumines-live/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lumines-live!"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":55,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software"],
			"synopsis":"Prepare for the fight of your life! Enter the world of Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 and discover 22 playable characters, classic fatalities, brutalities, friendships, and babalities with tons of environments, and multiplayer Kombat Mode as you fight to defeat Shao Kahn!<br><br>FINISH HIM!!!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4blWFPAnG1E"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932201-ultimate-mortal-kombat-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ultimate-Mortal-Kombat-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ultimate-mortal-kombat-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ultimate-mortal-kombat-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Mortal Kombat Wiki",
				"url":"http://mortalkombat.wikia.com/wiki/Ultimate_Mortal_Kombat_3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":56,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software", "Konami"],
			"synopsis":"In Contra, the world has been invaded and only two soldiers stand between the alien menace known as Red Falcon and the total annihilation of humanity. Lance and Bill, two veteran Special Ops soldiers, must fight their way through jungles, steel fortresses, and frozen tundra to rid the world of Red Falcon and all its minions.<br><br>Using high-tech weaponry such as the Mini Laser, the Fireball, and the dreaded Spread Gun, it's time to teach some alien scum not to mess with Earth. Enhanced for Xbox Live Arcade, the new version of Contra includes online multiplayer to play with your friends, leaderboards to go for your best score, achievements, updated graphics, and new sound effects .",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YpFmbYwaeXo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933054-contra-1987/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Contra/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/contra/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/contra-1987"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Contra Wiki",
				"url":"http://contra.wikia.com/wiki/Contra_(video_game)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":57,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Midway Games"],
			"synopsis":"The classic space shooter is back! Now for the first time you can play Defender on Xbox Live. Protect the humans on the planet surface by destroying the invading alien abductors.<br><br>In the future, the galaxy is invaded by hostile alien forces. Attacking in countless swarms, the aliens decimate any planet they encounter. Those who survive the initial invasions are harvested and forced serve the alien invaders. Mankind's only hope lies in you, the Defender!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZHE9vOxhlzc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932211-defender/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Defender/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/defender/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/defender"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":58,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gastronaut Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Small Arms is the frantic multiplayer brawling game where up to 4 players can join in the battles across dynamic and detailed levels. Choose from a cast of awesome fighters like cyborg tabby cats, assassin truffle pigs and mutant chimney sweeps. Jump from platform to platform shooting each other to pieces with 360 degrees aim.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Ivar & Gullarp: Best Friends Forever - Frozen in Time",
				"releaseDate":"2007/06/06",
				"achievements":35,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"After spending one million years frozen together in the Arctic, Ivar and Gullarp know everything about each other. How could they not! They spent endless hours rambling about how to get stains out of their fur underpants, how to make the best stone tools, and which baby seals were the cutest. Yes, Ivar & Gullarp will be best friends forever, because forever certainly can't take any longer than global atmospheric climate change. This package includes playable characters Ivar and Gullarp as well as their 'Arctic Ice Float' and 'Pillaged Village' levels! This pack contains 2 new PDA levels."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N9UUF0PZh98"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933918-small-arms/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Small-Arms/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/small-arms/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/small-arms"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":59,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Naked Sky Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"RoboBlitz is a fast-paced action game featuring puzzle-solving and unique physics-based weapons. Players blast through over 15 levels of high-intensity action as Blitz, a multi-talented robot on a mission to save its factory from a band of invading mechanical brains.<br><br>RoboBlitz combines the power of the Unreal Engine 3 and Ageia PhysX, which offers players a world built entirely from the latest in game technology and robot control theory. Completely driven by physics and without a single frame of hand-made animation, RoboBlitz offers the player a tremendous level of freedom and creativity through its interactive environments and emergent behaviors.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vRVsEFIgc2Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W6m5nYWkF9g"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928433-roboblitz/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/RoboBlitz/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/roboblitz/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/roboblitz"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":60,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Wanako Games"],
			"synopsis":"In Assault Heroes, take on the role of the only surviving member of an elite special forces unit searching for a secret underground lab. Play the mission alone or fight side-by-side with a friend in the two-player cooperative mode.<br><br>Hop into a heavily armed 4x4, maneuverable speed boat, or trusty military-issue footwear, blasting your way through enemy-infested territory while being assaulted by waves of formidable enemies with unrelenting attacks.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fss2rPMIgwI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LZyaaGZnxIM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935488-assault-heroes/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Assault-Heroes/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/assault-heroes/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/assault-heroes"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":61,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Stainless Games"],
			"synopsis":"On a planet ruled by the sadistic NovaLords, human beings secretly harvested from Earth are put in deadly gladitorial racing combat where the chances of survival are near impossible ... it's not good entertainment if everybody gets out alive! In this action racer, you aget behind the whell of one of 24 armed buggy-style vehicles, fighting across the game's 15 arenas in Multiplayer and Single Player modes - destroy your friends and neighbors online or battle the enemy aliens and face their menacing bosses in Career, Arcade and Free Play modes.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Bonus Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/03/21",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Buy the Novadrome Bonus pack for only 250 points and get 6 new arenas and 8 new vehicles - all playable in a brand spanking new Career mode. Unlock the new content and then play it over Xbox Live Arcade for more multiplayer madness! "
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M9x4pNcR7_Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Novadrome/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/novadrome/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/novadrome"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":62,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Namco"],
			"synopsis":"Namco's classic racing game returns -- drive around the 2D track at high speeds to cover as much ground as you can while avoiding the other cars on the road.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y6J4E607wqg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/New-Rally-X/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/new-rally-x/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/new-rally-x"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":63,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Namco"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the wildly popular series of the same name. For the Xbox Xbox Live Arcade. Gamers can track their high scores on the Ms. Pac-Man leaderboards, earn all 12 Achievements, and play all of the original maps (those with a Silver Tier account can demo two levels for free.)",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zDUdFPQZ2Ns"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935658-ms-pac-man/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ms-Pacman/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ms-pac-man/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ms-pac-man"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Pac-Man Wiki",
				"url":"http://pacman.wikia.com/wiki/Ms._Pac-Man_(game)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":64,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["PopCap Games"],
			"synopsis":"Heavy Weapon: Atomic Tank unleashes adrenaline-soaked, side-scrolling, shoot-em-up arcade action. With multiplayer modes exclusive to the Xbox Live Arcade version, Heavy Weapon: Atomic Tank brings classic shooter excitement and explosive power to Xbox Live Arcade. Players fight through 19 story-based missions to upgrade six weapon banks, or jump into instant action with the fast-paced Survival mode. Gamers can also team up with friends and storm across enemy lines in cooperative multiplayer modes either locally or on Xbox Live.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YCZIUtEZiwY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Heavy-Weapon/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/heavy-weapon/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/heavy-weapon-atomic-tank"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":65,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software"],
			"synopsis":"Get ready to serve! Rediscover the classic arcade game Root Beer Tapper on Xbox LIVE. Take on a room full of thirsty folks and keep their mugs full as they belly up to the bar, but don't drop the empties if you want to win.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BbYWBzkwdds"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Root-Beer-Tapper/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/root-beer-tapper/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/root-beer-tapper"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":66,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software"],
			"synopsis":"Can you deliver? Keep your subscribers happy by tossing newspapers on their doorsteps with perfect accuracy. Pedal fast and avoid obstacles to make the headlines and bring home the bacon. Challenge: Stay on the road and keep your subscribers happy in Easy Street, Middle Road, and Hard Way difficulties. Earn 12 different achievements to add to your gamerscore, as well. Multiplayer: Play with a friend online or off with co-op multiplayer modes in both split screen and Xbox Live modes. Xbox Live: Keep track of your victories with leaderboards updated weekly and for all time!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JgoZjIH14Uw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Paperboy/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/paperboy/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/paperboy"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":67,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["The Behemoth"],
			"synopsis":"They've got your spaceship, so blow up anything in your path to get it back. Completely hand-drawn high-definition graphics coupled with old-school game play results in ultimate mayhem. This addictive, side-scrolling shooter features cute, quirky humor and adjustable cartoon gore.<br><br>Alien Hominid HD features jump-in-anytime multiplayer action, immersive environments, award-winning bosses, and over 30 fashionable hats. This 2-D console experience comes jam-packed with seven mini-games, including several four-player party games. All You Can Eat, Neutron Ball, and PDA Games will keep the party going for hours on end.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"PDA Hot New Levels",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/04",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"These brand new, never before seen levels are hand crafted by The Behemoth and Newgrounds. These levels are guaranteed to keep you and your console busy for days! This pack contains 100 new PDA levels."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"PDA Euro Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/25",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"These 100 levels have never been seen in the United States. Be the first to try out these great European flavored levels."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"PDA Classic Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2007/05/23",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Enjoy the first 100 PDA levels from the original version of Alien Hominid hand created by the staff of The Behemoth."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"PDA Classic Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2007/06/20",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Now even more levels from your favorite developers, The Behemoth. Grab three of your best friends and try out these amazing new levels. This pack contains 100 new PDA levels. "
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Challenge Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/07/25",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"After testing PDA games for months on end, the new guys here at The Behemoth have designed 100 exciting new PDA levels. These 100 levels are packed with challenging puzzles that will test your game playing stamina."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oB-RUHFK0u8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3g6nT39gs9c"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/934459-alien-hominid-hd/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Alien-Hominid-HD/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/alien-hominid-hd/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/alien-hominid-hd"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Castlepedia",
				"url":"http://castlewiki.castlecrashers.com/Alien"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Behemoth Wiki",
				"url":"http://thebehemoth.wikia.com/wiki/Alien_Hominid_(Video_game)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":68,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Team17"],
			"synopsis":"Worms is a cleverly balanced turn-based strategy game in which teams of worms battle across bizarre randomly generated landscapes for supremacy. Each team takes its turn to pick off the opposing teams using crazy weapons, tools, and other utilities, as well as whatever foul strategies they can devise.<br><br>Worms die when they lose all of their energy or plunge into the water. The winning team is the one that manages to survive the mayhem and have worms left standing when the dust settles. Sound simple? Easy to play but difficult to master, it's a game of deep strategy that belies its simple appearance.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Jungle Landscape",
				"releaseDate":"2007/05/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Take Worms deep into the Jungle in this all new Landscape Pack!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Hell Landscape",
				"releaseDate":"2007/05/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Enter the depths of Hell with this all new Worms Landscape Pack!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Space Landscape",
				"releaseDate":"2007/05/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Take the battle into Space with this new Worms Landscape Pack! "
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Soundbank Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2007/05/30",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Vocally enhance your Worms with this soundbank pack brought to you by Team17."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Soundbank Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2007/07/04",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Vocally enhance your Worms with this soundbank pack brought to you by Team17."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Retro Landscape: Desert",
				"releaseDate":"2007/07/04",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Worms of Arabia! The Worms take a trip down memory lane with a visit to the Desert in this exclusively designed retro landscape brought to you by Team17."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XFFF7XP003M"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/937709-worms/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Worms/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/worms/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/worms"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Worms Wiki",
				"url":"http://worms.wikia.com/wiki/Worms_(2007)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":69,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software", "Konami"],
			"synopsis":"In celebration of the TMNT movie and videogame, the classic 1989 arcade game is back and available in its full form on Xbox Live Arcade. Bringing the coin-op arcade game into the comfort of the living room, this version features the original seven levels, two- to four-player co-op modes and voice-chat capabilities. Choose from one of four Ninja Turtles-Leonardo, Michelangelo, Donatello, or Raphael-and master their unique ninja weapons and abilities. Play through the original seven levels alone, or with up to three others cooperatively via Xbox LIVE.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DLnHKRAipjQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938488-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-2007/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/TMNT-1989-Arcade/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tmnt-1989-arcade/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-2007"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Turtlepedia",
				"url":"http://turtlepedia.wikia.com/wiki/Teenage_Mutant_Ninja_Turtles_(1989_video_game)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":70,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"Konami took the side-scrolling platformer to its fullest in this Castlevania. The game's enormous maps, huge range of weapons, constant enemies, and excellent balance all still puts this squarely on the all-time list, no questions asked. Add to that a memorable soundtrack and you have a gothic masterpiece that will serve as a benchmark for many future 2D action titles.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OOe90s04svM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/937723-castlevania-symphony-of-the-night/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Castlevania-Symphony-of-the-Night/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/castlevania-sotn/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/castlevania-symphony-of-the-night"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Castlevania Wiki",
				"url":"http://castlevania.wikia.com/wiki/Castlevania:_Symphony_of_the_Night"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":71,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rare"],
			"synopsis":"Rare's Jetpac Refuelled is a revamped and modernized version of the 1983 classic space blaster Jetpac. Clear a path through hordes of aliens to refuel your ship and amass a fortune over the course of 128 hi-definition levels, complete with achievements, leaderboards, and simultaneous multiplayer action.<br><br>Jetpac Refuelled provides everything you loved in the classic, plus 128 new levels of enhanced gameplay. Jetpac Refuelled can be played solo, or against another player on the same console or over Xbox LIVE.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vGp5nSUJcGE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ejqU5lIBGOw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Jetpac-Refuelled/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/jetpac-refuelled/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/jetpac-refuelled"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":72,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["MumboJumbo"],
			"synopsis":"Set, the Egyptian god of chaos, again threatens the Two Lands, and you must save Ancient Egypt from his terrible wrath in Luxor 2. Wielding the powers of Isis, battle your way across Egypt. Use your mystical winged scarab to shoot magical spheres and destroy encroaching colored spheres by making matches of three or more. Stop them all before they can reach the pyramids.<br><br>Unleash the powers of Isis by catching falling power-ups. Collect gems and jewelry for bonus points, or Golden Ankh coins to earn extra lives. Defeat Set in his temple stronghold or Egypt is doomed!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W-gK9N8Digw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Luxor-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/luxor-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/luxor-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":73,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bizarre Creations"],
			"synopsis":"In Boom Boom Rocket, players trigger rockets to the beat of the music while traveling through a 3D cityscape. The better the player times the explosions, the more spectacular the fireworks effects. The fireworks are choreographed to 10 original tracks created by Ian Livingstone. Players can play in single player mode or go head-to-head against a friend on the same console.<br><br>The game features three modes of gameplay: Normal, Speed and multiplayer head-to-head. Each song is choreographed into three skill levels to ensure that everyone can join in the fun. Successfully chain fireworks to fill the bonus meter and activate the psychedelic bonus mode for extra points. Players can unlock new firework designs by mastering each music track. You can also utilize the connected online element and see how their scores compare with other players on the Boom Boom Rocket leaderboard.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Guitar Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/30",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Boom Boom Rocket's Guitar Pack offers five new rock tracks that are perfect for the new guitar and dance mat peripheral support. Rock out to Cannon in D, Sugar High, Eine Kleine Rochtmusik, Sting of the Bumble Bee, and Explode to Joy!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jm0xCHSBT-Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Boom-Boom-Rocket/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/boom-boom-rocket/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/boom-boom-rocket"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":74,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Wanako Games"],
			"synopsis":"Grab your putter and head to the links for some of the most bizarre rounds of golf you'll see for a while -- you'll knock your ball through a Wild-West Saloon brawl, send it careening through Carnival bumper cars, and maybe even send it into orbit! With Mini Golf Adventures, you never know what the next course will bring!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3bQjXdLNQZI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/3D-Ultra-Minigolf-Adventures/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/3d-ultra-minigolf-adventures-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/3d-ultra-minigolf-adventures"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":75,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software", "Konami"],
			"synopsis":"In Gyruss, gamers fly a space ship from Neptune to Earth while battling enemies, satellites, asteroids and laser beam generators. Along the way the player's ship can be upgraded to better tackle the ever-increasing enemies that attack during the journey to Earth.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QTdDs-yfNJo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Gyruss/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/gyruss/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/gyruss"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":76,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Klei Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"A completely revamped version of the popular PC title of the same name. The main quest in Eets involves unbamboozling puzzles by collecting the numerous Puzzle Shards scattered throughout Eets World. Eets is easy to pick up, and features tons of unique, crazy characters. Eets: Chowdown offers new items, 120 new levels and the exclusive debut of Marsho Madness, a high-adrenaline action game in which players must keep the impending evil marshmallows at bay.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=egFSSbyWe48"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BV6mIDdnnKo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938057-eets-chowdown/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Eets-Chowdown/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/eets-chowdown/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/eets-chowdown"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":77,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Zen Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Zen Studios' Pinball FX offers an unparalleled pinball experience for novices and experts alike. It combines the arcade thrills of traditional pinball with enhanced gameplay and exciting, innovative features not found in any other pinball game. With the power of the Xbox 360 behind it, Pinball FX defines next-gen pinball physics and boasts high-resolution graphical detail. Unique to this game, players can operate the flippers via their arm movements with the Xbox 360 Live Vision Camera, or can engage in head-to-head online multiplayer bouts (with live chat, also via the Vision Camera.)",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Buccaneer Table",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/31",
				"achievements":10,
				"type":0
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Nightmare Mansion Table",
				"releaseDate":"2008/01/15",
				"achievements":20,
				"type":0
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Rocky and Bullwinkle Table",
				"releaseDate":"2008/04/02",
				"achievements":20,
				"type":0
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Street Fighter II Tribute Table",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/12",
				"type":0
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Earth Defense Table",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/21",
				"type":0
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kn2k4WyzW08"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BU5Je7Ez_8o"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/936694-pinball-fx/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pinball-FX/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pinball-fx/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pinball-fx"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":78,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Big Huge Games"],
			"synopsis":"Catan, based on the best-selling board game \"Settlers of Catan\", places you in the role of a colonist on a newly discovered imaginary island. Through strategy and trading, vie for control with other players over the territory and resources of this uncharted wilderness.<br><br>Compete online with your friends from around the world, or go up against a computer personality. Features include an all-new 3-D \"Living World\" environment and robust computer gameplay to challenge all skill levels--even the experts!<br><br>Catan is addictive fun for all ages, taking just minutes to learn and a lifetime to master!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CCFVumimssw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fi8hm2qnYvk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935185-catan/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Catan/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/catan/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/catan"
			},
			{
				"type":"Catan Wiki",
				"site":"World of Catan Wiki",
				"url":"http://catan.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":79,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Stainless Games"],
			"synopsis":"Enjoy two legendary arcade shooting games in one downloadable package!<br><br>The classic version of Centipede challenges gamers to defend their villages against an onslaught of centipedes, spiders, army ants and more. Xbox LIVE Arcade gamers also have access to an evolved version which features pre-rendered, high definition graphics, special effects like motion blur, trails and particle-based explosions that make this classic as enjoyable today as it was in the arcade decades ago.<br><br>In Millipede, the primary challenge is to obliterate chains of arthropods that creep down from the top of the screen. Scattered mushrooms are the gamers' main tool to shoot, destroy and redirect the menacing millipedes. Millipede also offers up Xbox LIVE Arcade gamers an evolved version of this coin-op classic.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KDZqKca9k7w"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/936561-centipede-and-millipede/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Centipede-Millipede/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/centipede-millipede/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/centipede-millipede"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":80,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Razorworks", "Technos"],
			"synopsis":"Double Dragon re-introduces martial Arts masters, Billy and Jimmy Lee (AKA Hammer and Spike), who must defeat the savage street gang known as the Black Warriors to rescue Billy's girlfriend, Marian. Fight your way through four levels from the street and factory to jungle/forest and castle, using every move available to you such as back-kicks, elbows, uppercuts and more. The Xbox Live Arcade version featurse a downloadable demo and original and graphical enhanced versions. Player action includes online co-op 2 player and one-on-one fighting for the final battle. The game also features the opportunity to score 12 achievement points for your online Xbox Live Arcade profile and an online leaderboard gives you the opportunity to show off your Double Dragon skills to your friends.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FKc3d1U9Hpw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938006-double-dragon/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Double-Dragon/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/double-dragon/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/double-dragon"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Double Dragon Wiki",
				"url":"http://doubledragon.wikia.com/wiki/Double_Dragon"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":81,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Microsoft Game Studios", "Carbonated Games"],
			"synopsis":"Team up with up to three of your friends and prepare yourselves for intense side-scrolling, sci-fi shooting action in Aegis Wing. It is set in the year 2105, when humanity must flee a dying Earth for the distant world Europa. But this new home is soon threatened by a powerful alien race, the Araxia. With stolen Araxian technology, the Europa fleet develops an experimental star fighter and assigns four ace pilots to test it. The Aegis Wing is born, and it becomes your mission to wield this new technology as humanity's last hope for survival. Up to four players can play together either locally or over Xbox LIVE to defeat waves of nefarious Araxian ships and bosses, and can even combine spacecraft in two-, three- or four-ship formations to access powerful Super Weapons.<br><br>Aegis Wing was originally conceived by three students and Microsoft Corp. interns - Scott Brodie, Danny Dyer and Matt Monson - during a summer internship at Xbox LIVE Arcade. The students worked in tandem with Carbonated Games to bring the game to the Xbox LIVE Arcade community.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UoJo5s4KGHA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939472-aegis-wing/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Aegis-Wing/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/aegis-wing/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/aegis-wing"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":82,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Silver Creek Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"In Soltrio Solitaire, play your favorite classic games like Spider, Klondike, FreeCell, and more, or play them with power-up bonuses, making your own playing cards in Voyage mode.<br><br>Looking for some head-to-head action? Duel it out in heated solitaire games, or play cooperative with multiplayer solitaire.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Game Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2007/06/13",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"10 Games including Compass, Clock, Sir Tommy."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Game Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2007/06/27",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"10 Solitaire games including Easthaven, Bristol, Golf."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Game Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2007/07/11",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"10 games including Blind Alleys, Grandfather and Beleaguered castle."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Game Pack 4",
				"releaseDate":"2007/07/25",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"10 games including Black hole, 40 thieves open and Four seasons."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Game Pack 5",
				"releaseDate":"2007/08/08",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"10 games including Steps, Streets, Sultan and TreFoil."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Game Pack 6",
				"releaseDate":"2007/08/22",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"9 games including Monte Carlo, Penguin and Freecell 2 deck. "
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Game Pack 7",
				"releaseDate":"2007/09/05",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"10 games including Canfield, Klondike 2 deck and Yukon."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Game Pack 8",
				"releaseDate":"2007/09/18",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"10 games including Spider 2 suit and Plait."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Game Pack 9",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"10 games including Pyramid, Fourteen out and Block ten."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E0T0S4TFqts"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Soltrio-Solitaire/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/soltrio-solitaire/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/soltrio-solitaire"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":83,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"This is a faithful next-generation update of this classic coin-op arcade title where the player assumes the role of a special forces agent sent behind enemy lines to infiltrate an enemy military complex and free captured prisoners of war.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5M-bxngNi70"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay (Comparison)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IGRFGh1KYOg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935659-rushn-attack/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rush-n-Attack/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rush-n-attack/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rushn-attack"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":84,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Namco"],
			"synopsis":"The world's first vertical scrolling shooter, Xevious, comes to Xbox LIVE Arcade with some unique gameplay features! Control your Solvalou ship and destroy the Xevious forces! Use blasters against air-based enemies and bombs against ground-based targets. Destroy the Andor Genesis mothership to earn bonus points!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8GGk-yeUb5g"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939646-xevious/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Xevious/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/xevious/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/xevious"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Xevious Wiki",
				"url":"http://xevious.wikia.com/wiki/Xevious"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":85,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Load Inc."],
			"synopsis":"Rev it up in Mad Tracks, an action-packed toy-car racing game. Races take place in everyday environments such as toy stores, mini golf parks, and restaurants. Extra challenges add to this car arcade party game's fast-moving fun. Play with friends on a split-screen, and gather up to 12 crazy achievements.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Encore",
				"releaseDate":"2007/06/27",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"So, you liked Mad Tracks? Ready for some extra challenges? Get the Mad Tracks Encore expansion pack! You'll get an additional nine nail-biting races and six action-packed mini games where you'll bolt down looped Victorian stairs, barrel across the skyline on rooftops, and speed over rickety wooden ramps in a German castle. Sound fun? Well it is!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Bravo",
				"releaseDate":"2007/07/25",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"So, you liked Mad Tracks? Want some extra challenges? Get the Mad Tracks Bravo expansion pack! You'll get an additional seven nail-biting races and eight action-packed mini games where you'll discover the treacherous conditions of Antarctica, compete in a spacious ballroom, and get a little culture in a museum (or not). Sound fun? Well it is!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7laMTKXEX-g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mad-Tracks/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mad-tracks/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mad-tracks"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":86,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bandai Namco Games"],
			"synopsis":"The \"Pac-Man Championship Edition\" is the same beloved \"Pac-Man\" game played in arcades of the '80s but is updated with new features that former \"Pac-Man\" fanatics and new generations of fans alike will love. It includes new mazes that dynamically change shape during gameplay, six new timed game modes, new soundtracks and high-definition (HD) graphics.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lnJ9Op7c_w4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0ILXMIn2Fis"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pac-Man-Championship-Edition/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pac-man-ce/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pac-man-championship-edition-dx"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Pac-Man Wiki",
				"url":"http://pacman.wikia.com/wiki/Pac-Man_Championship_Edition"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":87,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gameloft"],
			"synopsis":"The classic 1989 Prince of Persia game is here remade and brought back on Xbox Live, with new designs to enhance the perfect gameplay of the original. Prince of Persia Classic features the same intricate level design, exciting swordplay, puzzle solving, and storyline from the original. In play, it's the same great experience as always, but the game has received a brand-new coat of paint. New character designs, animations, visuals and lighting effects have been added, giving the game new life as well as helping to bridge the era between the original series entries and the new \"Sands of Time\" saga. To freshen the gameplay experience, new traps, puzzles and enemies have also been added.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nvMHo5rUr0w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U4DbHSCzZbA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939484-prince-of-persia-classic/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Prince-of-Persia-Arcade/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/prince-of-persia/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/prince-of-persia-classic"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Prince of Persia Wiki",
				"url":"http://princeofpersia.wikia.com/wiki/Prince_of_Persia_Classic"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":88,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["NinjaBee"],
			"synopsis":"Maal is an unhappy bug who needs structure and a purpose in his life, so he joins the royal army under the tutelage of the battle-hardened mantis warrior Tiernan. Now, he must begin his quest to save the Queen and the kingdom. NinjaBee's Band of Bugs puts you in Maal's shoes ... er, footpads, and sets you in the middle of a fast-playing, accessible, tactical strategy game designed specifically for Xbox LIVE Arcade.<br><br>This turn-based tactics game expands the genre by providing a unique Level Editor, allowing gamers to create levels and play them online with friends. One of the few turn-based tactics games available, Band of Bugs provides gameplay deep enough to be satisfying to established fans of the genre, but friendly enough to appeal to all types of casual gamers. The game includes a story-based campaign and stand-alone missions as well as several unique multiplayer modes: Elimination, Escape, and Capture. The game has fifty levels, but also features a Level Editor allowing you to design custom scenarios and play them solo or over Xbox LIVE with your friends.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Map Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2007/07/25",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This download consists of five new maps for multiplayer games and stand alone missions."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Map Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2007/07/25",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This download consists of five new maps for multiplayer games and stand alone missions."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Red Kingdom",
				"releaseDate":"2007/08/08",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Includes a new tile set (red rock) a new campaign consisting of ten levels and two new units (Cavalry and Siege Units). The units and tile set will be accessible to users of the Level Editor. Additionally, the tile set may override the defaults used in some levels of the initial game campaign."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Map Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2007/09/12",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This download consists of five new maps for multiplayer games and stand alone missions."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Ninja Sticks of Fury",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/10",
				"achievements":20,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Includes a new tile set (Snow) a new campaign consisting of ten levels and a new unit (Ninja). The unit and tile set will be accessible to users of the Level Editor. Additionally, the tile set may override the defaults used in some levels of the initial game campaign."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Tales of Kaloki",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/08",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Download the Tales of Kaloki expansion pack and experience some of the most game-changing DLC available. With a host of new features including spaceships, lasers, robotic villains and more, the new campaign launches your Band of Bugs game into the stars."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2aapArwqIJE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938058-band-of-bugs/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Band-of-Bugs/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/band-of-bugs/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/band-of-bugs"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":89,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sierra Online - Seattle"],
			"synopsis":"Named after the medieval fortified town of Carcassonne in southern France, famed for its city walls, Carcassonne for Xbox LIVE Arcade starts with an empty landscape and a single square tile. Using strategic tactics and a little luck, one to five players take turns selecting from 72 tiles displaying various features of a city including roads, the walls of a castle or fields. The medieval countryside thrives as players and their opponents place tiles and complete towns, roads, and farms while competing to accumulate the most points.<br><br>The rules of the game are easy with no elimination and fast gameplay - perfect for just about anyone! Although simple, devoted players will find layers of strategy that will keep them coming back for more. Combining a fresh visual experience and the opportunity to always have a playing partner, Carcassonne is the future for board game fanatics.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Rivers II Expansion Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/08/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This will add 12 new river tiles to the original game. There are no refunds for this item."
			},
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"King & Baron Expansion Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This will add 7 new tiles to the original game including a king and a robber tile that is earned in the game. Thus adding a new level of strategy not seen before in the original game or expansion packs."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KEmL2vcNpBo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JkI4cyh3WgQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g-2NmM4hfPg"
			},
			{
				"type":"How to play Carcassone (Board game)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kakQvPIKyPY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935186-carcassonne/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Carcassonne/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/carcassone/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/carcassonne"
			},
			{
				"type":"Board Game Wiki",
				"site":"Carcassonne Wiki",
				"url":"http://carcassonne.wikia.com/wiki/Carcassonne_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":90,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Stainless Games"],
			"synopsis":"While staying true to the original arcade classic, the enhanced \"Missile Command\" for Xbox LIVE Arcade has players acting as regional commander of three anti-missile batteries defending six cities in their zone. As Planet Zardon is under attack by an endless hail of interplanetary ballistic missiles from Krytol, players must act fast to fend off the missiles and keep their cities intact. Gliding across the sky, players complete levels by taking out all enemy weaponry. At the end of a level, players can earn bonus points for the more cities that remain and the fewer missiles that are used.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t3saNXJlxXc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay (Comparison)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A3wEyN4FA_k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Missile-Command/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/missile-command/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/missile-command"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":91,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SEGA"],
			"synopsis":"In Turtle Village, the children are fleeing for their lives! The invaders are brutal, ugly, and 12 feet tall, with huge arms, bellowing laughs, and fierce weapons for pounding you into the ground!<br><br>In this version of the classic arcade beat-em-up Golden Axe, three mighty heroes have a score to settle with the evil Death Adder. As a powerful fighter, a female Amazon, or a mighty dwarf, fight through Adder's henchmen with weapon and magic attacks, or ride the fearsome, fire-breathing dragon in Golden Axe.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uZM7BXDwAvc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942014-golden-axe/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Golden-Axe/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/golden-axe/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/golden-axe"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":92,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sonic Team"],
			"synopsis":"Sonic The Hedgehog brings Sonic to the Xbox 360. Everyone's favorite blue hedgehog dashes through some of your favorite stages in high definition with full leaderboard and achievement support. Sonic, the fastest blue hedgehog on earth, rockets through hair-raising loop-de-loops and take dizzying dives past bubbling lava, waterfalls and more! Gather up the rings and stop Dr.Eggman's (aka Dr. Robotnik) schemes for world domination!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=meWFmo5j3oE&list=PLpMHkY7NRFtWLDb9Wr1e0cO54BisXuvl1"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933063-sonic-the-hedgehog-live-arcade/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sonic-The-Hedgehog-XBLA/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sonic-the-hedgehog-arcade/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sonic-the-hedgehog-live-arcade"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sonic News Network",
				"url":"http://sonic.wikia.com/wiki/Sonic_the_Hedgehog_(1991)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":93,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Hudson Soft"],
			"synopsis":"Originally launched in the US in 1987, the game captured gamers' hearts with its simple yet challenging gameplay. With over 60 iterations on nearly all major consoles since then, and over 10 million units sold, winning accolades as the best multiplayer game of all time, this classic game has stood the test of time.<br><br>Fans can now compete with the best Bomberman players worldwide, as Bomberman Live delivers 8-player online. Fans can also play with their friends in 4-player local action on one system. In addition, Bomberman Live features new character customizations, which allow players to personalize their Bomberman from 10,000 possible combinations.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Bomb-up Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2007/08/29",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Can't get enough explosive Bomberman action? Grab this bomb-up pack and get 1 hot new game mode (Most Frags), 2 new arenas (Air Ship Attack & Viva Las Vegas!), and 10 crazy new characters, including a Dinosaur, Devil, and Alien! Download today!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Bomb-up Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2007/09/26",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Get more Bomberman bliss! Snag this bomb-up pack to get 1 new gameplay feature (Bomb Shelters), 2 new arenas (Speed Racer & Dreamland), and 10 new characters, including a wacky Jester, wispy Fairy, and a wicked Executioner! Download today! "
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Bomb-up Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/26",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Admit it, you're addicted to Bomberman Live! For all-new fiery fun, pick up this bomb-up pack, with 2 new arenas (Candy World & Inferno) and 10 new characters, including a body-slammin Wrestler, a fantastic Vampire, and a sneaky Ninja! Download today!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Fc9mrhpVmM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939528-bomberman-live/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bomberman-Live/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bomberman-live/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bomberman-live"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Bomberman Wiki",
				"url":"http://bomberman.wikia.com/wiki/Bomberman_Live"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":94,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"Training his whole life, Oolong is on a quest to become the ultimate champion. To fulfil his destiny, Oolong must face and defeat masters of the throwing shuriken, nunchaku, bo, chain and more at the Martial Arts Championship. With enhanced graphics, hand painted backgrounds and new achievements, this classic fighting game is sure to test any player's skills.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aPmY2lq4geQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935655-yie-ar-kung-fu/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Yie-Ar-KungFu/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/yie-ar-kung-fu/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/yie-ar-kung-fu"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":95,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"The fight for freedom continues! Reprise your role as either Bill Rizer or Lance Bean in this follow-up to the arcade classic Contra. The nefarious forces of Red Falcon have been wounded but they are far from defeated! The alien menace has taken control of a military installation in South America and they must be defeated for the sake of humanity. Experience the authentic gameplay of Super Contra with an updated look and feel by battling through several risky missions either solo or in two player co-op mode, just like in the original.<br><br>Play multiplayer over Xbox LIVE with upgraded graphics and sound. Do you have what it takes to save the world again?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EFnGymPWmro"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933055-super-contra/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Super-Contra/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/super-contra/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/super-contra"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Contra Wiki",
				"url":"http://contra.wikia.com/wiki/Super_Contra"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":96,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gaia Industries"],
			"synopsis":"Wing Commander Arena is a fast-paced space combat game where players can team up to attack other teams of ships. The game introduces the classic franchise to an arcade-style experience that allows up to 16 players online in battle at once. Players can propel their customized ship through space, fire torpedoes and unleash deadly gravity bombs as they try to climb the leader board. Online players will compete for Frag count, high score and dueling stats.<br><br>Wing Commander Arena features four styles of play: single player, multi-team, multi-player free for all and multi-player duel. Within the game there are eight game maps that include team maps, free for all maps and dueling maps, so Wing Commander Arena offers a gameplay experience for every Arcade gamer, whether they want a quick ten minutes of action or a longer more immersive game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1YvpvJHMxUg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tKvSHicBlOU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wing-Commander-Arena/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wing-commander-arena/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wing-commander-arena"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":97,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Freeverse", "Bungie Software"],
			"synopsis":"17 Years have passed since an alien race known as the Pfhor attacked the Tau Ceti colony destroying it and damaging the U.E.S.C. Marathon. Now, you have been awakened from your long stasis by the computer A.I. Durandal to uncover the mysteries of an ancient alien race known as the S'pht. Transported to the surface of Lh'owon armed only with a pistol, it is up to you to save humanity from the Pfhor, as they relentlessly search for the coordinates of Earth!<br><br>Bungie Studio's 1995 groundbreaking first-person shooter is now available on Xbox Live Arcade for the very first time! The compelling storyline of Marathon: Durandal stands on its own but also offers a clear intimation of the compelling gameplay, characters, and stories to come in Bungie's Halo franchise. This remake of Marathon: Durandal boasts all-new high definition graphics and support for 720p widescreen displays. A deep single player game is enhanced with 8-player co-op, \"King of the Hill\", \"Kill the Man with the Ball\" and \"Tag\" Live modes. An all new \"Survival Mode\" adds a quick arcade experience to the classic game. Live Leaderboards and Achievements (including four secret Achievements) let you track your progress through the game.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Jjaro Net Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/23",
				"achievements":30,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Download this in-game content for new maps. There are no refunds for this item."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Total Carnage Netmap Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/30",
				"achievements":20,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Somewhere in the heavens... they are waiting for even more multiplayer carnage. This map pack features hits from Marathon 1 and Infinity"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gCXJ-XXfgq0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z0VAPaXqrKA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/941993-marathon-durandal/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Marathon-Durandal/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/marathon-durandal/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/marathon-durandal"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Marathon Wiki",
				"url":"http://marathongame.wikia.com/wiki/Marathon_2:_Durandal"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":98,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Strange Flavour"],
			"synopsis":"Spyglass Board Games offers a fun new take on classic board games, like Chess, Checkers, Mancala, and Reversi. Play and chat socially on Xbox LIVE, or play against the computer. Use the Xbox LIVE Vision camera to personalize the game board, playing pieces, and video effects. Each game has custom pieces to choose from, such as a rook made of stone, or a furry checkers piece with cute gleaming eyes.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R5NoeYTsoDc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Spyglass-Board-Games/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/spyglass-board-games/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/spyglass-board-games"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":99,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software"],
			"synopsis":"The world title is on the line and you have to compete in six events to cement your legacy as a World Champion. Race the 100m Dash and 110m Hurdles, test your skills with the Javelin and Hammer Throw, and hop to it with the Long Jump and High Jump. Global leaderboards will compare your skills to see where you truly rank in the world.<br><br>The 1983 arcade hit from Konami has been given the Xbox Live Arcade treatment, offering players the same great gameplay as the original with authentic or enhanced graphics. And now, players can go head-to-head with up to four players on the same console or over Xbox Live.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jloJtTpKL9Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933059-track-and-field/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Track-and-Field/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/track-and-field/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/track-field"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":100,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Eclipse Software"],
			"synopsis":"An underwater storm has swept Ecco's family away, and it's up to you to help him find them. Using your sonar to guide you, you'll embark on an adventure of discovery and wonder as you come face-to-face with some of the dangers of the deep. Through 25 challenging levels, you'll be faced with a variety of puzzles, where the solution isn't always as obvious as you might think. The graphics are amazing, the gameplay is challenging, and the overall experience is one you'll never forget.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y1x1SeuPZDw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942661-ecco-the-dolphin/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ecco-the-Dolphin/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ecco-the-dolphin/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ecco-the-dolphin"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Ecco the Dophin Wiki",
				"url":"http://eccothedolphin.wikia.com/wiki/Ecco_the_Dolphin"
			}]
		}
	}]
}