{
	"catalog": [
	{
		"id":101,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"A next-gen entry in EA's rim-rockin', arcade-style street ball game. This entry in the franchise still allows you to throw down and go to town on others like any other NBA Street meet, but its focus is all about basketball giving hope to the streets that the sport is known in. Downtown streets are dangerous, and cities aren't always safe. There're villains, sure. But also, we've got heroes. And this game is about the heroes, the ballers whose skills on the court inspire those not sure which way to turn in life. In 3-on-3 basketball play, you battle to earn respect for your hometown. The ultimate goal is to beat NBA superstars from their hometown courts to the legendary parks across the land, finally putting your neighborhood on the map. Become a streetball legend, 90 feet at a time.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Street Legends & Brand Jordan Apparel",
				"releaseDate":"2007/05/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Adds the \"Street legends\", popular fictional characters from previous NBA Street games, and more Brand Jordan clothes for the player to wear."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=85sPjr0M5Mg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-m-E3Y9YbGs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-STREET-Homecourt/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-street-homecourt/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-street-homecourt"
			}]	
		}
	},
	{
		"id":102,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cavia"],
			"synopsis":"Set in 2013, Bullet Witch tells the story of a desperate fight between man, who is on the verge of extinction, and demons. You play as a witch named Alicia. Although the game clearly features some fantasy elements, it actually takes place in a realistic world setting. Bullet Witch is an action adventure with story sequences intermixed with gun fights and magic.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Dynamite Beauty",
				"releaseDate":"2007/03/28",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Mission: Dynamite Beauty - I am what you might call a witch. My allure breaks the hearts of all the men around me."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Clad in Streaming Black - Extra edition",
				"releaseDate":"2007/03/28",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Mission: Clad in Streaming Black - Extra Edition - \"Clad in Streaming Black\" has been redesigned for highly skilled players!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Caterpillar City",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/02",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Run through the streets exterminating Worm Men as you go until you reach the goal area!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"City of Screams Extra Edition",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/02",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"This is a harder version of City of Screams."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Endless",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/02",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Defeat the endless stream of Geists by destroying their source!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"White Witch",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/04",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The black-clad witch heads off to battle dressed in white. Behold the white witch Alicia."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Mummy Costume",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"My body is covered in bandages...but I'll keep fighting on despite my wounds!"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"10,000 ft of Flames Extra Edition",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/23",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"A harder version of 10,000 ft of Flames"
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"7 Minutes",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/23",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"In this time bomb operation, meet up with the Resistance waiting outside of the airport!"
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Schoolgirl Costume",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The \"Bullet Witch\" becomes a \"Bullet High-Schooler\"."
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Dawn in the Valley Extra Edition",
				"releaseDate":"2007/05/14",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"A harder version of Dawn in the Valley."
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Secretary Costume",
				"releaseDate":"2007/05/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Eyes like gun barrels hidden behind glasses."
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"The Bound Soul Extra Edition",
				"releaseDate":"2007/06/04",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"A harder version of The Bound Soul."
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"Geist Search and Destroy",
				"releaseDate":"2007/06/04",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Defeat the 50 hidden Geists within 30 minutes!"
			},
			{
				"id":15,
				"name":"Pixie Costume",
				"releaseDate":"2007/06/11",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The super hero Alicia has come to Earth from outer space to fight for justice!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_Cmu1WpjK-0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rnN9mwpomAI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/931220-bullet-witch/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bullet-Witch/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bulletwitch/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bullet-witch"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":103,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Kush Games"],
			"synopsis":"It's a whole new ballgame! Major League Baseball 2K7 redefines the pure baseball video game experience with true, next-gen details, all-new throwing mechanics and a revolutionary presentation system. Fielder positioning, relay and cutoff A.I. has been redesigned to allow for better, more authentic Major League defensive play. Defensive alignments are now based on who is at the plate. The Dynamic Throwing System is a responsive throwing mechanics coupled with unique animations for infield, outfield and situational throws. On the stats side, Inside Edge data is now tied into control at the plate. Playing into your pitcher's or hitter's strengths will now reward you with a boost in hitting power. And with the power of next-generation consoles, everything that you see about the players - faces, body type, accessories, uniforms and hats - match their real-world counterparts down to the minutest details.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GcCLIv2D5CM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yUqToL8PhJw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/936391-major-league-baseball-2k7/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MLB-2K7/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mlb-2k7/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/major-league-baseball-2k7"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":104,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Omega Force"],
			"synopsis":"Koei brings its tactical sim Empires concept on Omega Force's non-stop combat set of series (previously seen in Dynasty Warriors 5 Empires) to the world of Samurai Warriors. At the start of the game Feudal Japan is divided into warring states and it is up to the player to resurrect a nation using equal amounts of strategy and strength! The game's ultimate goal is to unite Japan's 25 regions into a single nation under one ruler. Prior to each battle, the player will meet with their war council to discuss military and political affairs; then it's time for combat. Using the unique tactical play of the Empires series, the game's deck of 90 policy cards, used to issue military commands and impose political policies, is boosted by 50 new cards inspired by Japanese history, while all-new formation cards are based on historically-authentic samurai attack formations.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YCz5P5Qpv5Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay (PS2)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AL7Sev83jVQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/937212-samurai-warriors-2-empires/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Samurai-Warriors-2-Empires/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/samurai-warriors-2-empires/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/samurai-warriors-2-empires"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Koei Wiki",
				"url":"http://koei.wikia.com/wiki/Samurai_Warriors_2:_Empires"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":105,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Chicago"],
			"synopsis":"Incorporating hip-hop culture into every aspect of the game, Def Jam: Icon delivers the intensity of a no-holds-barred street fight but with style and rhythm. Players can live out the life of a hip hop mogul, going from rags to riches. Music will effect how players fight in each venue and environmental interactions and hazards will become a key strategy to staying alive.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9WMkwXI4DCY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Au3XTCklL4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Def-Jam-Icon/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/def-jam-icon/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/def-jam-icon"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":106,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Red Storm Entertainment", "Ubisoft Paris"],
			"synopsis":"Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter 2 builds off of the events in the first game and places gamers in control of the U.S. military's elite fighting unit, the Ghosts. In the year 2014, the rising conflict between Mexican loyalists and insurgent rebel forces has thrown Mexico into full-scale civil war. Under the command of Captain Scott Mitchell, the Ghosts are called upon to face an imminent threat to the United States. The fate of two countries now lies in the hands of the Ghosts as they fend off an attack on U.S. soil. Equipped with the most cutting-edge weaponry and technology, the Ghosts must battle on both sides of the border to neutralize the escalating rebel threat.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Throwback Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2007/08/23",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Adds classic maps from past Ghost Recon games. The maps include: Bonfires, Desert Gulch, Fishing Village, Jungle Mines, Mountain Base, Mountain Falls, and Peninsula."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Throwback Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2007/08/28",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Adds 7 classic maps from past Ghost Recon games. In addition to the 7 maps, there is a new game mode called Co-op Exfiltration. All of these maps have upgraded visuals and support all of GRAW2's thousands of customizable game modes."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"More Guns pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/01/29",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Adds 8 additional weapons to be used in the Single Player."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Co-Op Collection",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/04",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The GRAW 2 Co-op Collection brings back some of the greatest maps in Ghost Recon history and let's you cooperate and compete in exciting new locales. An all new co-op campaign with 5 missions takes you back to some of the greatest locations from the Ghost Recon franchise. Inspired from the original Ghost Recon and remade to the stunning benchmark from GRAW 2. 9 new adversarial maps - 7 inspired from the greatest in the franchise and 2 brand new maps. Classic tactical combat in open areas with weather effects and close combat across rooftops. 9 new Achievements with a total of 125 points. Exciting new challenges that encourage different tactics. The ghosts are back again."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Co-Op Collection 2",
				"releaseDate":"2008/08/23",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"GRAW 2 Co-op Collection 2 brings back some of the greatest maps in Ghost Recon history and let's you cooperate and compete in exciting new locales. An all new co-op campaign with 5 missions takes you back to some of the greatest locations from the Ghost Recon franchise. Inspired from the original Ghost Recon and remade to the stunning benchmark from GRAW 2. 9 new adversarial maps - 7 inspired from the greatest in the franchise and 2 brand new maps. 8 new Achievements with a total of 125 points. Exciting new challenges that encourage different tactics. The ghosts are back again."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_Dq_90XmQus"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C04StoQONGE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/937003-tom-clancys-ghost-recon-advanced-warfighter-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tom-Clancys-Ghost-Recon-Advanced-Warfighter-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ghost-recon-aw-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tom-clancys-ghost-recon-advanced-warfighter-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Ghost Recon Wiki",
				"url":"http://ghostrecon.wikia.com/wiki/Tom_Clancy's_Ghost_Recon:_Advanced_Warfighter_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":107,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Mass Media"],
			"synopsis":"In Tetris Evolution for the Xbox Live Arcade players will enjoy not only traditional Tetris gameplay but numerous new modes including \"Go Low\" and \"Eraser\" for both single and multiplayer. The multiplayer mode not only allows for up to four players on a single console, but players can now compete with up to four players via the Xbox Live online entertainment service. There is also a new intelligent matchmaking system, which pits players against others within their skill level, as well as the online ladder system, which will enable players to track their overall skill level and accumulate Xbox Live achievement points to increase their Gamerscore.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=42zh_RA6njk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938250-tetris-evolution/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tetris-Evolution/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tetris-evolution/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tetris-evolution"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":108,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FromSoftware"],
			"synopsis":"Armored Core, the mech action game that defined the mech genre is back to take on next-generation platforms! Armored Core 4 reinvigorates the brand by offering an all-new storyline, new environments, and online capability. The 10th anniversary of the acclaimed franchise is punctuated with a leap to next-generation platforms that will ensure a new quality level in both gameplay and visual performance.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vh1Dk9VSRyQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7PPDF-5dGL0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930035-armored-core-4/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Armored-Core-4/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/armored-core-4/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/armored-core-4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Armored Core Wiki",
				"url":"http://armoredcore.wikia.com/wiki/Armored_Core_4"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":109,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sandlot"],
			"synopsis":"The Earth Defense Force needs you!! Planet Earth is under attack from alien invaders, and the EDF is our only chance for survival. Grab your gun, join your squad and repel the attacking forces in this action-packed, arcade-style shooter. Though the odds may seem impossible, you are not alone. Fighting by your side are your AI controlled Earth Defense Force teammates. This crew of soldiers will fearlessly charge into battle and assist you throughout the game. Join-up with a friend in co-op mode and work together to battle your way through the alien swarms. Take control of battle tanks, armored mechs, attack helicopters and hover bikes to help complete your mission across more than 50 missions.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_BWHyRCw3JI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3bW6kBcoWIw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/929255-earth-defense-force-2017/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Earth-Defense-Force-2017/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/earth-defense-force-2017/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/earth-defense-force-2017"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Earth Defense Force Wiki",
				"url":"http://theearthdefenseforce.wikia.com/wiki/Earth_Defense_Force_2017"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":110,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"This Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles game is based on the CG animated movie produced by Imagi Animation Studios and based on Mirage Studios' Foot Clan-kicking Turtle heroes. The game takes place in a New York City plagued by secretive villains and strange, otherworldly creatures. Faced with these perils, the Turtles will experience their most trying time as heroes and as a family, as Raphael, Donatello and Michelangelo lose their focus and struggle to maintain their unity and ninja discipline. It's up to Leonardo and the faithful father figure Splinter to reunite the band of brothers and save New York City from a monstrous evil that lurks around every corner. Players engage in over-the-top acrobatic navigation, collaborative combat and powerful fighting moves.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KI3GoN6WZ-Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aggjVNa2T9k"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/934472-tmnt/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/TMNT/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tmnt/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tmnt"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Turtlepedia",
				"url":"http://turtlepedia.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":111,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"The Xbox 360 version of UEFA Champions League 2006-2007 introduces a new way to play the game by introducing a unique virtual card system in the Ultimate Team mode that enables players to develop their team. This complements the traditional way of playing as their favorite club team from qualification right through to a virtual reproduction of the championship final. Plus, UEFA Champions League 2006-2007 features new game modes to test the most skillful players at the highest levels.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9qmsBL1Byvg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5dFG2TclgHI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/937756-uefa-champions-league-2006-2007/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/UEFA-CL-2006-2007/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/uefa-champions-league-2006-2007/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/uefa-champions-league-2006-2007"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":112,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sumo Digital", "SEGA"],
			"synopsis":"Virtua Tennis returns with enhanced, photo-realistic graphics and advanced player animations that perfectly match the behavior and mannerisms of individual professional athletes. Improvements to the game's AI have also upped the challenge to becoming the top seed of the tennis world.<br><br>In Career Mode, gamers will travel the world and take on the biggest stars of the tennis world. Improvements to the Player Creation Mode allow gamers to customize their own tennis star with a wealth of licensed tennis equipment and increased detail like never before. And, in addition to the popular mini-games from previous titles used to sharpen players' skills, there are a whole host of brand new challenges to keep players in top form.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yki0r2tgRis"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hhPJsK76dvI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932685-virtua-tennis-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Virtua-Tennis-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/virtua-tennis-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/virtua-tennis-3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":113,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Avalanche Software"],
			"synopsis":"Disney's Meet the Robinsons, based on the Walt Disney Pictures animated film, is a time-traveling action/adventure game. Players experience the adventure as Wilbur Robinson, helping him chase the dastardly Bowler Hat Guy and his diabolical robotic hat Doris through multiple timelines in an attempt to thwart their evil plans. The game weaves in and out of the film's plot, expanding the Robinson world and offering an all-new adventure. Wilbur will have a host of gadgets at his disposal as he battles enemies and solves puzzles while pursuing Bowler Hat Guy and trying not to alter the future.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kC_pFmh3qRU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/937748-disneys-meet-the-robinsons/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Meet-the-Robinsons/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/meet-the-robinsons/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/disneys-meet-the-robinsons"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":114,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"RedOctane's follow-up to the critically acclaimed rhythm game. Guitar Hero II features a brand-new and expanded track list, more venues and new play modes, and aims to rock longer and harder than its predecessor. RedOctane has once again teamed up with veteran music game developer Harmonix for the sequel, and is using famed recording studio WaveGroup for its music production, who also recorded the covers for the licensed tracks in the original Guitar Hero. The Xbox 360 version also adds 10 new songs, downloadable content features, leaderboards and online features, plus support for the Guitar Hero X-Plorer guitar controller.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable tracks",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/03",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"24 tracks available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ItBBkiEYOvs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VNuO-Lx_B4Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935834-guitar-hero-ii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Guitar-Hero-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/guitar-hero-ii/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/guitar-hero-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wikihero",
				"url":"http://guitarhero.wikia.com/wiki/Guitar_Hero_II_(Xbox_360)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":115,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montpellier"],
			"synopsis":"Rayman Raving Rabbids marks the return of the iconic video-game hero, Rayman, in his funniest and zaniest adventure ever. When the world of Rayman is threatened by a devastating invasion of crazed, out-of-control bunnies Rayman must rise up against his furry foes to foil their wicked plans. Utilizing an array of amazing new abilities, and with the help of magical creatures, Rayman must break out all the moves to save his world from these delirious bunnies and their hare-raising antics.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Fcw-SLJ7aw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1SrAy4mSAQw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rayman-Raving-Rabbids/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rayman-raving-rabbids/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rayman-raving-rabbids"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Rayman Wiki",
				"url":"http://rayman.wikia.com/wiki/Rayman_Raving_Rabbids"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":116,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Treyarch"],
			"synopsis":"Spider-Man 3 allows players to experience the actions of heroic red-suited Spider-Man and, for the first time ever, his darker, more mysterious black-suited persona. Set in a larger, dynamic, free-roaming New York City, the game gives players the freedom to choose their own gameplay experience through multiple movie-based and original storylines, fully integrated city missions and performance rewards including improved speed, combat maneuvers and agility. In Spider-Man 3, players draw upon Spider-Man's completely revamped combat abilities as they protect the city and defeat nemeses using expanded aerial fighting, finishing moves and dynamic webbing during missions and epic boss battles.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"New Goblin",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This adds the New Goblin (Harry Osborn) as a playable character. Rip through the City on your sky stick while deploying an arsenal of weapons against your foes."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EpVSLHVCA6k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lVVf0LaXa6c"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932030-spider-man-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Spider-Man-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/spider-man-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/spider-man-3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":117,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Los Angeles"],
			"synopsis":"Command & Conquer 3 gets the series back to its roots in the Tiberium universe, with new gameplay features that rewards players for their own unique play styles. Beyond the new story and gameplay tweaks, added new features include voice-over IP, integrated clan support, and new spectator modes.<br><br>It is 2047 and the stakes could not be higher. Tiberium - a self-replicating alien substance that has infected the Earth - is spreading like a radioactive ice age. The GDI, a high-tech alliance of the world's most advanced nations, is fighting to contain Tiberium, but Kane, the megalomaniacal leader of The Brotherhood of NOD has other plans for Earth. Kane's secret society turned superpower is bent on using Tiberium to take control and transform humanity into his twisted vision of the future. All-out war rages over Tiberium and the fate of the planet rests in the balance.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/06/19",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"What kind of commander are you? Are you a defensive specialist, an air-superiority junkie, or a clandestine operations fanatic? Whatever your preferred strategy, test your skills and your wits against other commanders in five new multiplayer maps. Ranging from brutal 1v1 shootouts to gigantic 2v2 showdowns, this pack has something for every commander. Includes: Black's Bigger Battle | Tiber River Valley | Frontier Fracas | Tiberium Gardens III | Tournament Desert Redux. All maps are playable in single-player skirmish mode as well."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Ground Zero Map",
				"releaseDate":"2007/06/19",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Lead your army against a rival commander in this 1v1 map featuring a huge meteor impact crater. Download this free map now! This map is also playable in single-player skirmish mode."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=er_r4E5l_18"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlhaV8WV68g"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/936936-command-and-conquer-3-tiberium-wars/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Command-Conquer-3-Tiberium-Wars/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/command-conquer-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/command-conquer-3-tiberium-wars"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Command & Conquer Wiki",
				"url":"http://cnc.wikia.com/wiki/Command_%26_Conquer_3:_Tiberium_Wars"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":118,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["7 Studios"],
			"synopsis":"In Shrek the Third, players adventure as Shrek and his friends to save Far Far Away in a hilariously twisted fairy tale from the movie and beyond. Fans play as their favorite heroes from the film: Shrek, Donkey, Puss-in-Boots, Fiona, Fiona's rebellious cousin Arthur and her fellow fairy tale heroine Sleeping Beauty. The game takes players on an epic journey through the worlds of Far Far Away after Prince Charming storms the city with an army of villains in order to seize the throne. Players are challenged to rescue pals, face off against Charming's henchmen, gather collectibles, test their gaming skills in numerous boss fights and engage in various mini-games that can be played in single-player or multiplayer modes.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WYpJl-mnBGk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ltdt9sPlbxY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935725-dreamworks-shrek-the-third/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Shrek-the-Third/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/shrek-the-3rd/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dreamworks-shrek-the-third"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":119,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eurocom"],
			"synopsis":"Live and die by the sword! Pirates of the Caribbean: At World's End is inspired by the events, environments and characters of both the Pirates of the Caribbean: At World's End and Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man's Chest films. Players must demonstrate their bravery and swordsmanship as they encounter all manner of crazed pirates and cursed creatures in treacherous, exotic locations. Play as Captain Jack Sparrow, Will Turner and Elizabeth Swann to prevent Jack's dark past from catching up with him.<br><br>Enjoy sword-assisted acrobatics, adaptive combat and classical dueling in unique gameplay. Experience the Pirates of the Caribbean world in never-before-seen detail, going beyond the films' events and storylines to introduce new locations, an extended story, legendary pirates and a unique ending.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EAmBoduzpHg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KdHYmQO5l_Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933119-pirates-of-the-caribbean-at-worlds-end/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pirates-of-the-Caribbean-At-Worlds-End/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pirates-of-the-caribbean-at-worlds-end/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pirates-of-the-caribbean-at-worlds-end"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Pirates of the Caribbean Wiki",
				"url":"http://pirates.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":120,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Turn 10 Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Forza 2 includes everything from Corvettes to Lamborghinis and includes many of the favorite features from the Xbox version of the game. However, the jump to 360 has also brought a few changes. The racing assists have been upgraded, the line that guides players along the sweet spot of the track dynamically changes color from green to red to show drivers when to break and accelerate, and the physics engine from the first game has also been rebuilt boasting about 360 calculations per second that contribute to exactly how the car reacts to the road.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"September Car Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/09/21",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Eleven New Cars: #8 Audi Sport Team Joest Audi R10 TDI, 1967 Lamborghini Miura P400, Lamborghini Miura Concept, Porsche 911 GT3 RS (997), 1970 Dodge Challenger R/T Hemi, Dodge Challenger Concept, Honda Civic Si Coupe, Honda Civic Type-R, Saturn Sky Red Line, SEAT Leon Supercup, SEAT Leon Cupra."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Motegi Track Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/26",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Japan's famous Twin Ring Motegi. This track pack includes four different routes, Super Speedway Oval and three road courses that range from very short with long straights for maximum speed, to very long with varied turns."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Road America Track",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/07",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"This track features 14 technical corners with plenty of elevation changes, high-speed straights and challenging bends."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"December Car Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/09",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Eleven New Cars: Audi R8, Audi Sport Quattro, BMW Motorsport M3 E30, Ferrari 599 GTB Fiorano, Ferrari FXX, Koenigsegg CCGT, Lamborghini Gallardo Superleggera, Pontiac Trans Am SD-455, Porsche 911 GT1 (996), Renault 5 Turbo, Renault Clio Renaultsport 197."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"March Car Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/19",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Thirteen New Cars: #1 Peugeot 207 Super 2000, Audi S5, Audi TT Coupe S-Line, BMW Motorsport M3 E92 1971, BMW Motorsport 3.0 CSL, Ferrari F50 GT, Ferrari 430 Scuderia, Ferrari F40 Competizione,Lamborghini Murcielago LP640, Maserati GranTurismo, Maserati MC12 Corsa, Mitsubishi Lancer Evolution X GSR, Porsche 911 GT2 (997)"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y3U5JUT51fA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9BPQmbAi0Mg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932731-forza-motorsport-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Forza-Motorsport-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/forza-motorsport-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/forza-motorsport-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Forza Motorsport Wiki",
				"url":"http://forzamotorsport.wikia.com/wiki/Forza_Motorsport_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":121,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FASA Studio", "Microsoft Game Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the revered paper-and-pen RPG (and short run of game releases), this next-gen Shadowrun combines first-person shooter gameplay with the complications of the RPG series.<br><br>In Shadowrun players vie for supremacy in an intense first-person shooter (FPS) experience that rewards cleverness, cunning and split-second improvisation through a unique combination of modern weapons, ancient magic and advanced technology. Up to 16 players can battle together across Xbox 360 and Windows Vista through the Xbox LIVE and Games for Windows - LIVE gaming and entertainment network.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZXJSLFKLwHM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uMNlOYlwRlc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/929196-shadowrun/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Shadowrun/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/shadowrun/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/shadowrun"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Shadowrun Wiki",
				"url":"http://shadowrun.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":122,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"Surf's Up is a surfing game set at the annual \"Reggie Belafonte Big Z Memorial Surf Off.\" Players choose from one of 10 characters from the film \"Surf's Up\" to play as, including Cody, the young challenger from Shiverpool; Tank, the merciless champion; or Big Z, the surfing legend from the past. Only by mastering and understanding the waves can the player become not only the new champion, but a true surf legend.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4BSW3Wl5kJA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Surfs-Up/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/surfs-up/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/surfs-up"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":123,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["G.Rev"],
			"synopsis":"G.rev's massively maniacal flying shooter game comes to the Xbox 360, with screen-filling special effects, online Xbox Live features and more. WarTech Senko no Ronde thrusts players into a distant future where humanity has colonized countless new galaxies and Earth has become a planet mined for its natural resources. A violent war has erupted as nations struggle for world domination. Rounder Mechs fill the skies as the fate of the world is determined through aerial combat. Players must take control of these \"Rider\" machines, making use of shields and dashes in order to evade opponent attacks. Players can play offline or participate in online play over Xbox Live.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h6Ps3yt_lMQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V7g756UtTQs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/929922-wartech-senko-no-ronde/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/WarTech-Senko-No-Ronde/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wartech-senko-no-ronde/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wartech-senko-no-ronde"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":124,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Techland"],
			"synopsis":"Call of Juarez is an epic adventure western themed FPS game. The game's plot is located in 19th century Wild West, with the player taking the roles of Billy, a sneaking fugitive, and the reverend Ray, the uncompromising bounty hunter on his trail. Fast paced revolver duels using historically accurate firearms, horseback riding and stealth action in memorable locations set after Western movies.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iB4xu1Zn7yw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fWf5tdWuI9M"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938524-call-of-juarez/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Call-of-Juarez/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/call-of-juarez/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/call-of-juarez"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Call of Juarez Wiki",
				"url":"http://callofjuarez.wikia.com/wiki/Project_McCall,_the_Call_of_Juarez_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":125,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Artificial Studios", "Immersion Games"],
			"synopsis":"Four friends get together for a party while the parents are away, but somebody... or something, is about to crash the party. In four-player melee action, you will fight off the monster invasion in this top-down action/shooting game. Customize and build your own weapons by grabbing parts from the house and town to create more powerful attack tools, and find rare parts to build some ultimate weapons. Jack abandoned vehicles and deck them out with weapons to ride through the terrain and take out creatures. Visit five locations, including the suburban town, the high school, and the \"Shopping Maul\". The use of the Ageia NovodeX Physics platform allows you to interact with the environments physics to give yourself an advantage, such as creating barrides or throwing large objects, while the visual system uses the advanced Unreal 3 Engine.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v2Wjx2LmeFI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zrm3dE8sJgA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928851-monster-madness-battle-for-suburbia/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Monster-Madness/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/monster-madness/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/monster-madness-battle-for-suburbia"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":126,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["K2", "FromSoftware"],
			"synopsis":"An installment in the ninja stealth series that is made exclusively for the Xbox 360. This time, the main protagonists are player-created characters who can be customized with many different special moves and costume accessories. This is also the first stealth action game to feature a cooperative 4-player mode, via system link or Xbox Live.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A_vBcCH1GAY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OSRH4xFaqGU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930036-tenchu-z/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tenchu-Z/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tenchu-z/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tenchu-z"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tenchu Wiki",
				"url":"http://tenchu.wikia.com/wiki/Tenchu_Z"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":127,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"Fantastic Four: Rise of the Silver Surfer features Marvel Entertainment's legendary super-powered foursome in its second big adventure. In the game and the film, Marvel's first family of Super Heroes faces its greatest challenge yet as the enigmatic, intergalactic herald, the Silver Surfer, comes to Earth to prepare it for destruction. As the Silver Surfer races around the globe wreaking havoc, the team must unravel the mystery of the Silver Surfer and confront the surprising return of their mortal enemy, Dr. Doom, before all hope is lost!<br><br>The game is based on both the popular comic book series, as well as the movie sequel, with exclusive plot elements that complement the film. It features all of the foursome's over-the-top super powers, as well as a unique fusion attack system that allows players to combine forces with one, two or all teammates, in order to execute devastating team attacks against the opposition. In addition to fighting familiar enemies from the Fantastic Four universe, players can unlock alternative costumes, comic covers and more!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OO_79cAm9rk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZXZVvOT0BfY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fantastic-4-Rise-of-the-Silver-Surfer/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fantastic-4-rise-of-the-silver-surfer/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fantastic-four-rise-of-the-silver-surfer"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":128,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Codemasters"],
			"synopsis":"A reinvigorated McRae rally ride, built for next-gen systems for the realistic feel of racing off-road. This edition goes beyond the series' point-to-point rallying to deliver its most diverse selection of extreme off-road competitions yet. Sensational gravel, mud and dirt racing events from the world over will include perilous Hill Climb, collision-packed Rally Cross events, and grueling C.O.R.R. (Championship Off-Road Racing) events. The game also features international rallying competitions, with official cars on tracks based on real roads and locations around the globe. McCrae expands on beat-the-clock racing and include events with multiple cars on track to satisfy gamers who want to push their on-the-edge driving further. This 2007 edition also features official cars and official events across a wide variety of off-road and rally disciplines, the most authentic and thrilling tracks ever in a McRae game, and modes that make the most of online multiplayer.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5JmKkooR2c8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_3iRmbzWye8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932886-dirt/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/DiRT/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dirt/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dirt"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Colin McRae DiRT Wiki",
				"url":"http://dirt.wikia.com/wiki/Colin_McRae_DiRT"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":129,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blue Castle Games", "Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"This over-the-top baseball action title puts an entirely new spin on Major League Baseball as it blends outrageous visuals and intuitive gameplay mechanics to bring fans a brand new MLB video game experience. Developed by Blue Castle Games, The Bigs brings blazing graphics to huge proportions with larger-than-life MLB player models and ballparks as gamers take advantage of spectacular power-ups with outrageous special effects.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-t6w4ujdINs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bZ5Uu4vLSCM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/936446-the-bigs/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-BIGS/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-bigs/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-bigs"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":130,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Starbreeze"],
			"synopsis":"On the eve of his 21st birthday, fearless mafia hitman Jackie Estacado is suddenly possessed by the terrifying and spectacular powers of The Darkness. Though his supernatural entity lets him wreak terrible havoc on his enemies, the Darkness also has a strong will of its own and now Jackie must learn how to control it. Gameplay features include a seamless and unique blend of modern crime drama and supernatural horror with both first and third person non-linear progression, ad well as highly destructible environments that enable players to stalk the gritty New York slums, harbors, subway tunnels and rooftops, then defeat the terrifying creatures of The Otherworld-a parallel reality where the Darkness dwells.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tmR3hYzjr1U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VaY7wU_r__o"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/927014-the-darkness/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Darkness/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-darkness/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-darkness"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Darkness Wiki",
				"url":"http://thedarkness.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":131,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA UK"],
			"synopsis":"In Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix, Harry returns for his fifth year of study at Hogwarts and discovers that much of the wizarding community is in denial about the teenager's recent encounter with the evil Lord Voldemort. The Minister for Magic has decided to teach courses in defensive magic, but this leaves the young wizards woefully unprepared to defend themselves against the dark forces threatening them. Meeting secretly with a small group of students who name themselves \"Dumbledore's Army\", Harry has taken it upon himself to teach them how to defend themselves against the Dark Arts, preparing the courageous young wizards for the extraordinary battle that lies ahead.<br><br>With the ability to play multiple characters (including Harry Potter, Dumbledore and Sirius Black) this Harry Potter videogame offers fans the opportunity to wield a wand, explore all around Hogwarts, and experience one of the most exciting and dangerous years in the life of the Boy Who Lived.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zh_zDN6TmBQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jqKlnGl1xpU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/936994-harry-potter-and-the-order-of-the-phoenix/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Harry-Potter-and-the-Order-of-the-Phoenix/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/harry-potter-and-the-order-of-the-phoenix/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/harry-potter-and-the-order-of-the-phoenix"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Harry Potter Wiki",
				"url":"http://harrypotter.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":132,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["N-Fusion Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Hour of Victory allows you to play a key role in the pivotal and cinematic battles from the European and North African theaters of World War II, using the skills and gameplay style you choose. Sneak into enemy territory as a covert operative, storm the gates as a British Commando, or snipe from afar as an Army Ranger - each character's unique attributes will be needed for the fulfillment of the overall objective. Only with all these skills working closely together will you be able to say that you helped define the Hour of Victory.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q-tai7nIZxA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-y5hfilzkHs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hour-of-Victory/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hour-of-victory/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hour-of-victory"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":133,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Triumph Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Taking control of a mysterious figure that has inherited the legacy of the long-dead evil Overlord, the player emerges near death from the ruins of the old Overlord's Dark Tower. Only the player's actions will determine if they will rise to become the new all-powerful Overlord; it's all up to how bad they want to be in order to succeed ... evil or really evil! With a dark sense of humor, the game immerses players in twisted parodies of classic fantasy stories and characters. In a unique twist, players will have control over an army of an army of Minions that will use their unique skills to fetch, fight and die for their new Overlord. Throughout the game players will actively control a horde of these gremlin-like creatures that will follow every bidding no matter how whimsical or life threatening it may be.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Challenge Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/14",
				"achievements":110,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Get 7 great new Multiplayer maps to play against your friends and foes. Select them from your Multiplayer (or if you've downloaded it, Split Screen) option and enjoy! Plus, start a New Game to experience Legendary difficulty mode. You will need to use all your minion managing and tactical skills to win under these bad-ass circumstances. Are you Overlord enough?"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Raising Hell",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/15",
				"achievements":140,
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Your rise as the Overlord reborn has sent shivers through the very fabric of the cosmos - and in your conquered lands gateways are opening... Defeat the first Hero and gain access to the first Raising Hell Abyss and hours of new single player story. As you progress youll uncover unique armor and weapons, all new minion upgrades and the toughest ever Dungeon Challenges! IMPORTANT MESSAGE FROM GNARL: Master, if you are close to completing Overlord you will have to defeat the final corrupted heroes for the first Abyss to become active."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Split Screen Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/21",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Download this free update to play head-to-head in the great new Split Screen mode (you'll need two controllers). Plus a new Survival map - Rocky Race, in which you'll have to escape from an advancing Super Rock Giant!. Select as you would another map and enjoy!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Ll9p7JSc2o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7uqv3tLx45A"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932853-overlord/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Overlord/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/overlord/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/overlord"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Overlord Wiki",
				"url":"http://overlord.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":134,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Heavy Iron Studios"],
			"synopsis":"In Disney/Pixar's animated adventure, a rat named Remy dreams of becoming a great French chef despite his family's wishes and the obvious problem of being a rat in a decidedly rodent-phobic profession. When fate places Remy in the sewers of Paris, he finds himself ideally situated beneath a restaurant made famous by his culinary hero, Auguste Gusteau.<br><br>In the game, players will assume the role of Remy and relive some of the film's most thrilling moments. Players will instantly recognize the storyline, characters and key locations of Ratatouille, as they engage in a series of unique mini-games, cooking challenges and head-to-head multiplayer. Ratatouille will allow players to create culinary masterpieces, evade detection from dangerous and often hungry enemies, and brave the perils of the dinner-rush in this senses-shattering journey to fulfill Remy's life-long dream of becoming a great chef.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7J8E9jlfaUg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9agv9yMnkdk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ratatouille/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ratatouille/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/disneypixar-ratatouille"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":135,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Traveller's Tales"],
			"synopsis":"Based on Paramount Pictures' live-action feature film, Transformers: The Game lets gamers control the outcome in the battle for Earth as they choose to protect it as Autobots or destroy it as Decepticons and experience the unstoppable power and massive scale of their favorite robots in disguise. As the Transformers' war comes to Earth, gamers make the choice to join the Autobots in protecting our planet or to join the Decepticons in destroying it. With dual campaigns, the fate of the world is in players' hands.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LwBJS-dMSsU&spfreload=1"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ddpR6uu5Vsc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932116-transformers-the-game/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Transformers-The-Game/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/transformers-the-game/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/transformers-the-game"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Transformers Wiki",
				"url":"http://transformers.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":136,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Artoon"],
			"synopsis":"Vampire Rain takes place in a city in suburban Los Angeles, where vampires have been determined to reside. Players take control of a special operative called John Lloyd and, having entered the city, must wipe out the vampires. The player must then traverse all areas of an eerie and rain soaked city by moving across rooftops and through back alleys, avoiding detection to ensure the best strategic use of high-tech weaponry.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"VR Bonus Level 1",
				"releaseDate":"2007/07/25",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Thanks for supporting Vampire Rain. Want to test your Sneak Attack skills? Play as Claire Kelly in this bonus level to Eliminate Nightwalkers using only the UV Knife for Sneak Attacks. Difficulty: 5 stars."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"VR Bonus Level 2",
				"releaseDate":"2007/07/25",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Thanks for supporting Vampire Rain. Ready for another gathering mission? Play as Duane Hanson in this bonus level to see how fast you can pick up all required equipment for your mission. Difficulty: 3 stars."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GyQhuZnXNK4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fyT6lMCbFTI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Vampire-Rain/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/vampire-rain/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/vampire-rain"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":137,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Game Arts", "Seta Corporation"],
			"synopsis":"Reminiscent of summer days spent hunched-over a coin-op machine in a dark arcade, Project Sylpheed is a 3-D makeover of the classic, mid-'80s scrolling shooter franchise. As Katana Faraway, players must pilot a Delta Saber space fighter equipped with a highly customizable arsenal of weapons. In order to succeed, Katana must execute squadron commands and monitor their speed, shield, radar and weapons as they maneuver out of challenging situations and defend Earth against the evil ADAN forces.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"6 New Missions & Weapons + Leaderboards",
				"releaseDate":"2007/07/25",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Think you are truly an ace pilot? 6 new missions will challenge your skills and add 6 new super-weapons to your arsenal plus Xbox Live Leaderboard suppport to track your rank. Requires Project Sylpheed full retail game. Access Challenge Missions from the EXTRAS menu."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MXH-3LwLF5o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R58PTRdtkFA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932514-project-sylpheed-arc-of-deception/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Project-Sylpheed/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/project-sylpheed/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/project-sylpheed-arc-of-deception"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":138,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"2K Sports brings football back to its videogame line-up with All-Pro Football 2K8, featuring legends of the gridiron brought together for a showdown of the greatest of the greats. The critically acclaimed 2K football gameplay engine has been brought up to the standards of next-gen consoles team, with innovative new features and hi-def visuals.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"2K ReelMaker",
				"releaseDate":"2007/07/18",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Download this powerful replay editor and construct your own highlight reels!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UWa92QL6SO0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IW78Yt8p8M0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938065-all-pro-football-2k8/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/All-Pro-Football-2K8/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/all-pro-football-2k8/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/all-pro-football-2k8"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":139,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"In NCAA Football 08, players look to be a leader and become a legend on the field. With all-new Leadership Control, players now lead by example and control the action on the field and can increase their sphere of influence by improving their players' personal ratings on each big play. The game also features a new and deeper recruiting system and an all-new Campus Legend mode.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=65_OMlyAguE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kXq9S6BDG0s"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938464-ncaa-football-08/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NCAA-Football-08/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ncaa-football-08/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ncaa-football-08"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":140,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"Take the wheel and drive your way to the NASCAR NEXTEL Cup Series championship. As the new rookie driver on the circuit, develop your racing skills to gain licenses and contracts from hungry owners and unlock legendary top performing cars from NASCAR's biggest stars. Gain new experiences during every race then modify your car's handling with over 40 tuning options to truly master every track. Share your setups with NASCAR's gaming community, then challenge the field in live races with up to 16 players online.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RS8UuE7qrww"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uar60jr3BuI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NASCAR-08/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nascar-08/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nascar-08"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":141,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"Feel what it's like to be a field general making key personnel decisions on both sides of the ball during the game's biggest moments in Madden NFL 08. Quickly identify your strongest players on the field before every snap then move them into position to make game-changing momentum-altering plays. Play to your team's strengths by immediately reading your opponent's schemes and reacting to the action as soon as the ball is snapped. Create mismatches and exploit weaknesses as you read and react with Madden NFL 08.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=80D1FpwtQ0I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KyyZfJ87WoM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938343-madden-nfl-08/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Madden-NFL-08/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/madden-nfl-08/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/madden-nfl-08"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":142,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["2K Boston"],
			"synopsis":"BioShock is a narrative-driven action experience that allows players to do the impossible as they journey through an amazing, immersive and terrifying world. Caught between powerful forces and hunted down by genetically mutated citizens, the player will come to grips with the mysterious and fascinating world of Rapture, a distinct Art Deco underwater utopia gone mad. BioShock not only challenges the players' capacity to adapt and survive, but brings to question their values and commitment to the inhabitants of Rapture. With smart and adaptive AI, no encounter ever plays out the same, while numerous customization options provide gamers with an experience that adapts to their playing style.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Ryan Industries Plasmids and Gene Tonics",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/12",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Stuck in a rut in Rapture? Has a Big Daddy been beating you down? Need a little more zing to your arsenal? Download these Gene Tonics and Plasmids and get your step back. Splice with Sonic Boom, EVE Saver, Vending Expert, and Machine buster today!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CoYorK3E4aM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yi1QhJMEVsw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/931329-bioshock/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/BioShock/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bioshock/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bioshock"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Bioshock Wiki",
				"url":"http://bioshock.wikia.com/wiki/BioShock_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":143,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["TopWare Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"The world changed when Aziraal, the god of war, was slain in the huge battle long ago. The hordes of Orcs lost their divine leader and were forced to withdraw to the southern wastelands. Now, thousands of years later, the location of Aziraal's tomb is still unknown, well hidden by other gods who did not dare to entrust the secret to mere mortals. However, now, a fragile peace between the civilized races and the hordes is at stake. When the dwarven mining expedition discovered an ancient temple dedicated to an unnamed deity, a silent war begun, and it will soon ignite the fires that will lead to the holy crusade of the Orcs. However, the real danger lies somewhere else. A powerful force churns silently - weaving a secret plot of fear and destruction. In the end one of the Two Worlds will remain.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xz5JkGCNx48"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=--7owuRkIPA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932336-two-worlds/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Two-Worlds/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/two-worlds/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/two-worlds"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Two Worlds Wiki",
				"url":"http://twoworlds.wikia.com/wiki/Two_Worlds_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":144,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Climax Studios"],
			"synopsis":"MotoGP '07 is the definitive next-generation motorcycle racing title. Featuring complete 2007 rider and team data, new 800cc MotoGP bikes and the Misano event. The title also features interactive track-side crowds, on-line tournament features, on-line \"pink-slip\" racing, and a revamped Extreme mode.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-s4l8cTrGXg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SjJsn9yLLmk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MotoGP-07/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/motogp-07/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/motogp-07"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":145,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Mistwalker"],
			"synopsis":"Famed game producer Hironobu Sakaguchi of Mistwalker game studio and developer Artoon present the highly anticipated Xbox 360-exclusive Blue Dragon. Featuring the character design of Akira Toriyama (who designed Dragon Ball Z) and music by Nobuo Uematsu (the composer for Final Fantasy), Blue Dragon is an epic RPG centered on a young boy named Shu and several of his friends. These unlikely heroes possess miraculous strength and magical power to control phantom shadows that mirror the actions of their masters.<br><br>Shu and company must use their shadows as weapons as they battle the evil forces and an antiquated human race of people who command a magical power thought to have perished long ago. Shu and friends must wield their skills to save their world from impending doom. Encountering various people on a planet with numerous ancient ruins, the characters and their shadows travel through a world full of mysteries and illusions, where the slightest touch can cause reactions of unparalleled magnitude.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Ultra Hard Mod",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/05",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"The Ultra Hard Mod adds three new features to Blue Dragon. New Game Plus is a game mode that allows you to start your game over using a saved game from near the end of Blue Dragon. The Hard game mode allows you to play at a difficulty level that is twice as high as the original. The Impossible game mode is the ultimate in difficulty and is meant to be played starting at Level 50 or higher."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"6 Treasures - Package of 6 Handy Items",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A brand new shipment of fresh items has arrived: Nothing Glasses, Spring Breeze Kerchief, Devee Phonograph, Whimsical Heart, Master Thief Manual, and Shuffle Helmet. All six items are waiting to be explored!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Shuffle Dungeon",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/16",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Shuffle Dungeon has arrived! This new content features a mysterious dungeon that changes every time you enter. Along with more than 30 new items, powerful monsters, and more than 10 new hard-to-beat bosses, there are certainly some challenges in store for you! Are you up for it? (Recommended Starting Level: 50 or higher. Supports Hard and Impossible game modes). Note that you will need to be near the end of the game, and have saved that game, in order to enter a Warp Cube to Shuffle Dungeon."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sdcpc8zSsGk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Anime Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c5BSuNgXjwc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2QLTN3A1cco"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/927950-blue-dragon/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Blue-Dragon/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/blue-dragon/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/blue-dragon"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Blue Dragon Wiki",
				"url":"http://bluedragon.wikia.com/wiki/Blue_Dragon"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":146,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Omega Force"],
			"synopsis":"Dynasty Warriors: Gundam takes gamers through an intergalactic conflict where the only hope for survival is to annihilate the encroaching opposing forces. It's one-versus-many as gamers fight at lightning speed aboard their favorite Mobile Suit, the ultimate weapon of war.<br><br>Gamers have the opportunity to explore the rich and detailed setting of the Gundam multi-verse from a myriad of perspectives. Assume the role of legendary heroes and villains while strategically enhancing their power, skills, and abilities. Play out the legendary scenes from the rich storyline and marvel at the subtle twists viewed through the eyes of each character. Furthermore, players can unlock Mobile Suits and Pilots from different Gundam universe time lines while accomplishing secret missions adding limitless replayability. With a variety of game types including Official, Original and Versus Mode, gamers must overcome impossible odds to bring their Mobile Suits to victory.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1SgAWzVny8E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_qX7TweQw-Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939446-dynasty-warriors-gundam/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dynasty-Warriors-Gundam/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dynasty-warriors-gundam/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dynasty-warriors-gundam"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Koei Wiki",
				"url":"http://koei.wikia.com/wiki/Dynasty_Warriors:_Gundam"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Gundam Wiki",
				"url":"http://gundam.wikia.com/wiki/Dynasty_Warriors_Gundam"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":147,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Paradigm Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Plunge into the adrenaline-fueled role of a Hollywood stunt driver in Stuntman: Ignition, and master the most breathtaking, death-defying vehicle-based stunts ever filmed. As the newest stuntman in Hollywood, you must rise to stardom by combining reckless maneuvering with perfect execution to unlock big-budget blockbusters and lucrative commercial deals. Create movie-magic in 6 uniquely-themed films on 36 different stunt runs with over 25 vehicles, or take the action online to challenge rival stuntman in the ultimate backlot showdown.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Director's Cut Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/30",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Play 6 new levels, one to each of the games movies."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Vehicle Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/19",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Drive brand new vehicles for Multiplayer and the Constructor mode."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7JktT4EXGPI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tGv6yKrGJGQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932101-stuntman-ignition/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Stuntman-Ignition/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/stuntman-ignition/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/stuntman-ignition"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":148,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"Tiger Woods PGA Tour 08 aims to take the sport to the next level with a new development team and a host of added game features. Taking online interaction beyond anything before in the series, EA Sports GamerNet enables players to create or play against interactive content. The game records everything from your greatest rounds to awe-inspiring shots which you can then post online for the world to try and beat. Earn points and the ultimate bragging rights by creating the best challenges or by beating them. Also featured is Game Face - now you can really put yourself in the game by uploading real-life photographs to create your in-game characters.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cEYJWIRD9Cg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Sxg3oyH9veU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tiger-Woods-PGA-TOUR-08/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tiger-woods-pga-tour-08/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tiger-woods-pga-tour-08"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":149,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Los Angeles"],
			"synopsis":"Step into the boots of Boyd Travers, Private First Class of the 82nd Airborne Division and engage in battles throughout Europe. From rocky beginnings in Sicily to war-winning triumphs in Germany, each mission begins behind enemy lines, with an intense and fully interactive airdrop. Your ability to determine your own starting point dramatically changes the way each mission plays out. View the entire operation from the air, and then control your parachute to choose your landing spot. On the ground, gather your senses and assess the terrain. A wide variety of authentic, customizable weapons are at your disposal, each with distinct characteristics. Choose your path in this free roaming FPS environment. The producers sought counsel from numerous expert sources to make certain the game is historically accurate and as true to the WWII Airborne experience as possible.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AVI9TyuFozM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qUH2uCOqr7k"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/931482-medal-of-honor-airborne/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Medal-of-Honor-Airborne/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/medal-of-honor-airbourne/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/medal-of-honor-airborne"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Medal of Honor Wiki",
				"url":"http://medalofhonor.wikia.com/wiki/Medal_of_Honor:_Airborne"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":150,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Midway Games"],
			"synopsis":"Chow Yun-Fat reprises the role of Inspector Tequila from John Woo's influential action film, \"Hard Boiled\" in this hyperkinetic shooting game. Run into danger with both fists full of lead and take down the organized crime bosses who stepped over the line when they took your family. Stop at nothing as you destroy the entire world around you to get them back. You are a desperate man following your own rules; honor thy family; do what's right; fear no man. Stranglehold features much of the hyperkinetic, choreographed action and freeze framed sequences that Woo is known for.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/01/04",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Download the Stranglehold Map Pack now! Gain access to 10 new Achievements, with 250 additional Gamerscore, 10 new multiplayer maps and 21 new characters. The Map Pack adds even more action and excitement to Stranglehold, the experience GameSpy called \"a must for action fans\"."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SOggbeUsato"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WUgdhuhCVis"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928104-stranglehold/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Stranglehold/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/john-woo-presents-stranglehold/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/stranglehold"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":151,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["KOEI Canada"],
			"synopsis":"Fatal Inertia is an aerial combat racing game that uses physics as a core component to its gameplay as futuristic vehicles battle and race in a variety of beautiful, natural environments. The game is set in the mid-23rd century, where a revolutionary new racing sport - mixing street racing, rally racing, and demolition derby - has emerged. The foundation of Fatal Inertia is its physics engine, which allows for weapons and environments that are unlike anything seen before. The beautiful natural environments aren't just scenery - they are there to be used in combat, and rock walls can quickly become avalanches to use against your opponents. A single weapon has a variety of uses - clever use of a rocket back-fire can race you ahead while a barrage of heavy magnetized projectiles stuck to one side of an opponent may throw off his control. The vehicles in Fatal Inertia are highly customizable, and with the large variety of designs and parts at your disposal, you can truly inject your personality into your ride.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1nlqUK7q578"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vaBkfnzYObY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fatal-Inertia/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fatal-inertia/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fatal-inertia"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Koei Wiki",
				"url":"http://koei.wikia.com/wiki/Fatal_Inertia"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":152,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Genki"],
			"synopsis":"Become the best samurai warrior in the land by playing one of nine real-life samurai, including swordsmen Musashi Miyamoto, Jubei Yagyu, Sanako Chiba, and more. Each has character has their own storyline, attack techniques and upgradeable attributes (health, stamina, attack power and defense). Four modes of play offer a range of gameplay options, including the storyline advancing Main Mode; Mission Mode which challenges players to complete 10 missions within a specific time frame; Combat Mode that features two-player, head-to-head battles; and Xbox Live Leaderboard where players compete for new equipment and the best ranking against other Xbox Live gamers by pitting AI profiles against each other.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tmyCkKDsvpg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gCb49Lz1gmM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kengo-Legend-of-the-9/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kengo-legend-of-the-9/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kengo-legend-of-the-9"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":153,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"EA aims to light the lamp again with the '08 edition of its annual hockey game. This year, runs on an all-new skating engine, which means new analog speed control of the left stick that gives you the variance you need to glide into the zone with control or get a burst of speed to step up on a defender. You have the control to perform crossovers to maintain speed or carve tight turns for an immediate change in direction. Also added are new Skill Stick Moments, where you have more control over 1-on-1 matchups. Use your stick to push the puck into space and walk around your defender. Once you're all alone in front, improved stick handling and shooting accuracy will give you the toolset to beat your goaltender for that decisive goal. On the sim side, players can develop AHL players from all 29 minor league AHL teams - play favorites rising stars or be a GM and manage a team as they develop into candidates for the pro circuit.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ET8S8XBuzIs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LUIaJa-dirU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939620-nhl-08/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NHL-08/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nhl-08/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nhl-08"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":154,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts", "Kush Games"],
			"synopsis":"Leveraging all of the next generation capabilities of the Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3, NHL 2K8 features innovative gameplay, revolutionary player models and stunning visuals to create an entirely new hockey experience, centered on authenticity and the NHL Signature Style. Utilizing 2K Sports' NHL Signature Style, NHL 2K8 will highlight unique player characteristics never before seen in a hockey game. To complement their true-to-life attributes, marquee players will be fitted with branded equipment including skates, sticks, pads and helmets - becoming visually recognizable on the ice.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"2K ReelMaker",
				"releaseDate":"2007/09/19",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"The 2K ReelMaker allows players to create their own highlight reels."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wkiy-SiNq7A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yr72z2Hy6Ts"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NHL-2K8/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nhl-2k8/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nhl-2k8"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":155,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Black Box"],
			"synopsis":"Skate delivers the real feel of skating in a fully reactive skateboarding city, utilizing the power of the Xbox 360 and PS3 consoles for advanced new control and physics techniques to feel through every kick-flip and land every aerial. The game features professional skaters such as Danny Way and PJ Ladd. Skate's unique control scheme captures the true feel of skating - with physics-driven animations, gamers will have a unique gaming experience every time they pick up the controller since no two tricks will ever be the same.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6JqElFb9Uig"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q67n7n974pY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935644-skate/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Skate/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/skate/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/skate"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":156,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tri-Crescendo"],
			"synopsis":"Eternal Sonata follows the adventures of famed composer Frederic Chopin as he travels through his own dream world filled with colorful characters and stunning locales. In a land where music influences both combat and exploration, Chopin sets out on a journey not only of self-discovery, but also one of redemption.<br><br>Utilizing a combat system that rewards players for careful battle coordination, Chopin and his allies can unleash devastating combo attacks for even more damage while on the battlefield. To add even more depth, combat is also influenced by the powers of light and darkness. Depending on whether enemies or heroes are in the light or darkness, their attacks, abilities, and even physical forms might undergo massive changes, adding a whole new dimension of variety to every encounter. Will Chopin learn the secrets of the mysterious world he finds himself in? Will the powers of evil forever cast a shadow of darkness over the land? The curtain is about to rise on a symphony of epic scope and scale... and the answers to those questions lie between the notes of dreams and reality.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LHkQPBu2xqg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kxVqMVMgFpg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/934162-eternal-sonata/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Eternal-Sonata/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/eternal-sonata/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/eternal-sonata"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Eternal Sonata Wiki",
				"url":"http://eternalsonata.wikia.com/wiki/Eternal_Sonata_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":157,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Juice Games"],
			"synopsis":"Get into the drift with Juiced 2 - the only place where superstar DJs, smokin' hot models and totally tuned cars come into close contact. Juice up your ride with complete customization and boost your NOS power as you draft, drift, slide, spook and fight for your rightful place on the racing line. Fast-paced, adrenaline-fuelled, pick-up-and-play action lets you enjoy the pure rush of powersliding your way around the globe. Wow the crowd, keep tabs on your opponents and take the crown as the rightful king of drift!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LsKSbm6xoCY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1yvJumpSqd0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938449-juiced-2-hot-import-nights/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Juiced-2-Hot-Import-Nights/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/juiced-2-hot-import-nights/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/juiced-2-hot-import-nights"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":158,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Romania"],
			"synopsis":"In this game, you are the leader of Operation Wildcard, an undercover and elite squad of pilots secretly created by the American government. Your mission is to sabotage and destroy the Third Reich's evil plans to create a weapon of mass destruction. During this mission you and your team discover that the bad guys also have an elite team of their own. In an attempt to disarm the enemy, you engage in dramatic and movie-like spy missions in some of the world's most exotic locations using experimental weapons and flying never-before-seen prototype aircraft.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h6SA_jMFW6k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mGbpx7ecLX0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/937958-blazing-angels-2-secret-missions-of-wwii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Blazing-Angels-2-Secret-Missions-of-WW2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/blazing-angels-2-secret-missions-of-wwii/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/blazing-angels-2-secret-missions-of-wwii"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":159,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Omega Force"],
			"synopsis":"Warriors Orochi is a crossover of two historical action epics, Dynasty Warriors and Samurai Warriors. In the game, Orochi the king of demons has merged together in time the Sengoku and Sangokushi periods in an attempt at world domination. The heroes of both Dynasty and Samurai Warriors must now fight together to defeat Orochi and his demon followers.<br><br>In addition to generals from both franchises, totalling over 70 playable characters in all, Warriors Orochi adds a new feature to gameplay: team battles with up to three team members. You can switch off between the three members as you take on the hundreds of enemies that line the fields and castles of the strange world created by the Orochi.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tnwD-lpq6p0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dL3Uj-g95k4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939310-warriors-orochi/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Warriors-Orochi/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/warriors-orochi/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/warriors-orochi"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Koei Wiki",
				"url":"http://koei.wikia.com/wiki/Warriors_Orochi"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":160,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Fun Labs", "Sand Grain Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Hunt 11 species of record trophy bucks in North America's top hunting locations with Cabela's Trophy Bucks. The game features all new hunts for waterfoul, upland birds, small game and varmints. Have your trigger finger ready for palm-sweating, heart-pounding action!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6CFF3sG0CI0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DjnJgeSRmDQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cabelas-Trophy-Bucks/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cabelas-trophy-bucks/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cabelas-trophy-bucks"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":161,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Telltale Games"],
			"synopsis":"Players will join Gil Grissom, Catherine Willows and the rest of the Las Vegas cast to help solve crimes using realistic techniques and lab equipment. Utilizing all-new gameplay concepts, CSI: Hard Evidence features forensic reconstructions and atmospheric crime scenes taken directly from the television show, including an all-new garage lab for analyzing large evidence such as cars and boats, improved evidence gathering, review and lab mini-games, and more areas to explore.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H45qB9Be5Cc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qC6ZbRXLRi0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939566-csi-crime-scene-investigation-hard-evidence/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/CSI-Hard-Evidence/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/csi-hard-evidence/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/csi-crime-scene-investigation-hard-evidence"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"CSI: Wiki",
				"url":"http://csi.wikia.com/wiki/CSI:Hard_Evidence"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":162,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bungie Software"],
			"synopsis":"The epic saga continues with Halo 3, the hugely anticipated third chapter in the highly successful and critically acclaimed Halo franchise. Master Chief returns to finish the fight, bringing the epic conflict between the Covenant, the Flood, and the entire human race to a dramatic, pulse-pounding climax.<br><br>Taking full advantage of the power of Xbox 360, Halo 3 expands on everything that has made the Halo franchise great, adding a wealth of graphical, technical and gameplay advancements, as well as offering a whole new level of online gameplay.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Heroic Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/11",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Heroic map pack contains three new maps, each presenting a totally different play style. Standoff's symmetrical valley, with its entrenched bases and fields of boulders is ideal for mid-sized objective and Slayer game types, while Rat's Nest's vast, labyrinthine passages bring something quite new to the Halo multiplayer experience - an indoor vehicle paradise, strongly influenced by the Campaign mode ideal for big team battles. Finally, Foundry is the ultimate Forge map - players can edit every single object in this voluminous industrial warehouse, place stairways, walls, bridges and tunnels to create an entirely new play space and build almost any kind of map they can think of.<br><br>This map pack became free on March 25, 2008. This map pack was included on a separate disc with Halo 3: ODST, which released on September 22, 2009."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Legendary Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/04/15",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Legendary Map Pack blends old and new. Ghost Town's asymmetrical mix of confined spaces and long lines of fire makes for frenetic games. Avalanche re-imagines the original Halo classic, Sidewinder, with new features, tweaked vehicles and massive outdoor spaces. Significant changes bring big improvements to the map, yet its contours and cliffs should provide a welcome sense of familiarity. Blackout, on the other hand, is the purest remake to date - all time favorite Lockout gets a graphical overhaul, but retains its challenging mix of ramps, platforms, tunnels and hallways.<br><br>This map pack was included on a separate disc with Halo 3: ODST, which released on September 22, 2009."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Cold Storage",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/07",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Warmly crafted, dutifully beautified update of Halo: CE classic multiplayer map, Chill Out. Love, Bungie. The map launched free in celebration of Bungie Day 2008. This map was included on a separate disc with Halo 3: ODST, which released on September 22, 2009."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Mythic Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/09",
				"achievements":325,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The long-awaited Mythic Map Pack drops into Xbox LIVE Marketplace. Investigate Orbital's abandoned hallways - before it was evacuated, the Quito Space Tether was heralded as the \"Civil Engineering Monument of the Millennium\". Witness Assembly, where Scarab hulls loom overhead, being decontaminated in preparation for the city-sized Lekgolo colonies that will breathe life into the massive metal husks. An excavation site surrounded by deadly Forerunner defenses, the mysteries of Sandbox are hidden high above, deep below, and right before your eyes.<br><br>This map pack was originally exclusive to owners of the collector's edition of Halo Wars, which released on March 3, 2009. This map pack was included on a separate disc with Halo 3: ODST, which released on September 22, 2009."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Mythic II Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/02",
				"achievements":175,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Includes the maps Citadel, Heretic, and Longshore. Heretic returns players to familiar ground, Halo 2's Midship, while Citadel forces small squads to stay in constant communication and Longshore's multitude of industrial buildings, elevated walks, and open inlets conspire to create a complex battleground tailored for multiple combat scenarios.<br><br>This map pack was originally exclusive to owners of Halo 3: ODST, which released on September 22, 2009."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"CGI Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GKDkKKt9Y7I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T9Ezd2FqxAU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"tps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UnSB03NjGu0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Campaign Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lPQ3a_dG4Zw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OA_C_QSWMZ4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Spot",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vjhSp7xGsMc"
			},
			{
				"type":"All Halo 2 Cutscenes",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UrIrI4FJZ0A"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/926632-halo-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Halo-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/halo-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/halo-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Halo Nation",
				"url":"http://halo.wikia.com/wiki/Halo_3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Halopedia",
				"url":"http://www.halopedia.org/Halo_3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Halo Machinima Comedy",
				"site":"Rooster Teeth",
				"url":"http://roosterteeth.com/archive/?id=88&v=more&s=1"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":163,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eutechnyx"],
			"synopsis":"Speed, power, performance and attitude - put your Hot Wheels races to the test! Race your way through crazy corkscrews, loops and hidden routes. Race with a collection of the world's coolest cars. And engage in high-octane multiplayer action, racing on tracks packed with wicked explosions and super-charged power-ups.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k6favrhrQEM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qLNgcqNSCeU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hot-Wheels-Beat-That/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hot-wheels-beat-that/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hot-wheels-beat-that!"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Hot Wheels Wiki",
				"url":"http://hotwheels.wikia.com/wiki/Hot_Wheels"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":164,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Left Field Productions, Inc."],
			"synopsis":"Enter the largest sporting event in the world - the World Series of Poker - and battle \"The Poker Brat\" Phil Hellmuth along the way! Build your bankroll and face off against some of the world's top pros in your quest to win the championship bracelet for the $10,000 Main Event!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=thNiD3zTh9c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=emfjfFlwN78"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943298-world-series-of-poker-2008-battle-for-the/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/World-Series-of-Poker-2008/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/world-series-of-poker-2008/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/world-series-of-poker-2008-battle-for-the-bracelets"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":165,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bugbear Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"FlatOut: Ultimate Carnage is an over-the-top racing game where players experience the drive of their lives as they race around fully destructible environments. Enhanced over the original version of FlatOut 2, the game features 12 types of racing cars, five all-new single player and two all-new multiplayer game modes, plus widescreen high definition resolution to make the racing experience more real.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FG3h40SKTkU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DLC2wM4ld2I"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/934329-flatout-ultimate-carnage/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Flatout-Ultimate-Carnage/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/flatout-ultimate-carnage/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/flatout-ultimate-carnage"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":166,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts", "Kush Games"],
			"synopsis":"The king of the hard court is back and better than ever with the all-new Sprite Slam Dunk Contest, all-new defensive controls, improved Signature Style technology, and more.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kPHjFPj_LFM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aYgJ79e1AL0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939852-nba-2k8/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-2K8/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-2k8/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-2k8"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":167,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"When the game is on the line and the ball is in your hands, what will you do? Will you penetrate, drive the lane and rise above the rim for a monster dunk, or find an opening on the perimeter and sink a game-winning three? Take control of the game with a full arsenal to win the one-on-one match-up from every spot on the floor with NBA Live 08.<br><br>Taking a page out of NBA STREET Homecourt's book, NBA Live 08 introduces Quickstrike Ballhandling. This intuitive gameplay mechanic is mapped to the right analog stick and gives you the direct responsiveness you need to perform a full repertoire of ankle-breaking ball-handling moves that let you dominate on the perimeter. Pass the ball inside and win in the post with all-new 'own the paint' post play for the big men down low. Use the new shot-countershot control to string together combos of fakes and shots to fool your defender into committing and create space for the game-defining bucket. On the perimeter, in the paint, and with complete authenticity to the sport of basketball, dominate with your go-to move with NBA LIVE 08.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JdXo9uE2oK8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4uF6Wm-KNgQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939306-nba-live-08/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-LIVE-08/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-live-08/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-live-08"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":168,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bizarre Creations"],
			"synopsis":"Right from the starting line, Project Gotham Racing 4 creates an emotionally-charged racing experience, where you become attached to your careers, profiles, and vehicles. There are several new features that embody this emotional experience, the most significant being the new career mode.<br><br>Get ready to be rewarded with a growing fanbase that cheers you on, reacts to your every move, and supports you through victory. Just imagine hearing the roar of the crowd as you cross the finish line with your own style and flair.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Premium Challenge Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/14",
				"achievements":170,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The Premium Challenge Pack adds new cars, single and multiplayer game modes, and achievements to Project Gotham Racing 4."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Free Challenge Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/14",
				"achievements":80,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"This free add-on for Project Gotham Racing 4 adds two new multiplayer game modes, seven new achievements, and a new car."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dhyYj2g8hb0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DcAvIEd0Ee8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935830-project-gotham-racing-4/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/PGR-4/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pgr-4/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/project-gotham-racing-4"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":169,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Next Level Games"],
			"synopsis":"Inspired by the Spider-Man film trilogy and the classic Spider-Man comics, Spider-Man: Friend or Foe challenges players to defeat and then join forces with notorious movie nemeses including Doc Ock, Green Goblin, Venom and Sandman, and embark on an epic quest to overcome a worldwide evil threat. Throughout the game's original story and thrilling battles, fans control Spider-Man and one of numerous Super Hero or Super Villain sidekicks and master unique fighting moves and styles while switching between characters to execute team combos and defeat foes.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a_Cgk6vkKf8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P7c0U_PVk1A"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939523-spider-man-friend-or-foe/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Spider-Man-Friend-or-Foe/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/spider-man-friend-or-foe/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/spider-man-friend-or-foe"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":170,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Radical Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"In a nefarious plot to unleash destruction, Crash Bandicoot 's arch-nemeses, Neo and Nina Cortex, have mutated the creatures of Crash's island into monstrous abominations! Never one to shirk from danger, our orange furry friend finds that with his potent mix of wacky bravado and daredevil action he is able to hijack the titanic monsters and wield their immense powers against each other! Bring on the titans, because with Crash in charge, the bigger the baddie, the better!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NpKrSIxPvjw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tGwY204T8cM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ieKm5T76zDo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939007-crash-of-the-titans/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Crash-Of-The-Titans/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/crash-of-the-titans/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/crash-of-the-titans"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Bandipedia",
				"url":"http://crashbandicoot.wikia.com/wiki/Crash_of_the_Titans"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":171,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"Featuring the image of two-time FIFA World Player of the Year Ronaldinho on the cover, the 2008 edition of FIFA once again rocks the world for fans of the game. For the first time ever, fans playing FIFA Soccer 08 will face the pressure to improve their game that real-world players endure every day. Be A Pro Mode locks you in the role of a single player and challenges you to master the same disciplines as a real soccer player-from positioning and tackling to reading the field and passing.<br><br>FIFA Soccer 08 puts you on the pitch to defy the odds, perfect your skills, elevate your game and rise up to win glory for your club. And the next-gen gameplay engine delivers animations and ball control that is so responsive you feel like you are actually on the pitch.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vl-mxRcbgDE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K1S687pWlDw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938657-fifa-soccer-08/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/FIFA-08/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fifa-08/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fifa-soccer-08"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":172,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Red Tribe"],
			"synopsis":"The Evil Mad Scientist is fed up with the Looney Tunes and plans to get rid of them once and for all. Using his homemade time machine and giant ACME eraser, he will travel through time and erase the Looney Tunes and their ancestors from existance.Little does he know though that the Looney Tunes have built their own time machine, and will fight the Evil Mad Scientist to save themselves from dissapearing.<br><br>Looney Tunes: Acme Arsenal is an action-adventure game featuring seven playable Looney Tunes characters, including Bugs Bunny, Daffy Duck, Tazmanian Devil, Foghorn Leghorn, Marvin the Martian, Gossamer and a special secret character, all rendered in high-definition, next-generation graphics. Gamers find themselves immersed in combat, puzzles, and vehicle-based action. Players also command an arsenal of ACME melee and projectile weapons in outrageous battles and travel to various locations such as Camelot, Ancient Egypt, Mars, and the Wild West.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c9ll743x8Es"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GKCve3JLgb8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Looney-Tunes-Acme-Arsenal/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/looney-tunes-acme-arsenal/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/looney-tunes-acme-arsenal"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":173,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Valve"],
			"synopsis":"Once again players assume the role of Gordon Freeman, a scientist destined to save the Earth from hordes of gruesome alien attackers. Valve has created a fully realized world in Half-Life 2, with objects and characters that feature accurate physics properties, behaving with the appropriate mass, density, and physical properties of their real-life counterparts. Extremely intelligent computer AI result in enemies that plan, adapt, and respond to the player's actions.<br><br>The next-gen console version comes packed with bonuses in addition to the genre-expanding original Half-Life 2 game. Half-Life 2: Episode One and Episode Two add-on levels are also on the disc, as are the stunningly complex puzzle game Portal and the online phenomenon Team Fortress 2.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"The Orange Box Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TWIUTMKzpwE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Half-Life 2 Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UKA7JkV51Jw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Half-Life 2: Episode One Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DL_mPw7KEU8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Half-Life 2: Episode Two Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n0l5N6Exjz0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Team Fortress 2 - All Trailers",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hiTyy7vvlX4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Portal Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TluRVBhmf8w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Half-Life 2 Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tYLvzCGJ2jM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Half-Life 2: Episode One Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0NaDHpJieyY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Half-Life 2: Episode Two Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eEMPtNAM7bs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Team Fortress 2 Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-mmFfGw4ez0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Portal Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jXT5Chi_s5Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/934384-the-orange-box/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Orange-Box/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/half-life-2-the-orange-box/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-orange-box"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Half-Life Wiki",
				"url":"http://half-life.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Team Fortress 2 Wiki",
				"url":"https://wiki.teamfortress.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Portal Wiki",
				"url":"http://theportalwiki.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Combine Overwiki",
				"url":"http://combineoverwiki.net/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":174,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SEGA Racing Studio"],
			"synopsis":"The classic rally racing series series hits next-gen consoles, with powerful new technology fueling its bumper-to-bumper racing. Vehicle selection affects driving strategy in Sega Rally Revo, as race course surfaces dynamically deform upon repeated contact with vehicle tires and changing weather effects. Sega Rally Revo features a variety of fully deformable surfaces, from gravel-littered tracks and smooth tarmac roads, to snow-covered mountain passes. Driving skills will also be tested by Sega Rally Revo's advanced AI which allows NPC drivers to dynamically adapt their driving style to the varied racing surfaces. Players can enjoy a comprehensive single-player campaign as they travel the globe racing the best drivers in the world. Sega Rally Revo also features online capabilities, with multiplayer splitscreen modes offering an extremely competitive rally experience against drivers around the world.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X0zDvzxztoY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u0SoYTCtr4g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sega-Rally-Revo/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sega-rally-revo/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sega-rally-revo"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":175,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Neversoft Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"For the first time, players will have the freedom to define their character, story and style based on the choices they make, the paths they choose and the style of skating they use on the proving grounds from Philadelphia and Baltimore to Washington, D.C.<br><br>Tony Hawk's Proving Ground features deeper customization than ever before, including a Video Editor with full-featured editing tools and visual effects for creating \"epic skate videos\", and a fully customizable online Skate Lounge where players can skate with friends in the ultimate pad. In addition, players will have the freedom to skate from single player to online seamlessly, as well as utilize new gameplay mechanics such as skateable terrain altering and building, and Bowl Carving, delivering the most empowered skating experience ever.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PeTUTnOYY8o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xo8Lo9p5BUI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939512-tony-hawks-proving-ground/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tony-Hawk-Proving-Ground/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tony-hawks-proving-ground/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tony-hawks-proving-ground"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":176,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bandai Namco Games"],
			"synopsis":"Experience the new high-definition, next generation sights and sounds of Beautiful Katamari as the Prince takes on a new high-rolling adventure, with his famous cousins in tow, to save the Katamari universe once again after the King of All Cosmos has a very un-royal and unfortunate accident. As usual, the King of All Cosmos demands the service of his son, the Prince, to roll anything and everything up into massive clumps and set things right, bringing harmony once again to the Katamari Cosmos.<br><br>The Prince can humbly ask the aid of over 50 of his cousins to get the ball rolling through his quest. The cousins have discovered new games to play since last time out, and love to compete with friends in multiplayer Katamari rolling games either together or online against players all across the globe! To keep his son inspired, the King of All Cosmos will provide another fresh and memorable Katamari soundtrack to keep players moving and grooving.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"High-calorie Katamari",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/21",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"A new level for the game, collect lots of food to make Cetus the Whale."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Milky Way Constellations",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/21",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"A new level for the game, roll up all 88 constellations to make the Milky Way."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Shopping Spree",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/21",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"A new level for the game, be a thrifty shopper and go on a shopping spree to make a Space Station."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"The Weaver Girl",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/21",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"A new level for the game, collect lots of string and yarn to make the Weaver Girl, Vega."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Accessory Set A",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"An accessory set featuring 12 Presents, including the Cloak and Long Nose!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Accessory Set B",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"An accessory set featuring 12 Presents, including the Crown and Thunder Drums!"
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Character Set A",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A character set consisting of 14 Cousins, including Ryu and Sherman!"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Character Set B",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A character set consisting of 14 Cousins, including Kunihiro and Mag!"
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Perfectly Sized Katamari",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/19",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"A new level for the game, make a katamari of just the right size as requested by the King. "
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Dangerous Katamari",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/19",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"A new level for the game, collect lots of dangerous objects to make Scorpius."
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Mechanical Katamari",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/19",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"A new level for the game, collect lots of mechanical objects to make Antlia."
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Accessory Set C",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"An accessory set featuring 11 Presents, including the Lollipop and Lights!"
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"Accessory Set D",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"An accessory set featuring 10 Presents, including the Drum and Newsreel!"
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"Character Set C",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A character set consisting of 14 Cousins, including Pu and Kyun! "
			},
			{
				"id":15,
				"name":"Character Set D",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A new level for the game."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aZNMqPAKlDA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2_kjFUU8vgo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939134-beautiful-katamari/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Beautiful-Katamari/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/beautiful-katamari/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/beautiful-katamari"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Katamari Wiki",
				"url":"http://katamari.wikia.com/wiki/Beautiful_Katamari"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":177,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Frontier Developments"],
			"synopsis":"Thrillville: Off the Rails lives up to its name with 20 death-defying rides so outrageous, they inspire the same word from every park visitor who sees them: \"WHOA!\" Players build these incredible \"WHOA Coasters\" to leap from one track to another, launch through the air like cannonballs, blast through burning rings of fire and more. A new lighthearted story ties together more than 100 missions, complete with 34 playable multiplayer theme-park games and improved social interaction with park guests. The in-depth conversations both advance the plot and suggest better ways to manage the park. But is every guest to be trusted? One never knows when a rival from the nefarious Globo-Joy might attempt to sabotage Thrillville parks with deceptive information...",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Booster Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/21",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"All-new levels for three of your favorite minigames on Thrillville: Off the Rails! Think you've mastered Stunt Rider? Think again! Rev up for these 10 new levels - each more fiendish than the last. Bandito Chinchilla's fists of fury are also back for more brawlicious action. This time arch-nemesis Vengo Vico has brought on hordes of his best minions to take you on. Battle your way to the top of the tower and take on Vico himself. And when you're done there, round it out with three classic Thrillville original Entertainer tracks playable for the first time ever on Xbox 360: \"Emo Skater Girl\", \"Loop It\", and the award-winning \"Dr. Kunkle's Funnkel Cake\". All new levels in the Booster Pack are playable in Off the Rails' Party Play!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UH4ATqeN03U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E__RQl-GyYQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Thrillville-OTR/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/thrillville-off-the-rails/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/thrillville-off-the-rails"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":178,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Project Aces"],
			"synopsis":"Ace Combat 6: Fires of Liberation takes air combat warfare to new heights as it boasts the new \"Dynamic Operation System\" where massive battles unfold on a \"living battlefield\", as up to six independent land, sea or air conflicts can break out at any time at multiple locations as allies and enemies clash in real-time. Players can experience the realism of war when battlefields come alive with engagingly authentic audio and visual effects: thundering explosions, dense vapor trails of air to air missiles, piercing machine gun fire, booming anti-aircraft artillery fire, mid-air explosions, gigantic columns of black smoke and more.<br><br>Prove your supremacy on a global scale as you pilot highly detailed, authentic aircraft online via Xbox Live. For an all out worldwide battle for the sky, players can choose from a variety of different online modes including the death match and team death match style game modes. Or they can team up with friends to play in co-op, where players combine strategy and skill to work together to take on computer-controlled adversaries.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"F-16C - Type Ace 2",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-16C Fighting Falcon, Ace Combat 2 Aircraft Now Available! A faithful recreation of the Ace Combat 2 aircraft performance design. Outstanding stability and lack of recoil provide for a truly unique sense of flight. Although possessing an extremely durable body, this aircraft lacks SP weapons, which were not introduced until after Ace Combat 2. Experience what it was like to fly back in the day! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack01, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as default colors."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"F-14D - Halloween",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-14D Super Tomcat, Halloween Aircraft Now Available! An enormous jack-o'-lantern decorates the body of this aircraft, but don't let it's outward appearance fool you. This aircraft is more than meets the eye. That is, if you can keep your eye on it... Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack01, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as default colors."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"F-15E - Active Stripes",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-15E Strike Eagle, Active Stripes Aircraft Now Available! The redesigned light-weight frame sacrifices durability and payload for a marked increase in turning performance. Blind your opponents with this mesmerizing pattern. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack01, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as default colors."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"F/A-18F - Scarface Emblem",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F/A-18F Super Hornet, Scarface Squadron Aircraft Now Available! This aircraft's armor has been reinforced at the expense of maneuverability. With the main military force unable to respond, the mercenary tactical strike force, Scarface, was entrusted to rescue the Usean continent from the hands of a brutal military coup d'etat. Download now, and take the Scarface Squadron to the skies of Ace Combat 6! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack02, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as default colors."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"A-10A - Thunder Shark",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A-10A ThunderBolt II, Shark Mouth Aircraft Now Available! Severe sacrifices have been made to speed and maneuverability to facilitate an unprecedented number of armaments. The Shark Mouth is one of the most recognized of all nose art. Lay waste to your enemies with more than enough ammo to spare! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack02, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as default colors."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Su-33 - The Idolmaster Miki",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Su-33 Flanker, The Idolmaster, Miki Hoshii Aircraft Now Available! The stars of the hit game \"The Idolmaster\" make their Ace Combat debut! First to debut is Miki Hoshii. The world can't wait to see what talents this future star has hiding under her wings. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack02, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as default colors."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"F-16C - Historic Windhover",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-16C Fighting Falcon, Windhover Squadron Aircraft Now Available! The Ace Combat 6 Windhover Squadron's special color. Sacrificing stability and armor, this aircraft boasts unrivaled freedom of movement. Download now and dance around your enemies. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack02, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as default colors."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Mirage 2000-5 - Experimental",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Mirage 2000-5, Experimental Aircraft Now Available! This phenomenally fast aircraft is the culmination of exhaustive experimentation on thrust refinement. The increase in speed, however, comes at a great expense to stability, limiting this aircraft to only the most skilled of pilots. Tame this wild beast, and never look back! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack02, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as default colors."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"F-22A - Mobius",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-22A Raptor, Mobius Squadron Aircraft Now Available! Fitted with enough armaments to single handedly maintain air superiority, low damage control due to reduction in armor is its only weak point. Become the hero of Ace Combat 04, and a legend on the battlefield. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack03, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as default colors."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"F-117A - The Idolmaster Yukiho",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-117A Night Hawk, The Idolmaster Yukiho Hagiwara Aircraft Now Available! The stars of the hit game \"The Idolmaster\" make their Ace Combat debut! The second up is the shy but eager Yukiho Hagiwara. It's up to you to steer her to stardom before she stumbles and falls. One can hardly wait to see how fast and free she can fly. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack03, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as default colors."
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"A-10A - Xmas",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A-10A ThunderBolt II, Holiday Aircraft Now Available! Seemingly unaffected by gravity, even during inverted flight, exceptional aerodynamic performance is achieved at the loss of this aircraft's otherwise characteristic durability. This A-10A is something else altogether. Witness its magical maneuverability on a cold winter's night, and one could easily mistake it for a reindeer and a sleigh. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack03, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as default colors."
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"F-15E - Pixy",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-15E Strike Eagle, Pixy Aircraft Now Available! Armor has been lightened to increase stability. With an array of counterstrike customizations, this aircraft can immediately adapt to changes on the battlefield. Take on the role of \"Solo Wing Pixy\", and head into all new battles. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack03, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as default colors."
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"F-15E - Cipher",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-15E Strike Eagle, Cipher Aircraft Now Available! This aircraft's armor has been lightened to facilitate greater fire power. Fully customized preemptive striking capabilities place this fighter at the forefront of any battle. Crush the opposition as the \"Demon of the Round Table\". Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack03, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as default colors."
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"Mirage 2000-5 - Scarface Emblem",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Mirage 2000-5, Scarface Squadron Aircraft Now Available! The heroes of Ace Combat 2, Scarface Squadron Aircraft. This aircraft's armor has been reinforced at the expense of stability. With the main military force unable to respond, the mercenary tactical strike force, Scarface, was entrusted to rescue the Usean continent from the hands of a brutal military coup d'etat. Download now, and take the Scarface Squadron to the skies of Ace Combat 6! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack03, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as default colors."
			},
			{
				"id":15,
				"name":"Team Battle",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/26",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"New Online Battle, Team Battle Now Available! A maximum of 16 players can take part in this Team Battle above a cloud covered mountain range. Powerful allied reinforcements are granted to the first team to destroy the targets before they sink into the sea of clouds below. Allied reinforcements offer a 60 second chance to overpower and destroy your enemies! The losing team must fight it out for the next shot at the targets. Select Player Match via Online Battle after download to play (This system is not available in Ranked Match)."
			},
			{
				"id":16,
				"name":"Su-47 - The Idolmaster Miki-EX",
				"releaseDate":"2008/01/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Su-47 Berkut, The Idolmaster, Miki-EX (Miki Hoshii) Aircraft Now Available! The stars of the hit game \"The Idolmaster\" make their Ace Combat debut! The third to debut is Miki-EX. Having awoken to her true potential, it's anyone's guess what hits she will captivate the world with next. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack04, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":17,
				"name":"Tornado GR.4 - Raging Shark",
				"releaseDate":"2008/01/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Tornado GR.4, Shark Mouth Aircraft Now Available! A massive increase in payload and armor come at the expense of speed. The advantages of this tradeoff are exercised in anti-ground offensive capabilities. The Shark Mouth is one of the most recognized of all nose art, and is loved for its brash and ferocious style. Shoot to your heart's content, and burn down the world! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack04, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":18,
				"name":"Su-33 - Yellow Squadron",
				"releaseDate":"2008/01/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Su-33, Yellow Squadron Aircraft Now Available! Ace Combat 04 rival Yellow Squadron aircraft. This lightly armored aircraft possesses unsurpassed maneuverability. Join the elite Yellow Squadron and become the pride of Erusea. Take your rightful place as king of the sky. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack04, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":19,
				"name":"F-14D - Razgriz",
				"releaseDate":"2008/01/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-14D SuperTomcat, Razgriz Squadron Aircraft Now Available! Advanced accident prevention systems, and high durability have been incorporated into the design to ensure the survival of all squadron members. This enigmatic squadron became known as both the heroes and demons of Ace Combat 5. Join them in their road to victory, and strike your opponents down. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack04, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":20,
				"name":"CFA-44 - Prototype",
				"releaseDate":"2008/01/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"CFA-44 Nosferatu, Prototype Aircraft Now Available! Ace Combat 6 ace pilot Ilya Pasternak's experimental aircraft. A stability centric design facilitates a fully maximized EML weapon system. Slice through the atmosphere, and vaporize anything caught in your sites! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack04, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":21,
				"name":"Typhoon - UPEO Emblem",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/06",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Typhoon UPEO, Aircraft Now Available! The heroes of Ace Combat 3, UPEO Squadron Aircraft. A stripped down payload for increased stability coupled with outstanding turning performance allow this aircraft to weave through any battlefield with ease. Join UPEO in their sole role as world peace protectorate, and soar into the limitless sky, free of all political and cultural boundaries. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack04, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":22,
				"name":"F-15E - The Idolmaster Chihaya",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/27",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-15E Strike Eagle, The Idolmaster, Chihaya Kisaragi Aircraft Now Available! The stars of the hit game \"The Idolmaster\" make their Ace Combat debut! The fourth up is the moody girl wonder, Chihaya Kisaragi. Take care not to get on her bad side, aim for the top, and take to the skies! We can't wait to see what she's got! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack05, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":23,
				"name":"Razgriz Set 01",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/27",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Razgriz Set 01 (4 Aircraft) Now Available! Four aircraft including F-16C Fighting Falcon, F-2A, Su-33 Flanker, Rafale M. Advanced accident prevention systems, and high durability have been incorporated into the designs to ensure the survival of all squadron members. This enigmatic squadron became known as both the heroes and demons of Ace Combat 5. Join them on their road to victory, and strike your opponents down. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack05, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":24,
				"name":"Ace OF Aces Mission 01",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/27",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"A challenge exclusively for masters of Ace Combat. Exceeding that of ACE, Mission 01 is now available on the highest difficulty level, Ace of Aces. Protect Gracemeria from the reinforced Estovakian invasion. New Counter-Charge System! When you see the Mission timer, that's your chance to increased Allied Support! Destroy the enemy within the time limit, to secure more allied numbers. The greater the number of enemies destroyed, the greater the number of allies who come to your aid. Time your kills right, and break through even the toughest enemy line.<br><br>Campaign Mode, Mission 01 must be cleared, and Free Mission Save Data available to use this download content. Select Ace of Aces via Free Mission after download to play."
			},
			{
				"id":25,
				"name":"Siege Battle",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/27",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"New Online Battle, Siege Battle Now Available! A maximum of 8 players can take part in this Siege Battle above the snowy plains. The attacking side must dispose of enemy defense drones before downing a unit of transport aircraft. Destroying radar vehicles will temporarily disable the transport defenses. The attacking side will receive additional defense drones for each enemy aircraft downed. A delicate balance of offense and defense is necessary to see the transports safely to their destination. Skillful teamwork holds the key to victory. Select Player Match via Online Battle after download to play (This system is not available in Ranked Match)."
			},
			{
				"id":26,
				"name":"Battle Royale",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/27",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"New Online Battle, Battle Royale Now Available! A maximum of 16 players can take part in this South Sea Battle Royale amongst heavy command cruisers. Avoid the Gyges and Kottos barrage, and strike down the opposition! Select Player Match via Online Battle after download to play (This system is not available in Ranked Match)."
			},
			{
				"id":27,
				"name":"Su-33 - Crimson Wing",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/27",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Su-33 Flanker, Monotone Color, Crimson Aircraft Now Available! A modified sky painting aircraft for shows and exhibitions, this aircraft is equipped with colored smoke missiles. With a maximized missile payload, the sky is your canvas! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack05, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":28,
				"name":"Mirage 2000-5 - Advanced",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/27",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Mirage 2000-5, Advanced Aircraft Now Available! Reductions in armor coupled with a stable thrust engine bestow this aircraft with advanced handling characteristics. Responding to the slightest adjustment in thrust, this aircraft offers an entirely new sense of acceleration. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack05, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":29,
				"name":"Co-Op Battle 01",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/27",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"New Online Co-Op Battle Stage Now Available! Join up to four other players in hunting down the enemy forces scattered across the canyon. The primary mission consists of four individually timed successive operations. Progression to the next operation can be achieved without destroying all TGTs within the time limit. However, successfully destroying all TGTs will lead to increased fortifications during the secondary mission, and a chance to score bigger points. Work with your wingmen to successfully clear all operations, and unleash the full power of Ragno Fortress! Select Player Match via Online Battle after download to play (This system is not available in Ranked Match)."
			},
			{
				"id":30,
				"name":"Razgriz Set 02",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Razgriz Set 02 (3 Aircraft) Now Available! Three aircraft including Su-47 Berkut, A-10A and Typhoon. Advanced accident prevention systems, and high durability have been incorporated into the designs to ensure the survival of all squadron members. This enigmatic squadron became known as both the heroes and demons of Ace Combat 5. Join them on their road to victory, and strike your opponents down. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack06, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":31,
				"name":"Co-Op Battle 02",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/26",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"New Online Co-Op Battle Stage Now Available! Join up to four other players over the frozen arctic as you endeavor to conquer the Chandelier doomsday weapon! The modified cooling units quickly come back online once deactivated. Swiftly taking out all units offers the only promise of victory. Once the subsequent back-up cooling units are offline the cannon will open, offering a momentary chance to strike at the core. Destroy the Chandelier, and end the war once and for all! Team work is of the essence! Select Player Match via Online Battle after download to play (This system is not available in Ranked Match)."
			},
			{
				"id":32,
				"name":"Mirage 2000-5 The Idolmaster Yayoi",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Mirage 2000-5, The Idolmaster, Yayoi Takatsuki Aircraft Now Available! The stars of the hit game \"The Idolmaster\" make their Ace Combat debut! The fifth up is the ultra-energetic Yayoi Takatsuki. Bursting with 200 percent energy she screams full speed ahead. We can't wait to see the heights her hidden talents take her. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack06, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":33,
				"name":"F-22A - The Idolmaster Haruka",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-22A Raptor, The Idolmaster, Haruka Amami Aircraft Now Available! The stars of the hit game \"The Idolmaster\" make their Ace Combat debut! Sixth up is the pure hearted music lover, Haruka Amami. She's got a bad habit of getting herself into trouble, but her friendly and positive nature hold an undeniable charm. We can't wait to see how bright this star will shine! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack06, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":34,
				"name":"Ace of Aces Mission 02",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/26",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"A challenge exclusively for masters of Ace Combat. Exceeding that of ACE, Mission 02 is now available on the highest difficulty level, Ace of Aces. Hold back the unrelenting enemy onslaught, and save Vitoze, the last remaining Emmerian stronghold. New Counter-Charge System! Allied reinforcements are rewarded based on the number of enemies downed during the time limit. Call in Allied Support, and destroy the enemy! New enemy ECM reported! A detrimental effect on missile performance has been reported, but details remain scarce. Stay alert!<br><br>Campaign Mode, Mission 01 must be cleared, and Free Mission Save Data available to use this download content. Select Ace of Aces via Free Mission after download to play."
			},
			{
				"id":35,
				"name":"F-14D - Zipang",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-14D SuperTomcat, Cherry Blossom Aircraft Now Available! Specialization of turning performance has resulted in precision mobility and stability. Like cherry blossoms on the wind, soar into the open sky! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack06, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":36,
				"name":"F-22A - Indigo Wing",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-22A Raptor, Monotone Color, Indigo Aircraft Now Available! A modified sky painting aircraft for shows and exhibitions, this aircraft is equipped with colored smoke missiles. With a maximized missile payload, the sky is your canvas! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack06, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":37,
				"name":"Orange, Violet Set",
				"releaseDate":"2008/04/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Orange, Violet Set (2 Aircraft) Now Available! Two aircraft including Typhoon (Orange), Su-47 Berkut (Violet). A modified sky painting aircraft for shows and exhibitions, this aircraft is equipped with colored smoke missiles. With a maximized missile payload, the sky is your canvas! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack07, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":38,
				"name":"Razgriz Set 03",
				"releaseDate":"2008/04/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Razgriz Set 03 (4 Aircraft) Now Available! Four aircraft including Tornado GR. 4, F-15E Strike Eagle, F/A-18F SuperHornet, CFA-44 Nosferatu. Advanced accident prevention systems, and high durability have been incorporated into the designs to ensure the survival of all squadron members. This enigmatic squadron became known as both the heroes and demons of Ace Combat 5. Join them on their road to victory, and strike your opponents down. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack07, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":39,
				"name":"Rafale M - The Idolmaster Iori",
				"releaseDate":"2008/04/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Rafale M, The Idolmaster, Iori Minase Aircraft Now Available! The stars of the hit game \"The Idolmaster\" make their Ace Combat debut! Seventh up is the stubbornly charming, Iori Minase. Take the controls and show the world just how bright this flawless beauty can shine. We can't wait to be blinded by her light! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack07, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":40,
				"name":"Typhoon - Rot",
				"releaseDate":"2008/04/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Typhoon, Rot Team Aircraft Now Available! The Ace Combat Zero rival Rot Team aircraft. Extremely agile maneuverability assures this aircraft's dominance in a dogfight. Hindered by low durability, overwhelming attack prowess is its foremost form of defense. Embrace the pride of the \"Red Swallow\", and strike down anyone who dares stand in your way! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack07, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":41,
				"name":"Razgriz Set 04",
				"releaseDate":"2008/05/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Razgriz Set 04 (3 Aircraft) Now Available! Three aircraft including F-22A Raptor, F-117A Night Hawk, Mirage 2000-5. Advanced accident prevention systems and high durability have been incorporated into the designs to ensure the survival of all squadron members. This enigmatic squadron became known as both the heroes and demons of Ace Combat 5. Join them on their road to victory, and strike your opponents down. Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack08, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":42,
				"name":"Su-33 - Type Ace 2",
				"releaseDate":"2008/05/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Su-33 Flanker, Ace Combat 2 Aircraft Now Available! A faithful recreation of the Ace Combat 2 aircraft performance design. Outstanding stability and lack of recoil provide for a truly unique sense of flight. Although it boasts improved speed performance, this aircraft lacks SP weapons, which were not introduced until after Ace Combat 2. Experience what it was like to fly back in the day! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack08, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":43,
				"name":"The Idolmaster Ami, Mami Set",
				"releaseDate":"2008/05/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-2A, The Idolmaster, Ami Futami, and F-16C Fighting Falcon, The Idolmaser, Mami Futami Aircraft Now Available! The stars of the hit game \"The Idolmaster\" make their Ace Combat debut! Eighth up are the cheerful and mischievous twins, Ami and Mami Futami. It's time for these fun-loving pranksters to strut their stuff! Let's see what tricks they've got up their sleeves! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack08, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":44,
				"name":"Jungle, Flamingo Set",
				"releaseDate":"2008/05/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Jungle, Flamingo Set (2 Aircraft) Now Available! Two aircraft including F-14D SuperTomcat (Green), A-10A ThunderBolt II (Pink). A modified sky painting aircraft for shows and exhibitions, this aircraft is equipped with colored smoke missiles. With a maximized missile payload, the sky is your canvas! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack08, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":45,
				"name":"Su-47 - Grabacr Emblem",
				"releaseDate":"2008/06/04",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Su-47 Berkut, Ace Combat 5 Grabacr Aircraft Now Available! An aircraft that boasts increased mobility in designated speed zones, but a slight decrease in all other zones. The need for precise speed control makes this aircraft suitable for experienced pilots. Let this fighter bring out the ace pilot in you! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack08, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":46,
				"name":"Su-47 - Gault",
				"releaseDate":"2008/06/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Su-47 Berkut, Gault Team Aircraft Now Available! An aircraft used by the Gault Team from Ace Combat Zero. Although this fighter's thrust performance has been decreased, it features improved turning performance in reduced speed zones. Lead your enemy right where you want them and take charge of the battle! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack09, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":47,
				"name":"Typhoon - Type Ace 3",
				"releaseDate":"2008/06/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Typhoon, Ace Combat 3 Aircraft Now Available! A faithful recreation of the Ace Combat 3 aircraft performance design. Although hindered by slow turning response, this fighter boasts outstanding speed performance and durability. However, the aircraft lacks SP weapons which were not introduced until after Ace Combat 3. Experience what it was like to fly back in the day! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack09, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":48,
				"name":"Dark, Shining Set",
				"releaseDate":"2008/06/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Dark, Shining Set (2 Aircraft) Now Available! Two aircraft including F-2A (Black), Rafale M (Gold). Modified sky painting aircraft for shows and exhibitions, these aircraft are equipped with colored smoke missiles. With a maximized missile payload, the sky is your canvas! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack09, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":49,
				"name":"F/A-18F - The Idolmasster Ritsuko",
				"releaseDate":"2008/06/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F/A-18F Super Hornet, The Idolmaster, Ritsuko Akizuki Aircraft Now Available! The stars of the hit game \"The Idolmaster\" make their Ace Combat debut! Ninth up is the no-nonsense leader, Ritsuko Akizuki. You've got the brains, she's got the moves - let's get lots of enemies! We can't wait to see her show off her smooth moves! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack09, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":50,
				"name":"F-14D - The Idolmaster Azusa",
				"releaseDate":"2008/06/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-14D Super Tomcat, The Idolmaster, Azusa Miura Aircraft Now Available! The stars of the hit game \"The Idolmaster\" make their Ace Combat debut! Tenth up is the easygoing Azusa Miura. Sit back and let her take you on a smooth ride to victory! Let's see just what kinds of skills she's got! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack09, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":51,
				"name":"A-10A - Distant Thunder",
				"releaseDate":"2008/06/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A-10A Thunderbolt II, Distant Thunder Aircraft Now Available! An aircraft with a thoroughly reworked design and anti-aircraft capability that allows it to hold its own in air combat. Although less durable than the previous design, this aircraft features an increased weapons payload. Use your increased firepower to strike down the enemy like a bolt of lightning! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack09, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":52,
				"name":"Ace of Aces Mission 03",
				"releaseDate":"2008/06/25",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Mission 03 is now available on the highest difficulty level, Ace of Aces. Rush onto the snowy plain of Sipli Field, and burst through the massive enemy line! New Counter-Charge System! Allied reinforcements are rewarded based on the number of enemies downed during the time limit. Call in Allied Support, and destroy the enemy! New enemy ECM reported! A detrimental effect on missile performance has been reported, but details remain scarce. Stay alert!<br><br>Campaign Mode, Mission 01 must be cleared, and Free Mission Save Data available to use this download content. Select Ace of Aces via Free Mission after download to play."
			},
			{
				"id":53,
				"name":"F-14D - Wardog Emblem",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"F-14D Super Tomcat, Ace Combat 5 Wardog Squadron Aircraft Now Available! An aircraft with a Wardog Squadron emblem that features improved speed performance for emergency interception missions, as well as an increased anti-air weapons payload for better defense. Take to the skies with the fighter of the legendary \"Four Wings of Sand Island\"! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack09, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":54,
				"name":"CFA-44 - ACES",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"CFA-44 Nosferatu, ACES Aircraft Now Available! Emblazoned with the logo of the Ace Combat development team, this fighter boasts a streamlined payload and excellent maneuverability. After all, a remarkable sense of control is the sign of a true ace! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack10, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":55,
				"name":"Typhoon - The Idolmaster Makoto",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Typhoon, The Idolmaster, Makoto Kikuchi Aircraft Now Available! The stars of the hit game \"The Idolmaster\" make their Ace Combat debut! Eleventh up is the androgynous Makoto Kikuchi. She has a few faults, but her agility captures the hearts of all who gaze upon her! We can't wait to watch her dance through the skies! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack10, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors"
			},
			{
				"id":56,
				"name":"Ace of Aces Mission 04",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/23",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Mission 04 is now available on the highest difficulty level, Ace of Aces. Destroy the impenetrable Bartolomeo Fortress positioned in the natural defenses of Mt. Marcello. New Counter-Charge System! Allied reinforcements are rewarded based on the number of enemies downed during the time limit. Call in Allied Support, and destroy the enemy! New enemy ECM reported! A detrimental effect on missile performance has been reported, but details remain scarce. Stay alert!<br><br>Campaign Mode, Mission 01 must be cleared, and Free Mission Save Data available to use this download content. Select Ace of Aces via Free Mission after download to play."
			},
			{
				"id":57,
				"name":"A-10A - The Idolmaster SP",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A-10A ThunderBolt II, The Idolmaster SP Aircraft Now Available! The stars of the hit game \"The Idolmaster\" make their Ace Combat debut! Twelfth up is the staff of 765 Productions! This unusual aircraft from our friends at 765 Productions makes flying fun! We can't wait to take this baby for a test flight! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack10, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			},
			{
				"id":58,
				"name":"Ace of Aces Mission 09",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/23",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Mission 09 is now available on the highest difficulty level, Ace of Aces. Penetrate the fleet's defenses and destroy the heavy command cruiser, Aigaion! New Counter-Charge System! Allied reinforcements are rewarded based on the number of enemies destroyed during the time limit. Call in Allied Support, and destroy the enemy! New enemy ECM reported! A detrimental effect on missile performance has been reported, but details remain scarce. Stay alert!<br><br>Campaign Mode, Mission 01 must be cleared, and Free Mission Save Data available to use this download content. Select Ace of Aces via Free Mission after download to play."
			},
			{
				"id":59,
				"name":"Rafale M - Espada",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/29",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Rafale M, Espada Aircraft Now Available! An aircraft used by the Espada Squadron from Ace Combat Zero. Although hindered by decreased speed performance, this fighter's turning ability has been improved to give it a dominant position in air combat. Fly circles around your enemies before striking the final blow! Once downloaded other player aircraft will also reflect the content of Aircraft Pack10, otherwise other player aircraft will appear as Emmerian colors."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yeDHeSeV1BA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Uw5mEfiU38U"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938702-ace-combat-6-fires-of-liberation/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ace-Combat-6-Fires-of-Liberation/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ace-combat-6-fires-of-liberation/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ace-combat-6-fires-of-liberation"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Acepedia - The Ace Combat Wiki",
				"url":"http://acecombat.wikia.com/wiki/Ace_Combat_6:_Fires_of_Liberation"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":179,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["MercurySteam"],
			"synopsis":"A supernatural horror action game with a story devised by the master mythmaker, novelist and filmmaker Clive Barker. Mingling the darkest elements of Barker's horror fiction and films, Jericho deals with the mysterious reappearance of a lost city in a remote desert. When a form of evil that goes right back to the dawn of days resurfaces from there, a Special Forces squad, trained in both conventional warfare and the arcane arts, is sent in. Their mission: hunt down and destroy the evil that lurks at the heart of the city before it destroys humanity.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wePhq7wNR-Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xna6Zawqeh0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6Q8YlqHGgAA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/934443-clive-barkers-jericho/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Clive-Barkers-Jericho/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/clive-barkers-jericho/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/clive-barkers-jericho"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":180,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Nihilistic Software"],
			"synopsis":"Conan is an action adventure game featuring a story of epic brutality, sheer evil and visceral combat. Players follow the journey of Conan the Cimmerian as he fights a vicious battle against a variety of enemies and an elusive power that threatens to consume the Hyborian world. Playing as Conan, players take advantage of a deep and gratifying combat system that offers a variety of deadly weapons, fighting styles and interactive environments to battle hordes of enemies. In addition, the Conan harnesses next generation hardware to deliver a cinematic game play experience, complete with special effects, lighting and a powerful, epic soundtrack, to capture the essence of the Conan universe.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8U9daKYHN7A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B9SKJC90l5Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938400-conan/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Conan/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/conan/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/conan"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":181,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Crystal Dynamics", "Buzz Monkey Software"],
			"synopsis":"Created with an advanced version of the engine used for Lara Croft Tomb Raider: Legend, the gameplay mechanics, artificial intelligence and level puzzles of Tomb Raider: Anniversary are now more refined, in-depth and complex. Now fans can explore the original adventure on a much grander scale, while enjoying the elements which made the original such a success.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pkLD9-HlfPU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qaG0BhLBlAs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Tomb Raider 1 vs Anniversary Comparison",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jmgYxNa5Row"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/940567-tomb-raider-anniversary/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tomb-Raider-Anniversary/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tomb-raider-anniversary/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tomb-raider-anniversary"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tomb Raider Wiki",
				"url":"http://www.tomb-raider.wikia.com/wiki/Tomb_Raider_Anniversary"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":182,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Neversoft Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Rock out to the third entry in in Red Octane's music series for guitar gods! Songs for Guitar Hero III include Barracuda by Heart, Sabotage by Beastie Boys, Rock And Roll All Nite by Kiss, and much more! In addition, players can experience an incredible number of added features and explosive content including a new multiplayer action-inspired battle mode, grueling boss battles, a bevy of exclusive unlockable content and authentic rock venues. Expanded online multiplayer game modes also allow axe-shredders worldwide to compete head-to-head for true legendary rock status.<br><br>Also for the first time ever, Guitar Hero fans can thrash and burn with new wireless guitar controllers available for each platform. The exclusive Gibson guitars include innovative features such as removable faceplates that will allow fans to personalize their guitars and make it their own, and a new button color design that is integrated for an even greater authentic feel and rock experience.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable tracks",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/28",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"59 tracks available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9mTj9M6kAXo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ogzfullPjT8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Through The Fire and Flames 100% Expert",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4Sfg2RG0kTw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939093-guitar-hero-iii-legends-of-rock/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Guitar-Hero-3-Legends-of-Rock/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/guitar-hero-iii/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/guitar-hero-iii-legends-of-rock"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wikihero",
				"url":"http://guitarhero.wikia.com/wiki/Guitar_Hero_III:_Legends_of_Rock"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":183,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rainbow Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Cars Mater-National offers fans of the film a fresh adventure set in the super-fueled world of Radiator Springs. The video game features all-new international characters vying for their chance to compete against Lightning McQueen in the First Annual Mater-National Race Festival. Players explore the new and improved open world of Radiator Springs, complete with new tracks, mini-games and more than 10 multiplayer games.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SYwB-bDSwwE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N52V7qQ6YBA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938971-cars-mater-national-championship/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cars-Mater-National-Championship/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cars-mater-national/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cars-mater-national-championship"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":184,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Beenox"],
			"synopsis":"Based on DreamWorks Animation's Bee Movie film due out this fall, Bee Movie Game lets players race, chase and fly their way through an adrenaline-fueled world of adventure as they experience the hilarious antics of Barry B. Benson, a dynamic and daring bee who knows there is more to life than making honey.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Oi77hlIIiYQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vu6ambPs_H8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bee-Movie-Game/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bee-movie-game/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bee-movie-game"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":185,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"Naruto: Rise of a Ninja takes place in a world where ninja are the ultimate power. Infused with the spirit of a once fearsome Nine-Tailed Fox demon, Uzumaki Naruto is a ninja-in-training who is learning the art of ninjutsu with his classmates Sakura and Sasuke. The trio studies under the instruction of their teacher, Kakashi, who helps the group face a series of dangerous and daunting tests and challenges. Through their adventures, the young ninjas learn the importance of friendship, teamwork, loyalty, hard work, creativity, ingenuity and right versus wrong.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Choji & Temari",
				"achievements":30,
				"type":2
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Jiraiya & Sarutobi",
				"achievements":30,
				"type":2
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Shikamaru",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":2
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bg0wVlNk7Vk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xviz3Xnb3h0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932520-naruto-rise-of-a-ninja/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Naruto-Rise-Of-A-Ninja/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/naruto/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/naruto-rise-of-a-ninja"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Narutopedia",
				"url":"http://naruto.wikia.com/wiki/Narutopedia"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":186,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Redwood Shores Studio"],
			"synopsis":"Homer, Marge, Bart, and Lisa use exciting, all-new powers to save the world from rising chaos. To help the Simpsons, gamers at home must journey through all of Springfield (as well as vast worlds beyond!), vanquish an amazing array of villains, and fight their way through parodies of multiple popular games.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PGlzCaV_0aA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NbTjaT9MuY4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939416-the-simpsons-game/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Simpsons-Game/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-simpsons/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-simpsons-game"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Simpsons Wiki",
				"url":"http://simpsons.wikia.com/wiki/The_Simpsons_Game"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":187,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Saber Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"TimeShift empowers players with the gift of time manipulation, including the ability to slow down, stop and rewind the world around them, allowing them to move freely while opponents and game objects are frozen in time. Featuring complex time control puzzles as an integral part of gameplay, TimeShift takes first-person action games in an entirely new direction.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Futures-Past Multiplayer Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/05/15",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Free Map Pack Download! Receive 5 brand new Maps for the Timeshift multiplayer game. This Map Pack contains 5 maps all of which support One-on-One, Deathmatch, and Team Deathmatch. For TimeShift's new multiplayer modes, Akasen Blues, SmokeStack Lightning, and Jump, Jive an' Wail all support King of Time, while Dust My Broom supports Meltdown Madness. If Capture the Flag is your game of choice, we have two new maps to support it as well, Dust My Broom, and Beware, Brother, Beware!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Urban ReDuel Multiplayer Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/05/21",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Download this 2nd map pack and receive 5 new maps for TimeShift multiplayer. With this download you'll receive 5 single-player campaign maps which now support TimeShift's unique multiplayer action.  Every new map will support Deathmatch and Team Deathmatch, and Can I Kick It? will exclusively support TimeShifts's unique team based mode, Meltdown Madness. On Lived Life Slow, King of the Ave, and Don't Push Me, you'll play the new King of Time game mode and battle one-on-one, which is also available on Bang Bang Boogie. Experience truly distinctive Multiplayer combat through the use of Chrono Grenades that will slow, stop or reverse anyone or anything caught within their blast radius. TimeShift - Master Time to Become the Ultimate Weapon!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nllpZZaN9Yw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mRsCjxout40"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fB1u75xI1UE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/929531-timeshift/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/TimeShift/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/timeshift/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/timeshift"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":188,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SEGA-AM2"],
			"synopsis":"The fifth entry in SEGA's popular fighting game series, Virtua Fighter 5 features detailed stages from around the world where players face off in fast-moving martial arts battles against one of 17 characters, including two new characters who join the elite group of fighters. Players are given the opportunity to learn and employ the new \"Offensive Move\" technique to take down their opponents from different angles, adding a new dimension to the game. Virtua Fighter 5 also includes the ability to customize characters by selecting from four base costumes and a wide range of unlockable accessories and earnable items. As players win more tournaments they will not only earn costumes and accessories, but also prizes and in-game money that will allow them to buy items from the in-game shop.<br><br>For the Xbox 360 release, the game also features an online two-player versus mode via Xbox Live. Players will not only achieve victory by defeating highly-skilled opponents, but also by competing for prizes and earning in-game money which allow them to buy many items at an in-game shop.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Item Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The first character customization item pack for Virtua Fighter 5. Includes three items for each character, to help you build fighters that are truly your own."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Item Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/04",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The second character customization item pack for Virtua Fighter 5. Includes two items for each character, to help you build fighters that are truly your own."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Item Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2008/01/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The third character customization item pack for Virtua Fighter 5. Includes two items for each character, to help you build fighters that are truly your own."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mqt2ucM4aME"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=saKBjyD4HKY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/937423-virtua-fighter-5-online/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Virtua-Fighter-5/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/virtua-fighter-5/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/virtua-fighter-5-online"
			}]	
		}
	},
	{
		"id":189,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Krome Studios"],
			"synopsis":"A multiplayer game expanding the Viva Pinata experience. Compete in a variety of zany battles and races in the social party game Viva Pinata: Party Animals. Control the fame, fortune, and destiny of all your favorite characters from Viva Pinata: Fergy Fudgehog, Paulie Pretztail, Franklin Fizzlybear, and Hudson Horstachio. It's party time!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pXmymDmVIKM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ic8D-hmhHZE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Viva-Pinata-Party-Animals/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/viva-pinata-party-animals/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/viva-pinata-party-animals"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Viva Pinata Wiki",
				"url":"http://vivapinata.wikia.com/wiki/Viva_Pinata_Wiki"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Pinata Island",
				"url":"http://pinataisland.info/viva/Main_Page"
			}]	
		}
	},
	{
		"id":190,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Infinity Ward"],
			"synopsis":"War rages on in the fourth edition of Activision's acclaimed war game. For the first time in the series, Call of Duty moves away from WWII to the modern battlefield. Armed with an arsenal of advanced and powerful modern day firepower, players are transported to treacherous hotspots around the globe to take on a rogue enemy group threatening the world. As both a U.S Marine and British S.A.S. soldier fighting through an unfolding story full of twists and turns, players use sophisticated technology, superior firepower and coordinated land and air strikes on a battlefield where speed, accuracy and communication are essential to victory. The epic title also delivers an added depth of multiplayer action providing online fans an all-new community of persistence, addictive and customizable gameplay.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Variety Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/04/04",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Reinforcements have arrived! The Variety Map Pack includes four new multiplayer maps featuring a variety of locations. \"Creek\", a wide-open village ravaged by combat where concealment is the difference between life and death. \"Broadcast\", fight throughout an enemy communications building with confined corridors and wide-open parking lots. \"Chinatown\", a foggy downtown district, lit only by a full moon and the neon glow of the city. \"Killhouse\", featuring a desolate training warehouse filled with a variety of building mock-ups and soft and hard cover points."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ygx1EU5OWN0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LhuIjNSg7Gg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Single-Player Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xS9BoEDOTso"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5obaoq03648"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939212-call-of-duty-4-modern-warfare/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Call-of-Duty-4/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/call-of-duty-4-modern-warfare/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/call-of-duty-4-modern-warfare"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Call of Duty Wiki",
				"url":"http://callofduty.wikia.com/wiki/Call_of_Duty_4:_Modern_Warfare"
			}]	
		}
	},
	{
		"id":191,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Omega Force"],
			"synopsis":"Bladestorm: The Hundred Years War brings to life the intensity and drama of a war-torn Medieval Europe featuring a rich tapestry of legendary characters including Joan of Arc and Prince Edward, the Black Prince.<br><br>Utilizing a next-generation game engine, the game's armies collide on the battlefield at an unprecedented scale. Countless numbers of men consumed with ferocious intensity converge on screen, where tactics and cunning combine with valor and might to determine who is left standing at the end of the day. The game puts players in the role of a rogue commander and gives them direct control of mercenary units in fierce clashes with English and French forces. You must adjust strategies as skirmishes evolve, and then deploy the unit best-suited to handle the challenge. Game progression is wholly dependent on a player's decisions and accomplishments on the battlefield.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p-KNMrJh5fw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9UCCA4XZVDI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1mTO_pdgofI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/937017-bladestorm-the-hundred-years-war/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bladestorm-The-Hundred-Years-War/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bladestorm-the-hundred-years-war/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bladestorm-the-hundred-years-war"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Koei Wiki",
				"url":"http://koei.wikia.com/wiki/Bladestorm:_The_Hundred_Years'_War"
			}]	
		}
	},
	{
		"id":192,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Fun Labs"],
			"synopsis":"Take an incredible adventure to the world's marquee hunting locations in pursuit of the most sought-after and exotic big game trophy animals. You will need to put yout hunting skills and techniques to the test to master real-life hunting strategies and bring down legendary big game. Along your journey, you will meet hunting guides who will offer helpful hints, find unlockable hunts for birds and small game, and have surprise encounters with dangerous game. Are you ready for the hunting adventure of a lifetime?",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Rifle and Sheep Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/01",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"This pack makes available a new, powerful rifle to use in either Career or Instant Hunt modes. Also, a new animal becomes available to hunt in Instant Hunt mode, the Stone Sheep. It's a great way to add to your list of trophies!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aNa8cigHx2U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p0J9vbwsksI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cabelas-Big-Game-Hunter/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cabelas-big-game-hunter-2008/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cabelas-big-game-hunter"
			}]	
		}
	},
	{
		"id":193,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["TimeGate", "Day 1 Studios"],
			"synopsis":"F.E.A.R. Files uses combat adaptable AI to provide an intense \"action movie\" experience while keeping players engrossed in it's spine-chilling storylines. Gamers will assume the roles of an elite soldier trained in combating unusual and unimaginable situations. Called in to confront a mysterious force, the player must escape from a crisis spiraling out of control. F.E.A.R. Files contains two F.E.A.R. missions (the all-new F.E.A.R. Perseus Mandate campaign, as well as F.E.A.R. Extraction Point) which provide the player with a unique fusion of stylized first-person shooter and supernatural suspense that will keep gamers at the edge of their seats.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QGiLBvTwjZI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Perseus Mandate Campaign Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-D3vqSQteLM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Extraction Point Campaign Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x8cUGHBuvTU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/FEAR-Files/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fear-files/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fear-files"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"F.E.A.R. Wiki",
				"url":"http://fear.wikia.com/wiki/F.E.A.R._Files"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":194,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Traveller's Tales"],
			"synopsis":"Building on the success of both LEGO Star Wars videogames, LEGO Star Wars: The Complete Saga enables families to play through the events of all six Star Wars movies in one videogame for the first time ever. From the Trade Federation's \"negotiations\" with Obi-Wan Kenobi and Qui-Gon Jinn in The Phantom Menace to the space battle above Endor in Return of the Jedi, The Complete Saga allows players to kick some brick through 36 Story Mode levels, including Episode II's newly added high-speed pursuit of bounty hunter Zam Wessell. Traveller's Tales has revamped levels from the original LEGO Star Wars to match the gameplay evolutions found in LEGO Star Wars II, and Prequel Trilogy characters can now be mixed and matched with those from the Original Trilogy - more than 160 in all. Features include new playable characters, an upgraded character customizer, and new bonus levels.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oWU-noCTe08"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UYk1kS_PCgE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939579-lego-star-wars-the-complete-saga/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/LEGO-Star-Wars-the-Complete-Saga/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lego-star-wars-the-complete-saga/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lego-star-wars-the-complete-saga"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Brickipedia",
				"url":"http://lego.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Star_Wars:_The_Complete_Saga"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Lego Star Wars Wiki",
				"url":"http://legostarwars.wikia.com/wiki/Lego_Star_Wars:_The_Complete_Saga"
			}]	
		}
	},
	{
		"id":195,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Screenlife", "WXP Inc."],
			"synopsis":"The popular DVD board game is now easier to play than ever thanks to this Xbox 360 version. Your favorite film scenes will play, and it's up to you to buzz in and answer the trivia questions. The Xbox 360 version includes four controllers to play the game with your friends.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NgirOA2S2kk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mf1r4FE21gg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Scene-It-Lights-Camera-Action/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/scene-it-lca/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/scene-it-lights-camera-action"
			}]	
		}
	},
	{
		"id":196,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["THQ"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the popular Avatar: The Last Airbender animated series, Avatar: The Burning Earth continues the epic adventure of Aang and his courageous battle to restore balance to his war-torn world. Join him and his friends Katara, Toph, and Sokka as they master their skills and fight their way to defend the greatest Earth Kingdom city against a Fire Nation invasion!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TUCVbksIvU8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ykpmeD0nIGI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Avatar-The-Burning-Earth/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/avatar-the-burning-earth/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/avatar-the-last-airbender----the-burning-earth"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Avatar Wiki",
				"url":"http://avatar.wikia.com/wiki/Avatar_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":197,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Midway Studios - Austin"],
			"synopsis":"Following on the heels of the arcade and console shooter sensations, BlackSite: Area 51 is an action packed, first person shooter experience which pits gamers against alien enemy forces using the infamous U.S. government landmark, Area 51, and the surrounding areas as the battlefield backdrop. Set in present day, players take the role of a decorated military veteran charged by the government to lead a squadron of \"secret soldiers\", each with his/her own specialty skill set, into the Rachel, Nevada area to fight off the invasion of unidentified enemy races. The player's modern-day emotions and fears are driven into a world charged with grave responsibility affecting lives hanging in the balance and eventually finding himself torn between his professional orders and his own ethical standards. In the end, only the actions of the player and his squad can shape the outcome of BlackSite: Area 51 during this potentially pivotal moment in history.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bV3FfLu5CwI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-a5gHYm37eM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pMqn7y1uPWU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/937988-blacksite-area-51/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/BlackSite-Area-51/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/blacksite-area-51/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/blacksite-area-51"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"BlackSite: Area 51 Wiki",
				"url":"http://area51.wikia.com/wiki/BlackSite:_Area_51"
			}]	
		}
	},
	{
		"id":198,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"From the team that brought the world Prince of Persia and Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell comes a sophisticated franchise utilizing the power of next-gen technology for its complex action.<br><br>The setting is 1191 AD. The Third Crusade is tearing the Holy Land apart. You, Altair, intend to stop the hostilities by suppressing both sides of the conflict. You are an Assassin, a warrior shrouded in secrecy and feared for your ruthlessness. Your actions can throw your immediate environment into chaos, and your existence will shape events during this pivotal moment in history.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cc-ClutaN_I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay (Damascus)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4H1iIsxVDDo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay (Acre)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kJTlshCvSK0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay (Jerusalem)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vi-5MpUeKn4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Free Roam gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C1xWMgyAJro"
			},
			{
				"type":"Free Roam gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dG9mnANEw-8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930278-assassins-creed/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Assassins-Creed/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/assassins-creed/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/assassins-creed"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Assassin's Creed Wiki",
				"url":"http://assassinscreed.wikia.com/wiki/Assassin%27s_Creed"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":199,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Tiwak", "Ubisoft Shanghai"],
			"synopsis":"You are Beowulf, legendary Norse warrior with the strength of 30 men. Arrogant, self-serving, and lustful for gold and glory, you journey to Denmark to destroy a bloodthirsty beast wreaking havoc on a frigid land. But evil persists, and you succumb to its lure of even greater fame, quietly maneuvering to claim the Danish throne. As King, you must face the consequences of ambition, even as war descends on the realm. Lead your thanes into battle, slay the Titans of a dying age, and crush the enemies that threaten to annihilate both your kingdom and your people. Only then, when you look Destiny in the eye, will you know what kind of hero you truly are...",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jh3Z4W3dNBs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bIQ4gTwEI2E"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942279-beowulf-the-game/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Beowulf/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/beowulf/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/beowulf-the-game"
			}]	
		}
	},
	{
		"id":200,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Torus Games"],
			"synopsis":"Experience extreme monster truck action as you catch massive air, crush cars, perform crazy stunts, destroy everything in your path, race to the finish line and more. Battle through stadium races, freestyle competitions and outdoor circuit tracks on your way to becoming the Monster Jam world champion!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p9553r5swHs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Monster-Jam/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/monster-jam-07/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/monster-jam"
			}]	
		}
	}]
}