{
	"catalog": [
	{
		"id":1,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rare"],
			"synopsis":"Blending the heady thrills of exploration and puzzle-solving with the adrenaline rush of real-time 3D battles, Kameo: Elements of Power is an ambitious title from the makers of GoldenEye and Banjo-Kazooie. The concept mixes combat action with creature transformations, letting the title's female star morph into monsters and use their special powers against others as Kameo searches out and battles ever-present evil. The Xbox 360 game also features multiplayer co-op play, both online and offline.<br><br>Originally scheduled for release on Xbox in 2003 (after the GameCube version was cancelled), Kameo for Xbox was moved to the console's successor, the Xbox 360.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Winter Warrior Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2005/11/14",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Morph into the holidays with customized outfits perfect for warrior winter wear. Even Kameo herself takes a cool approach to ringing in the season making Red your new favorite color. "
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Co-Op Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/05",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Download this to enable co-op play in the action levels over Xbox Live and System Link!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Masquerade Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"10 great costumes for Kameo! Use the Bonus menu in the last page of the Wotnot to change your costume in-game."	
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Fright Warrior Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Swap to these horror-themed costumes when selecting a Warrior in the Wotnot. For Kameo, use the Bonus menu."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Power Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/09/12",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Think you've mastered Kameo? Test your skills in the new Expert mode where you'll find yourself in twisted new versions of the game's levels where only the strongest will survive! New Rune Battle Versus mode, Time Attack Co-op, 15 new Achievements and Armor costume pack are also included."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Design-A-Skin Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/09/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"You've seen what Rare can do; now find out what the designers of tomorrow came up with for the Kameo Design-A-Skin Contest! Enjoy 11 all-new skins for Kameo and her Warriors based on designs from the games' fans! Download this free pack now and find out what Ash would look like as a Griffin, what happens when you mix Snare with a giant cobra, and why poor Thermite feels as though he has the weight of the world on his shoulders!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U3mPs0WmTYs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IXV0UYiygLY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AT7fu9k20d8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Video walkthrough",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C7HX2z3g4S0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/516505-kameo-elements-of-power/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kameo/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kameo-elements-of-power/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kameo-elements-of-power"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"RareWiki",
				"url":"http://rare.wikia.com/wiki/Kameo:_Elements_of_Power"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":2,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Indie Built"],
			"synopsis":"Amped 3, like snowboarding itself, isn't just about the sport. Sure, there's an all-new physics engine, an innovative artificial intelligence engine, and perfected controls, so you get the most authentic riding experience at some the world's greatest winter resorts... but snowboarding is all about style. That's why Amped 3 offers incredible customisation, a fat helping of boarding culture, and deep, wide mountains of sandbox-style ride-anywhere gameplay.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B-lwdL31rZ8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KtMmxpl-YIs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928316-amped-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Amped-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/amped-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/amped-3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":3,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Monolith Productions"],
			"synopsis":"You are FBI agent Ethan Thomas, whose pursuit of relentless serial killers leads him through detailed urban environments filled with terrifyingly real sociopaths who lurk on the periphery of humanity. Gruesome weapons can be fashioned by clever players from the environment: paper-cutter handles, wooden planks and lead pipes ripped from walls can all be used to attack opponents. But watch your step, as enemies don't merely run at you; they find an appropriately powerful weapon to attack with and then hide in the shadows, waiting for an open opportunity to strike.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0GEKywQIm9g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Q2fuykknQQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/926309-condemned-criminal-origins/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Condemned-Criminal-Origins/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/condemned/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/condemned-criminal-origins"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Condemned Wiki",
				"url":"http://condemned.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":4,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"EA celebrates its new exclusive FIFA World Cup interactive entertainment partnership with the release of FIFA 06, a game that immerses players into the emotional intensity of the next-generation football. Utilizing the power of the Xbox 360, fans are able to revel in the world' most sophisticated representation of football ever. Experience a newly enhanced gameplay engine that delivers extremely responsive controls and greater level of depth. New physics and animations mean that players will now react more realistically to every tackle, shot or pass of the ball. For the first time you'l see and feel the joy, anguish and pain of 90 minutes of soccer in a videogame. Through the power of high-definition technology you'll see how the detail of the players is accurately recreated in fine detail. The power of the Xbox 360 truly brings to life 80,000 chanting fans in a stadium and immerses you in the emotional intensity of FIFA World Cup football.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qYMEnCZlkCs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lVNQuzG_xz4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/2006-Road-To-FIFA-World-Cup/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fifa-06/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fifa-06-road-to-fifa-world-cup"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":5,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Neversoft Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Experience the brutality, lawlessness, greed, and lust, that was the West. When life robs Colton White of all that matters, the only thing left he can trust is his GUN. From award-winning developer, Neversoft, and accomplished screenwriter, Randall Jahnson (The Mask of Zorro, The Doors), GUN follows Colton on his quest for discovery as he seeks to exact vengeful justice on those who have wronged him. GUN is a realistic epic action/adventure that lets gamers experience the brutality of the lawless West.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-YyAqBH8ty0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yK8iKJIUzPE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/929179-gun/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Gun/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/gun/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/gun"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":6,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"2006's edition in the unstoppable football series features a brand new passing game in the Quarterback Vision Control system - depending on where you are looking and how good your QB is, your zone of view affects how accurate your toss is as well as allowing you precision placement ahead of or straight to the receiver. The game now also feature Formation Specific Audibles and other tweaks to the offensive and defensive game. Outside of the huddle, Madden NFL 06 features a brand new Superstar Mode single player game, allowing you to live the life of a single NFL star, earning one of more than 60 Personas ranging from MVP to Movie Star. Import players from NCAA Football NFL STREET 2 player into NFL Superstar Mode to give him a head start, and experience a story mode of endorsement deals, minigames and more.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=02ajPL3Kna4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=svcPOvrIcI0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/927449-madden-nfl-06/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Madden-NFL-06/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/madden-nfl-06/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/madden-nfl-06"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":7,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"Achieve NBA superstar status with the new 24/7 mode, where created players now partake in training camps, competitions and even land endorsement deals. Elevate your game by utilizing the innovative V.I.P. System to challenge profiles of friends and other NBA 2K6 ballers across the country that match their gameplay tendencies down to every minute detail. Then head over to The Crib to customize your pad, buy music and unlock mini-games with crib credits earned playing the game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fJRs0vhLBbE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tnHJUyaBzWc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928263-nba-2k6/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-2K6/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-2k6/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-2k6"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":8,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"The evolution of the EA SPORTS Freestyle Control continues with all-new EA SPORTS Freestyle Superstars. Users now dictate the actions of the top NBA stars with full user control over dazzling passes, rebounds, dunks and steals within 5-on-5 gameplay. With the superstars of the NBA playing like their real-life counterparts, Playmakers deliver fast break Freestyle passes on the fly, Stoppers control the paint, and Power players dominate the opposition with powerful user-controlled dunks. An enhanced transition game yields an up-tempo, fast-break, and physical brand of basketball that features players running the lanes and awaiting the open pass. With the NBA LIVE 06 advancements in gameplay and enhanced player graphics, the NBA's superstars look and play more like their real-life counterparts than ever before. A rich collection of game modes adds to the deepest offering of NBA LIVE ever - including Dynasty Mode, EA SPORTS Online, and NBA All-Star Weekend.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Sa110hckHyE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5rU5rUlr6R8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/search/index.html?game=NBA+Live+06"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-LIVE-06/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-live-06/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-live-06"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":9,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"Need for Speed Most Wanted combines the tuner customization of Need for Speed Underground with an expanded take on the police chases of the Need for Speed: Hot Pursuit series. The game features a Rap Sheet option that works hand in hand with a player's street reputation as they move up from the \"Black List\" to the A-List. Users are also able to go head-to-head with their opponents while simultaneously trying to avoid more than six different police cars at once through a dynamically changing open-ended world. Get your car peaked for outrunning the cops by customizing your muscle cars, supercars, tuners, and sports cars.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1JR1vOv3n-M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ODm2IK13nWo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/927143-need-for-speed-most-wanted-2005/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NFS-Most-Wanted/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/need-for-speed-most-wanted/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/need-for-speed-most-wanted-2005"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Need for Speed Wiki",
				"url":"http://nfs.wikia.com/wiki/Need_for_Speed:_Most_Wanted"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":10,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Kush Games", "Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"NHL 2K6 continues its legacy on the ice with more control, more emotion and more detail than ever before. Take command of tape-to-tape passing, behind-the-net plays and precision give-and-go attacks. Dominate the ice with NHL caliber goaltending, skating, checking and puck handling with the deeply enhanced animation system.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bpbob1smSCM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Sm13KvrPhsI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928463-nhl-2k6/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NHL-2K6/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nhl-2k6/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nhl-2k6"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":11,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bizarre Creations"],
			"synopsis":"The popular PGR franchise zooms onto the Xbox 360, expanding many of the Project Gotham Racing features that gamers have grown to love. PGR 3 creates the ultimate roster of the hottest supercars in existence, introduces them to the high-definition era, and drops them into a completely new gaming world, where style rules the road. Gamers drive with style and daring to earn Kudos in front of large crowds, and win badges to reward their skills in all areas of the game. Racers define and create individually customized gameplay, and can race each other - online or offline. The Project Gotham Racing franchise is designed by Bizarre Creations, a long-established independent games developer, based in Liverpool, England.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Speed Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/14",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"The speed pack add-on adds 12 new cars, and a few game updates."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Cadillac V-Series Collection",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/22",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"This free add-on adds 3 new Cadillac \"V-Series\" cars."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Style Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/07/11",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"This add-on pack adds 12 new cars and 3 online multiplayer modes."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AIF_DZ_Uyho"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k6TQJdRe41E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eTI7KVpn5ws"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/927245-project-gotham-racing-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/PGR-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pgr-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/project-gotham-racing-3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":12,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Electronic Arts"],
			"synopsis":"Hit the course with Tiger in Electronic Arts TIGER WOODS PGA TOUR 06 for the Xbox 360. Including new controls, a massive character customization system, and much more, golfers will find everything they want in the 06 entry in the series. The biggest change in TIGER WOODS PGA TOUR 06 is the control system, which has been revamped and redesigned. The shape stick feature allows players to carefully influence the spin and flight of the ball, making it possible to avoid sand traps or land a ball on the green when it wasn't quite lined up. The gamebreaker also makes an appearance, allowing players to add distance to shots or make putts more accurate. Putt controls, too, have been tweaked. The greens now include a grid showing slope and arrows indicating how far the ball would travel if the surface were level. Players then have to decide how the slope will affect their putt. When creating their virtual golfer, players will find a huge number of different options. Everything from facial features to clothing to accessories can be customized. Players will then have to pass a number of different challenges that test their ability to drive, putt, and more. All of these challenges help players gain the abilities needed to earn their PGA Tour card. Golfers of all levels will find that TIGER WOODS PGA TOUR 06 has something for them. With various game modes, new controls, and fun challenges, the game easily scores a hole in one.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QNDrGo7N4L8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tiger-Woods-PGA-TOUR-06/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tiger-woods-pga-tour-06/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tiger-woods-pga-tour-06"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":13,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Neversoft Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"For the first time ever, Tony Hawk's American Wasteland gives players the freedom to experience continuous skating and BMX biking action without leaving the game or waiting for load times as they explore and choose missions in a massive, living Los Angeles skate world.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6X3VHKxnHoI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AcOU_cNmVa0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928296-tony-hawks-american-wasteland/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tony-Hawks-American-Wasteland/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/american-wasteland/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tony-hawks-american-wasteland"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tony Hawk's Games Wiki",
				"url":"http://tonyhawkgames.wikia.com/wiki/Tony_Hawk%27s_American_Wasteland"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":14,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Infinity Ward"],
			"synopsis":"Call of Duty 2 lets players experience four individual soldier stories as they overcome insurmountable odds in multiple campaigns. Players have the freedom to follow each of the four storylines through for the ultimate character-driven experience, or they can engage in the historic battles chronologically for quick hitting action. Along with the new missions, the game features an enhanced engine, advanced AI, and even more authenticity than before.<br><br>A launch title for Xbox 360, Call of Duty 2 was ported over from the PC original.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Bonus Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/10",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Two all-new Call of Duty 2 multiplayer maps bring combat realism to new heights. Both are for online, split-screen, and system-link play. This pack is only compatible with the English language version of Call of Duty 2 and is not authorized for download in Germany, Switzerland or Austria. Vossenack, Germany challenges you with limited cover and varied terrain. Wallendar, Germany is perfect for squad-based combat, including hidden paths, rubble, and high-cover areas. Its war-torn cityscape embodies World War II-style urban warfare."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Skirmish Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/31",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Two all-new multiplayer maps for Call of Duty 2. This pack is only compatible with the English language version of Call of Duty 2 and is not authorized for download in Germany, Switzerland or Austria. Both are for online, split-screen, and system-link play. Kalach, Russia is a multi-level war zone with twisting passageways perfect for sniper attacks. Beaumont-Hague, France features open fields for rushes and clustered buildings for ambush maneuvers."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Invasion Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/06/29",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Five new Call of Duty 2 multiplayer maps for online, split-screen, and system-link play! This pack is only compatible with the English language version of Call of Duty 2 and is not authorized for download in Germany, Switzerland or Austria. Fight through three French towns, an Egyptian desert stronghold, and a Russian harbor. Abandoned vehicles and other defensive cover make for an intense combat experience."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UMaOIhzCi-4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XRy_w-JQl0Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zG_I_1GMY4g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Video walkthrough",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tFy6o3KGaNo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/927725-call-of-duty-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Call-of-Duty-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/call-of-duty-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/call-of-duty-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Call of Duty Wiki",
				"url":"http://callofduty.wikia.com/wiki/Call_of_Duty_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":15,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rare"],
			"synopsis":"The Xbox 360 prequel to Rare's Nintendo 64 hit, Perfect Dark. Players once again slip into the role of Joanna Dark and fight their way through a twisting sci-fi storyline. The franchise's staple multiplayer mode returns, this time with full online support.<br><br>Set in the year 2020, three years before the original hit game Perfect Dark, Perfect Dark Zero features a gripping story, multiple game scenarios for endless replayability, a massive arsenal of weapons and combat-enabled vehicles. The sci-fi, first-person shooter features a fully interactive world, support for up to 50 players online via Xbox Live, breathtaking high-resolution graphics and spectacular special effects.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Map Pack One",
				"releaseDate":"2006/06/07",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Four new multiplayer maps: Plaza, Rooftops, Trench, and GasPlant."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Map Pack Two",
				"releaseDate":"2006/11/08",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Two new multiplayer maps based on classic Perfect Dark maps: Facility and Ruin."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9raDvahTThI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xw-D-HdO-qg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Video walkthrough",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NeCGG1csNnI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/516508-perfect-dark-zero/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Perfect-Dark-Zero/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/perfect-dark-zero/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/perfect-dark-zero"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Perfect Dark Wiki",
				"url":"http://perfectdark.wikia.com/wiki/Perfect_Dark_Zero"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":16,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Namco"],
			"synopsis":"In Ridge Racer 6, the classic Namco franchise returns with more speed, excitement and gameplay variety than ever before. Players enter a world of high-definition, high-speed races and can choose to challenge others or take control of the wheel alone in a variety of on- and offline modes. Online compatibility lends to features such as Vs. Battles and downloadable content, further enhancing the game's replayability.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"01: Highride",
				"releaseDate":"2005/12/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"02: Warp Trooper",
				"releaseDate":"2005/12/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"03: Bassrider",
				"releaseDate":"2005/12/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"04: Pulse Phaze",
				"releaseDate":"2005/12/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"05: Chrome Drive",
				"releaseDate":"2005/12/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"06: Synthetic Life",
				"releaseDate":"2005/12/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"07: Disco Ball",
				"releaseDate":"2006/01/19",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"08: Night Stream",
				"releaseDate":"2006/01/19",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"09: Light Groove",
				"releaseDate":"2006/01/19",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"10: Vanishing Horizon",
				"releaseDate":"2006/01/19",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"11: Tunnel Visionary",
				"releaseDate":"2006/01/19",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"12: Tek Trek",
				"releaseDate":"2006/01/19",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"13: Rotterdam Nation Remix",
				"releaseDate":"2006/02/16",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"14: Speedster Remix",
				"releaseDate":"2006/02/16",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":15,
				"name":"15: Drive U 2 Dancing Remix",
				"releaseDate":"2006/02/16",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":16,
				"name":"16: Rareheroes",
				"releaseDate":"2006/02/16",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":17,
				"name":"17: Blue Topaz Remix",
				"releaseDate":"2006/02/16",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":18,
				"name":"18: Motor Species Remix",
				"releaseDate":"2006/02/16",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":19,
				"name":"19: Ridge Racer",
				"releaseDate":"2006/03/16",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":20,
				"name":"20: Grip",
				"releaseDate":"2006/03/16",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":21,
				"name":"21: Euphoria",
				"releaseDate":"2006/03/16",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":22,
				"name":"22: Silver Stream",
				"releaseDate":"2006/03/16",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":23,
				"name":"23: Naked Glow",
				"releaseDate":"2006/03/16",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":24,
				"name":"24: Your Vibe",
				"releaseDate":"2006/03/16",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":25,
				"name":"25: Move Me",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/20",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":26,
				"name":"26: Movin' in Circles",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/20",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":27,
				"name":"27: Eat'em Up!",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/20",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":28,
				"name":"28: TuiTui",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/20",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":29,
				"name":"29: Samurai Rocket",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/20",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":30,
				"name":"30: Daredevil",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/20",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":31,
				"name":"31: Deep Resonance",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/18",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":32,
				"name":"32: Liquid Soul",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/18",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":33,
				"name":"33: Mars Landing",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/18",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":34,
				"name":"34: Divas",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/18",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":35,
				"name":"35: Funk-A-Tronic",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/18",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":36,
				"name":"36: Rising",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/18",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":37,
				"name":"37: T Minus Ten",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/18",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":38,
				"name":"38: Monte Carlo",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/18",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":39,
				"name":"39: Carmine",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/18",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":40,
				"name":"40: Boombox",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/18",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			},
			{
				"id":41,
				"name":"41: Time Compression",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/18",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Additional BGM"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g38xo7TEFPI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IcESrlhKSOI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ridge-Racer-6/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ridge-racer-6/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/search/all/Ridge%20Racer%206/results"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Ridge Racer Wiki",
				"url":"http://ridgeracer.wikia.com/wiki/Ridge_Racer_6"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":17,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Id Software"],
			"synopsis":"The next-gen chapter of id's infamous shooter series (built on the DOOM 3 engine) for consoles and PC systems. In the game, you are Matthew Kane, an elite member of Rhino Squad and Earth's valiant invasion force. Fight alone, with your squad, and in hover tanks and mechanized walkers as you engage in a heroic mission into the heart of the Strogg war machine. But, in this epic war between worlds, the only way to defeat the Strogg is to become one of them. Battle through early missions as a deadly marine, then after your capture as a marine-turned-Strogg with enhanced abilities and the power to turn the tide of the war.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HN0PHBXuEw4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-H4r8ELBbek"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928233-quake-4/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Quake-4/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/quake-4/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/quake-4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Quake Wiki",
				"url":"http://quake.wikia.com/wiki/Quake_4"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":18,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Paris", "Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"Working very closely with Peter Jackson and Wingnut Films, Ubisoft's Montpellier studio (Beyond Good & Evil), its Montreal studio (Splinter Cell), and game director Michel Ancel have created a game reflecting the visual interpretation, character dynamics and dramatic narrative of Jackson's epic take on the classic King Kong story.<br><br>In this epic adventure, you will experience the fateful legend of Kong from the perspective of both man and beast. Survive Skull Island as unwitting hero Jack Driscoll in first-person shooting action, and unleash the staggering power of the 25-foot-tall King Kong in third-person action sequences. Use everything in the jungle to your advantage, exploiting the natural food chain of the prehistoric predators and grabbing objects from the environment to kill those hunting you.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v7IqRouCUkk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3yOFmbjXUxY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LSsN_wtCxYs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox/920341-peter-jacksons-king-kong-the-official-game-of-the/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/King-Kong/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/king-kong/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/peter-jacksons-king-kong-the-official-game-of-the-movie"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":19,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Team Ninja"],
			"synopsis":"Dead or Alive 4 defines the fighting experience on next generation consoles with the first tournament fighter on Xbox 360. Dead or Alive 4 once again raises the bar in both online and offline fighting, with 3D high definition graphics and sound, online capabilities via Xbox Live (featuring large scale global online tournaments, increased worldwide simultaneous online play, detailed scoreboards, clans and more), new incredible interactive stages, and an all star line-up of old and new favorite characters (with new costumes and storylines). The fighting system has been overhauled, allowing even more mastery and strategy of your favorite character, including the most complex DOA countering system yet!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ajHW7PbK1Os"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y5kIwOK53bw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928260-dead-or-alive-4/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dead-or-Alive-4/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dead-or-alive-4/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dead-or-alive-4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dead or Alive Wiki",
				"url":"http://deadoralive.wikia.com/wiki/Dead_or_Alive_4"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":20,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Pseudo Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Combine raw horsepower with awesome firepower in a race that demands both precision aim and breakneck speed. Destroy your enemies and tear the world apart as you master a wide arsenal of weaponry and a stunning selection of armor-laden cars. Xbox Live support ensures significant replay value for gamers itching to take on human opponents in both grand-scale arena modes and full-throttle races.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KmijcdNdLQE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EGsQ1x9VLq4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Full-Auto/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/full-auto/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/full-auto"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":21,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Chicago"],
			"synopsis":"EA Sports Fight Night Round 3 brings the most intense boxing videogame experience to the virtual ring. On the way to becoming boxing's greatest legend, train to fight like the best including Muhammad Ali and Oscar De La Hoya or create a boxing style unique only to your boxer. Go toe-to-toe with greats such as Ali, De La Hoya, Joe Frazier, Bernard Hopkins and Roy Jones Jr. Outside of the ring, gamers can establish intense rivalries through pre-fight events putting purpose and passion behind every hit.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oqHyte77Ul0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9GlAWRs7tS4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930863-fight-night-round-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fight-Night-Round-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fight-night-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fight-night-round-3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":22,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Criterion Games"],
			"synopsis":"A next-generation version of Criterion's breakthrough racing series. The hopped-up Xbox 360 version features new Xbox Live features, including online downloadable replays and the Live Revenge feature for following your rivals so you can see how well they're doing and how much they deserve you to come after them. Tracks have been retouched to make use of the Xbox 360's power, and the crash and explosion effects have been pumped up, allowing you to literally rip cars to shreds in the most explosive crashes in the series' history.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Spike TV Car",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/12",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"An exclusive car sponsored by Spike TV."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Yellowcard Car",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/12",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"An exclusive car sponsored by Yellowcard."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Xbox Live Car",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/12",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"An exclusive Xbox Live-branded car."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Alienware Car",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/12",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"An exclusive car sponsored by Alienware."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Dolby Car",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/12",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"An exclusive car sponsored by Dolby."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Monster Car",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/12",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"An exclusive car sponsored by Monster Cable Products."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Plantronics Car",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/12",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"An exclusive car sponsored by Plantronics."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SH2Zyk5wb1A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PIsOWVu6iqE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928661-burnout-revenge/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Burnout-Revenge/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/burnout-revenge/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/burnout-revenge"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Burnopedia",
				"url":"http://burnout.wikia.com/wiki/Burnout_Revenge"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":23,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"College Hoops 2K6 provides gamers all the action, pageantry and authenticity college basketball fans crave. Players are immersed in the game with Xbox 360 exclusive features including stunning player models, detailed college arenas complete with full 3D crowds and realistic animated sections for the band, home and visiting crowds. Also included are fan-favorite features such as Pre-season and Selection Sunday broadcast shows, the Coach's Clipboard, Midnight Madness, Strip 'n' Rip System, Shot Stick and V.I.P. System. The college style of play is authentically brought to the Xbox 360 with focus on defense in the post, players' shot distribution. and overall game speed.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HGoTiptNmgI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928311-college-hoops-2k6/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/College-Hoops-2K6/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/college-hoops-2k6/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/college-hoops-2k6"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":24,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Paris", "Ubisoft Tiwak"],
			"synopsis":"In 2013, the U.S. Army will implement the Integrated Warfighter System evolving what we know as the modern soldier. IWS combines advanced weapon systems, satellite communication devices and enhanced survivability into one fully integrated combat system. The IWS program has been developed to meet these new threats head on. Now, it can be tested on the battlefield.<br><br>Embody Captain Scott Mitchell as he commands the Ghosts and Special Forces allies equipped with the IWS in the quest to save the president of the United States, recover stolen nuclear codes and eliminate a vicious band of renegade soldiers hell-bent on unleashing catastrophe. Amongst the major features in Advanced Warfighter is the new Cross-Cam eye-piece communication device, utilizing the power of the Xbox 360 to deliver consistent and complete battlefield awareness.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Chapter 2",
				"releaseDate":"2006/06/21",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Pack includes 4 new Cooperative missions (Coffee Plantation, Port, River Depot, and Jungle Mine), 8 revisited and re-lit adversarial maps, 2 all-new game types, 1 new game mode (Team Battle), 2 new camouflage patters, and 5 new weapons (SR-25 Silenced, M468, M468/M320, AK-47 LMG, and the SCAR-H SV)"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DKZjxoJyI8g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rJY1sYqLIA0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/926971-tom-clancys-ghost-recon-advanced-warfighter/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tom-Clancys-Ghost-Recon-Advanced-Warfighter/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ghost-recon-aw/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tom-clancys-ghost-recon-advanced-warfighter"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Ghost Recon Wiki",
				"url":"http://ghostrecon.wikia.com/wiki/Tom_Clancy's_Ghost_Recon:_Advanced_Warfighter"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":25,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Relic"],
			"synopsis":"The Outfit delivers explosive third person WWII combat through an epic, story driven campaign, complete with the freedom of total destruction. The game allows players the option to choose from three playable squad leader personalities (or six in multiplayer), each with their own specific skills and abilities. Players will accumulate Field Units (FUs) and utilize it to call in Destruction on Demand, choosing between an extensive array of troops, weapons, vehicles and air strikes.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Multiplayer Map: Arnhem Mayhem",
				"releaseDate":"2006/03/02",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Arnhem Mayhem is an exciting new multiplayer map for use in The Outfit."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Collateral Damage Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/07/25",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Experience the non-stop action of three brand new Multiplayer maps for use over Xbox Live!, System Link and Split Screen: The Bleak Mile, Eagle's Nest and The Luftwaffe Finale."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9hA9-Vc6BaE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iqH5Z02ng4U"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928324-the-outfit/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Outfit/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-outfit/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-outfit"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":26,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bethesda Game Studios"],
			"synopsis":"After the mysterious and untimely death of the Emperor, the throne of Tamriel lies empty. With the Empire ready to crumble, the gates of Oblivion open and demons march upon the land - laying waste to everything in their path. To turn the tide of darkness, you must find the lost heir to the throne and unravel the sinister plot that threatens to destroy all of Tamriel.<br><br>In development since 2002, Oblivion is another leap forward in role-playing with its combination of freeform gameplay and cutting-edge graphics for the world under The Elder Scrolls.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Horse Armor Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Tamriel is a dangerous place. Protect your horse from danger with this beautiful handcrafted armor."			
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"The Orrery",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/17",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Harness the power of the stars. Rebuild the defiled Orrery and unlock the secrets of this Mages Guild Inner Sanctum."			
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Wizard's Tower",
				"releaseDate":"2006/04/25",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"In the frozen mountains of Cyrodiil stands Frostcrag Spire, a tower of wonders for your magic-oriented character to call home."			
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Thieves Den",
				"releaseDate":"2006/05/22",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Uncover a famous pirate's lost ship and claim it for your own. Designed for stealth-based characters."			
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Mehrune's Razor",
				"releaseDate":"2006/06/16",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Conquer one of the deepest and most challenging dungeons in all of Cyrodiil to claim this fearsome weapon."			
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Knights of the Nine",
				"releaseDate":"2006/06/16",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"A fallen King has been unchained from the darkness of Oblivion to seek vengeance upon the Gods who banished him. Only a champion pure of heart can vanquish the evil that has been released upon the land. You must heed the call, reclaim the lost relics of the Divine Crusader, and return the Nine to glory. New dungeons, characters, quests, and mysteries await."			
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"The Vile Lair",
				"releaseDate":"2006/07/13",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Deepscorn Hollow is an asylum for the wicked, a refuge from the persecution of the virtuous. Designed for evil characters."			
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Spell Tomes",
				"releaseDate":"2006/09/01",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Adds spell tomes - books that teach you spells - to dungeon loot lists."			
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Shivering Isles",
				"releaseDate":"2007/03/27",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The Shivering Isles is a large expansion pack for Oblivion that takes place outside the main gameworld. Shivering Isles features more than 30 hours of new gameplay as you are sent to explore the realm of Sheogorath, the Daedric Prince of Madness. Shivering Isles adds to the existing world of Oblivion, so you can continue playing with your existing save game/character, or create an all-new character just to explore the new content in Shivering Isles. New quests, creatures, weapons, armor, ingredients, and more await in the land of Mania and Dementia."				
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Fighter's Stronghold",
				"releaseDate":"2007/10/15",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Become the Lord of Battlehorn Castle; a sprawling stronghold nestled deep in the Colovian Highlands."			
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer (Opening)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gGzKapvOb_M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Launch Trailers",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RHNEfJhCtH0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SflbaKhBs5I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Shivering Isles Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fuIe5ZSx5iU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Lore",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A-chDClmdos"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/927345-the-elder-scrolls-iv-oblivion/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Oblivion/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/elder-scrolls-oblivion/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-elder-scrolls-iv-oblivion"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Elder Scrolls Wiki",
				"url":"http://elderscrolls.wikia.com/wiki/The_Elder_Scrolls_IV:_Oblivion"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Unofficial Elder Scroll Pages",
				"url":"http://www.uesp.net/wiki/Oblivion:Oblivion"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":27,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Romania"],
			"synopsis":"In Blazing Angels Squadrons of WWII, players test their air-combat skills as they experience the most famous battles of World War II. As a squadron leader, players can fly up to 38 WWII aircraft in both single-player and multiplayer missions. The game features squadron-based combat, in which each artificial intelligence wingman's specialized skill can be used to the pilot's advantage. During the course of the 18-mission campaign, players will evolve along with their wingmen into an ace fighting force. The heroic storyline that follows the evolution of a single squadron and the cinematic presentation create moments reminiscent of classic World War II movies. Pilots fly in close to Germany's industrial terrain during a bombing raid or emerge from the fog and cloud cover over London to engage the enemy. Up to 16 players online can engage over Xbox Live online game service in head-to-head dogfights or cooperative team play between squadrons in 10 additional missions.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1Yo5vxdKBLo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YRMDhUJ5xhI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/931005-blazing-angels-squadrons-of-wwii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Blazing-Angels-Squadrons-of-WWII/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/blazing-angels/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/blazing-angels-squadrons-of-wwii"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":28,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Omega Force"],
			"synopsis":"A second edition (and first for Xbox 360) in the tactical strategy variant in Koei's brutal, historical action series. The player's ultimate goal is to conquer the 25 regions of Ancient China and build an entire Empire using cunning diplomacy and uncompromising force. Dynasty Warriors 5: Empires gives armchair generals total control of their kingdom. Now, gamers can issue direct orders to each officer or signal general commands to officers on the field. There's even greater authority over Government, Product Development, Diplomacy and Battle Tactics with the game's 25 new policies for a total of 75 in all. The game's imperial-sized action includes 4 scenarios to unlock, 2-Player Co-Op play in \"Empire\" and \"Free\" modes, new items to unlock, and control of over 200 officers! Once the dust has settled, there's the real history of Ancient China to discover in the game's detailed Encyclopedia.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kenY8GyyD8A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BXDnI_LJtZI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/931415-dynasty-warriors-5-empires/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dynasty-Warriors-5-Empires/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dynasty-warriors-5-empires/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dynasty-warriors-5-empires"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Koei Wiki",
				"url":"http://koei.wikia.com/wiki/Dynasty_Warriors_5:_Empires"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":29,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal", "Crytek Studios"],
			"synopsis":"You're Jack Carver, stranded on a remote tropical island. A legion of elite mercenaries equipped with a military stockpile is rapidly closing in. Outmanned and outgunned, your survival won't come easy. Only with skill, instincts and ingenuity can you conquer the enemy and make it out alive.<br><br>This Xbox 360 version of the hit shooter, features both Far Cry Instincts Next Chapter and an enhanced version of the original Far Cry Instincts game. Gamers will experience advanced pathfinding and new enemy and vehicle artificial intelligence for improved chase scenes and more enemies on-screen at one time, allowing for more adrenaline-rushing fast-action sequences.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sNyXjdJEBow"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hlKPmFeAtHc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/931339-far-cry-instincts-predator/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Far-Cry-Instincts-Predator/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/farcry-instincts/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/far-cry-instincts-predator"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Far Cry Wiki",
				"url":"http://farcry.wikia.com/wiki/Far_Cry_Instincts:_Predator"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":30,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Yuke's Media Creations"],
			"synopsis":"The vixens of wrestling are back. Sure Rumble Roses XX delivers the visual \"enhancements\" that you would expect for a next generation game, but this is more than just another pretty face. Get in the ring and unload submission holds, reversals, and an increased number of other new moves to take down your opponent. Go online and team up with another beauty in the all-new Tag Team mode or compete in a free-for-all to determine who is Queen in the all-new Battle Royal mode. Fight fair or fight dirty - humiliation is the name of the game.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Costumes",
				"releaseDate":"2007/08/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"90 Costumes available for download (downloaded individually)"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_rYH6-aVkcs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w4U2_jwzVJI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/929261-rumble-roses-xx/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rumble-Roses-XX/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rumble-roses-double-x/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rumble-roses-xx"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Rumble Roses Wiki",
				"url":"http://rumble-roses.wikia.com/wiki/Rumble_Roses_XX"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":31,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Indie Built"],
			"synopsis":"Everything you loved about Top Spin is back and made even better. Take on, play as, or team up with 24 of the world's top ranked professionals, featuring tennis stars like Maria Sharapova, Venus Williams, Andy Roddick, Lleyton Hewitt and Roger Federer. Over the span of multiple seasons, coach your player through training camps, junior championships, sponsored tournaments, and all four Grand Slam events. With Digital Identity, create realistic player models and customize them with the highest level of details. Hairstyles, shirts, shorts, shoes, etc. allow you to create a player with your look and your style.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SJFK6n8OiYQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h_js9OP852A"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928289-top-spin-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Top-Spin-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/top-spin-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/top-spin-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":32,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Kush Games"],
			"synopsis":"The 2K6 edition of 2K Sports' baseball game includes innovative features such as a new movement system and realistic player collisions on the infield and outfield to take the virtual baseball experience to the next level. New broadcast elements include flashback replays, and a unique player morale system will unfold the drama like never before in a baseball video game. New York Yankees All-Star shortstop Derek Jeter is featured as the cover athlete and official spokesperson for the exclusive and official Major League Baseball multi-platform videogame.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XCZHhW3rjts"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U6EPR19uCgg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MLB-2K6/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mlb-2k6/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/major-league-baseball-2k6"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":33,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["DICE"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the blockbuster online multiplayer war Battlefield franchise, EA and developer Digital Illusions are taking the battle to another realm with a modern-war era edition somewhat similar to Battlefield 2 for PCs but developed exclusively for console gamers. Players from the United States, China and the Middle East Coalition will all be represented in harrowing 24-player battles. Command tanks, choppers and any other of more than 30 military vehicles, and make use of more than 70 kinds of weapons (including heat-seaking missles, laser designated bombs and other modern military hardware.)",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lcxC2jrstek"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mHsCGINFIgA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z0czGjv8Tk8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hNJWNb83sEA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/926055-battlefield-2-modern-combat/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Battlefield-2-Modern-Combat/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/battlefield-2-mc/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/battlefield-2-modern-combat"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Battlefield Wiki",
				"url":"http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Battlefield_2:_Modern_Combat"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":34,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Square Enix"],
			"synopsis":"Squaresoft's first massively multiplayer game comes to the Xbox 360. With FFXI, the legendary Final Fantasy series embarked on an entirely new adventure where players from around the world are able to join forces for an online RPG quest. Players from around the world control the fate of the world of Vana'diel as they volunteer for missions to defend its nations and people. Customizable characters allow players to tailor physical attributes and skills to suit individual tastes. Adventures span over 100 different areas such as mountains, deserts, oceans, castles and dungeons. Environments take on a life of their own as time and weather constantly change. Fight, explore, email and chat with other people from around the world.<br><br>Features on disc all of the Final Fantasy XI universe included, up to the Treasures of Aht Urhgan expansion.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Wings of the Goddess",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/20",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":6,
				"synopsis":"Experience the next chapter in the immersive and ever expanding world of Vana'diel in Final Fantasy XI: Wings of the Goddess, a content-rich expansion pack that brings exciting new features to the world of Final Fantasy XI. Delve into new quests, meet new players, view new sights and experience the fourth chapter in the award-winning MMORPG.<br><br>Final Fantasy XI is capable of triple-platform simultaneous multiplayer, allowing players to take up arms together on the PlayStation 2 computer entertainment system, Windows and Xbox 360 video game and entertainment system from Microsoft, whether they are in North America, Europe or Japan."			
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Seekers of Adoulin",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/26",
				"type":6,
				"synopsis":"Final Fantasy XI Online: Seekers of Adoulin is the fifth full expansion pack for Final Fantasy XI Online. It was released on the PlayStation 2 (Japan Only), Xbox 360 and Windows.<br><br>The new expansion takes players to the western continent of Ulbuka, and it's capital of Adoulin. There, players will try to reclaim the land outside of the city walls which have become areas of extreme danger, and enormous beasts."			
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4TGe6PC-Tk4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LFy_sxb8ZR4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928330-final-fantasy-xi/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Final-Fantasy-XI/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/final-fantasy-xi/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/final-fantasy-xi"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"FFXIClopedia",
				"url":"http://wiki.ffxiclopedia.org/wiki/Main_Page"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Final Fantasy Wiki",
				"url":"http://finalfantasy.wikia.com/wiki/Final_Fantasy_XI"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":35,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"Celebrating the 2006 FIFA World Cup Germany - the world's largest sporting event - 2006 FIFA World Cup brings you to the games with the world's superstar players, 12 official stadiums that will be used at 2006 FIFA World Cup Germany and stadiums from each qualifying region. Gamers can play as their favorite team from qualification right through to a virtual reproduction of the tournament in Germany.<br><br>In addition to enabling gamers to participate in the 2006 FIFA World Cup Germany by taking control of one of 127 national teams, the game features new compelling modes of play, including the Global Challenge that recreates classic moments in FIFA World Cup history. Furthermore, the game supports up to eight-way multiplayer matches and boasts a plethora of in-game unlockable content such as legendary players and exclusive apparel.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eHGr_1uOo2I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=98o_bxvyaQs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932164-fifa-world-cup-germany-2006/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/2006-FIFA-World-Cup/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/2006-fifa-world-cup/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fifa-world-cup-germany-2006"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":36,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Z-Axis"],
			"synopsis":"An official bridge between the events of the two films, X2: X-Men United and X3: The Last Stand, X-Men: The Official Game follows main characters Wolverine, Nightcrawler, and Iceman as they embark on a 28-mission journey to defeat Hydra, the Brotherhood, and a collection of other surprise villains. Features include character-specific level geometry and super-powers, voice-overs from select members of the motion picture cast, and an original narrative written by Chris Claremont and Zak Penn.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YGm1MK_T5UQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fknNcSsoQlg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/931979-x-men-the-official-game/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/X-Men-The-Official-Game/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/x-men-the-official-game/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/x-men-the-official-game"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":37,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rockstar San Diego"],
			"synopsis":"No guns, no violence, just straight up ping pong from the studio that brought us such games as Midnight Club and Red Dead Revolver. Rockstar San Diego's game takes advantage of the Xbox 360's graphic power and technology to capture the intensity, speed and excitement of Table Tennis. The game features 11 playable characters from around the world, over 15 international arenas and supports up to 8 player tournaments via Xbox Live.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kL5UQgULz_U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Zr7f6TddUk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932239-rockstar-games-presents-table-tennis/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rockstar-Table-Tennis/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rockstar-table-tennis/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rockstar-games-presents-table-tennis"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":38,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Io-Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"The fourth in the chilling Hitman series featuring the cold-blooded killer Agent 47. Finding that members of his contract agency, The ICA, are now being quietly (and mortally) eliminated, Agent 47 suspects a larger organization is moving in. Fearing he may be the next target, he heads to America. His jobs now will pay in straight-up cash - and how he spends the money will affect what weapons he has and what he does next. The developer added new gameplay systems, such as the concepts of notoriety and of blood money. The new Notoriety system means that anyone causing a bloodbath worthy of front page news is risking being recognised by civilians and guards in the future. Blood Money lets players spend their earnings on fully customisable precision weapons and specialist equipment, or they can buy additional information upon the targets and location at hand, to aid a successful and professional hit.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JJGreeRmVHw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ma2o1lZK1wM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932470-hitman-blood-money/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hitman-Blood-Money/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hitman-blood-money/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hitman-blood-money"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Hitman Wiki",
				"url":"http://hitman.wikia.com/wiki/Hitman:_Blood_Money"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":39,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Climax Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Building on the successes of its Xbox predecessors, MotoGP '06 re-launches the franchise on Xbox 360. Gamers will be met with new tracks, bike models, refined handling and Live! functionality, making this a truly fresh and aspirational title for even the most hardened fans of the series. MotoGP '06 will launch with the current 2006 season data, giving an unprecedented accuracy to the real sport, in addition to visual effects that surpass any racing title to date. All extreme mode circuits have been revamped, streamlined for speed and fast-flowing racing action. Customize and ride all new extreme bikes in street racing action from the gleaming skyscrapers of Rio de Janeiro to the jagged mountains of Tuscany.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZaoFcs5zCog"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q7svH8uBmhA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MotoGP-06/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/motogp-06/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/motogp-06"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":40,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Taito"],
			"synopsis":"In Over G Fighters, a terrorist organization threatens the world's peace and security as players take to the skies in a united world air force. Players command more than 30 of the most powerful jet fighters ever conceived and battle for air superiority in massive dogfights in the skies above Europe, Asia, Africa and North America. Players combat enemies in the air and on the ground with challenging and dangerous strike missions against well defended targets deep in the heart of hostile territory.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ky1kKLscqrw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-GJwR_lxnHY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/929256-over-g-fighters/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Over-G-Fighters/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/over-g-fighters/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/over-g-fighters"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":41,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Los Angeles"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the PC version of the same name, The Lord of the Rings, The Battle for Middle-earth II for the Xbox 360 will bring players into the heart of Middle-earth to live the battles seen in the blockbuster New Line Cinema films and classic J.R.R. Tolkien literary fiction. The game boasts a new and intuitive console-specific control scheme that will allow novice players to enjoy the game's signature strategy gameplay while giving expert players the flexibility needed to engage in a deeply complex strategy experience. Players will directly control hundreds of units in an attempt to defeat enemy armies, conquer new lands, and seal the fate of Middle-earth.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Northern Badlands",
				"releaseDate":"2006/09/20",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"This map pack features 3 new maps: Forochel, Grey Mountains, and Carn Dum."			
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8ZYdn232WPY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C5Y15YjNllk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/931424-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-battle-for-middle-earth/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Lord-of-the-Rings-Battle-for-Middle-Earth-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lord-of-the-rings-bfme-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-lord-of-the-rings-the-battle-for-middle-earth-ii"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":42,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FromSoftware"],
			"synopsis":"This squad-based action title puts gamers in control of giant mechanized military weapons of war. Chromehounds offers an intense look at war from the cockpits of colossal metal vehicles. These heavily-armed weapons of war, called Hounds, dominate ground battles during warfare in the near-future. Squads of Hounds take to the field in international factions, cooperating with and complementing each other in terms of firepower, range of movement, and abilities.<br><br>Domination of the world is the prize for the mightiest army on the field. Strategic planning, snap reflexes and communication are key to winning the day in this battle-hardened action title. Players will take the role of either a Squad Member or a Tactics Commander, who is responsible for strategically guiding the team to victory with verbal commands on Xbox Live.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PinvyUUwVwk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Anwr91RzvrY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1Z6igBq-lpY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928456-chromehounds/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Chromehounds/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/chromehounds/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/chromehounds"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":43,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Venom Games", "Human Head Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Prey tells the story of Tommy, a Cherokee garage mechanic stuck on a reservation going nowhere. Abducted along with his people to a menacing mothership orbiting Earth, he sets out to save himself and his girlfriend and eventually his planet.<br><br>In Prey, players enter a living spaceship which enslaves alien races and devours humans for lunch. A unique twist on the first person shooter genre, Prey features such innovations as the ability to walk on walls, manipulate gravity and perform a \"spirit walk\" by leaving your physical body behind. Designed by Human Head and brought to Xbox 360 by Venom Games (under the direction of 3D Realms), Prey features full online support for up to eight players, utilizing the game's play innovations for unique multiplayer experiences.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Jen",
				"releaseDate":"2006/10/10",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Multiplayer character: Tommy's girlfriend. Those years running a bar are useful when kicking ass."			
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Becky",
				"releaseDate":"2006/10/10",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Multiplayer character: A female victim of the Sphere. She escaped, but finds herself in even more trouble!"			
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Hunter",
				"releaseDate":"2006/10/10",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Multiplayer character: A minion of the Sphere. No sense just letting the humans have all the fun."			
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Elite",
				"releaseDate":"2006/10/10",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Multiplayer character: Another type of Hunter. Forced by the Sphere into doing its bidding."			
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Elhuit",
				"releaseDate":"2006/10/10",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Multiplayer character: The leader of the Hidden. Don't let the dress fool you. She's tough."			
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Tunnel Rat",
				"releaseDate":"2006/10/10",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Multiplayer map: Use your Spirit Attack to gain the advantage in this gravity arena. Up to 8 players."			
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Topillogical",
				"releaseDate":"2006/10/10",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Multiplayer map: 360 degree run-and-gun inside a giant sphere of death. Best with 4 players."			
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Space Oddity",
				"releaseDate":"2006/10/10",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Multiplayer map: Control the gravity crossover with the Launcher to rack up kills. Best with 4 players."			
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Gravity Labs",
				"releaseDate":"2006/10/10",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Multiplayer map: Snipers get an edge this time around on a floating extension of the Spindle. Best with 6 players."			
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m5HZnujR25U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ryO8_GPrpYY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928189-prey/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Prey/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/prey/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/prey"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Prey Wiki",
				"url":"http://prey.wikia.com/wiki/Prey"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":44,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"The 2007 edition of EA's college pigskin franchise. NCAA Football 07 is all about turning the tide and features an all-new momentum system where big plays, defensive stops, and special teams keep you in constant struggle for momentum and can change the game at any time. Unprecedented graphics produce living stadiums that capture every moment in complete detail, including the authentic stadiums, mascots, and marching bands.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Apvyos9Mqbo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L3eb5RKRy7k"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932196-ncaa-football-07/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NCAA-Football-07/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ncaa-football-07/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ncaa-football-07"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":45,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Capcom"],
			"synopsis":"Dead Rising follows the harrowing tale of Frank West, an overly zealous freelance photojournalist on a hunt for the scoop of a lifetime. In pursuit of a juicy lead, he makes his way to a small suburban town only to find that it has become overrun by zombies. He escapes to the local shopping mall, thinking it will be a bastion of safety but it turns out to be anything but. It will be a true struggle to survive the endless stream of undead, but players will have full reign of a realistic shopping center, utilizing anything they find to fight off the flesh-hungry mob and search for the truth behind the horrendous epidemic. The variety of different stores in the mall offers players an endless supply of resources including vehicles, makeshift weapons and more. Players will also encounter other survivors along the way and by helping them can acquire valuable clues as to what has happened.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Round Shades Key",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this key to the locker containing the [Round Shades] outfit to access the costume in the game."			
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Burgundy Wine Key",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this key to the locker containing the [Burgundy Wine] outfit to access the costume in the game."			
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Grandpa Key",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this key to the locker containing the [Grandpa] outfit to access the costume in the game"			
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Pink Paparazzi Key",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this key to the locker containing the [Pink Paparazzi] outfit to access the costume in the game."			
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Man in Black Key",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this key to the locker containing the [Man in Black] outfit to access the costume in the game."			
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Weekender Key",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this key to the locker containing the [Weekender] outfit to access the costume in the game."			
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Casual Key",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this key to the locker containing the [Casual] outfit to access the costume in the game."			
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Miami Nights Key",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this key to the locker containing the [Miami Nights] outfit to access the costume in the game."			
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Coldhearted Snake Key",
				"releaseDate":"2006/09/06",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this key to the locker containing the [Coldhearted Snake] outfit to access the costume in the game."			
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Accountant Key",
				"releaseDate":"2007/06/07",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this key to the locker containing the [Accountant] outfit to access the costume in the game."			
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Stripe Key",
				"releaseDate":"2007/06/07",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this key to the locker containing the [Stripe] outfit to access the costume in the game."			
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Pure White Suit Key",
				"releaseDate":"2007/06/07",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this key to the locker containing the [Pure White Suit] outfit to access the costume in the game."			
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YzuTDSnfbeU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iImRp9oONdU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928326-dead-rising/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dead-Rising/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dead-rising/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dead-rising"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dead Rising Wiki",
				"url":"http://deadrising.wikia.com/wiki/Dead_Rising"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":46,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Q Entertainment", "Phantagram"],
			"synopsis":"In a struggle between light and dark, a new world order is established after the destruction of the \"mysterious power stone\". Warriors are destined to battle in a place far beyond their imagination, as a magnificent story spun of drama and emotion unfolds from multiple perspectives. From the collaboration between famed game developer Tetsuya Mizuguchi (Q Entertainment) and leading Korean developer Phantagram, the epic fantasy-action game Ninety-Nine Nights combines large-scale battles and exhilarating action. Players enjoy a full complement of more than 100 different weapons and fighting styles, in addition to a vast number of magic skills and spells. Multiple playable characters are available, each with their own dedicated plot line that ultimately intertwines with that of the larger story.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E5xxyep-IzE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MTm9UUQsmMs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928270-ninety-nine-nights/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ninety-Nine-Nights/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ninety-nine-nights/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ninety-nine-nights"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":47,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"The 2007 edition of EA's unstoppable football franchise. The 2007 edition of EA's unstoppable football franchise. In its 17th installment, you control the running game like never before. For the first time ever, step up as the lead blocker to create a hole, and then take control of the tailback and smash through, overpower, or slash away from would-be tacklers as you fight for every yard. Innovative rushing controls give you a game-breaking ground attack featuring all-new jukes, cutbacks, and the distinct running styles of your favorite backs.<br><br>For the Xbox 360, exclusive features include Madden Gamer Level (which tracks your career accomplishments in Franchise Mode for points that you can wager online towards rewards) and a unique Create a Player, which uses mini-games to set skills and off-season Mini-Camps to condition players or rehab injuries to get back on the field faster.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"LA Rams Classic Stadium",
				"type":2			
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Seattle Seahawks Classic Stadium",
				"type":2		
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VRocBatZFeY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KHuqAUcJw9M"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932189-madden-nfl-07/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Madden-NFL-07/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/madden-nfl-07/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/madden-nfl-07"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":48,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Hudson Soft"],
			"synopsis":"A totally reinvented Bomberman, which switches out the super-deformed bomb dropper with supersonic, cybernetic warriors and new gameplay modes (including a \"First Person Bomber\" mode set up somewhat like an FPS Deathmatch bout.) With an all new storyline and shocking new dark themes, Bomberman: Act Zero is set in a post-apocalyptic world where cyborgs are pitted against cyborgs in a duel to the death. Equipped with armored battle suits, players can fight for survival through the single player game's 99 levels or go head-to-head online with up to eight players in multiplayer matches.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eH_2DWVfP-A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sT1CX7c_qeE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/929921-bomberman-act-zero/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bomberman-Act-Zero/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bomberman-act-zero/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bomberman-act-zero"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":49,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FromSoftware"],
			"synopsis":"The Xbox 360's first Japanese RPG places you in the control of Atsuma, who early in his adventure manages to inadvertently open a seal which revives the fierce Devil Golem. You'll make use of Golem support characters as you work through the game's strategic battle system. The game has over 100 Golems which can be assembled using ingredient items. Characters can be customized using the \"SP\" experience points that you gain in battle. As the story develops, players face increasingly difficult challenges and learn to master Atsuma's special fighting and magical abilities.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iBOA2Quy6vY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gUqUbEsLoMo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928678-enchanted-arms/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Enchanted-Arms/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/enchanted-arms/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/enchanted-arms"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":50,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Volition"],
			"synopsis":"Under threat from rival gangs and corrupt officials, the 3rd Street Saints must conquer the city of Stilwater or face destruction. From the spectacular opening battle to regain control of the local hood, Saints Row offers the freedom to explore StilWater, a living, breathing city. Players are free to engage in the multitude of different activates at their leisure, all while building up respect in a gameplay-rich world. Build enough respect and the 3rd Street Saint's lieutenants will trust the player with more dangerous missions.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Funky Fresh Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Pack contains 69 new wear options for your character; including clothing, bling, tattoos and hair."	
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Industrial Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/11/06",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"This fast paced level takes place in an abandoned factory. Available for Gangster Brawl and Big Ass Chains."		
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Ho Ho Ho Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/12/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Ho Ho Ho pack is a free downloadable pack that adds 'Santa Claus' clothing to the game. This clothing can be used in both single and multiplayer modes."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Gankster Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2006/12/19",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Gankster Pack includes the Heist co-op level and two new vehicles."	
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Exclusive Unkut pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/01/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Unkut clothes designed by BOOBA: T-Shirts, trousers, jackets, polo shirts and baseball caps."		
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bs_8pYO0U5E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fGC98jjsbGU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928235-saints-row/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Saints-Row/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/saints-row/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/saints-row"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Saints Row Wiki",
				"url":"http://saintsrow.wikia.com/Saints_Row"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":51,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Point of View"],
			"synopsis":"From opening bet to showdown, this game puts you at the high stakes table, bluffing and trying to steal the pot - like you're right across the table from some of the world's top poker-playing personalities you will need nerves of steel and a stone-cold poker face to make your fortune. Put your stamina and resolve to the ultimate test. Come face to face with the legends... Keep your calm and gamble like a pro; make your fortune and become a legend yourself.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Tw7O915dAk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932273-world-championship-poker-featuring-howard-lederer/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/WCP-All-In/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wolrd-championship-poker-all-in/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/world-championship-poker-featuring-howard-lederer---all-in"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":52,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eden Games"],
			"synopsis":"Test Drive Unlimited challenges players online to experience the most exotic and fastest cars and bikes on more than 1000 miles of diverse Hawaiian roads. Visit the most sophisticated car and bike dealers and chose to purchase new vehicles or simply take them for a spin. Collect and trade rare performance parts and customize each vehicle to make it one-of-a- kind. Gamers win races, challenges, missions and tournaments to earn credits and purchase new cars, bikes, rare performance parts, clothes, apparel, homes and garages. Boasting huge online content, racers around the world can challenge others to join them in the virtual paradise of the game's persistent online racing world.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=POwg7kdG_Yw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z2np5XHKgsM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928101-test-drive-unlimited/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Test-Drive-Unlimited/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/test-drive-unlimited/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/test-drive-unlimited"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":53,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Traveller's Tales"],
			"synopsis":"The Empire strikes back in this sequel to the endearing Star Wars game made all of LEGOs. LEGO Star Wars II follows the Rebel Alliance's battle to dismantle the Galactic Empire and rebuild a galaxy in pieces. From Darth Vader's pursuit of Princess Leia aboard her blockade runner to a showdown on the reconstructed Death Star, the game includes even more of the family-friendly LEGO action. The sequel finally allows you to build with your LEGO blocks, as a new Free Play mode allows gamers to customize the vehicles for new ship designs, as well as Free Play all of the playable characters (over 100 in total) by mixing and matching body parts, forming the likes of \"Stormbacca\", \"Chew Vader\" and \"Leia Wan Kenobi.\" Other additions include cool new character-specific attacks and maneuvers, Power Brick items, playable mini-kit vehicles, an improved two-player camera, a greater challenge for advanced players, and more.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pHVB_ZNiaKY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wC_mPd95q0I"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932914-lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/LEGO-Star-Wars-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lego-star-wars-ii/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lego-star-wars-ii-the-original-trilogy"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Brickipedia",
				"url":"http://lego.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Star_Wars_II:_The_Original_Trilogy"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":54,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"The golden age of console hockey returns when NHL 07 debuts with gameplay innovations that will allow players to feel like they are actually on the ice. The revolutionary EA Sports Skill Stick gives users the power to play in the game as it is on the ice, without taking their thumbs off the analog sticks. New presentation design, AI enhancements and animation overhauls create players who look, act and play like they would in the NHL. Gone are the days when a one-timer was the only way to score in a hockey videogame. Now look to your teammates and know how to best use their strengths with new Player-Specific Behaviors. Be the Playmaker and find your Sniper open in the slot, or let your Dangler make pylons out of the defense. Off the ice, act as the General Manager in an enhanced Dynasty Mode. Do whatever it takes to meet an owner's expectations by properly managing rosters and using your creativity to fit player salaries under the new cap.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f6vR-TqQASU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Of1yjYXYd94"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NHL-07/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nhl-07/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nhl-07"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":55,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Kush Games", "Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"Spend another year knocking hosers' teeth out with the 2007 entry in Visual Concepts' and 2K Sports' hockey game. NHL 2K7 notches a 2nd year of next-generation domination with a groundbreaking presentation system of cinematic style, bringing raw emotion and exciting drama to every hockey game. New additions to ProControl empower players to turn up the defensive pressure on specific opposing players.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TLJ5LXXn8_U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o91Nu_k8Ks0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox/933144-nhl-2k7/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NHL-2K7/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nhl-2k7/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nhl-2k7"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":56,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FUN Labs"],
			"synopsis":"Players will use a combination of skill and strategy to complete 38 hunting and fishing adventures across 12 vast Alaskan regions from the North Slope to Ketchikan.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Alaskan Bonus Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2006/10/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Includes two firearms, a Mountain Man clothing set and Super Med Kit that can be used in the game. And a new animal too!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KIg07S8qoa8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933860-cabelas-alaskan-adventures/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cabelas-Alaskan-Adventures/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cabelas-alaskan-adventures/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cabelas-alaskan-adventures"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":57,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Redwood Shores Studio"],
			"synopsis":"The book by Mario Puzo and Francis Ford Coppola's classic film serve as dual inspirations for Electronic Arts' action/adventure The Godfather. In it gamers can join the Corleone family to exploit loyalties and fear as they rise through the ranks to become Don in 20th century New York City. Carry out orders, earn respect, and make the Big Apple all your own. Featuring non-linear gameplay, The Godfather provides players with countless choices for solving family problems with brutal violence, skillful diplomacy, or a cunning mixture of both. From mob hits and bank heists to drive-bys and extortion, step deep inside a world where intimidation and negotiation are your tickets to the top. Custom-built for the Xbox 360, players will choose their path in this rough and tough world with enhanced BlackHand combat, enhanced graphics and HDTV support.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Corleone Challenges",
				"releaseDate":"2007/12/21",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"The Corleone Challenges DLC Pack features 12 additional challenges. Unlock 10 more Achievements and an additional 250 Achievement Points."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Favor Pack - 3 Favor Missions",
				"releaseDate":"2006/10/24",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Get three additional favor missions, which enable to you get past 100 game completion."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ryqrQpx1HWw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zkozIpE6RCg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928332-the-godfather/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Godfather/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-godfather/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-godfather"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":58,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"Open Season is a riotous romp in the great outdoors, where the rowdy brood of forest animals turns the tables on a bunch of unsuspecting hunters. When a domesticated grizzly named Boog gets lured into leaving the creature comforts of home by a fast-talking mule deer named Elliot, he finds himself lost in the woods just three days before hunting season. Forced to \"rough it\" in the great outdoors, Boog goes native, rallying all the forest animals to take back their home and send the hunters packing. The Open Season video game allows players to relive the movie experience by playing as Boog and Elliot. Throw skunk bombs, hurl rabbits, use acorn-firing squirrels and pull outrageous woodland pranks to scare the pants off the hunters in this action-adventure romp through the forest.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=swnyAAHyKSk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932550-open-season/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Open-Season/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/open-season/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/open-season"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":59,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Omega Force"],
			"synopsis":"The second entry in the Samurai Warriors series once again places players in control of Sengoku era generals. In addition to new generals, the game includes new gameplay systems and updated areas.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Chiyojo Mochizuki for Hire",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The guard Chiyojo Mochizuki will become available for employment at the game Shop."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Koji Kashin for Hire",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The guard Koji Kashin will become available for employment at the game Shop."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Nobutsuna Kamiizumi for Hire",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The guard Nobutsuna Kamiizumi will become available for employment at the game Shop."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Persian Mare for Sale",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The mount Persian Mare will become available for purchase at the game Shop."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Matsukaze for Sale",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The mount Matsukaze will become available for purchase at the game Shop."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Hisahide Matsunaga for Hire",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The guard Hisahide Matsunaga will become available for employment at the game Shop."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Seikai Miyoshi for Hire",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The guard Seikai Miyoshi will become available for employment at the game Shop."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Otsu Ono for Hire",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The guard Otsu Ono will become available for employment at the game Shop."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Tenkai Nankobo for Hire",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The guard Tenkai Nankobo will become available for employment at the game Shop. There are no refunds for this item."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Tsuru for Hire",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The guard Tsuru will become available for employment at the game Shop."
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Juzo Kakei for Hire",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The guard Juzo Kakei will become available for employment at the game Shop."
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Kai for Hire",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The guard Kai will become available for employment at the game Shop."
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"Moon Child for Sale",
				"releaseDate":"2006/08/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The mount Moon Child will become available for purchase at the game Shop."
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"Samurai Warriors 2: Xtreme Legends",
				"releaseDate":"2008/04/16",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Samurai Warriors 2 Xtreme Legends is an expansion pack for Samurai Warriors 2 that adds new scenarios, battlefields, characters, weapons, and a new Mercenary mode."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UKODzKE_GZg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UNEVc2HawGE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932837-samurai-warriors-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Samurai-Warriors-2-XL/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/samurai-warriors-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/samurai-warriors-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":60,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Left Field Productions, Inc."],
			"synopsis":"Tournament of Champions takes a story-based approach, putting players on the Pro Circuit as a new pro and protege of Chris \"Jesus\" Ferguson. Players test their skills at the premier Circuit Events in hopes of qualifying for the winner-take-all, invitation-only Tournament of Champions at the Rio Resort in Las Vegas. Along the way, they face-off against more top pros than ever before, including Joseph Hachem, the 2006 World Series of Poker Main Event Champion, and Jennifer Tilly, the Academy Award-nominated actress and World Series of Poker bracelet holder, among others in hopes of bringing home the Tournament of Champions trophy.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tx3H8yJdrm4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=emfjfFlwN78"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/WSOP-TOC/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/world-series-of-poker/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/world-series-of-poker-tournament-of-champions"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":61,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Avalanche Studios"],
			"synopsis":"In Just Cause, you take on the role of the flamboyant Rico Rodriguez - an undercover CIA operative specialising in regime change - as he tries to overthrow the corrupt government of San Esperito. This rogue South American island is suspected of stockpiling WMDs and it's your job to negate the threat to world peace. It could be to your advantage that this tropical paradise is about to implode as various factions vie for power - it just needs a gentle nudge in the right direction.<br><br>Just Cause offers the freedom to tackle your assignment however you want: play the island's factions off against one another; incite a rebellion among the masses; or build alliances with rebel forces and drug cartels. Explore the game's world of 1,225 square miles of mountains, jungles, beaches, cities and villages with a variety of air, land and sea craft.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vkWMI0bLsu0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L2FOX3-vXhs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932363-just-cause/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Just-Cause/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/just-cause/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/just-cause"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Just Cause Wiki",
				"url":"http://justcause.wikia.com/wiki/Portal:Just_Cause"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":62,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts", "Kush Games"],
			"synopsis":"Voted best current and next-generation NBA hoops franchise by both press and gamers, NBA 2K7 continues its legacy of dominance this year on the hard court with incredible graphics, tight control and a revolutionary shooting game. Every player's play style has been captured for the first time in a simulation for a look and feel that plays as individually as the athlete. And the revolutionary Shot Stick Pro is back with more intuitive shooting touch, control and finesse than ever. Plus, the 24/7: Next feature allows you to play your way through street mode with a fully developed storyline where you can prove you belong with the NBA's elite.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZJd58ZlITl8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q4_v_2Bn5Kk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932864-nba-2k7/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-2K7/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-2k7/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-2k7"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":63,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"The 2007 game of EA's hoops sim, designed with a new development philosophy that drives gameplay and feature innovation. This year, NBA Live 07 introduces the next generation of basketball gameplay with EA Sports' Total Freestyle Control, a new feature that gives users more control over athletes than they ever imagined. By introducing a ground-breaking next generation AI system that is both intuitive and intelligent, combined with advancements to fan-favorite features like All-Star Weekend and Dynasty Mode, NBA Live 07 will continue to deliver its award-winning gameplay experience to fans worldwide. Also this year, NBA Live 07 partners with the worldwide leader in sports to deliver more ESPN content in-game while you play than ever before.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JMcBgdN13wM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cdY4bjzjbms"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933709-nba-live-07/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-LIVE-07/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-live-07/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-live-07"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":64,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Genki"],
			"synopsis":"Import Tuner Challenge is an authentic and extremely customizable street-racing game that challenges racers to immerse themselves in Tokyo's underground to take on the fastest street-racing teams. Players can customize and race licensed import sports cars using real tuner parts and tuning techniques. More than five million combinations are possible in customizing a car's interior, exterior and engine.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T9wUceoDEdY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=co7xJQzAZ00"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/934694-import-tuner-challenge/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Import-Tuner-Challenge/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/import-tuner-challenge/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/import-tuner-challenge"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":65,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Redwood Shores Studio"],
			"synopsis":"Feel the pressure of competing against the top golfers in the world's best tournaments in Tiger Woods PGA Tour 07. All-new universal facial capture or UCAP technology brings realism and emotion to the golf course like never before, while players see and hear the crowds around them with enhanced playing environments. Course content doubles in this year's version of the world's best selling golf game franchise. Compete for The FedEx Cup, the new PGA TOUR championship playoff system against the world's best golfers, including newly added Luke Donald, Michael Campbell, Steve Elkington, and Annika Sorenstam.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6vmZS4q3h30"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tiger-Woods-PGA-TOUR-07/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tiger-woods-pga-tour-07/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tiger-woods-pga-tour-07"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":66,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal", "Ubisoft Shanghai"],
			"synopsis":"Veteran agent Sam Fisher is back. But he's never faced an enemy like this before. To stop a devastating terrorist attack, he must infiltrate a vicious terrorist group and destroy it from within. For the first time ever, experience the relentless tension and gut-wrenching dilemmas of life as a double agent. As you infiltrate a terrorist organization in its American headquarters, you must carefully weigh the consequences of your actions. Kill too many criminals and you'll blow your cover. Hesitate too long and millions will die. Do whatever it takes to complete your mission, but get out alive.<br><br>The fourth game in the Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell series thrusts players into a new breed of gameplay that promises to innovate and revolutionize the Splinter Cell franchise. Ubisoft takes the saga of Sam Fisher into entirely new territory, expanding the story and depth of his character.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Multiplayer Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/07/26",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"2 new multiplayer maps (Kinshasa and Secret base), 4 new challenges on those maps and a brand new character with 3 outfits : the Spy Girl."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v3CJKW9u7CA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RhGZk3UJybM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xyo4iGbVWT4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/926934-tom-clancys-splinter-cell-double-agent/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tom-Clancys-Splinter-Cell-Double-Agent/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/splinter-cell-double-agent/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tom-clancys-splinter-cell-double-agent"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Splinter Cell Wiki",
				"url":"http://splintercell.wikia.com/wiki/Tom_Clancy%27s_Splinter_Cell:_Double_Agent_(Version_1)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":67,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rainbow Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Race to the finish line as you live all the fun and excitement of the Walt Disney Pictures & Pixar Animation Studios film, \"Cars\". Play as all your favorite characters as you help Lightning McQueen capture the coveted Piston Cup Championship. Fans will discover unique characters and environments inspired by the film with more than 10 playable characters and 30 races and minigames to choose from. The game features a fully immersive re-creation of all major environments introduced in the movie, including Radiator Springs and Ornament Valley, which will offer distinctive racing experiences to players while maintaining the artistic style of the film.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6bwCfX8ryyI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox/932076-cars/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cars/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cars/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cars"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":68,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Raven Software"],
			"synopsis":"In this superhero-filled action-RPG, players assume the roles of more than 20 Marvel Super Heroes including Spider-Man, Wolverine, Blade and Captain America, and through their actions determine the fate of both planet Earth and the Marvel universe. The game features total team customization, where players create their own team name, icon and vehicle, as well as establish their team reputation as they play throughout the story. Battle the world's most notorious Marvel Super Villains in the air, underwater, and on the ground, using grappling, blocking and dodging moves, and even environmental objects as one and two-handed weapons. The storyline is designed open, and the missions that you choose to accept affect the outcome of the Marvel Universe. Also featured are competitive and co-operative multiplayer modes.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Playable Hero Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/26",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This pack adds four new playable heroes: Hulk, Hawkeye, Nightcrawler, cyclops."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Playable Villain Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/26",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This pack adds four new playable villains: Magneto, Sabretooth, Venom, Dr.doom."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NHZXt9dMLpM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aJCuGAKIVOg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932586-marvel-ultimate-alliance/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Marvel-Ultimate-Alliance/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/marvel-ultimate-alliance/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/marvel-ultimate-alliance"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":69,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sonic Team", "Total Entertainment Software"],
			"synopsis":"This enormous game offers two complete RPG experiences - a single-player action-adventure spanning multiple planets, and a robust online multi-player component. In offline mode, this action-RPG offers more than 40 hours of gameplay, an emotionally engaging story, traditional cut scenes, and strong character development. In online mode, players are given the opportunity to travel with a squad of other adventurers, enter urban sprawls teeming with hundreds of players, and build their unique avatars into powerful warriors",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Ambition of the Illuminus",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/20",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The first and only expansion to Phantasy Star Universe, Ambition of the Illuminus adds new missions, weapons and new weapon types, Photon Arts (special attacks), items and also re-balances all of the character classes and Photon Arts progression."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l6iNtNkE6Gs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=80I7Jgsvlpo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932621-phantasy-star-universe/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Phantasy-Star-Universe/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/phantasy-star-universe/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/phantasy-star-universe"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Phantasy Star Wiki",
				"url":"http://phantasystar.wikia.com/wiki/Phantasy_Star_Universe"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":70,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"FIFA 07 throws you into the rollercoaster ride of a football season. Employ real world tactics, make realistic decisions, and think like a player in order to win matches. An entirely new game engine will be included for the 360.<br><br>FIFA Soccer 07 on the Xbox 360 moves away from the traditional animation-based game engine and now enables raw physics and data to drive the action, creating true-to-life movement and the most advanced visuals seen in a soccer game. Player characteristics are based on brand-new traits and twice the number of attributes, so you won't see two players moving in exactly the same way. Instead they look and behave like the athletes we see gracing the pitch week-in, week-out.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jzTIw8hPVRU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lDRoLEw3bKc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933693-fifa-07-soccer/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/FIFA-07/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fifa-07/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fifa-07-soccer"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":71,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"The next-gen edition of Winning Eleven (aka Pro Evolution Soccer). The Xbox 360 boasts significantly improved visuals and animation over the original version while keeping all of the intense action and features for play on the pitch. Player AI has been upgraded, with players working to turn defenders, and defenders themselves now smart enough to back off slightly to prevent such moves. This edition also includes a much-refined shooting system - players can now attempt more snap shots than previously possible, while the volley and half-volley mechanics have been overhauled. Additional abilities include all-new feints, backwards dribbling (thanks to improved dribbling controls) and the ability to retain control of the ball when performing a sliding tackle. Clubs from major leagues appear with their real name. The game includes updated Master League modes, a new international challenge mode and a random selection mode for more intense multiplayer matches.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FWBK96rZlHM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4rdQKHtk-CY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930760-winning-eleven-pro-evolution-soccer-2007/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pro-Evolution-Soccer-6/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pro-evolution-soccer-6/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/winning-eleven-pro-evolution-soccer-2007"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":72,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Day 1 Studios", "Monolith Productions"],
			"synopsis":"F.E.A.R. (First Encounter Assault and Recon) is a first-person close-quarters combat game for the PC. The story begins when a paramilitary force infiltrates a multi-billion dollar aerospace compound, and the government responds by sending in Special Forces. The group loses contact with the government when an eerie signal interrupts radio communications-and when that interference subsides moments later, the team has been destroyed. That's where you come in. As part of a classified strike team created to deal with threats no one else can handle, your mission is simple: eliminate the intruders at any cost, determine the origin of the signal, and contain the potential crisis before it gets out of control.<br><br>This 360 version features brand new single player content, as well as brand new multiplayer content created to fully utilize Xbox Live.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ylyf9dfp2-c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8s24hQNyPTc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932585-fear/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/FEAR/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fear/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fear"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"FEAR Wiki",
				"url":"http://fear.wikia.com/wiki/F.E.A.R.:_First_Encounter_Assault_Recon"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":73,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Black Box"],
			"synopsis":"Need for Speed Carbon delivers the next generation of adrenaline-filled street racing as players face the ultimate test of driving skill on treacherous canyon roads. What starts in the city is settled in the canyons as Need for Speed Carbon immerses you into the world's most dangerous and adrenaline-filled form of street racing. You and your crew must race in an all-out war for the city, risking everything to take over your rivals' neighborhoods one block at a time. As the police turn up the heat, the battle ultimately shifts to Carbon Canyon, where territories and reputations can be lost on every perilous curve. Need for Speed Carbon delivers the next generation of customization giving you the power to design and tweak your crew's cars in every way using the ground-breaking new Autosculpt technology. Represent your car class, your crew, and your turf in Need for Speed Carbon, the next revolution in racing games.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Dump Truck",
				"releaseDate":"2007/01/12",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"This free download for Need For Speed Carbon lets you get behind the wheel of a dump truck and tear up the road with brute power! If speed and style don't interest you, then the Dump Truck is for you! Don't expect tight handling, rapid acceleration or a blazing top speed - but do expect to overpower every other car on the road with size and strength. Whether you're hauling dirt or gravel, or just taking it out for a joyride, grab the Dump Truck now to add a little size to your Carbon collection!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Fire Truck",
				"releaseDate":"2007/01/12",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Thankfully, there aren't any major fires in Carbon Canyon, but you can still feel the thrill of piloting a Fire Truck by grabbing this free download. If you thought the fishtailing in some of the muscle cars was bad, wait until you're trying to drive a vehicle over 30 feet long! This is not the car to use if you're going up against a Lamborghini or Porsche or even a Dodge Charger, but go head-to-head with another Fire Truck or square off against the Dump Truck and add a new dimension to Need For Speed Carbon. Cool fireman uniforms not included."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=krrTTkriMGw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VcNNLTUj1A4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933691-need-for-speed-carbon/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Need-for-Speed-Carbon/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/need-for-speed-carbon/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/need-for-speed-carbon"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Need for Speed Wiki",
				"url":"http://nfs.wikia.com/wiki/Need_for_Speed:_Carbon"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":74,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Point of View", "Midway Games"],
			"synopsis":"The series known as NFL Blitz pushes on without the NFL license into an all-new realm of dramatic and intense football, as Midway goes behind the scenes to bring you lifestyles, controversy, and the nitty-gritty real world of pro football players. Blitz: The League exposes the harsh and troubling, behind-the-scenes stories of a fictional professional football league.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pZzO-3l740A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e6SsI2NjWWA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932867-blitz-the-league/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Blitz-The-League/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/blitz-the-league/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/blitz-the-league"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":75,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Treyarch", "Pi Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Through the eyes of four Allied soldiers, Call of Duty 3 brings players closer than ever to the fury of combat as they fight through the Normandy Breakout, the harrowing offensive that liberated Paris and changed the fate of the world.<br><br>In Call of Duty 3, new close-quarters battle mechanics bring you face-to-face with your enemy. Fight hand-to-hand, disarm traps, improvise explosive devices and execute a host of other battlefield challenges that require cunning and swift reflexes. Next-generation level design provides multiple attack routes that let you decide how to confront the enemy. Each choice you make requires you to use special tactics, from sniping and demolition to straight out frontal assaults. And in online multiplayer battles of up to 24 players, gamers battle it out as a variety of player classes, including riflemen, infantry, scouts and others. Multiple-occupancy vehicles let you coordinate attacks with friends, driving while they fire a mounted machine gun from the turret.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Bonus Map: Champs",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Champs is a free bonus map for Call of Duty 3. The map is based in Port Royal de Champs, a wartorn French village."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Valor Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/01/27",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Five all new maps for Call of Duty 3, both for multiplayer and split-screen. - Crossing, Ironclad, La Bourgade, Stalag 23, Wildwood."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Bravo Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/05/31",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Two PC maps returning from Call of Duty and Call of Duty: United Offensive, Gare Centrale, and Marseilles. As well as three brand new maps, Aller Haut, Seine River, and Rimling."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HDfQ18eioM4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H4r3cLwCc8A"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928655-call-of-duty-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Call-Of-Duty-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/call-of-duty-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/call-of-duty-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Call of Duty Wiki",
				"url":"http://callofduty.wikia.com/wiki/Call_of_Duty_3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":76,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Epic Games"],
			"synopsis":"A third-person tactical shooter from Epic, running on the Unreal Engine 3. Gears of War thrusts gamers into a deep and harrowing story of humankind's epic battle for survival against the Locust Horde, a nightmarish race of creatures that surface from the bowels of the planet.<br><br>Unlike other shooters, Gears of War is all about teamwork in a big way. All game modes, levels and scenarios are designed specifically to encourage co-operative play, whether it be with A.I. partners or human players (with A.I. teammates designed with specific strengths, weaknesses and personalities.) On top of that, voice recognition will be available for players, and obviously voice chat to discuss strategy with your friends. In addition to voice chat, gamers will be able to experience individualized matchmaking, view player statistics, earn player achievements, customize their games, and build and personalize their gamer profiles over Xbox Live.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Multiplayer Map Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2007/01/10",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"This map pack adds two new maps: Old Bones and Raven Down. This was released free of charge, thanks to sponsorship from Discovery Channel. Raven Down and Old Bones.<br><br>Raven Down: A Raven helicopter has gone down in the middle of a large-scale battle. Gears have taken out a Seeder, and forces are now moving into the crash site from all angles to find survivors.<br><br>Old Bones: In an attempt to eradicate human culture, the Locust have emerged under Sera's Capitaline Museums and have started destroying them brick by brick."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"'Hidden Fronts' Multiplayer Map Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2007/05/03",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"This map pack adds four new maps: Bullet Marsh, Garden, Process, and Subway.<br><br>Bullet Marsh: In this Kryll-infested swamp, an old generator still powers the area lights. A few stray bullets could easily knock out the generator, leaving players in the dark to fend for themselves against the hungry Kryll.<br><br>Garden: This overgrown and crumbling conservatory still has a working fertilization and pesticide system. This system can pose a serious health hazard to anyone who ventures into the greenhouse without first venting the air.<br><br>Process: Teams must fight for control of this subterranean Imulsion processing plant, still active despite the cessation of the Pendulum Wars.<br><br>Subway: Timgad's Central Subway Station used to serve as a central hub for commuters. Now the tunnels are crawling with Locust."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer - Mad World",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M-2AjBSxU88"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9m2am6cF5aM"
			},
			{
				"type":"PC Extra Level",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DduXG47dig0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928234-gears-of-war/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Gears-of-War/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/gears-of-war/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/gears-of-war"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Gearspedia",
				"url":"http://gearsofwar.wikia.com/wiki/Gears_of_War"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":77,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cauldron"],
			"synopsis":"Immerse yourself in the intensity, carnage, and chaos of the war that divided a nation! Play as a Confederate or Union soldier in America's most legendary battles including Gettysburg, Bull Run and Antietam. Use authentic firearms, fight in intense hand-to-hand combat, place explosives, sabotage enemy artillery, destroy buildings, and more!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HQ2fQBI0b_E"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933872-the-history-channel-civil-war-a-nation-divided/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/History-Channel-Civil-War/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/history-channel-civil-war/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-history-channel-civil-war---a-nation-divided"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":78,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Neversoft Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Tony rides again in a totally redesigned next-gen Tony Hawk's Pro Skater game from Activision. The game challenges players to experience the intensity and pressure of skating against some of the world's top pros in true to life competitions as they aim to become the #1 skater. With an entirely new gameplay engine, the trick-based gameplay features amazing, detailed character animations that react realistically on and off their boards, a new physics system, an innovative bail mode and the ability to move ramps and rails throughout the city.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L_0Wt1ytUoQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w3XvoE1UlGQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932714-tony-hawks-project-8/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tony-Hawks-Project-8/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tony-hawks-project-8/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tony-hawks-project-8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tony Hawks Games Wiki",
				"url":"http://tonyhawkgames.wikia.com/wiki/Tony_Hawk's_Project_8"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":79,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rare"],
			"synopsis":"A wild and easy-to-control kids' game by famed developer Rare. Designed together with the \"Viva Pinata\" Saturday morning 3-D animated TV series, this Xbox 360 game is a customizable, social and spontaneous game that invites players of all ages and skills to explore an immersive world where they are challenged to create and maintain a living garden ecosystem that grows in realtime.<br><br>Beginning with a few basic tools, players build and take control of their environment to attract and host more than 60 species of wild pi&ntildeata, utilizing hundreds of customizable elements to create their very own, distinctively unique, thriving paradise.<br><br>Viva Pinata gameplay continues to evolve with new content available via the Xbox Live service and the ability to play, trade and interact with Viva Pinata players everywhere.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=loPW6MXexPA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5L_v0BUuIgA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932328-viva-pinata/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Viva-Pinata/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/viva-pinata/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/viva-pinata"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Viva Pinata Wiki",
				"url":"http://vivapinata.wikia.com/wiki/Viva_Pinata_Wiki"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Pinata Island",
				"url":"http://pinataisland.info/viva/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":80,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Yuke's Media Creations"],
			"synopsis":"The WWE knocks the snot out of the world with the 2007 edition of this multi-platform wrestling smackfest. Added features this year include a brand new analog control grappling system, new high-impact move-sets, user-controlled environmental hotspots and an interactive fighting area within the crowd. In addition, the game includes updated rosters for Raw and SmackDown, an expanded General Manager Mode and online multiplayer game play with voice chat support.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KnRr3a3xv-Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H2-z32qxk-M"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932465-wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-2007/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/WWE-Smackdown-vs-RAW-2007/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-2007/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-2007"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Smackdown vs Raw Wiki",
				"url":"http://smackdown.wikia.com/wiki/WWE_SmackDown_vs._Raw_2007"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":81,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Team Ninja"],
			"synopsis":"Another round of sun and fun on the beach awaits in this volleyball side-project sequel from Tecmo. The girls of DOA take a break from snapping necks and kicking in skulls to bounce around in beach volleyball challenges and minigames.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Crystal Boutique",
				"releaseDate":"2006/12/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"At the Crystal Boutique you can buy swimsuits with Microsoft Points for the DOA girls."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oHbTD-1dRNY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jvkjLIgl1a0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928676-dead-or-alive-xtreme-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dead-or-Alive-Xtreme-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dead-or-alive-xtreme-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dead-or-alive-xtreme-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dead or Alive Wiki",
				"url":"http://deadoralive.wikia.com/wiki/Dead_or_Alive_Xtreme_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":82,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["TT Games"],
			"synopsis":"Bionicle Heroes takes you to the amazing island of Voya Nui, a world filled with heroes and villains, past and present. Take control of the heroic Toa Inika and battle the villainous Piraka in a fight for the future. Explore jungles, volcanoes and mountains on the mysterious island and master the unique weapons and abilities of the Toa Inika in this epic quest.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mwlKbMQ70I8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935869-bionicle-heroes/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bionicle-Heroes/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bionicle-heroes/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bionicle-heroes"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":83,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Stormfront Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the best-selling novel and feature film, this epic fantasy-adventure centers on a young farm boy named Eragon whose destiny is revealed with the help of a dragon. Eragon, now a Dragon Rider, is swept into a world of magic and power, discovering that he alone has the power to save - or destroy - an Empire. Gamers will engage in intense battles with an unparalleled combo and magic-based combat system, including stunning finishing moves, multiple grapples and degradable blocks with unique counter attacks. The adventure is heightened with breathless dragon flight-based combat and devastating dragon summon attacks. Fantasy fans can also share the adventure with 2 player co-op featuring team attack bonuses and dragon fight/flight combo gameplay.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=99KlnHNBSuk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d3bjY43Z-Ao"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932594-eragon/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Eragon/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/eragon/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/eragon"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":84,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sonic Team"],
			"synopsis":"Sonic celebrates his 15th anniversary by blazing his way onto the next-generation consoles, with his first adventure set in the human world! Featuring interactive 3D environments and a large cast of returning and new characters, get ready for the reinvention of Sonic The Hedgehog, in his most intense, high velocity escapade to date!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Additional Mission Pack \"Sonic/Very Hard\"",
				"releaseDate":"2007/02/08",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Play a new set of Very Hard missions for Sonic. You need to complete Sonic Episode to play Very Hard missions in some stages."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Additional Mission Pack \"Shadow/Very Hard\"",
				"releaseDate":"2007/02/08",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Play a new set of Very Hard missions for Shadow. You need to complete Shadow Episode to play Very Hard missions in some stages."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Additional Mission Pack \"Silver/Very Hard\"",
				"releaseDate":"2007/02/08",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Play a new set of Very Hard missions for Silver. You need to complete Silver Episode to play Very Hard missions in some stages."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Additional Mission Pack \"Team Attack Amigo\"",
				"releaseDate":"2007/02/20",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"You can play additional missions for Team Attack Amigo. Team Attack Amigo will be added to ACT TRIAL."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Additional Mission Pack \"Sonic Boss Attack\"",
				"releaseDate":"2007/03/20",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Play Consecutive Boss Battle Mode for Sonic. You need to complete Sonic Episode to play all the stages in this mode."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Additional Mission Pack \"Shadow Boss Attack\"",
				"releaseDate":"2007/03/20",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"You can play Consecutive Boss Battle Mode for Shadow. You need to complete Shadow Episode to play all the stages in this mode."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Additional Mission Pack \"Silver Boss Attack\"",
				"releaseDate":"2007/03/20",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"You can play Consecutive Boss Battle Mode for Silver. You need to complete Silver Episode to play all the stages in this mode. "
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e7zCCU1RtDM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eAsHOa8hidg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/929717-sonic-the-hedgehog/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sonic-The-Hedgehog/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sonic-the-hedgehog/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sonic-the-hedgehog"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sonic News Network",
				"url":"http://sonic.wikia.com/wiki/Sonic_the_Hedgehog_(2006)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":85,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Arcade"],
			"synopsis":"Big Bumpin' looks like a traditional carnival bumper car ride and features familiar Burger King icons, including the Subservient Chicken and Brooke Burke. But, there's a catch - Big Bumpin' arenas come with some big hazards, like surprise saws, bottomless pits and power up items that let gamers dole out thundering bumps. With several different types of game play, gamers have a chance to hone their bumper car skills in a variety of challenging scenarios. The game features theme parks, including the Ice Box, Broiler, King's Court, The Deep and Monsoon of Doom, and three modes of play for each - intense four-player and Xbox Live-supported.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lz9PixCX0K4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ObFSyg1EGnI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935894-big-bumpin/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Big-Bumpin/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/big-bumpin/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/big-bumpin"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":86,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Arcade"],
			"synopsis":"Welcome to the wild world of Pocketbike racing where players race the King and his miniature motorbike crew through five fun, yet challenging speedways. Each track varies in level of difficulty and players navigate long straights, tight bends and sharp turns at high speeds while attempting to earn enhancements and tools that they can use to gain an advantage over opponents. Featuring Have It Your Way customization options, players select a bike and a driver and then hit the track of their choice: a Burger King restaurant parking lot, a construction site, a backyard, the King's garden or the fabled Fantasy Ranch set. In addition to individual play, four players can race against each other in classic split-screen set-up or eight players can battle it out online using Xbox Live.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DZaA9hdKFJQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pocketbike-Racer/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pocketbike-racer/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pocketbike-racer"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":87,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Arcade"],
			"synopsis":"Only the King can turn an everyday act into an art form and now players can step into the King's royal shoes and use cunning stealth to sneak up behind unsuspecting people and bestow them with a delicious meal. The goal of Sneak King is to surprise hungry citizens with Burger King sandwiches and other menu items throughout the day before they pass out from hunger. Whether in a logging yard, construction site, suburban neighborhood or downtown urban scene - each rich with detail and hidden pathways - players can hide out and earn points based on how elaborate the delivery is executed.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8er--tp08Mg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5z2QMl5b5xU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935895-sneak-king/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sneak-King/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sneak-king/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sneak-king"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":88,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"Shoot for the Final Four with the 2007 entry in Visual Concepts' and 2K Sports' college b-ball game. Leadership makes a difference this year, as team chemistry plays a vital role in a team's performance-especially come tournament time. The college atmosphere is fully realized with updated mascots, improved crowd interaction and more fight songs. Also featured are over 325 NCAA Division 1 schools and a deep legacy mode.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"2K ReelMaker",
				"releaseDate":"2006/11/08",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Download this powerful replay editor and construct your own highlight reels!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HEyUzo0cOSg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/College-Hoops-2K7/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/college-hoops-2k7/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/college-hoops-2k7"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":89,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"In Superman Returns: The Videogame, you explore and protect the truly living city of Metropolis - one that is not only expansive (with 80 sq miles and over 9,000 buildings), but also changes dynamically with you as you affect gameplay. Citizens will run away in terror from newly-erupting danger and also exit their cars to cheer and snap photos as you fly overhead to save them. Superman may be invincible, but Metropolis is not. Player choice matters, as Metropolis' destruction will affect your ability to progress. You must face the internal conflict facing Superman at every turn: will you pause your pursuit of super villains to stop a massive tornado sweeping through the city and save its civilians? Every decision made is critical to Metropolis' existence and can affect the collateral damage meter, which ultimately keeps the player in the game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v10rhHcyzY0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q5fuYe91Wwo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930272-superman-returns/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Superman-Returns/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/superman-returns/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/superman-returns"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":90,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"The stakes are high when the world's most elite counter-terrorism unit enters Las Vegas, where over 36.7 million men, women and children visit each year. \"Sin City,\" the home of the famous Las Vegas Strip, flashy hotels, high-rolling casinos and world-famous celebrities, becomes the setting for a terrorist threat of global proportions. What happens when one of the world's most famous cities is held hostage by terrorists?",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Player's Pack: Red Edition",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/18",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Pack includes two new game modes, Assassination and Total Conquest, and five multiplayer maps which support all Rainbow Six Vegas multiplayer game modes. New Maps included: Doscala Restaurant, Marshalling Yard, Roof, Killhouse Redux, and Border Town Redux. * Price changed to FREE on 07/06/07"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Player's Pack: Black Edition",
				"releaseDate":"2007/06/26",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Pack include 5 new multiplayer maps which support all Rainbow Six Vegas multiplayer modes. New maps include: Neon Graveyard, Red Lotus, War Town, Presidio (Raven Shield), and Streets Redux. * Price changed to FREE on 06/30/07 due to a pricing error. 800 Points were reimbursed to erroneous purchasers."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hDm-FeZTLZU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K1vPo92pa6o"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932240-tom-clancys-rainbow-six-vegas/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tom-Clancys-Rainbow-Six-Vegas/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rainbow-six-vegas/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tom-clancys-rainbow-six-vegas"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Rainbow 6 Wiki",
				"url":"http://rainbowsix.wikia.com/wiki/Tom_Clancy's_Rainbow_Six:_Vegas"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":91,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FUN Labs"],
			"synopsis":"Players discover Africa's untamed wild as they hunt a variety of African big game in pursuit of the ultimate hunting challenge - the feared Big Five - leopards, lions, elephants, rhinos and Cape buffalo. In Cabela's African Safari, players choose from seven, 10 or 14 day safaris including open safari, game tracking, baiting and herd hunting missions. The game features over 30 exotic species of animals including sable, kudu, gemsbok, eland, waterbuck, impala and much more, as well as all new African waterfowl and upland bird hunting. Cabela's African Safari also features an unlockable Big Five Trophy level where gamers can experience the world's most dangerous animals at their fiercest. Hunters also have access to an arsenal of authentic firearms including big caliber weapons they will need to bring down charging rhinos and thundering elephants. In addition, all-new shooting controls and features including Adrenaline Mode, Hunter Sense and Shot Cam, allow gamers to hone in on their prey with more accuracy and ease.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Safari Bonus Animal",
				"releaseDate":"2006/12/08",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"This bonus pack will give you a new animal (Caracal) to be hunted in the Safari Hunt mode."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y_AunJidlUQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933868-cabelas-african-safari/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cabelas-African-Safari/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cabelas-african-safari/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cabelas-african-safari"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":92,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FUN Labs"],
			"synopsis":"Rapala Tournament Fishing lets players embark on all new angling adventures to the world's most desirable fishing locations and features authentic gear from Rapala, the world's largest manufacturer of fishing lures and the most widely recognized fishing brand in the world. Players can also compete in 20 tournaments on some of the world's most prestigious angling waters. Fill your live well with bass, pike, trout, walleye, catfish, salmon and more.<br><br>Xbox 360's analog controller enhances the game's realism by giving the user total control. Use your controller to cast and reel, jig your bait, set the hook, drive the boat and more.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"California Delta Bonus Level",
				"releaseDate":"2006/12/19",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"This is a bonus fishing level - California Delta. It will be available for you in the Free Fishing mode."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DFfurMYHJk0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/936838-rapala-tournament-fishing/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rapala-Tournament/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rapala-tournament-fishing/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rapala-tournament-fishing"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":93,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eutechnyx"],
			"synopsis":"Enter Pimp City, where bling is king, and style is everything. On these streets, if your car isn't fully pimped out, you'd be better off walking. You and Xzibit will take on the challenge of hooking up your homies, and transforming their hoopties, buckets and beaters into the hottest whips on the street, while redlining through the highways and alleyways of Pimp City. You choose the mods, you choose the route, but pimpin' ain't easy. It will take speed and style to hook them up. Do you have what it takes to Pimp Their Ride?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tQAshBCbung"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dVCuejhJj5A"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933864-pimp-my-ride/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pimp-My-Ride/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pimp-my-ride/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pimp-my-ride"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":94,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Mad Doc Software"],
			"synopsis":"This game spans the history of Star Trek, following the challenges facing the Starfleet as an Admiral of a task force of warships. Gameplay campaigns play out in all of the Star Trek eras (from the founding days of Enterprise to the adventures of classic Star Trek to the bold unknown of The Next Generation, as well as the trials and tribulations facing Deep Space Nine and Voyager), as the Federation faces an entirely new enemy that has the power to travel through time. With full multiplayer support, players can choose from small-scale engagements to all-out war involving multiple star systems in addition to tracking stats and player rankings.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aRRpDG0xzKY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xwrzILYWQhg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/931493-star-trek-legacy/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Star-Trek-Legacy/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/star-trek-legacy/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/star-trek-legacy"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":95,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Capcom"],
			"synopsis":"A riveting sci-fi action shooter for the Xbox 360. Set within the merciless frozen tundra of a hostile planet, humans struggle for survival as conflicts arise between man, the surrounding indigenous creatures and the monstrous beings that have invaded. Enormous world maps unfold as players battle the menacing invaders during blistering weather conditions throughout vast snow fields and deserted cities. Fostering a real-time loading system, players can expect a seamless experience that leaves them completely immersed. Multiplayer modes add to the value of Lost Planet by allowing players to partake in intense team battles via the Xbox Live online game service.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Multiplayer Maps #1",
				"releaseDate":"2007/03/09",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Two new maps for LOST PLANET online multiplayer have arrived! This first batch includes \"Radar Field\" and \"Island 902\"."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Multiplayer Maps #2",
				"releaseDate":"2007/04/06",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Two additional multiplayer maps are now available for LOST PLANET! The second batch includes \"Hive Complex\" and \"Trial Point\"."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Battleground Map",
				"releaseDate":"2007/06/07",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The online multiplayer map Battleground. This abandoned city has been ravaged by relentless fighting."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Multiplayer Maps #3",
				"releaseDate":"2007/08/16",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Three unique maps, Lost Technology, Ruins and Ice Drop are now available as battlefields for LOST PLANET online!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tfjXpTr5dos"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BdLhKl9awwo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/931114-lost-planet-extreme-condition/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lost-Planet/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lost-planet/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lost-planet-extreme-condition"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Lost Planet Wiki",
				"url":"http://lostplanet.wikia.com/wiki/Lost_Planet:_Extreme_Condition"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":96,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"In the 2007 edition of EA's college b-ball game, watch the intensity rise on the college court, then watch as each player responds differently, trying to maintain composure. Your player composure ratings affect the all-new Intensity Control that changes momentum by allowing you to pump up the crowd, motivate your teammates, raise your own composure or even intimidate your opponent. Plus, become immersed like never before by interacting with student sections, school mascots, cheerleaders, and even the band.<br><br>Beyond the atmosphere, NCAA March Madness 07 delivers an authentic college basketball gameplay experience by offering custom playbooks for each team through the Floor General Playcalling system, the EA Sports Lockdown Stick that allows your players to pressure the ball, force turnovers and harass opponents on the court, and an enhanced Dynasty Modewith new School Pride and Recruiting features that let you build your school into a national powerhouse.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hFn3D42dcJg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KhsIuX6Zr0M"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/936427-ncaa-march-madness-07/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NCAA-March-Madness-07/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ncaa-march-madness-07/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ncaa-march-madness-07"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":97,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eidos Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Battlestations: Midway blends intense 3rd-person action with epic, large-scale naval combat and brings to life the great Pacific battles of World War II. From the chaos of Pearl Harbor, through the Philippines, Java and the Coral Sea all the way to the epic Battle of Midway. Players can relive classic battles with realistic locations and accurate historical detail and take part in huge multi-unit online battles with up to eight players controlling over 60 units. Players can take direct control of over 60 different warships, planes and submarines, many of which are based on actual historical vehicles, from a 3rd-person perspective. Single Player mode features 11 large-scale campaigns with 12 bonus challenge missions while the online multi-player combat offers an entirely new online battle experience and features head-to-head and co-operative battles featuring over 60 Allied and Japanese units.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Iowa Mission Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/03/28",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The Iowa Mission Pack includes a new multiplayer map, a new singleplayer mission, and five new units."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CZaF3qhN0f8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FRfVyW3mE48"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932655-battlestations-midway/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Battlestations-Midway/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/battlestations-midway/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/battlestations-midway"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":98,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Games"],
			"synopsis":"A downloadable version of the Xbox classic, provided on Xbox Live as an Xbox Originals release.<br><br>Fuzion Frenzy is a non-stop party game. which combines frenetic action of a futuristic street sport with the action-packed fun of mini-games set in a dynamic 3-D urban environment. The game includes six arenas and more than 45 mini-games.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KCpyckI_CPU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fuzion-Frenzy-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fuzion-frenzy-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fuzion-frenzy-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":99,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"DDR makes its next-generation debut on the Xbox 360, taking dancing to a whole new level with high definition graphics, a massive song list and all-new game modes. Players can dance with friends in the new relay mode and even download exclusive songs and dance steps to keep groovin' into the night.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Mega Pack",
				"type":9
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z9l37WY0x6I"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932935-dance-dance-revolution-universe/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dance-Dance-Revolution-Universe/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dance-dance-revolution-universe/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dance-dance-revolution-universe"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":100,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Realtime Worlds"],
			"synopsis":"Crackdown is a futuristic, online take on the wide-open Grand Theft Auto genre. You play as a super-human agent assigned to take out the filth that has starting filling up all corners of your city. The city's thousands of gangsters have grouped together into three criminal organizations: Cai-Shen Corp, an Asian gang that uses hitmen to extract revenge, The Volk, a Russian gang that specializes in guns, and La Muerta, a Spanish group that loves cars. Your overall goal as an agent is to defeat the bosses of these organizations, bringing peace to the city. You are a one-man super army, but if the going gets too tough, a friend can jump in and play along with you in co-op mode to bring an unstoppable crime fighting force to Pacific City.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Four-Play Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/02/27",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Before getting busy, download and get into the action with these four new Agents."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Getting' Busy Bonus Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/05/10",
				"achievements":210,
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"5 new weapons (the Lobber & friends), 3 new sets of wheels (armored car, anyone?), new mini-games, new Achievements, not to mention Street Racing. Kitchen sink not included."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Free-For-All Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2007/05/17",
				"achievements":140,
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Add potent new powers to your Agent repertoire - claim the \"Keys to the City\" (unlimited cheats), impound vehicles, and resurrect gang members."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fZ0ZHtLj0Zo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4vzPsR_FdPE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930144-crackdown/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Crackdown/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/crackdown/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/crackdown"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Crackdown Wiki",
				"url":"http://crackdown.wikia.com/wiki/Crackdown"
			}]
		}
	}]
}