{
	"catalog": [
	{
		"id":201,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cauldron"],
			"synopsis":"When a routine escort mission goes horribly wrong, freelance mercenary Thomas Mason finds himself battling an insidious enemy that knows no boundaries. Traditional armies can not handle these extremists - only underground guns for hire can fight a war this dirty and get results.<br><br>Soldier of Fortune Payback evolves the signature gameplay of its predecessors with refined controls, tension-packed warzones, and an enemy damage system that may be shocking to even experienced FPS players. Boasting more weapons options than any previous Soldier of Fortune installment, Soldier of Fortune Payback's impressive arsenal includes an array of more than 30 weapons including sub-machine guns, assault rifles, sniper rifles, projectile explosives, weapon attachments and cutting-edge tactical weapons.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N_FpgH8XjOU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ySG40tZn7yo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ktw7m_X8LU8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Soldier-Of-Fortune/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/soldier-of-fortune-payback/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/soldier-of-fortune-payback"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":202,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Yuke's Media Creations"],
			"synopsis":"WWE SmackDown vs. Raw 2008 lets players develop the WWE Superstars of today into the Legends of tomorrow. The #1 wrestling franchise in the world delivers more depth and strategy with prominent features, key annual enhancements and incredible graphics. It's time to live the life of a Superstar. How will you play?",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Roster Update 1",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"New characters include: Evan Bourne, Ted DiBiase, Super Crazy and Charlie Haas. The Roster update also includes alternate ring attire for Chris Jericho."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Roster Update 2",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"New characters include: Vader, Doink the Clown, Earthquake, and the Bushwhackers."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l644vWm73Sg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nkkMpr_z1yU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938801-wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-2008/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/WWE-SmackDown-vs-RAW-2008/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-2008/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-2008"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":203,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Io-Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Kane & Lynch: Dead Men is a violent and chaotic journey of two men - a flawed mercenary and a medicated psychopath - and their brutal attitude towards right and wrong. Now, they must partner up as a mess of cash makes for hell on Earth in this co-op action game.",				
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Dope Bag",
				"releaseDate":"2008/04/17",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Dope Bag contains 4 new scenarios for Fragile Alliance: Clean Cut, Hookers' Trail, Flying High and Hasta la Vista."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0J5GArmR1OM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nof7b5oA6_A"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/934403-kane-and-lynch-dead-men/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kane-And-Lynch-Dead-Men/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kane-and-lynch-dead-men/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kane-lynch-dead-men"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":204,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Black Box"],
			"synopsis":"A new spin on the Need for Speed franchise, ProStreet thrusts players into a head-to-head competition against the best street racers in a multitude of racing showdowns. The game is a true taste of raw adrenaline and racing with consequences. Every dent, every scratch and every crumpled body panel is a battle scar, proof of your commitment and competitive mettle. With an aggressive and skilled AI system, you become immersed in an unmatched believable race experience. Add in a revolutionary online mode that will redefine the meaning of competitive social play, and Need for Speed ProStreet is the ultimate formula for an emotionally charged street racing showdown. It also pushes the \"Autosculpt\" technology to a new level, allowing you to directly impact your car's performance for the first time as well as personalize its appearance.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Collector's Edition Upgrade",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/13",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"True automotive aficionados need look no further than this unparalleled package of dream cars and more. The Need for Speed ProStreet Collector's Edition features five exclusive cars: get the '01 Acura Integra LS, '05 Acura NSX, '06 Lexus IS350, '06 Audi RS4 and the '06 Pontiac Solstice GXP to complete your ultimate car collection. In addition, extend your racing experience with four additional career race days."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Stage 4 Performance Blueprint Bundle",
				"releaseDate":"2008/02/15",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Maximize your performance with four unique blueprints created by the editors of Super Street, Import Tuner, Sport Compact Car and Turbo magazine. Featuring the following cars - Nissan 240 SX, Nissan GT-R, Mazda RX-7 and the Mitsubishi EVO IX."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Extender Pack Premium Car Bundle #1",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/21",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"This premium car bundle - only available after downloading the Energizer Lithium Extender Pack - includes the following cars: Dodge Challenger Concept, Lancia Delta Integrale Evo, Porsche 911 GT3 RS, Lamborghini Gallardo Superleggera, Porsche Carrera GT, Aston Martin DBR9."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"xtender Pack Premium Car Bundle #2",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/21",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"This premium car bundle - only available after downloading the Energizer Lithium Extender Pack - includes the following cars: Honda S2000, Porsche 911 GT3, Audi R8, Aston Martin DB9, Mercedes-Benz SL65 AMG, Koeniggsigg CCX."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3YcFDXp4tD8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nIYAXCUDQkw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939664-need-for-speed-prostreet/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Need-for-Speed-ProStreet/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/need-for-speed-prostreet/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/need-for-speed-prostreet"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Need for Speed Wiki",
				"url":"http://nfs.wikia.com/wiki/Need_for_Speed:_ProStreet"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":205,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Red Storm Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"America's Army: True Soldiers allows players to immerse themselves within the infantry experience of a modern Soldier. Play in single players mode and take on roles such as Rifleman, Grenadier, Automatic Rifleman and Sniper. Or, play in multiplayer mode using the Xbox LIVE gaming service Clan support to compete online.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BxAHhXAw870"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q3O-0Pvd7-U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Americas-Army-True-Soldiers/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/americas-army-true-soldiers/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/americas-army-true-soldiers"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":206,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"College Hoops 2K8 continues the legacy of the NCAA franchise with all new features, including the 6th Man Advantage feature that lets the crowd atmosphere affect the game performance of teams, a training mode where players can improve their skills through practice, and more.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"2K ReelMaker",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/12",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"A replay editing feature allowing users to compile multiple replay clips and add special effects and audio to create a \"highlight reel\"."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YAgp6bfi_1U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=haxWHpHvjDw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/College-Hoops-2K8/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/college-hoops-2k8/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/college-hoops-2k8"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":207,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["BioWare"],
			"synopsis":"Set 200 years in the future in an epic universe, Mass Effect places gamers in a vast galactic community in danger of being conquered by a legendary agent gone rogue. A spectacular new vision from legendary developers BioWare, Mass Effect challenges players to lead a squad of freedom fighters as they struggle against threatening armies to restore peace in the land.<br><br>Mass Effect is the first in a trilogy of games with an overarching story. As the first human Specter - sworn defenders of galactic peace - your mission is to halt the advancing armies of a legendary agent gone rogue. But as you lead your elite team across hostile alien worlds, you will discover the true threat is far greater than anyone imagined.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Bring Down The Sky",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/05",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Batarian extremists have hijacked a mobile asteroid station in the Asgard system, setting it on a collision course with the nearby colony world of Terra Nova. Only you can save the human hostages on the asteroid and reroute it before it crashes into the world, killing millions of innocent civilians."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Pinnacle Station",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/25",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Test the limits of your combat prowess aboard a remote, top-secret Alliance space station. Do you have what it takes to hold the top spot amongst the best of the best? This module includes a new landable space station, 13 exciting combat scenarios, and approximately 2-3 hours of gameplay. Required: you must achieve Spectre status before embarking on this mission."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yqJuJTIus7U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M-ql42tj72A"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930279-mass-effect/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mass-Effect/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mass-effect/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mass-effect"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Mass Effect Wiki",
				"url":"http://masseffect.wikia.com/wiki/Mass_Effect"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":208,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"Rock Band allows gamers to perform music from the world's biggest rock artists with their friends as a virtual band using drum, bass/lead guitar and microphone peripherals, in addition to offering deep online connectivity. Built on deals with the world's biggest record labels and music publishers, the music featured in Rock Band spans all genres of rock and include many of the master recordings from the biggest songs and artists of all time.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable tracks",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/20",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"More than 1000 tracks available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IiXMHLTZxkY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Enter Sandman",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jOhDLj5hGH4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938870-rock-band/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rock-Band/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rock-band/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rock-band"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Rock Band Wiki",
				"url":"http://rockband.wikia.com/wiki/Rock_Band_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":209,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cauldron"],
			"synopsis":"The History Channel takes you to the Battle for the Pacific, where you can experience history brought to life in one of the defining campaigns of World War II. Relive epic land battles fought on some of the most brutal and unforgiving battlefields in recorded history. Play through the eyes of an American GI as you experience intense, no holds barred action against an opponent for which surrender isn't an option!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vZv86oFmSnY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f43XrmGW2xc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942745-the-history-channel-battle-for-the-pacific/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/History-Channel-Battle-for-the-Pacific/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/history-channel-battle-for-the-pacific/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-history-channel-battle-for-the-pacific"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":210,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"The series' encore performance on the next generation console delivers new gameplay options along with a sundry mix of songs from the 70s to today, online play and downloadable music, enhanced graphics as well as accessibility for players of all ages.<br><br>DDR Universe 2 brings back familiar modes from previous games and expands on them with the debut of Freestyle Mode on the Xbox 360 and the introduction of the enhanced Quest mode. Delivering added proof of the game's \"universal\" appeal is the soundtrack, which draws inspiration from four decades of both classic and current smash-hits to deliver the most complete music library of any DDR game to date. From the 70s, 80s, 90s and today, DDR Universe 2 has songs that fit everyone's tastes. For those who want an even wider array of music, they can take their game to the online \"universe\" via Xbox Live, where they can download new songs as well as compete head-to-head, and even have access to exclusive DDR-related items.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K3_9NWMIwOU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942056-dance-dance-revolution-universe-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dance-Dance-Revolution-Universe-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dance-dance-revolution-universe-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dance-dance-revolution-universe-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dance Dance Revolution Wiki",
				"url":"http://dancedancerevolutionddr.wikia.com/wiki/DanceDanceRevolution_II"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":211,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Shiny Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Players assume the role of a young girl named Lyra as she travels through the frozen wastes of the North in an attempt to rescue a friend kidnapped by a mysterious organization known as The Gobblers. Travelling with her are an armored polar bear and her pet demon Pantalaimon (Pan). Together, they must use a magical golden compass and other items to explore the land and fight their way through confrontations in order to help Lyra's friend.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NVFDtTv0KNM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5psA9RzAeRM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Golden-Compass/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/golden-compass/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-golden-compass"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":212,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"NCAA March Madness 08 has a plethora of rich details that brings the college game to life, including new authentic arenas, new player models with form-fitting uniforms, breakaway basketball hoop rims, and the ability of players to slap the backboard on layups. The game also features custom playbooks for each team through the Floor General Playcalling system, the EA SPORTS Lockdown Stick that enables your players to pressure the ball, force turnovers and harass opponents on the court, a deeper Dynasty Mode that lets you build your school into a national powerhouse, the Pre and Post season NIT and the McDonald's High School All American game and an online feature set that includes customized leagues and ESPN on Demand.<br><br>Also included in NCAA March Madness 08 has created a strategic new gameplay experience called Dynamic Post Play that enables you to take complete control over running your offense through the post, and defending your opponent in the paint.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=REFBxy9qOlk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wMTTui6HFVk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NCAA-March-Madness-08/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ncaa-march-madness-08/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ncaa-march-madness-08"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":213,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rainbow Studios"],
			"synopsis":"MX vs. ATV Untamed kicks it up a notch and shifts into high gear as the best selling offroad franchise returns. Rainbow Studios has evolved their legendary Rhythm Racing engine to include throttle based power slides, near upside down whips and new scrubs at full speed all while retaining the smooth and authentic feel not found in any other game.<br><br>Attempt to own the offroad by dominating the innovative new \"X-Cross Tournament\". X-Cross brings together 8 unique racing series like Endurocross, Opencross, Supercross, Waypoint and SuperMoto and then crosses them into one ultimate offroad championship. Brand new styles of racing are born as powerful vehicles tear through treacherous trails in the new Opencross mode, while then shifting gears to navigate boulders, logs, and water pits in Endurocross. Players can take control of the new ORV Sport and multiple other vehicles, including Monster and Trophy Trucks, as they blitz through rough rivers, rip though swampy everglades, and blaze through the desert dunes. Amp up your favorite vehicles' power, handling, and acceleration with more than 100 sponsor parts and accessories.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qvq_OLbVBYk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jqu6Vt7AJG0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/941952-mx-vs-atv-untamed/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MX-vs-ATV-Untamed/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mx-vs-atv-untamed/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mx-vs-atv-untamed"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":214,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blueside", "Phantagram"],
			"synopsis":"The fourth installment in the Kingdom Under Fire series. Unlike its RTS-style predecessors, Circle of Doom is an action RPG. Instead of controlling armies on large battlefields, you now play as an individual hero who grinds for experience, gold, and other useful items. Up to 4 players can team up for cooperative dungeon-crawling action via Xbox Live.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=srcoLJi8noI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UXBCPLDVWLs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932035-kingdom-under-fire-circle-of-doom/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kingdom-Under-Fire-Circle-of-Doom/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kingdom-under-fire-circle-of-doom/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kingdom-under-fire-circle-of-doom"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Kingdom Under Fire Wiki",
				"url":"http://kingdomunderfire.wikia.com/wiki/Kingdom_Under_Fire:_Circle_of_Doom"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":215,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"A superstar replacement for EA's NFL Street series, NFL Tour brings the spectacle of a traveling NFL road show alive, with intuitive controls, fast-paced gameplay, and visually stunning graphics. Gamers will be able to embark on a fictional NFL road show. With real NFL players as teammates, players will travel across the country to play against each of the NFL teams in newly designed stadiums. As players defeat each of the NFL squads, they come one step closer to winning a NFL contract.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gtBskrOqXUM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aK_9BX2SVmA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NFL-Tour/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nfl-tour/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nfl-tour"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":216,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Criterion Games"],
			"synopsis":"The fifth entry in the gonzo racing series, Burnout Paradise gives players license to wreak havoc in Paradise City, the ultimate racing battleground, with a massive infrastructure of traffic-heavy roads to abuse. Gone is the need to jump in and out of menus and aimlessly search for fun like many open world games; in Burnout Paradise, every inch of the world is built to deliver heart-stopping Burnout-style gameplay. Every intersection is a potential crash junction and every alleyway is an opportunity to rack up moving violations. Feel the adrenaline course through your veins as you take to the road for the first time in Paradise City, where the action is all around you. Explore the city, discover events, and look for the best opportunities to crash, jump and pull signature takedowns. In Burnout Paradise you are given the keys to the city, but it's up to you to earn the keys to the meanest and most dangerous cars on the street, and earn your Burnout license.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Burnout Paradise Party",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/05",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Share your Burnout experiences with your friends as you gather around the TV for this new multi-player game mode. Compete against up to 7 friends as you try to showcase your skills across multiple challenges featuring all of your favourite Burnout cars and locations."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Hunter Cavalry Bootlegger",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/19",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"This custom Cavalry is made especially for those who live on the wrong side of the law. Hit the special button to sound the distinctive horns and go off something big. Looks great in orange!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Hunter Manhattan Spirit",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/19",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"This converted Manhattan station wagon might not be the fastest or fleetest car in Paradise City, but one thing's for sure - people will definately know what's hit them. Hit the special button to fire off the lights and sirens. All together now - \"Boosting makes me feel good!\""
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Jansen 88 Special",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/19",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"This classic 1980's styled silver sports car is based on the fan-favourite Jansen P12, but we've made a few very interesting modifications. Fill the gauge and hit boost to trigger burning flame trails from your back wheels. The 88 Special's fast, maneuverable and great in the air. In fact, if you want to take off, this is just the car for you. Hit the special button and switch to hover mode - the wheels retract and the car takes off and hovers through Paradise City at head height."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Carson GT Nighthawk",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/19",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Developed in secret, the GT Nighthawk shouldn't exist. Denied by the Government, disowned by Carson, the GT Nighthawk is the ultimate super pursuit vehicle. Featuring a fully digital interior and state of the art aerodynamics. Firing the boost on this car pops the rear spoiler and lets everyone know you're coming. Jump in for a glimpse of the future."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Toy Hunter Citizen",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/05",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"This collection gets you all of the fantastic Burnout Paradise Toys in one pack. Hunter bring you the Cavalry, Manhattan, Citizen and Takedown 4x4. Carson wade in with the GT Concept and Inferno van, Jansen offer up the wonderful P12 and the Krieger WTR rounds off the cars. Last but not least, Nakamura have created a Toy version of the fantastic Firehawk bike. All of the fan favourites in Toy form at incredible value."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Carson Extreme Hot Rod",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/12",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Carson's Extreme Hot Rod - With a one shot Boost system that will have you firing and never-forgetting! Fill the Boost then fire it off and hang on for the ride of your life because once it's on, it's on for good."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Hawker Mech",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/12",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"The team at Hawker have come up with something very special here. The wonderful Solo has had its Boost system specially modified with a unique ability. Now, at will, the driver can switch between Stunt, Speed and Aggression Boost systems. This car could truly be the ultimate all-rounder."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Cops & Robbers",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/30",
				"achievements":90,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Fans of the game will be familiar with the PCPD Special and the Hunter Citizen - our two cop cars. We've added Police liveries to another 33 cars and built a brand new team game for up to 8-players online. Your goal is to find and retrieve Gold located throughout Paradise City. Cops must recover the Gold before the Robbers get it back to their base. Simple Online Fun!"
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Big Surf Island",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/11",
				"achievements":110,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Get this pack and head over the suspension bridge at the end of 4th Street to reach Big Surf Island! A whole new location packed with gameplay:<br>- The Dust Storm Buggy available to drive straight away<br>- 8 New Cars to Win<br>- 15 Events (Including all New Island Tours)<br>- 10 Freeburn Challenges<br>- 12 New Roads to Rule<br>- 75 Island Smashes<br>- 45 Island Billboards<br>- 15 Island Mega Jumps.<br><br>Explore every part of Big Surf Island from the roads to the roof-tops and when you feel like a change of scenery head off-road to Perren's Point."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I053bNHvGc4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8dikcXs0NCo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933706-burnout-paradise/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Burnout-Paradise/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/burnout-paradise/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/burnout-paradise"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Burnopedia",
				"url":"http://burnout.wikia.com/wiki/Burnout_Paradise"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":217,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Omiya Soft", "Rocket Studio, Inc."],
			"synopsis":"In Culdcept Saga, individuals known as Cepters move around a game board by the roll of the dice, using magical cards to call upon creatures and cast spells to occupy each area they encounter. Using cards, players can customize different decks to assist in their struggle for territorial dominance. As they maneuver their way around the board and land on occupied properties, opponents can opt to pay a fee for their brief stay or attack the guarding creature to inhabit the zone. Players can fortify their decks and develop strategies in single player mode, then apply those tactics against up to 3 friends on Xbox Live or on a single console. Gamers can further modify the game with their own style when they alter their characters' appearances using parts won during matches.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=txkTPcCrTaw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=elqbCNrHq4Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932515-culdcept-saga/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Culdcept-SAGA/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/culdcept-saga-ntscj/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/culdcept-saga"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Culcept Central",
				"url":"http://www.culdceptcentral.com/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":218,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Capcom Production Studio 1"],
			"synopsis":"Long ago the Dark Knight Sparda rebelled against the dark emperor and waged a one-man war to save humanity. Thousands of years later, a religious organization worships this renowned savior and has taken it upon themselves to rid the world of all evil. Residing in Fortuna, this organization is known as the \"Order of the Sword\", and is made up of an elite group of \"Holy Knights\". One day a young knight named Nero witnesses Sparda's legendary son Dante slaughter his fellow warriors. Has the renowned devil hunter turned his back on mankind? What does this encounter mean for these two individuals?<br><br>In Devil May Cry 4, players control the formidable Nero who comes to grips with his newly found power as his beliefs and allegiance are tested. Continuing the legacy of fast paced action synonymous with the series, Devil May Cry 4 pushes the envelope of excellence even further with the inclusion of a new combat system that incorporates Nero's \"Devil Bringer\". This new feature has players delivering overwhelming damage to enemies with non-stop combos, while gaining new power for Nero's right arm.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5wC_DtzO8Jw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C2ZOFCwhSMk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938686-devil-may-cry-4/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Devil-May-Cry-4/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/devil-may-cry-4/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/devil-may-cry-4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Devil May Cry Wiki",
				"url":"http://devilmaycry.wikia.com/wiki/Devil_May_Cry_4"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":219,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Games"],
			"synopsis":"Karaoke Revolution Presents: American Idol Encore allows players to play the part of an \"American Idol\" contestant as they audition, earn an invitation to Hollywood, perform on center stage and receive verbal feedback on their performance from the judges. Just like the TV show, the evaluation by the game's judges - Randy Jackson, Paula Abdul and the always entertaining Simon Cowell - will affect whether or not they move on to the next round of competition.<br><br>Players can personalize their own contestant with clothing, hair styles and accessories in the Character Customization mode, creating a specialized look that is sure to catch the attention of the judges and the crowd. Players can also create a 3D model of their own heads with the Xbox LIVE Vision to bring them directly into the actual competition. Xbox 360 gamers can also select and download from a catalog of over 140 songs via Xbox LIVE.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SIHaqAUX4oQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NVjnmkxwYkM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Karaoke-Revolution-American-Idol-Encore/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/karaoke-revolution-american-idol-encore/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/karaoke-revolution-presents-american-idol-encore"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":220,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Stormfront Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Plunge deep into a fantasy world full of mystical creatures when you join the Grace children on their quest to discover the secrets of The Spiderwick Chronicles. Based on Paramount Pictures and Nickelodeon Films' movie adaptation of the best-selling book series, the video game lets players take on the roles of Jared, Simon and Mallory Grace as they enter the hidden world of the unseen. Play as all three Grace siblings, each with unique abilities, along with Thimbletack the Brownie, whose small size allows players to discover the inner passages of the enchanted Spiderwick home.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=igy55l6F4zA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942723-the-spiderwick-chronicles/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Spiderwick-Chronicles/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-spiderwick-chronicles/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-spiderwick-chronicles"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The SpiderWick Chronicles Wiki",
				"url":"http://spiderwick.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":221,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Propaganda Games"],
			"synopsis":"Turok is an epic, story-driven FPS game set on a dark, mysterious planet in the near future. Players take on the role of Joseph Turok, a former Black Ops commando, now part of an elite Special Forces squad on a mission to take down a war criminal on a genetically-altered planet. After the ship is shot down while approaching the planet, Joseph Turok must use his instincts and elite military training to elude an army of well-trained soldiers, and the ravenous, unpredictable creatures that populate the dangerous environment. Joseph Turok's mission? Survive at all costs.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Multiplayer Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/27",
				"type":1
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=97KJybQEHbQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fEfCJIU5zUU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930158-turok/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Turok/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/turok/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/turok"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Turok Wiki",
				"url":"http://turok.wikia.com/wiki/Turok_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":222,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Crystal Dynamics"],
			"synopsis":"The first Tomb Raider title to be designed by Crystal Dynamics (after years under original creator Core), Tomb Raider: Legends is an all-new start for Lara Croft. New character animations and control schemes compliment the more natural character design and level details for the most immersive chapter in the series. Lara comes packing modern devices such as a magnetic grappling device, binoculars, frag grenades, personal lighting device and communications equipment for her all-new adventure.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Tomb Raider: Anniversary - Episodes 1 & 2",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/22",
				"achievements":110,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Episodes 1 & 2 of Lara's next adventure. Also includes the Croft Manor bonus level. Tomb Raider: Anniversary was also released as a full retail package.<br><br>Explore remote regions of Peru and ancient Greece as Lara begins her quest to obtain a mythical artifact known as the Scion."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Tomb Raider: Anniversary - Episodes 3 & 4",
				"releaseDate":"2007/11/22",
				"achievements":140,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Episodes 3 & 4 of Lara's next adventure. Also includes the Croft Manor bonus level. Tomb Raider: Anniversary was also released as a full retail package.<br><br>Lara's search for the Scion takes her to the lost tombs of ancient Egypt and an undiscovered remote island to confront her arch enemy."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DcWrQyVOSS8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NggxeGqDnk8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/926821-tomb-raider-legend/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tomb-Raider-Legend/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tomb-raider-legend/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tomb-raider-legend"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tomb Raider Wiki",
				"url":"http://www.tomb-raider.wikia.com/wiki/Tomb_Raider:_Legend"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":223,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Pivotal Games"],
			"synopsis":"When the US government needs intelligence but wants no association with an operation, deniable operatives are dispatched. Responsible for covert paramilitary actions, the Special Activities Division is a division of the Central Intelligence Agency's former Directorate of Operations, now the National Clandestine Service. Members of the unit must bear no identity; no objects, papers or clothing that could associate them in any way with their employees...<br><br>Conflict: Denied Ops draws its inspiration from this group of highly skilled individuals. An innovative new two player co-op FPS, Conflict: Denied Ops is set in today's delicately balanced political climate, focusing on two covert field operatives, experts in weapons and military tactics. Conflict: Denied Ops allows players the freedom to switch seamlessly, at any point, between these two operatives to lay down cover fire, explore different paths through levels, create a distraction or pin down the enemy under crossfire.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Eagle Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/05/01",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Take your multiplayer experience to a new level. Download five all-new multiplayer maps for unrivalled Deathmatch, Team Deathmatch and Conquest action. Fight your way up through the catacombs of the Lost City; take cover amongst the burnt-out wrecks in Tank Yard; administer 'last rites' to your opponents in Sanctuary; battle for control of the wooden walkways in the Killing Zone; and clear the decks from the crow's nest with your sniper rifle in Adrift. All maps are compatible with both online multiplayer and offline splitscreen multiplayer modes."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mpCdEXP_Z64"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vj1tsKHJS-Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B29GCsZsz9I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Conflict-Denied-Ops/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/conflict-denied-ops/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/conflict-denied-ops"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":224,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Annecy"],
			"synopsis":"Dark Messiah brings the legendary RPG to life in new ways, providing a wholly immersive first-person RPG experience. Explore the most remote recesses of Ashan, populated with fearless orcs, dreadful undead, elusive cyclops and many other creatures that defy nature's creation. This is the darkest side of the legendary Might and Magic universe, where the forces of evil are stronger and more cunning than ever. Challenge the forces of evil in intense melee combat with swords, bows, staffs and daggers. Alternately, kill your enemy by summoning your magic powers or by skulking in the shadows.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Exclusive Maps, Classes and Weapons",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/11",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Extend your quest on Dark Messiah of Might and Magic: Elements with new maps, classes and weapons from Xbox Live Marketplace. Use these new weapons to crush your opponents. According to your character's type, either Undead or Human, you can use exclusive powerful weapons such as bows, swords, or staffs. Also included, two new classes for the single player mode:<br>- Paladin, will subsequently use his powerful Charm and Shrinking spells to gain the upper hand.<br>- Warlock, will seek to weaken his enemies from a distance with his spells before moving in for the kill using his sword."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CXzBwMW5pzw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Elements Edition Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AyU6dz8aNtY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IVDqBG-HgiQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats (PC)",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/pc/929360-dark-messiah-of-might-and-magic/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dark-Messiah-Might-and-Magic-Elements/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dark-messiah-of-might-and-magic-elements/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dark-messiah-of-might-and-magic-elements"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Might & Magic Wiki",
				"url":"http://mightandmagic.wikia.com/wiki/Dark_Messiah_of_Might_and_Magic"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":225,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Red Tribe", "Collision Studios"],
			"synopsis":"A videogame based on the science fiction-action-thriller directed by Doug Liman.<br><br>Jumpers, people with a genetic anomaly that enables them to teleport themselves instantaneously to anywhere on the globe, have existed for centuries. An age-old battle rages between the Jumpers and the Paladins, a clandestine organization set on eliminating them from the planet. The Jumper game extends the film's storyline, following Griffin, a battle-hardened Jumper determined to avenge the death of his parents at the hands of the Paladins. Griffin's quest to find the killer spans exotic locales around the world.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rQNbHvrYYJo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LE2H6FXuPoM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943992-jumper-griffins-story/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Jumper/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/jumper/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/jumper-griffins-story"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":226,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Mistwalker", "Feel Plus"],
			"synopsis":"The second of two epic RPG projects for Microsoft by Mistwalker, the studio founded by Square-Enix's Hironobu Sakaguchi. You play as Kaim, a man who's been sentenced to live for 1,000 years. The game's storyline takes you through Kaim's life as he lives through multiple generations, becomes a part of many families, falls in and out of love and gets into conflicts. All this is set in a world that is on the verge of a \"mystical industrial revolution\", where mankind has attained dark powers.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Seeker of the Deep",
				"releaseDate":"2008/05/23",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Seeker of the Deep is a dungeon expansion for Lost Odyssey. Explore 25 levels of the Experimental Staff Remains. Collect exclusive items and fight the boss."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Triple Bonus Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/04/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Adds Killer Machine ring, Shattered Bond, and Memory Lamp valuable items"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uwJOe-Y918A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KgtBM23ltuw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928334-lost-odyssey/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lost-Odyssey/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lost-odyssey/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lost-odyssey"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Lost Odyssey Wiki",
				"url":"http://lostodyssey.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":227,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"FIFA Street 3 creates a hyper-real world that merges the game's biggest stars with environments that pulsate to the music in exotic locales around the world. Featuring over 250 of the world's best players representing 18 of the top international teams, each player has been rendered into a stylized caricature with heroic qualities. Decked out in authentic training kits, every player boasts their own, distinctive style of play with unique abilities to match. Choose from Tricksters, Enforcers, Playmakers and Finishers to give you different options on the ball and make your mark on the street.<br><br>Using the same engine as the critically acclaimed NBA Street Homecourt basketball arcade game, combined with the market-leading AI from FIFA Soccer 08, FIFA Street 3 delivers animations and ball control that enables you to take complete control of your players with a responsive and intuitive control system that makes it easier than ever to pull off sensational moves. Use the simple button configuration and analog stick to seamlessly combine moves - providing you with hundreds of different ways to show off your street skills. Fill up your all-new Game Breaker to power your ultimate abilities and express yourself like never before. Maneuver your players to leap past defenders, flip off walls, or perform gravity-defying one-timers to score spectacular goals.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Arena Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/03/15",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":2
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hbk5Sa6GbRo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w523uDShM9Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943743-fifa-street-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/FIFA-Street-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fifa-street-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fifa-street-3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":228,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bizarre Creations"],
			"synopsis":"For most people, The Club exists only as an urban legend - a game where criminals are paid huge amounts to carry out gunfights and where online spectators view, gamble and cheer them on in a deadly game of skill. Yet the rumours are true. People are getting rich. People are dying. The first task is to survive, but according to their rules - quickly, relentlessly and with style...<br><br>Players choose between eight unique fighters, each with their own combat style and agendas, as they travel the globe in a series of visceral urban battlefields. In addition to a variety of single-player scenarios, The Club boasts an array of multiplayer options to satisfy even the most discerning action aficionado.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=THy4-HmbB6Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FQ8RiRWiqrQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Club/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-club/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-club"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":229,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Omega Force"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the epic novel, Romance of the Three Kingdoms, the genre-defining Dynasty Warriors series depicts the massive battles ignited by the fall of the Han Dynasty when three rebellious states moved to overthrow the Emperor of China. Expanding over the original with a new combat engine, Dynasty Warriors 6 delivers the exhilaration of single-handedly destroying thousands of soldiers on massive fields of combat. The lightning-fast king-fu fighting, fluid animation, intuitive combat system and immersive game environments push the limits of tactical action!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ePLjVEOPzj4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NARNJUQ1PBs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942654-dynasty-warriors-6/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dynasty-Warriors-6/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dynasty-warriors-6/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dynasty-warriors-6"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Koei Wiki",
				"url":"http://koei.wikia.com/wiki/Dynasty_Warriors_6"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":230,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Kaos Studios"],
			"synopsis":"The first project for Kaos Studios (a division of THQ founded by veterans of Trauma Studios, creators of Desert Combat and Battlefield 2 R&D projects), Frontlines: Fuel of War uses the advanced Unreal 3 engine for futuristic, intense fights in an open-world battlefield. In this all-too-bleak future of constant wars over natural resources, two sides compete for global supremacy: the Western Coalition (the United States and the European Union) and the Red Star Alliance (Russian/People's Republic of China). The game's nonlinear single-player campaign has players advancing their side's frontline into enemy territory.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Boneyard Map",
				"releaseDate":"2008/06/30",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Join up to 50 players in the first of five all new downloadable maps for Frontlines: Fuel of War, featuring the never before seen Automatic Shotgun, Rocket Jeep and Red Star Transport Helicopter. As Western Coalition armor closes in on the last functional Red Star nuclear missile facility, Alliance tanks rally to defend their last hopes for victory in Europe. The frontlines have been drawn across the Shilnaya Balka missile silos. Coalition and Alliance troops stare each other down across the complex, each waiting for the other to blink. Better watch where you shoot."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Conquer Mode",
				"releaseDate":"2008/09/13",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"You wanted more. Now you got it. Available now on Xbox LIVE, Frontlines: Fuel of War Conquer Mode opens up the battleground by allowing players to capture objectives in any order, anywhere on the map. Replay all of your favorite Frontlines maps and discover new strategies and tactics in this free, game mode expansion."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"4 Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/09/19",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Kaos Studios presents four all-new multiplayer maps for the hit first-person shooter Frontlines: Fuel of War. From the intense armor engagements of Wide Awake to the massive air battles of Hindsight, this map pack features some of the largest, most wide-open multiplayer levels your Xbox 360 has ever seen. Looking for more close-quarters combat? Then take on the concentrated firefights of Infiltration and the vertical infantry combat of Sunder in two of the most high-intensity maps ever seen in Frontlines: Fuel of War."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e6eWy993Up8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ri82yV40iKA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Single Player Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8NZ0B_Wxh4Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932615-frontlines-fuel-of-war/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Frontlines-Fuel-of-War/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/frontlines-fuel-of-war/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/frontlines-fuel-of-war"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":231,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"As a passenger of Oceanic flight 815, you survived the crash and find yourself on an uncharted island somewhere in the Pacific Ocean. As you begin to unravel mysteries of the island, you begin to discover secrets of your own. You will have to understand your past mistakes in order to survive and find your way home...<br><br>Based on the popular TV show, the game incorporates familiar locations and will feature main characters from the show. Solve puzzles, outsmart enemies, battle the smoke monster, and overcoming many other challenges to survive the island and ultimately come out alive.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k104av4eGks"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bnsuTh1Bt4g"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942291-lost-via-domus/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lost-Via-Domus/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lost-via-domus/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lost-via-domus"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Lostpedia",
				"url":"http://lostpedia.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":232,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Spark Unlimited"],
			"synopsis":"Turning Point: Fall of Liberty delivers an explosive FPS experience in a world where famous locations and landmarks appear startlingly different under Nazi occupation, and will pose a new, very personal battle for players on their home turf. As Dan Carson - a reluctant New York City construction worker turned freedom fighter - gamers must survive the initial invasion before regrouping with other U.S. resistance members to take the fight back to the Nazis. Always outmanned and outgunned, players have to use a handful of guerilla tactics as they attempt to stop the world's now notorious war machine.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z_2xNsvIPuk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NxeN-jNylhM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6QrTEEzDBB0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935324-turning-point-fall-of-liberty/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Turning-Point/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/turning-point-fall-of-liberty/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/turning-point-fall-of-liberty"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":233,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Kush Games"],
			"synopsis":"Major League Baseball 2K8 returns to the diamond with the most complete MLB experience available. Revolutionizing your control of the 5 tools in baseball are brand new pitching, fielding and baserunning controls and completely overhauled batting interface. Featuring a totally unique trading card mode, robust Minor League system, all-new Signature Style animations for 2008, and more, Major League Baseball 2K8 brings a new level of fun to the virtual baseball world.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7x_1tmP4WUQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JJrT8OSFnEY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MLB-2K8/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mlb-2k8/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/major-league-baseball-2k8"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":234,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"Army of Two throws gamers into hot spots ripped from current day headlines where they will utilize unique two-man strategies and tactics while seamlessly transitioning between playing with intelligent Partner AI (PAI) and a live player. When one man is not enough, it will take an army of two to fight through war, political turmoil and a conspiracy so vast it threatens the entire world.<br><br>Unlike other co-op games, Army of Two not only focuses on winning, it's about getting paid. As ex-Army Rangers now turned contractors for a Private Military Corporation, players spend their hard earned cash on more accurate and deadly customizable weapons. Players can use special co-op features to complete their paid missions including the new and unique Aggro feature that ensures their partner goes unnoticed when approaching enemies. Dependent on the intensity of their gun fire, distance, line of sight and type of weapon, players can put the enemy's attention on one player while the other plans a sneak attack to take them out!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"SSC Challenge Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/04/24",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Expand the two-man combat experience in Army of Two with the SSC Challenge Map Pack! This new content gives players a chance to test their skills in a different setting while retaining the action-packed co-op intensity of Army of Two. Four two-player co-op maps will allow gamers to compete in the SSC Challenge versus mode for the chance to earn big cash rewards. Each team must work co-operatively and compete in a race through grueling obstacle courses as they test skills in accuracy, two-man tactics and highly lethal combat."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Veteran Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/06/12",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This pack features two additional co-op campaign maps and a new multiplayer. This pack contains two new missions for the Army of Two experience, and can be experienced solo, or alongside a friend in co-op. One of the missions added takes place in Kiev, Ukraine, while the other presents an Alternative Ending to the game."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1yO2LAP5Ls8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n6A3rMHS4Ag"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932860-army-of-two/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Army-of-Two/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/army-of-two/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/army-of-two"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Army of Two Wiki",
				"url":"http://armyoftwo.wikia.com/wiki/Army_of_Two_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":235,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rockstar Vancouver"],
			"synopsis":"You're not going to take it anymore. From edgy publisher Rockstar's Vancouver development team comes this dark comedy set in the most vile and sadistic setting yet in a Rockstar videogame: the schoolyard. As a troublesome schoolboy, you'll laugh and cringe as you stand up to bullies, get picked on by teachers, play pranks on malicious kids, win or lose the girl, and ultimately learn to navigate the obstacles of the fictitious reform school, Bullworth Academy.<br><br>Both the Wii and Xbox 360 versions will retain the wit and deep gameplay of the previously released PlayStation 2 computer entertainment system title and will boast additional new content.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pi6A-JxQ7LY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QKEJm86vkxk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942199-bully-scholarship-edition/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bully-Scholarship-Edition/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bully-scholarship-edition/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bully-scholarship-edition"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Bully Wiki",
				"url":"http://bully.wikia.com/wiki/Bully_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":236,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Monolith Productions"],
			"synopsis":"Players will assume the identity of Ethan Thomas, former Serial Crimes Unit investigator, who has been called back to duty to track down his missing partner. The disturbing events from Ethan's past have left him a broken man - a desperate burnout drifting aimlessly through society in an inexplicable decline. Fighting inner demons throughout his one-man investigation into a sinister conspiracy, Ethan will need to use anything and everything in the environment to survive as he unravels the mysteries shrouding the city in darkness.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RDLV9Lnsuco"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WmtuC5eGk0g"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939452-condemned-2-bloodshot/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Condemned-2-Bloodshot/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/condemned-2-bloodshot/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/condemned-2-bloodshot"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Condemned Wiki",
				"url":"http://condemned.wikia.com/wiki/Condemned_2:_Bloodshot"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":237,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"PES 2008 takes soccer to the next level. The game features a brand new intelligence system, called Teamvision, that adapts and reacts to players own gameplay styles to ensure that the computer controlled opponents are always challenging and forcing the player to think and chance their style of play to avoid being out-thought by the game. It learns counter attacks that target your weaknesses and looks to exploit any repetitive tactics players use.<br><br>Meanwhile in PES 2008 defenders react better to danger, closing down the ball and charging at shots and the goalkeepers will hold shots that are closer to them as well. Teammates make more intelligent runs into space and the close control has been sharpened to ensure quick and fluid passing and speedy attacks can be built.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ga1qG-3OPiw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4dZvD6kSy_E"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/940560-pro-evolution-soccer-2008/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pro-Evolution-Soccer-2008/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pro-evolution-soccer-2008/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pro-evolution-soccer-2008"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":238,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sumo Digital"],
			"synopsis":"SEGA Superstars Tennis features classic SEGA characters - including Sonic the Hedgehog and Ulala from Space Channel 5 - plus some of the most unusual courts and outrageous settings ever imagined in a rousing match of tennis. Developed by Sumo Digital (the team behind the enjoyable Virtua Tennis 3), this title features a toal of 15 playable characters (and a host of SEGA icons cheering on from courtside), each with their own over-the-top tennis skills. Courts are SEGA-themed too, with Green Hill Zone and Samba de Amigo's Carnival Park.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tiMtaApI18w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i9jBKpP1y2U"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943720-sega-superstars-tennis/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sega-Superstars-Tennis/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sega-superstars-tennis/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sega-superstars-tennis"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sonic News Network",
				"url":"http://sonic.wikia.com/wiki/Sega_Superstars_Tennis"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":239,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Vegas 2 - the sequel to the award-winning next-generation first-person shooter - returns to Sin City. Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Vegas 2 is your last chance to rescue America's sexiest city from an escalating terrorist siege that will force you into heart-pounding action from beginning to end. The best are back and this time winner takes all.<br><br>Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Vegas pushes the franchise to new heights by adding new gameplay features and even more visuals. Players encounter an intense solo campaign that uses new tactical possibilities in various locations around Sin City. Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Vegas 2 also breaks new ground in both co-op and adversarial modes, while providing interaction between the solo and multiplayer modes.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Gift Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/03",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Pack includes reworked versions of familiar favorites to storm your way through: Calypso Casino, Murdertown - Dark and CQB Training - Dark."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZfG3vjxnQlk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cD4N3jkjlcc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xaq0BRzAsoI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944073-tom-clancys-rainbow-six-vegas-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tom-Clancys-Rainbow-Six-Vegas-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rainbow-six-vegas-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tom-clancys-rainbow-six-vegas-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Rainbow Six Wiki",
				"url":"http://rainbowsix.wikia.com/wiki/Tom_Clancy's_Rainbow_Six:_Vegas_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":240,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digital Extremes"],
			"synopsis":"A modern-day superhero saga, Dark Sector is a third-person shooter where players assume the role of the protagonist, Hayden Tenno who gains the ability to morph into dramatically different combat forms. Set in the crumbling infrastructure of a fictional Soviet-bloc country in the near future, the game features both single and multi-player action, with players working their way through a world where bio-weapons are no longer science experiments, but a hellish nightmare let loose on an unsuspecting populace.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fnsjVO3Y6Rw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MLLZYCIbA-8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928149-dark-sector/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dark-Sector/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dark-sector/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dark-sector"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":241,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Petroglyph"],
			"synopsis":"Universe at War: Earth Assault is set in the near-future when multiple factions from across the galaxy have come to Earth to wage epic warfare. Deadly sci-fi weapons and alien powers allow players to destroy cities and other territory while fighting for Earth. The game also allows players to retrain and customize units in the midst of battle, modify their weapons and defenses in real-time, and even control the development of technology that will help them to victory.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zZMP5hgvp8I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FB8oIscSBIo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fn99fYgDQXQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939445-universe-at-war-earth-assault/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Universe-at-War/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/universe-at-war-earth-assault/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/universe-at-war-earth-assault"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Universe at War Wiki",
				"url":"http://universeatwar.wikia.com/wiki/Universe_At_War:Earth_Assault"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":242,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Creative Assembly"],
			"synopsis":"A fierce struggle is taking place within the realm of the Norse Gods. The Goddess Hel has been banished for defying Odin, Lord of Asgard. Angry at her fate, Hel has raised an army of undead warriors to enslave the mortal realm of Midgard, and then provoke Ragnarok - the apocalyptic battle that that will destroy Asgard and the Gods themselves. The task of stopping Hel and defending the future of mankind falls to Skarin, a promising but deeply flawed young warrior, ignorant of the true reason for his favour with the Gods...<br><br>Leave a bloody trail of dismembered foes as you master an involving and addictive combat style with destructive mythical powers and abilities. Explore vast and visually stunning open-world environments whilst slaying your enemies with a huge array of devastating and brutal combat moves. Tame mighty dragons and unleash their rain of fire, laying waste to the enemy hordes that stand in your way. Free enslaved warriors to wage war on Hel's legion and lead them into huge, epic battles featuring colossal giants, powerful shaman, deadly assassins and Hel's own champions. Here players can use Skarin's emerging skills to help turn the tide of conflict with a timely murder or through the brutality of a visceral wave of slaughter.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bAWnOFti1yk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wJF-SHRCEDs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942960-viking-battle-for-asgard/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Viking/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/viking-battle-for-asgard/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/viking-battle-for-asgard"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":243,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Midway Amusement Games"],
			"synopsis":"NBA Ballers: Chosen One allows players to live the life of an NBA superstar. Featuring new competitive combo and super-move systems, the NBA Ballers Franchise returns with the amazing realistic graphics for which the franchise is known as players take part in the ultimate challenge to become the next Chosen One. The fast-paced one-on-one and two-on-two action returns as players can select from more than 65 NBA superstars to be the next \"Chosen One\". The franchise's hallmark pick-up-and-play gameplay allows Ballers of all skill levels to master combos and pull off amazing super-moves as they hoop-it-up with the best players in the NBA.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nnHjaIbNonE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qJwoeVGex7E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-Ballers-Chosen-One/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-ballers-chosen-one/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-ballers-chosen-one"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":244,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rockstar North"],
			"synopsis":"GTA IV reinvents the series with a renewed version of Liberty City detailed to the last pothole and rooftop vent. There are now four boroughs to explore plus extra area outside of Liberty City proper. With the ability to climb obstacles, drive cars, steer boats and pilot helicopters, the world of GTA is more accessible than ever before.<br><br>In this fourth installment of the popular series, players take on the role of Niko Bellic, a rough-around-the-edge chap from Eastern Europe. Niko has arrived in America, in Liberty City - a land full of promise and opportunity. His cousin convinced him to emigrate, to join him in his mansion and life of luxury, but as soon as he steps off the boat, Niko discovers the truth about the American way. Still, the wealth, the comfort, the bliss of the good life, it all really is here .... And it's all for the taking.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Lost & Damned",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/17",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Johnny is a veteran member of The Lost, a notorious biker gang. Johnny has been creating business opportunities for The Lost in Liberty City, but his first loyalty must be to the patch he wears on his back and to Billy Grey, the club's President. However, when Billy returns from rehab hell-bent on bloodshed and debauchery, Johnny finds himself in the middle of a vicious turf war with rival gangs for control of a city torn apart by violence and corruption. Can the brotherhood survive?<br><br>Developed by series creator Rockstar North and set in Liberty City, Grand Theft Auto IV: The Lost and Damned features a new main character, Johnny Klebitz, and plot that intersects with the storyline of Grand Theft Auto IV; new missions that offer an entirely fresh way to explore Liberty City with new multiplayer modes, weapons and vehicles; and a diverse soundtrack with additional music - all with the incredible production values that are the trademarks of Grand Theft Auto. All-new missions and a new storyline that interweaves with the original story arc of Grand Theft Auto IV. Play as Johnny, a member of The Lost Motorcycle Club.<br><br>Experience Liberty City now with the perspective and lifestyle of a member of a biker gang. Added range of weapons - including the all-new grenade launcher and sawed-off shotgun. New weapons will be available for use in single-player and in all new multiplayer modes. New vehicles - featuring a collection of bikes that include Johnny's own customized heavy-duty chopper. New and improved bike handling and physics. Set of new action-packed multiplayer modes - details coming soon. All-new in-game TV, internet and radio content featuring new radio shows and original music. Plus new side-missions and Xbox 360 Achievement."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"The Ballad of Gay Tony",
				"releaseDate":"2009/10/29",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Grand Theft Auto IV's second downloadable episode, The Ballad of Gay Tony injects Liberty City with an overdose of guns, glitz, and grime. As Luis Lopez, part-time hoodlum and full-time assistant to legendary nightclub impresario Tony Prince (aka \"Gay Tony\"), players will struggle with the competing loyalties of family and friends, and with the uncertainty about who is real and who is fake in a world in which everyone has a price."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FO25p4JdB1U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=902iUo5xCuk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/609600-grand-theft-auto-iv-the-complete-edition/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Grand-Theft-Auto-4/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/grand-theft-auto-iv/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/grand-theft-auto-iv"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"GTA Wiki",
				"url":"http://gta.wikia.com/Grand_Theft_Auto_IV"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":245,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Secret Level"],
			"synopsis":"Iron Man, one of Marvel's most indestructible Super Heroes, blast onto videogame platforms with this adaptation of the big screen movie. This third-person action game immerses players in the world of Tony Stark - the brilliant industrialist and inventor who both created and became the world's toughest hero - Iron Man. By customizing the advanced technology in Iron Man's suits, gamers can take advantage of a wide array of high-impact weapons to strategically blow-up and destroy any enemy force and fight to rid the world of weapons of mass destruction.<br><br>Drawing from both the movie and comic book storylines, Iron Man features the voice talent of the stars from the major motion picture - Robert Downey Jr, Terrence Howard, and Shawn Toub. Utilizing the power of next-gen gaming consoles, Iron Man offers photo-realistic graphics, non-linear gameplay and huge open worlds in which gamers can travel as far as the eye can see.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D-ri-4gVY_w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yBYUuCtJMns"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/936559-iron-man/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Iron-Man/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/iron-man/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/iron-man"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":246,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Traveller's Tales"],
			"synopsis":"Revisit the rich, fantasy land of Narnia. Based on the second Walt Disney and Walden Media film of the epic Narnia series, Prince Caspian finds Lucy, Edmund, Susan, and Peter whisked back to Narnia to help drive out the cruel King Miraz.<br><br>The game allows players to assume the role of 20 different characters from the film, including non-human Narnians. In addition, the game supports two-player, drop-in/drop-out cooperative gameplay and includes a level that is unique from both the novel and the film. This level, which is set between the events of \"The Lion, The Witch and The Wardrobe\" and \"Prince Caspian\", takes place at the castle of Cair Paravel and tells the story of how Narnia fell to the Telmarine hordes.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p94nHLFCay4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BOaQA359i6U"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942122-the-chronicles-of-narnia-prince-caspian/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Prince-Caspian/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-chronicles-of-narnia-prince-of-caspian/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-chronicles-of-narnia-prince-caspian"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wikinarnia",
				"url":"http://narnia.wikia.com/wiki/The_Chronicles_of_Narnia_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":247,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Electronic Arts"],
			"synopsis":"Electronic Arts Inc. celebrates the passion fans have for their national teams and all of the excitement of the UEFA European Soccer Championship with the only official and exclusive licensed videogame of UEFA Euro 2008. Take on the challenge of leading one of over 50 European national teams to glory as UEFA EURO 2008 recreates all of the drama and excitement of the official tournament in Austria and Switzerland. Play as your favorite country from qualification right through to a virtual reproduction of the championship tournament.<br><br>A new game mode called Captain Your Country enables gamers to customize them on the pitch and wear the shirt of their national team. Work through eight status levels to earn the captaincy of your team and then lead your country into battle for championship glory against your rivals. Go online in Battle of the Nations to earn status points for yourself and your country in a competition for continental supremacy.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cp1Y0QiilL0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6iR7drdmd0g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/UEFA-EURO-2008/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/uefa-euro-2008/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/uefa-euro-2008"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":248,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Nerve Software", "Splash Damage"],
			"synopsis":"Enemy Territory: Quake Wars pits the armies of Earth against the invading alien Strogg in an online strategic shooter. Players choose to battle as one of five unique classes in either the EDF (Earth Defense Force - humans) or the barbaric alien Strogg armies. Troops use 40+ conventional and futuristic vehicles, deployable structures, and defense systems like quad-bikes, tanks, and alien walkers for epic ground assaults; or helicopters and anti-gravity ships to lend firepower from the air. Throughout each battle, teams establish bases, deploy defense structures, artillery, radar, and advanced forward-command systems into enemy territory while constructing and demolishing obstacles to speed progress and gain a tactical advantage over the enemy.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1gHu2IDRIUU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v04tcaLUJK8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938348-enemy-territory-quake-wars/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Enemy-Territory-Quake-Wars/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/enemy-territory-quake-wars/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/enemy-territory-quake-wars"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Quake Wiki",
				"url":"http://quake.wikia.com/wiki/Enemy_Territory:_Quake_Wars"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":249,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Luxoflux Corp."],
			"synopsis":"In Kung Fu Panda, players embark on an epic, action-packed adventure as they master the specialized Kung Fu fighting styles of Po the Panda, his teacher Shifu, and the legendary Kung Fu masters. Through 13 legendary levels from the movie and beyond, players must work to become the Dragon Warrior and defeat the ultimate enemy Tai Lung, as they battle a variety of foes, overcome dangerous obstacles, navigate multi-tiered environments and solve challenging puzzles.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6O0jK_PjrSo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E13PpcsubhY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945168-dreamworks-kung-fu-panda/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kung-Fu-Panda/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kung-fu-panda/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dreamworks-kung-fu-panda"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Kung Fu Panda Wiki",
				"url":"http://kungfupanda.wikia.com/wiki/Kung_Fu_Panda_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":250,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Traveller's Tales"],
			"synopsis":"Once again rendering a beloved George Lucas creation in LEGOs, LEGO Indiana Jones features the intrepid explorer in an epic adventure based on the film series. Developed by the same team that created the LEGO Star Wars series, LEGO Indiana Jones presents a tongue-in-cheek take on the first three cinematic adventures of pop culture's most iconic archaeologist, including Indiana Jones and the Raiders of the Lost Ark, Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom and Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IYCZLHy_9w0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HK4ycyr-oXU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942421-lego-indiana-jones-the-original-adventures/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/LEGO-Indiana-Jones/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lego-indiana-jones/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lego-indiana-jones-the-original-adventures"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Brickipedia",
				"url":"http://lego.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Indiana_Jones:_The_Original_Adventures"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Lego Indiana Jones Wiki",
				"url":"http://legoindianajones.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Indiana_Jones_Wiki"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Indiana Jones Wiki",
				"url":"http://indianajones.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Indiana_Jones%3A_The_Original_Adventures"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":251,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Team Ninja"],
			"synopsis":"The sequel to the blockbuster action game by Tecmo's heralded Team Ninja. Gamers must guide Ryu Hayabusa on a mission to avenge his clan and prevent the destruction of the human race. Armed with an assortment of ninja weaponry, players must help Ryu skillfully maneuver through a world fraught with peril and danger. Running on an entirely new gameplay engine, Ninja Gaiden 2 evolves the action in the sequel with an auto-generation health system, new enemies and locales, and thrilling combat built upon an extensive assortment of ninja weaponry.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Fiend Hayabusa Costume Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/01",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Update Hayabusa's in-game look with an all new costume set with 5 color variations. Inspired by the Hayabusa family's namesake, the falcon, this demonic costume mirrors the intensity of Ryu's vengeance and fury as he fights to regain the honor of his clan."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Biometal Hayabusa Costume Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/01",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Update Hayabusa's in-game look with an all new costume set with 5 color variations. This costume, organically forged to his body with liquid cooled channels and reinforced armor, gives Ryu a completely new and foreboding look."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Shadow Walker Hayabusa Costume Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/01",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Update Hayabusa's in-game look with an all new costume set with 5 color variations. This futuristic interpretation of the classic cloth ninja garb is reinforced in all the right areas to protect Ryu in battle."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Mission Mode",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/29",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Introducing Mission Mode, a brand-new gameplay expansion for the acclaimed action game Ninja Gaiden II. In this all new game mode, challenge your skills in self-contained missions featuring trials and tribulations not found in the standard story mode. Karma Attack missions task you with obtaining the highest score, while Survival missions give you a single weapon to fight off as many enemies as possible. Take your high scores online with Xbox LIVE and compete with players around the world on the mission leaderboards!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uS-IhxhW4T8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=frjKmmmO-b8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Sav7qAwoDyk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943273-ninja-gaiden-ii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ninja-Gaiden-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ninja-gaiden-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ninja-gaiden-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Ninja Gaiden Wiki",
				"url":"http://ninjagaiden.wikia.com/wiki/Ninja_Gaiden_II"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":252,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Codemasters"],
			"synopsis":"Grid is a true evolution for Codemasters' acclaimed racing series, which first appeared as the TOCA (DTM/V8) Touring Car games (1997-2000) and became the TOCA (DTM/V8) Race Driver series (2002-2006). Challenging players to become the number one race driver in a new world of exhilarating motorsport, Race Driver: Grid takes players on a tour like never before; to beautifully realized racing locations through Europe, the U.S., Japan and beyond. The game will feature the most extensive range of events in the series, combining official circuit-based championships with road races and urban street competitions.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"8-Ball Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/04",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"The '8 Ball' pack for GRID features 8 thrilling new cars and two new online events as the first in a series of three new extensions for the game. Each carefully selected and beautifully realised vehicle is a thoroughbred racing car chosen for its unique personality to deliver a stunning race experience. All 8 cars become available in 'Race Day' mode and in online races. Two new multiplayer events, set on existing circuits from across GRID's three continents, have been created to test drivers to their very limit online. Car List: McLaren F1 GTR, TVR Cerbera Speed 12, Mitsubishi 2.0 Turbo Lancer Evolution X, Honda S2000, Nissan GTR GT500, VW Nardo, Pontiac Firebird Trans AM, Volvo C30 Green Racing."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q9p84vY6V8Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b9jLTb6uDFU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eRYpOaFnY4U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dM5FXYDCs_k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hTFqTI6LKS0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939160-grid/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/GRID/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/race-driver-grid/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/grid"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":253,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["High Moon Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Robert Ludlum's The Bourne Conspiracy, gives players the experience of becoming a 30 million dollar elite agent, fusing an experience that delves deep into Jason Bourne's character with gameplay and game presentation inspired by the aggressive filmmaking and frenetic action found in the films. Only by playing Robert Ludlum's The Bourne Conspiracy will players discover Bourne's true identity and experience the very moment he became a malfunctioning weapon, first hunting targets around the world as a deadly government assassin then marking himself as his agency's most wanted.<br><br>The game promises constant tension and action, with players adopting Jason Bourne's piercing sense of survival, cunning nature, heightened target awareness and firearms training that allow him to engage and eliminate small armies. As a third-person espionage action game, players move from fistfights to firefights to experience sequences that, unlike any other game, seamlessly blend Bourne's signature hand-to-hand combat with intense shooting and the ability to escape and evade deadly situations.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nIsJTrwOtNI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OXEAMRXCeEo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/941631-robert-ludlums-the-bourne-conspiracy/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Bourne-Conspiracy/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/robert-ludlams-the-bourne-conspiracy/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/robert-ludlums-the-bourne-conspiracy"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Bourne Directory",
				"url":"http://bourne.wikia.com/wiki/The_Bourne_Directory"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":254,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Edge of Reality"],
			"synopsis":"Fueled with fury, he Incredible Hulk features key moments from the film, as well as additional plotlines and characters from the character's rich comic-book universe. Players smash through New York City, battling gigantic enemies amidst soaring skyscrapers in a massive open world. Players can demolish anything in their path and also use it as a weapon - pieces of a crumbling building...a passing car...a light standard. They can even demolish buildings with their bare hands. Damage is persistent, and gamers can use it to gain access to previously unreachable areas.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Multiplayer Expansion Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/09/09",
				"type":1
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7hY-noxnJtQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k7OWRTf0maw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XhHMcl6uhQY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944982-the-incredible-hulk/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Incredible-Hulk/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-incredible-hulk/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-incredible-hulk"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":255,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Venom Games"],
			"synopsis":"Don King Presents: Prizefighter brings an innovative feature set and story line to the ring with the aim to set the standard in boxing video games. Developed by Venom Games, the game focuses on putting together the realism of live action match-ups and the true tactics of the sweet science. More than just a night at the fights, players will be responsible for building a career by overcoming adversity, avoiding temptation, and balancing their commitments to train and promote, all while focusing on the goal of ultimately winning and defending the title belt. The story is told by a revolutionary sports documentary-style narrative never before seen in a video game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9_om5xUGeB8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qQmfRApe_tc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YQhPb-t9-NI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Prizefighter/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/don-king-presents-prizefighter/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/don-king-presents-prizefighter"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":256,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Dimps"],
			"synopsis":"Dragon Ball Z: Burst Limit is revolutionizing the series by entering the realm of next-generation gaming. Complete with fierce online battles and radical 3D graphic effects, Dragon Ball Z: Burst Limit will blur the line between videogame and iconic anime series. Jam-packed with graphically enhanced playable characters, realistic battle stages and environments, players can take hold and experience Dragon Ball Z as never before.<br><br>During each battle, find conditions to create new dramatic scenes. After the battles, watch a unique story unfold each time you play. There is also a stronger element of offence and defence, due to added energy saving and fighting techniques.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oz6G3iFHfvc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WuY-AJL6S08"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TSwJUy3XiTM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944316-dragon-ball-z-burst-limit/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dragon-Ball-Z-Burst-Limit/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dragon-ball-z-burst-limit/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dragon-ball-z-burst-limit"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dragon Ball Wiki",
				"url":"http://dragonball.wikia.com/wiki/Dragon_Ball_Z:_Burst_Limit"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":257,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"Race YOUR way with the 2009 edition of the racing phenomenon! Choose a driving model that fits like a glove, create your ultimate dream car with endless design options, and generate unique driving credentials that feature your very own photo. NASCAR 09 is all about you! In fact, NASCAR's four-time champion Jeff Gordon will even take you under his wing and personally guide you through key aspects of the game. Use his advice to your advantage when racing in the all-new career mode or the Sprint Driver Challenges to earn reputation and become a NASCAR champion. Get ready to race for premier contracts as you work your way to the top with NASCAR 09.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=luHi30kT3no"
			},
			{
				"type":"Single Player Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8qHRaxjGpY8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0SyTNXTvoWk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NASCAR-09/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nascar-2009/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nascar-09"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":258,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Liquid Dragon Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Battle 40-foot waves, storms, ice and a nearly 100-percent crew member injury rate in the dangerous hunt for undersea riches on the Bering Sea with the videogame based on the hit Discovery Channel series. The game lets gamers captain their own boat in the frenzied search for an undersea jackpot. Players select one of five real crab boats, including the Northwestern, Cornelia Marie and Sea Star - all featured on the series, or create and customize their own boat. Gamers then recruit and lead their own crew from a roster of twenty real crab fishermen. Selecting the wrong boat or recruiting the wrong crew member can mean the difference between landing a Bering Sea jackpot or disaster. Lead your fatigued, hungry and hardworking crew in the strategic search for King Crab and Opilio Crab, while battling to secure your catch and livelihood before other captains and crews get to the crab first.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OZvgoLYn3Nk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wK_sZwOHUco"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/946237-deadliest-catch-alaskan-storm/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Deadliest-Catch-Alaskan-Storm/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/deadliest-catch-alaskan-storm/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/deadliest-catch-alaskan-storm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":259,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["DICE"],
			"synopsis":"Battlefield: Bad Company drops gamers behind enemy lines with a squad of renegade soldiers who risk it all on a personal quest for gold and revenge.<br><br>Featuring a cinematic single-player experience loaded with adventure and dark humor, the game delivers the series' trademark sandbox gameplay in a universe where nearly everything is destructible. Battlefield: Bad Company also features a full suite of the franchise's trademark multiplayer options with deep gameplay designed to take full advantage of the game's massively destructible environments.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Conquest",
				"releaseDate":"2008/08/07",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"An old friend returns! The Conquest game mode was hugely popular in previous Battlefield games and now sees its addition to DICE's latest blockbuster. Download the Conquest Pack for Battlefield: Bad Company for free and battle it out on four modified maps from the core game. In Conquest mode, the aim is to reduce the opposing team's tickets to zero. Killing an enemy soldier depletes one ticket per kill, whilst capturing control points on the map causes enemy tickets to count down. See you on the Battlefield soldier!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Community Choice Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/10/31",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The community has spoken! Battle it out on Par For the Course and Acta Non Verba, two single player levels turned into playgrounds for fierce multiplayer Conquest warfare as chosen by the players. This FREE map pack also contains the two DICE choices Crossing Over and Ghost Town, bringing the total number of maps to four. See you on these new battlefields, soldiers!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"All Trailers",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B3az5PLh3GQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Single Player Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GYtBaowd_m0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gf0sior1lgM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935085-battlefield-bad-company/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Battlefield-Bad-Company/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/battlefield-bad-company/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/battlefield-bad-company"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Battlefield Wiki",
				"url":"http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Battlefield:_Bad_Company"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":260,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Los Angeles"],
			"synopsis":"An expansion pack to C&C3, Kane's Wrath returns to the Tiberium universe with Kane at the center of an epic new single player campaign. The expansion allows players to experience a new story that spans 20 years - from the rebirth of the Brotherhood of Nod after the Second Tiberium War through the dramatic events of the Third Tiberium War and beyond. The story is told through a new set of high-definition live action video sequences starring a celebrity cast.<br><br>Command & Conquer 3: Kane's Wrath also features a new strategic layer to gameplay that allows players to establish bases, build customized armies, and attack their enemies on a global scale - and then dive into the frenzied tactical combat where their skills as a commander will make the difference in battle. The game introduces six new sub-factions and a wealth of new units, structures, and powers to the armies of the Global Defense Initiative, the Brotherhood of Nod, and the enigmatic alien Scrin.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/28",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Kane Lives! Download this map pack and wreck havoc on 4 new maps that can be used in both Skirmish or against other commanders in Xbox LIVE. Choose your army and conquer the world in Command & Conquer 3: Kane's Wrath, the follow up to 2007's best selling real-time strategy game, C&C 3 Tiberium Wars. This standalone game features the new CommandStick interface, making RTS easier to pick up and play than ever before. Kane's Wrath includes all the units, structures, and superpowers from Tiberium Wars, giving you over 100 units and structures to command and 9 unique armies, each with its own play style!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=96LNtvpIjiQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oLNr2DOWR-g"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942785-command-and-conquer-3-kanes-wrath/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Command-Conquer-3-Kanes-Wrath/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/command-and-conquer-3-kanes-wrath/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/command-conquer-3-kanes-wrath"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Command & Conquer Wiki",
				"url":"http://cnc.wikia.com/wiki/Command_%26_Conquer_3:_Kane's_Wrath"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":261,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Hellbent Games", "Gas Powered Games"],
			"synopsis":"For a millennium war has raged between the United Earth Federation, the Cybran Nation and the Aeon Illuminate. Unwavering, dramatically opposing systems of belief have locked the three forces of humanity into a bitter, merciless conflict that has come to be known as the Infinite War. Now, after centuries of struggle, a war that has torn the galaxy asunder has finally reached a turning point. A leader has risen above all others, and only this Supreme Commander holds the key to ending the Infinite War once and for all.<br><br>The groundbreaking game puts players in command of one of three factions - the United Earth Federation, the Cybran Nation or the Aeon Illuminate - that they must lead to victory and end the thousand-year Infinite War. Featuring a newly designed, intuitive console control scheme, Supreme Commander offers gameplay on an unprecedented scale. A revolutionary Strategic Zoom control allows for immediate viewing and command of entire armies as gamers battle through one of the three vast campaigns or against online enemies. Xbox 360-exclusive units, new online game modes and updated maps will bolster Xbox Live play as gamers wage war against opponents around the globe.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sm6dgtueTaA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Supreme-Commander/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/supreme-commander/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/supreme-commander"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Supreme Commander Wiki",
				"url":"http://supcom.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":262,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["PAM Development"],
			"synopsis":"In Top Spin 3, players compete online and offline to rise in the ranks against current top ranked professional players. Created by 2K's Paris studio, PAM Development, Top Spin 3 immerses players in a visually and physically realistic tennis experience. Using next generation technology, gameplay and graphics, Top Spin 3 features dynamic weather changes, evolutionary player visuals and the most comprehensive online offerings. Adding a unique user-generated component, players can also use new player creator features that include free-form body sculpting, makeup and tattoos.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ixFpP1ieRxU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_Drn3QsyS4I"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942070-top-spin-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Top-Spin-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/top-spin-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/top-spin-3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":263,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eden Games"],
			"synopsis":"Taking the fear to a new level, the next-gen Alone in the Dark features the macabre style of the series played with new gameplay mechanics and a broader-reaching, action-packed play style. Explore fully-interactive realtime worlds, interacting with physics and roaming the wide-open, fright-filled environments.<br><br>This next-gen Alone in the Dark is also built around a unique episodic game structure - the story is split into a number of distinct 30-40 minute episodes, doled out one at a time as you play. Each time the player launches a saved game, the episode will begin with a video summary of the previous episode to quickly re-immerse the player in the story and removing the need to remember where they were or what they were doing. Every episode will close with a nail-biting cliff-hanger ending to rattle players' nerves, and if the player is leaving the game a video teaser of the next episode will play to leave them wanting more.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fSYIKaf9_Bc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B-5Rco_BHLo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930280-alone-in-the-dark/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Alone-In-The-Dark/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/alone-in-the-dark/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/alone-in-the-dark"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Alone in the Dark Wiki",
				"url":"http://aloneinthedark.wikia.com/wiki/Alone_in_the_Dark_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":264,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Wideload Games"],
			"synopsis":"Hail to the Chimp begins after the Lion is deposed as King following a series of embarrassing scandals. The rest of the animals decide it's time to give democracy a try and hold an election for the next King giving even the lowliest of animals (the Clams) a say in things. The election quickly becomes a chaotic multiplayer free-for-all, with each candidate using a combination of brute force and dirty tricks to turn out the Clam vote. Ten animals will compete to become the next King. During the game, all ten candidates will need to form, and break, alliances with their rivals to gain the upper hand. Multiple game types and hazard-filled arenas keep the action flowing nonstop as the shifting loyalties, truces and vendettas build up to epic proportions.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eEYgNmBKo8s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fkugK9R1cao"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hail-to-the-Chimp/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hail-to-the-chimp/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hail-to-the-chimp"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":265,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Krome Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Hellboy provide players with fresh adventures featuring the unmistakable fusion of action, atmosphere and humor of the comic book and movie franchise. Hellboy uncovers a Nazi plot for world domination and must rush to defeat the crazed Hermann Von Klempt before he can exert his evil will upon a hapless world. As a visceral brawler, the game lets players unleash Hellboy's superhuman abilities as they smash their way through hordes of enemies with contextual use of the environment for added destructive power and strategy.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gmh0Bw0dLO4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=17dbMUVyHx8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933078-hellboy-the-science-of-evil/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hellboy-the-Science-of-Evil/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hellboy-science-of-evil/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hellboy-the-science-of-evil"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Hellboy Wiki",
				"url":"http://hellboy.wikia.com/wiki/Hellboy_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":266,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Success"],
			"synopsis":"Operation Darkness puts you in command of a British Special Forces squad during World War II that has been tasked with taking out the Nazis and Hitler while fighting a host of supernatural characters like zombies, skeletons, vampires, werewolves, and even dragons. Characters can use magic, change into supernatural beings, improve their weapons skills by becoming familiar with different artillery, and much more.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E0qz_EtpKpU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=amL42cplxgs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-twgulPrrFg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vvOGZWLfdfU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/929259-operation-darkness/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Operation-Darkness/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Operation-Darkness/walkthrough.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/operation-darkness"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":267,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Heavy Iron Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Race, fly and shoot as you take futuristic robots WALL-E and EVE through a fast-paced adventure. From the desolate waste-lands of Earth to the Axiom space cruiser, throw cubes and blast robots and obstacles while you relive some of the movie's most thrilling moments and explore worlds filled with non-stop action and adventure, along with head-to-head multiplayer challenges. Dodge dangerous enemies, carry out intense missions and navigate your way through a futuristic galaxy!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qj8c-vfH94Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wall-E/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wall-e/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wall-e"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":268,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Neversoft Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Guitar Hero: Aerosmith puts players in the shoes of Perry (guitar), Whitford (guitar) and Hamilton (bass)as they rock out alongside frontman Tyler and drummer Kramer. Gamers experience Aerosmith's legendary career, from their first gig to becoming rock royalty.<br><br>As players progress through the game, they can rock out to scores of Aerosmith's greatest hits, as well as songs from celebrated artists that the band has either performed with or has been inspired by in some way. Venues from historical moments during the band's illustrious career offer the experience of \"sweet emotion\" and further capture the essence of the band's rise to fame.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KyTxyNBLnXA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay (Love in an Elevator)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WxAxg754vnM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay (Walk This Way))",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dfI5M-VjU9s"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944963-guitar-hero-aerosmith/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Guitar-Hero-Aerosmith/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/guitar-hero-aerosmith/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/guitar-hero-aerosmith"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wikihero",
				"url":"http://guitarhero.wikia.com/wiki/Guitar_Hero:_Aerosmith"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":269,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eurocom"],
			"synopsis":"The Official Video Game of the Beijing 2008 Olympic Games, this multi-console game features a wide variety of Olympic sports - 35 events from the Beijing 2008 Olympic Games! The game also boasts online gameplay so that for the very first time, fans of the Olympic Games will be able to experience the thrill of competing against other gamers across the globe in the world's greatest sporting event. Gamers can experience the thrill of competing in many of the official venues ranging from the famous Beijing National Stadium (the \"Bird Nest\") to the National Aquatics Center (the \"Water Cube\").",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8XblaI5sCac"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PR_lERp1NYY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Beijing-2008/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/beijing-2008/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/beijing-2008---the-official-video-game-of-the-olympic-games"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":270,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Epic Games"],
			"synopsis":"The Necris invasion has begun, and your clan was one of the first to be slaughtered. Head to the front lines and join this Epic battle to defend humanity while taking your revenge. Unreal Tournament 3 marks the return of the premiere tournament-style first-person shooter. Unreal Tournament 3 unleashes the full power of Unreal Engine 3, taking graphics, gameplay, and challenge to a whole new level. Players engage in intense and hyper-real battles with other human players online or against incredibly realistic Unreal artificial intelligence. Over two dozen weapons and vehicles have been upgraded and enhanced for maximum killing potential. Take on all comers in a variety of game modes including Deathmatch, Team Deathmatch, Capture the Flag, an all-new Warfare mode and more.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q0R5eXZ0DMM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-O2dG6yIhDA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Deck",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=awhAeqi-UsU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Facing Worlds",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1Dm1n0G8-9I"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928301-unreal-tournament-iii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Unreal-Tournament-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/unreal-tournament-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/unreal-tournament-iii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Unreal Wiki",
				"url":"http://unreal.wikia.com/wiki/Unreal_Tournament_3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":271,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Firaxis"],
			"synopsis":"Sid Meier's Civilization Revolution offers players a chance to experience the epic empire-building world of Civilization in an all new accessible, visually immersive, and action-packed world specifically designed for the console and handheld gamer. There are 16 civilizations to master and lead to victory, with an array of famous historical leaders to play as or compete against, and accessible maps and streamlined time scale for quicker games, intense combat, and constant action.<br><br>In multiplayer mode, players will compete for world conquest and glory among their peers as they battle in teams, head-to-head or epic free-for-all matches. In addition, auto-matching, ranked games, leaderboards, achievements, downloadable extra content and integrated video and voice chat make the online play more versatile and fun than any previous version of Civilization and will allow players to see where they stand against the competition. Finally, the position of ruler of the world can be settled online.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1ddLcyliggg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WZvfyiIu5Vc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/941684-sid-meiers-civilization-revolution/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Civilization-Revolution/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sid-meiers-civilization-revolution/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sid-meiers-civilization-revolution"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Civilization Wiki",
				"url":"http://civilization.wikia.com/wiki/Civilization_Revolution"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":272,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"NCAA Football 09 brings all-new football action to the Xbox 360. The game unveils the Break Away Animation Engine, which allows gamers to break in and out of moves giving the user more direct control as well as instant influence and responsiveness on the field. NCAA Football 09 also focuses on wide-open collegiate style gameplay featuring unique animations that you will only find on college football Saturdays.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H9SbOEW3lVE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1u2tXFrqVOU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944961-ncaa-football-09/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NCAA-Football-09/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ncaa-football-09/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ncaa-football-09"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":273,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Red Tribe", "Wicked Witch Software"],
			"synopsis":"Unleash your inner chimp! Play as both Ham the Third and Luna with your Space Chimp crew to free the imprisoned aliens on the planet Malgor. You must use your brains and acrobatic brawn to survive thick alien jungles, escape dry and desolate canyons, and well-guarded dungeons in order to defeat the evil Zartog and find your way home.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p6JS2InafMw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Space-Chimps/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/space-chimps/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/space-chimps"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":274,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Project Soul"],
			"synopsis":"From Namco's acclaimed weapon-based fighting series comes the fourth chapter in the series (and first for Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3). Delivering new gameplay modes, characters and enhanced features with unprecedented 3D modeling and animation, Soulcalibur IV aims to be a definitive fighting game experience.<br><br>Set to finally reveal the origins of the Soulcalibur saga, the game features both new and familiar faces from across the galaxy who seeks the rival swords for their own goals. Continuing the tradition of breaking new boundaries, legendary Star Wars icons Darth Vader and Yoda invade the Soulcalibur universe to add a new layer of depth, challenge, and mystery. Also for the first time in the franchise, customized characters or original favorites can be taken online to challenge others for the top spot of this timeless series.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable Music: Complete Set",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/31",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Pack contains all the original music from the original SoulCalibur (1999)."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Customization Equipment 1",
				"releaseDate":"2008/07/31",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Equipment from previous Soul Calibur games."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Customization Equipment 2",
				"releaseDate":"2008/09/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Trick or treat with the Halloween equipment set. Frighten your opponent away by turning your characters into a scary character by combining items from this set with the numerous equipments which can be acquired in game. This equipment can be used for both female and male characters."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Additional Character: Darth Vader",
				"releaseDate":"2008/10/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Play as Darth Vader who has descended into the SoulCalibur universe. Experience the true power of the mighty Dark Lord. Darth Vader was previously exclusive to PS3 copies of the game."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Customization Equipment 3",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Christmas is here with the Santa equipment set. Turn Santa sexy by picking Ivy or Amy. This equipment can be used for both female and male characters."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oHe-AxsB450"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-E3XeU32qWw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/940048-soulcalibur-iv/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Soulcalibur-IV/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/soulcalibur-iv/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/soulcalibur-iv"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"SoulCalibur Wiki",
				"url":"http://soulcalibur.wikia.com/wiki/Soul_Calibur_IV"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":275,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Idea Factory"],
			"synopsis":"Magic Era: 996. The ten kingdoms of the land, seizing the opportunity provided by Overlord Janus's death, are attempting to unify the continent under their own banners. This is the beginning of the Great Neverland War. In order to bolster their defenses, kingdoms have begun hiring mercenary units. As new members of the Norius Mercenaries, you and your friend Diaz are eager to prove yourselves. When the squad's commander Judo is mortally wounded in battle, the mantle of leadership is entrusted to you, and so the adventure begins...",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GM5CF9G5ug8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IXSQC_rekUA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930013-spectral-force-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Spectral-Force-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/spectral-force-3-us/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/spectral-force-3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":276,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["49Games"],
			"synopsis":"Summer Athletics brings sports right into your living room: exciting competitions in over 25 of the most popular summer sports disciplines, such as sprinting, hurdles, cycling, archery, javelin, hammer throw, and swimming, will provide long-lasting fun. Four different difficulty levels in two gaming modes, arcade and career, will provide sporting challenges for both experienced and casual gamers alike. The game will feature a character editor, lifelike 3D graphics, realistic athlete animations, and an impressive stadium atmosphere with the flair of live competitions.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nXMQVE8R9Wc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j1Vec1pczxs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Summer-Athletics/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/summer-athletics/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/summer-athletics-the-ultimate-challenge"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":277,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"Celebrating 20 years of innovation and counting, Madden NFL 09 aims to deliver its most complete NFL football package ever. Whether you're a seasoned veteran or picking up the game for the first time, players of all skill levels will enjoy a unique, yet challenging experience with the innovative Adaptive Difficulty Engine, which tailors the game to match your playing style. Instantly improve your game with the all-new virtual Training Center or incorporate feedback with EA SPORTS BackTrack, allowing you to learn from your mistakes on the fly. For passionate Madden NFL fans, this year's iteration will take authenticity and depth of gameplay to an entirely new level with more than 85 new features and enhancements.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5bzcvRk67_4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=myLDskML1OA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945504-madden-nfl-09/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Madden-NFL-09/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/madden-nfl-09/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/madden-nfl-09"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":278,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Namco"],
			"synopsis":"Making the most of the power of Xbox 360, Smash Court Tennis 3 boasts enhanced graphics including improved player animations, realistic shadows, skin shaders and High Dynamic Range rendering which combine to deliver a greater level of realism and immersion for the player. A host of customizing options allows players to choose rackets, shoes, hairstyles, skin tone and clothing to create their own unique star of the courts. New gameplay includes a system which lets all players, no matter what their skill level, benefit quickly from the powerful shots and finely honed skills of the star players.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fUI9Cy1pM2E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BQ16T68OQqE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Smash-Court-Tennis-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Smash-Court-Tennis-3/walkthrough.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/smash-court-tennis-3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":279,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Silicon Knights"],
			"synopsis":"As the Cybernetic God Baldur, players are thrust into the midst of an ongoing battle that threatens the existence of mankind. An ancient machine presence has forced the God's hand. In the first of a three part trilogy, Baldur is charged with defending mankind from an onslaught of monstrous war machines bent on eradication of human life. Players are treated to a nonstop barrage of action powered by the seamless integration of melee and ranged firearms combat. Battles unfold in awesome scale as players engage in spectacular battles with vast numbers of enemies.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vb4bOeaQCeY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cl7Qk4RJFLs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2S5Rqmi7BY0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928546-too-human/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Too-Human/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/too-human/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/too-human"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Too Human Wiki",
				"url":"http://toohuman.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":280,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Synetic"],
			"synopsis":"Various exciting cases await the player as part of the \"Cobra 11\" police force. Solving them requires several diverse missions to be successfully completed: Be it helicopter chases,jumps across moving trains or reconnaissance runs in tanks.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-0OHjDJ34YE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VXFj46juroQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Crash-Time/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/alarm-fur-cobra-11-crash-time/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/crash-time-autobahn-pursuit"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":281,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bandai Namco Games"],
			"synopsis":"The debut of the Tales series on the Xbox 360, Tales of Vesperia is set in a world reliant on a mysterious ancient technology known as Blastia. The game follows former knight Yuri as he delves into a shadowy plot to use these magical devices to control civilization, or destroy it.<br><br>The game makes significant additions to the series' trademark real-time combat system, allowing players to do battle in massive battlefields and learn new special attacks that are tied to individual weapons. New finishing blows allow players to take down enemies in a single hit with correctly timed button combinations, while mission-based battles increase the variety of each encounter as players gain unique items by fulfilling various battle objectives. Players can also use materials collected by successfully executing finishing moves to craft rare and unique equipment for their characters.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KcPGb9Ao_Sw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MOpT98qll9M"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945075-tales-of-vesperia/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tales-of-Vesperia/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tales-of-vesperia/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tales-of-vesperia"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Aselia: The Tales Wiki",
				"url":"http://aselia.wikia.com/wiki/Tales_of_Vesperia"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":282,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"Tiger Woods' coach is now your coach! In Tiger Woods PGA TOUR 09, Hank Haney will be there from the start to assess your skills, help you tune your clubs and give you feedback after every round as you attempt to climb the leaderboards and win the FedExCup. Tiger Woods PGA TOUR 09 is a highly adaptable game that allows both the rookie and the seasoned veteran the ability to have a personalized and customized day on the links. This year's game also features enhancements to the online experience with a highly integrated EA Sports GamerNet experience as well as an all-new online engine powering Simultaneous Play.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PHKVeCOZXbE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hxHTWW8SKOw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945511-tiger-woods-pga-tour-09/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tiger-Woods-PGA-TOUR-09/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tiger-woods-pga-tour-09/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tiger-woods-pga-tour-09"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":283,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Pandemic Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Mercenaries 2: World in Flames is an explosive open-world action game set in a massive, highly reactive, war-torn world. A power-hungry tyrant messes with Venezuela's oil supply, sparking an invasion that turns the country into a warzone. But for you, international crisis is all upside: You are a mercenary, and you profit from chaos. These are world powers with deep pockets, deep grudges, and enough arms and ammo to start World War III. This is your kind of environment.<br><br>Mercenaries 2 features the latest and most dangerous in civilian and military tech, everything from shiny new sports cars, to the future-tech satellite-guided bunker-busting mini-nuke. Tanks, APCs, boats, luxury automobiles - you name it, you can have it delivered to you in real time. And if you run out of cash you can always 'acquire' the gear you need in the field. You are not a soldier. You don't have to play by anyone's rules. You have your own code: you will fulfill the terms of the contract, no matter what.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Blow It Up Again Content Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/03",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Blow it up again with four new explosive missions and new playable characters!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ggjtBkN2sis"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1WWynIVjWA4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Spot",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NcJyCdbC08c"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932882-mercenaries-2-world-in-flames/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mercenaries-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mercenaries-2-world-in-flames/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mercenaries-2-world-in-flames"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Mercenaries Wiki",
				"url":"http://mercenaries.wikia.com/wiki/Mercenaries_2:_World_in_Flames"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":284,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tri-Ace"],
			"synopsis":"Deep in a forest, in one of the Order's prisons, a young boy named Capell was being held captive. His captors called him the \"Liberator\", though he had no clue as to what they meant. On the third day of his imprisonment, he was rescued by a spirited young woman named Aya. She was a member of a small band of brave warriors who had gathered under the banner of Sigmund the Liberator to free the world from the iron grip of the Order. Upon meeting Sigmund, he was surprised to find a man who shared his very face and appearance. This meeting would change Capell's life forever and shake the foundation of the world itself.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DclTL8Qi5HY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tlx333U9Arg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935661-infinite-undiscovery/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Infinite-Undiscovery/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/infinite-undiscovery/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/infinite-undiscovery"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Infinte Undiscovery Wiki",
				"url":"http://infiniteundiscovery.wikia.com/wiki/Infinite_Undiscovery_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":285,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Fun Labs"],
			"synopsis":"Developed by Fun Labs in close collaboration with Rapala, the world's largest manufacturer of fishing lures and #1 fishing brand in the world, the title supplies heart-pounding fishing action in over 20 tournament events.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pZ7rOIAMv-8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4EB1UaxhRyQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rapala-Fishing-Frenzy/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rapala-fishing-frenzy/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rapala-fishing-frenzy-2009"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":286,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rare"],
			"synopsis":"The original Rare Ltd. team behind Viva Pinata has reunited to bring gamers Viva Pinata: Trouble in Paradise, the newest pinata adventure that invites gamers to return to magical Pi&ntildeata Island. Unfortunately, not all is well on the island, as Professor Pester along with his gang of Ruffians have wiped out Pinata Central's computer records, which poses a threat to parties everywhere. To help Pinata Central, players must gradually rebuild the computer database by sending Pi&ntildeatas at full candiosity to parties all around the world. While thwarting Professor Pester's evil plot, players still build and maintain pi&ntildeata gardens - using their creativity and imagination to attract, trap, protect, train and manage more than 100 different Pi&ntildeata species.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ff0JSVXuUrE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wivB6hwQ8oA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/946126-viva-pinata-trouble-in-paradise/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Viva-Pinata-Trouble-In-Paradise/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/viva-pinata-trouble-in-paradise/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/viva-pinata-trouble-in-paradise"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Viva Pinata Wiki",
				"url":"http://vivapinata.wikia.com/wiki/Viva_Pi%C3%B1ata:_Trouble_in_Paradise"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Pinata Island",
				"url":"http://pinataisland.info/viva/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":287,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Black Hole Entertainment", "Cinegi Productions"],
			"synopsis":"This Xbox 360 version of the hit strategy game includes the original content from Warhammer: Mark of Chaos and its Battle March expansion as well as all-new features, intuitive control schemes and support for online play via the Xbox LIVE online entertainment network.<br><br>Thrusting players into Games Workshop's renowned fantasy world, players will be able to control six unique armies - the Empire, Chaos, Skaven, High Elves as well as the all-new Dark Elf and Orcs & Goblins forces - as they battle for supremacy in a world torn apart by constant warfare. The individual units of each army can be customized in great detail, allowing players to put their own mark on their fighting force and strike fear into their opponents with terrifying combinations of weaponry and armor. Players can also control Heroes and Champions for each army, high-powered units that gain new abilities as they tear through the opposition. On Xbox LIVE, up to four players can engage in massive multi-army clashes in head-to-head and team-based modes of play.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jrQShb5T1BM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y-FUFqQOXe0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h_Q8sf1Qa60"
			},
			{
				"type":"Campaign Gameplay (PC)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KLSNdn9SOFU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Warhammer-Battle-March/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/warhammer-battle-march"
			},
			{
				"type":"Warhammer Wiki",
				"site":"Lexicanum",
				"url":"http://whfb.lexicanum.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			},
			{
				"type":"Warhammer Wiki",
				"site":"Warhammer Wiki",
				"url":"http://warhammerfb.wikia.com/wiki/Warhammer_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":288,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"An arcade-styled boxing game developed by EA Canada. Created by the same team that developed the award-winning Fight Night Round 3, FaceBreaker offers irreverent fun, immersive gameplay and eye-popping stylized graphics. In this in-your-face, arcade world full of ego-wielding characters, each boxer comes to life with unique attributes and distinct personal style, including Romeo, a Latin lover known for his pelvic thrusts, and Molotov, an oversized Russian demolitions expert with a penchant for fighting dirty.<br><br>Laugh out loud as you pummel your opponent with a barrage of blows to the face and watch in satisfaction as your progress is illustrated by real-time facial deformation. With haymakers, face shots and body blows, wait for the right moment to drop a super punch to make your presence known. Taunt your adversaries and flaunt your talent, by tying one hand behind your back to add ultimate humiliation to your bout. In FaceBreaker, it just feels good to rearrange your opponent's face.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q8YByKTr-CQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1eH4_hdZMv4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hyFhsqLmmKs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/FaceBreaker/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/facebreaker/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/facebreaker"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":289,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"NFL Head Coach 09 is a unique NFL experience that gives gamers the power to make decisions that define their career and ultimately the fate of their franchise as a head coach in the NFL. The game provides a complete NFL experience, offering a variety of different ways to control an NFL franchise, on and off the field, in-season and off-season. With strategic game planning features, NFL Head Coach 09 places gamers in the coach's seat by allowing gamers to comprehensively scout the opponent, build playbooks, and develop a team that will adapt to the philosophy and system of an NFL franchise. The sideline is your playing field in NFL Head Coach 09 - gamers can make adjustments to plays and game strategies in an instant. The outcome of every game depends on game-time decisions made on the sideline. Success depends on proper preparation and knowledge of the opposing teams' strategies, as well as expert and timely play calling.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qY3ynySYTM4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1XyyWMwljms"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oY-Zcay1Uxo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945118-nfl-head-coach-09/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NFL-Head-Coach-09/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nfl-head-coach-09/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nfl-head-coach-09"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":290,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"Do you long for the days when hockey video games didn't require an engineering degree to master? 2K Sports has listened to the masses by bringing the fun back to hockey video games with an intuitive control scheme and hard-hitting action. Developed by award-winning Visual Concepts studios, NHL 2K9 brings a the NHL experience to life with an in-game presentation system, as well as fresh player animations and controls that fans will enjoy from the moment they play their first game, until well after they become a seasoned veteran. Further adding to an unmatched level of fun and celebrating the NHL's uniqueness are a Zamboni mini-game, playoff beards, a new fighting engine and more!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6gaMZLme5p0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8ZJbZwbAJ4A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NHL-2K9/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nhl-2k9/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nhl-2k9"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":291,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"EA aims to light the lamp again with the '09 edition of its annual hockey game. NHL 09 brings Be A Pro to the ice, allowing gamers to step on the ice as themselves through a dynamic camera angle. In Be A Pro Mode you will earn your own hockey card as you progress from the AHL to the NHL.<br><br>The Skill Stick system from the past two NHL games evolves yet again in NHL 09 to bring precision control to the defensive side of the puck. The all new defensive skill stick gives you 360 degrees control over your stick's movement. Block passing lanes, poke check more effectively and for the first time ever, lift an opponent's stick to prevent a shot.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dnftVKYAGlE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=85LJjeD5wlE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/946759-nhl-09/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NHL-09/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nhl-09/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nhl-09"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":292,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Midway Studios - Los Angeles"],
			"synopsis":"Spike TV's innovative six-sided wrestling ring is now yours to step into with this game based on the TNA Wrestling league. This is the exclusive Total Nonstop Action Wrestling game based on the top-rated weekly television show! Enter the signature six-sided ring and prepare for all of the high-flying slams and takedowns with more than 20 TNA stars like Kurt Angle, AJ Styles and Samoa Joe. Or, build the ultimate wrestler with custom appearance, moves and style to deliver the hard-hitting, adrenaline pumping action seen only in TNA Wrestling!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a1k4TNEBGTY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pJifUAXU4Q4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933905-tna-impact/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/TNA-iMPACT/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tna-impact/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tna-impact!"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":293,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Atlus"],
			"synopsis":"When war broke out between the world's two main superpowers, the Guylos Empire and the Republic of Helic, the effects rippled across the globe, dragging other nations into the fight. Two such nations were Maroll and Jamil.<br><br>During the war, Maroll's attacks on the neighboring Jamil were devastating, and even a decade after the war had ended, Jamil's economy and infrastructure hadn't fully recovered. Animosity, paranoia, and mutual mistrust between the two nations hindered their ability to find a common ground and complete their peace talks. For ten long years, the two nations found themselves in the middle of a cold war.<br><br>After a mysterious explosion at one of Maroll's military bases, two covert ops teams are sent into Jamil territory, their exact mission details never disclosed. Somehow, the events of the present are inextricably linked to the past-to the final days of the war, ten years ago...",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Paint Scheme Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/09/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Six new paint schemes"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iJVvmQVnpNw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cla-KVYvdtc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938315-zoids-assault/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Zoids-Assault/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/zoids-assault/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/zoids-assault"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Zoids Wiki",
				"url":"http://zoids.wikia.com/wiki/Zoids_Assault"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":294,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"With the original Rock Band title providing millions of players with a new way to interact with the music and artists they love, Rock Band 2 builds upon its core band foundation to offer an unparalleled, deeper, dynamic gameplay experience.<br><br>Rock Band 2 is set to revolutionize music gaming with the ability to export most of the songs from the original Rock Band disc, Online World Tour, daily Battle-Of-The Band Tournaments, Auto-Calibration to eliminate TV lag, wireless drums, quieter, velocity sensitive drum heads, support for up to three cymbals (sold separately), advanced voice detection technology, No Fail Mode, and a real Drum Trainer. Rock Band 2's massive list of innovations also includes the ability to export your in-game band avatar to the internet and order custom Rock Band merchandise including apparel and figures.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable tracks",
				"releaseDate":"2008/09/14",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"More than 1000 tracks available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A52QGpGnB8k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JSyrFzkN0BM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Welcome Home",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uRiJWBBqxNg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - That's What You Get",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cd43SN_qjIs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/949926-rock-band-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rock-Band-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rock-band-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rock-band-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Rock Band Wiki",
				"url":"http://rockband.wikia.com/wiki/Rock_Band_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":295,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FromSoftware"],
			"synopsis":"In the distant future, massive urban development and pollution have critically damaged the planet. There is widespread fear that the end of the world is approaching. The League corporations, a military superpower, control the planet's infrastructure and have forced most of the world's population to live in huge aerial communities, called Cradles, to avoid the contamination. The ORCA, a rebel resistance still residing on the surface of the polluted planet, have amassed a formidable arsenal and are mobilizing to attack The League's bases to put an end to their iron grip on the planet. As a mercenary armed with cutting-edge military robot technology, choose your side and defeat the other factions by harnessing the power of the deadliest and most gigantic weapons ever created by mankind.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=53sK4vLkSIk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sy00gEDJJGI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bzEojTCFO1I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JC4Y6HztqVY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944262-armored-core-for-answer/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Armored-Core-for-Answer/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/armored-core-for-answer-ntscj/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/armored-core-for-answer"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Armored Core Wiki",
				"url":"http://armoredcore.wikia.com/wiki/Armored_Core:_For_Answer"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":296,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["ARC System Works"],
			"synopsis":"There was once a time when the world was engulfed in darkness. Mankind fought six battles to save their world, but lost every single one. All hope was lost for humanity, but one day the darkness was finally driven back by the swords of four heroes. Light returned to the world, and with it came peace and serenity. The world was then divided into two major countries: The Magic Kingdom and the Steam Empire. The people prospered like never before. But in recent months, rumors spread among the people that the darkness was returning. However, fate has once again brought together warriors from all over the world. Some fight in the relentless pursuit of justice. Some fight due to their conviction and faith.<br><br>Developed by ARC System Works, creators of the highly popular Guilty Gear series, Battle Fantasia utilizes RPG-stylish elements and blends them with high level gameplay. Players will also be able to pick between 12 beautifully illustrated characters by Emiko Iwasaki, and battle it out in front of gorgeous high-definition 3D environments.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D4hQSYlScV8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cJg4VK5z2dU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945013-battle-fantasia/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Battle-Fantasia/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/battle-fantasia/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/battle-fantasia"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":297,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Black Rock Studio"],
			"synopsis":"Designed by the speed fanatics who have brought gamers such hits as ATV Off-Road Fury and MotoGP, Pure is the new racing phenomenon that gives gamers the raw thrills of off-road, extreme quad racing. Expect big air, ballsy tricks, mass-crush online play for up to 16 racers, and no end to the mayhem.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LzBwMIl9e48"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZYVPV2TV_Rw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RAYzRfgNJ-E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ybKctf4viNY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944936-pure/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pure/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pure/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pure"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":298,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["LucasArts"],
			"synopsis":"This entry in the Star Wars saga casts players as Darth Vader's \"Secret Apprentice\", unveiling new revelations about the Star Wars galaxy. The expansive story, created under direction from George Lucas, is set during the largely unexplored era between Star Wars: Episode III Revenge of the Sith and Star Wars: Episode IV A New Hope. In it, players will assist the iconic villain in his quest to rid the universe of Jedi - and face decisions that could change the course of their destiny. As its name implies, The Force Unleashed completely re-imagines the scope and scale of the Force by taking full advantage of newly developed technologies only possible on next-gen consoles that will be seen and experienced for the first time anywhere in videogaming.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Character Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Now that you've unleashed the force you can download 7 brand new characters to the make the experience even more memorable! Play as characters such as Jedi Knight Anakin Skywalker, Jedi Knight Obi-Wan Kenobi, Jedi Knight Luke Skywalker, Imperial Commando, Darth Sion, Ki-Adi-Mundi and Kit Fisto. Also you'll get 3 all new Secret Apprentice costumes including Hooded Combat Gear, General Starkiller and Sith Assassin."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Character Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/04",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"In this pack you get seven new characters including Republic Trooper, Tatooine Luke, Ben Kenobi, Jedi Master Plo Koon, Count Dooku, Jango Fett, and C-3P0. You'll also get three new Secret Apprentice costumes including Utility Combat Suit Apprentice, Animated-style Apprentice, and Spirit Apprentice."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Jedi Temple Mission Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/04",
				"achievements":220,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The Apprentice Mission Pack contains an entirely new single-player mission set in the Jedi Temple on the planet Coruscant. In this mission Darth Vader's Secret Apprentice turns to the Jedi Temple to learn more about his father, and while searching through the rubble of the destroyed building he must confront his inner demons... Download this mission pack and you'll also get 6 brand new characters and 3 all new Secret Apprentice costumes.<br><br>The skins include Temple Exploration Gear, Cybernetic Reconstruction, Darth Maul, Qui-Gon Jinn, Mace Windu, Dark Stalker, Sith Training Gear, Lightsaber Training Droid, Combat Training Droid. The mission is a separate campaign. New players can access it directly and old players won't be able to use their save. Jedi Temple also adds 7 achievements and 220 points."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Tatooine Mission Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/27",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Artoo-detoo (R2D2) and See-Threepio (C3PO) have crash-landed on Tatooine carrying important data that the Apprentice (\"Starkiller\") must intercept. After fighting Jawas, Tusken Raiders, and Jabba the Hutt's minions, Starkiller must battle the famed bounty hunter Boba Fett before engaging in a final confrontation with one of the galaxy's last remaining Jedi!"
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Hoth Mission Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/23",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The search for Luke Skywalker leads the Apprentice (\"Starkiller\") to the Rebel's hidden base on the ice planet, Hoth. Under orders by the Emperor to turn Skywalker to the dark side, Starkiller must infiltrate Echo Base and fight through Rebel forces and enthrall skywalker to the dark side or the rebels will defeat the empire."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mhO2t9I_Olo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QFejspmzS5k"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933156-star-wars-the-force-unleashed/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Star-Wars-the-Force-Unleashed/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/star-wars-the-force-unleashed/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/star-wars-the-force-unleashed"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Force Unleashed Wiki",
				"url":"http://theforceunleashed.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wookieepedia - The Star Wars Wiki",
				"url":"http://starwars.wikia.com/wiki/Star_Wars:_The_Force_Unleashed"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":299,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["2XL Games"],
			"synopsis":"In Baja, players will conquer more than 100 square miles of the toughest terrain Mother Nature has to offer, including the steepest mountains, thickest mud and deepest canyons ever created. With more than 40 vehicles in eight classes, including Trophy Trucks, 4x4s and buggies, Baja features a full array of upgradeable options with hundreds of authentic parts that affect each vehicle's performance. Players will put their off-road machines to the test in near-vertical Hill Climb challenges, head-to-head Open Class races, circuit races and the ultimate off-road endurance challenge: the Baja. Baja's open worlds extend thousands of miles across all landscapes in races that can last up to four hours. The game's revolutionary vehicle physics deliver unprecedented life-like handling, and a support management system allows gamers to monitor and repair realistic vehicle damage as fenders fly, tires are blown, suspension is stressed and engines overheat. Baja supports four-player split screen multiplayer capability, 12-player online and LAN as well as multiple-screen panoramic view.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dHcsAb5P-mA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pAYreLSMbQY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Baja-Edge-of-Control/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/baja/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/baja-edge-of-control"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":300,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gearbox Software"],
			"synopsis":"Gearbox's third entry in the venerable Brothers In Arms series heads up to the front as with the first of the series for next-generation systems. Delivering on the franchise's compelling story, unrivaled authenticity and intense squad-based action, Brothers In Arms Hell's Highway drops you into Operation Market-Garden, the largest airborne operation of World War II. Lead Matt Baker, Joe Hartsock and the rest of the 101st Airborne Division as they fight to open \"Hell's Highway\" in a daring bid for a quick end to the war. The game , makes use of the new Unreal Engine 3 technology for its delivery of the war experience, with new cutting-edge gameplay features and a completely redesigned online component.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IFhDW3BYyXk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bf3qglfftWU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930277-brothers-in-arms-hells-highway/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Brothers-in-Arms-Hells-Highway/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/brothers-in-arms-hells-highway/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/brothers-in-arms-hells-highway"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Brothers in Arms Wiki",
				"url":"http://brothersinarms.wikia.com/wiki/Brothers_in_Arms:_Hell's_Highway"
			}]
		}
	}]
}