{
	"catalog": [
	{
		"id":1201,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Artech Studios"],
			"synopsis":"This colorful and energetic family-friendly game is exploding with electrifying mini-games that keep your entire body moving fast -- ducking, dodging, catching and balancing whatever might be thrown at you! From juggling soccer balls to dodging blocks to controlling robots to hacky sacking, Motion Explosion's 12 games pack in ten levels each, mixing it up along the way with additional gameplay elements like inverse controls, faster pace and new tricks to make you think quick on your feet and keep your body moving!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eI1auEF8FUg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j_PsKrcOmkA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XuSC1XYR-Ww"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XaRtrn3KuJc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lZjvvASXGZw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Motion-Explosion/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/motion-explosion!"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1202,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Behaviour"],
			"synopsis":"Based on ABC's popular TV game show, the game gives players greater control as they test their agility, endurance and abilities.<br><br>For the first time ever, players can design, play, and share their very own chaotic courses with the all new Course Creator. Choose from easy, medium or hard obstacles and try to beat your course, and then share the unique code with your friends and family! In addition, compete as either fan-favorite or all-new characters in over-the-top new courses like Prehistoric Panic and Wipeouts Ahoy with all new themed obstacles. You can also challenge your friends to reign supreme in side-by-side or team local multiplayer.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WUAZ619h1t8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=909Ly22C6k4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wipeout-Create-and-Crash/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1203,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["High Voltage Software"],
			"synopsis":"Kids can move, groove and learn to improve as they dance along with their Nickelodeon friends -- Dora, Diego, The Backyardigans, and The Fresh Beat Band. This new dance game is designed to help kids stay physically active as they twist, shake, and shout to original Nickelodeon songs and popular favorites too! Kids can really get their heart pumping with the super cool fitness feature for more heart healthy fun with the Nickelodeon gang!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9U5JSh1B3oc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NiIckXJbfSE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Nickelodeon-Dance/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nickelodeon-dance/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1204,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["High Voltage Software"],
			"synopsis":"The dance party's back and bigger than ever in Nickelodeon Dance 2! Gamers of all ages can dance, sing and workout with new Nickelodeon characters, innovative game modes, original dances, and energetic songs from the network's hit TV shows.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sXZKgnTB654"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eKt-HOwaXB4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Nickelodeon-Dance-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nickelodeon-dance-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nickelodeon-dance-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1205,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sumo Digital"],
			"synopsis":"Get fitter, faster and stronger with Nike+ Kinect Training, a personalized training experience built from the ground up with athletic expertise and inspiration from Nike coupled with powerful and precise technology from Kinect for Xbox 360. Nike+ Kinect Training brings world-class Nike training directly into the home to help individuals meet their fitness goals and reach their personal best.<br><br>Through the magic of Kinect, Nike+ Kinect Training can see how the body moves, assess physical strength and athleticism, identify areas for improvement, and create a personalized workout plan tailored to each person. With real-time feedback to make sure positions and movements are correct and a customized program that evolves over time, Nike+ Kinect Training is for everybody, whether a professional athlete, an everyday athlete or someone just getting started. With fitness assessments every four weeks and the ability to work out with friends over Xbox LIVE and tap into the Nike+ community, Nike+ Kinect Training helps athletes stay motivated every step of the way.1 Take training even further by competing in challenges, sending encouragement to friends and keeping workouts on track with a mobile companion app.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Upper Body and Core Workout",
				"releaseDate":"2012/12/26",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The Fast and Focused: Upper Body and Core pack is a 15-minute workout with personalized drills to target your upper body while burning calories. Your Nike trainer will select a mix of strengthening and toning drills combined with fun, intense cardio to help you reach your goals. This pack integrates with your ongoing Nike+ Kinect Training program, adding on new, difficult drills as you progress."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Lower Body and Core Workout",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/15",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The Fast and Focused: Lower Body and Core pack is a 15-minute workout with personalized drills to target your lower body while burning calories. Your Nike trainer will select a mix of strengthening and toning drills combined with fun, intense cardio to help you reach your goals. This pack integrates with your ongoing Nike+ Kinect Training program, adding on new, difficult drills as you progress."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=301wlnaQRrs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D5glY_K8u14"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Nike-Plus-Kinect-Training/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Nike-Plus-Kinect-Training/walkthrough.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nike+-kinect-training"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1206,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Griptonite Games"],
			"synopsis":"Save the world from Dolphin Domination! Dr. Blowhole is out to conquer the world and is using the Penguins to achieve that goal -- whether they realize it or not. Jump into an all-new, raucous experience with 3 episodes and over 12 exciting levels as the Penguins embark on adventures in, under and outside of the zoo culminating in the grand finale in Dr. Blowhole's Liar. Only you and zany Team Penguin can stop Dr. Blowhole from taking over the world!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M9QjfDXKLCw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b45SaoLRMPQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Penguins-of-Madagascar/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-penguins-of-madagascar/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Madagascar Wiki",
				"url":"http://madagascar.wikia.com/wiki/Dr._Blowhole_Returns-Again_(Game)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1207,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Longtail Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Leveraging the Kinect technology, PowerUp Heroes is the ultimate super power-infused full-body fighting game. Players control each move in combat by using their entire body to launch projectiles, dodge strikes and counter deadly attacks. Players can unleash super assaults on their opponents in a two-player cosmic showdown online. Additional modes include local two-player versus and four-player tournament.<br><br>Players use their unique Xbox 360 avatars to create custom playable superheroes in the game and prepare their avatar for battle by infusing their super suit with deadly powers and special abilities. After the player's character destroys an enemy in battle, they will strip them of the super suit and wield their power for their next battle. There are 20 super suits to collect including the mighty Necromancer suit which allows the player to control a horde of skeletons, and the Mentalist suit that gives the player the ability to break into their enemy's mind.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CfBmUjNjdj8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YDRHh_yvUnE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4Xv1NwAvqrg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/PowerUp-Heroes/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/powerup-heroes/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/powerup-heroes"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1208,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Digifloyd"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the action-packed TV show, Power Rangers Samurai follows a new generation of five Rangers who must master the ancient Samurai Symbols of Power, which give them control over the elements of Fire, Water, Sky, Forest and Earth. Under the guidance of their all-knowing Samurai mentor, Ji, and with the aid of their devoted animal Zords (Lion, Dragon, Ape, Turtle and Bear), they battle to save Earth from the dark forces of the Netherworld led by the evil Master Xandred.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1vXrwiWX2LQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WJDsc5WgJ4k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Power-Rangers-Super-Samurai/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/power-rangers-super-samurai"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Ranger Wiki",
				"url":"http://powerrangers.wikia.com/wiki/Power_Rangers_Super_Samurai"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1209,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Game Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Step into the boots of Puss In Boots, star of the upcoming film from DreamWorks Animation, and use your sword fighting moves and sly skills to become the legendary hero!<br><br>Master the style and charm of Puss in Boots in an engaging swashbuckling experience. Duel banditos with style and flair, use cat-like sneaking skills to fool your foes, and team with characters from the film to catch the Golden Goose... Plus, strum your guitar to serenade the se&ntilde;oritas along the way!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CEOW2LaRx-I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e5vRpxNrn_M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Puss-In-Boots/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/puss-in-boots/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dreamworks-puss-in-boots"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1210,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Now Pro"],
			"synopsis":"Rapala for Kinect features an arcade style fishing experience controlled completely by a player's movements with intuitive commands that creates a sport fishing title never before seen on Kinect for Xbox 360.<br><br>One to four players will compete in exciting contests in a race against the clock. Traveling between fishing hot spots will boil down to fast paced, motor mashing player versus player races. A rapid fire, forty five seconds from cast to catch, ensures fun, quick and intense angling action. Players will drop in and out of the action with barely a pause.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TuvOyE3tvhQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=THxWTTNaLRA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rapala-for-Kinect/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rapala-for-Kinect/walkthrough.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1211,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montpellier"],
			"synopsis":"The Rabbids have already invaded the past, the world, your TV, and the moon. They've invaded our daily lives for years, and you've never really considered them to be a serious threat. You just never imagined that they could even possibly be ... real. Well, you were wrong!! They really do exist!<br><br>With Raving Rabbids: Alive & Kicking and Kinect, you will see them with your own eyes... Rabbids will come to life right in your own home, coming out from the floor and interacting with you through ridiculous and humorous physical challenges. Go face to face against the Rabbids with all your friends by jumping, rolling, twisting, contorting, slapping, and dancing in the the craziest and most insane moves and situations ever imagined in the series through tons of new mini-games. Watch as the Rabbids mess with your life in front of your very eyes!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SdQKGY-qt2c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iPPX8K_QrN4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Raving-Rabbids-Alive-and-Kicking/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/raving-rabbids-alive-kicking"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1212,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SEGA"],
			"synopsis":"Rise of Nightmares offers a spine-tingling horror experience which uses the innovative new controls of Kinect to give players new encounters filled with fearful anticipation and terror. Using their whole body the player will experience fear and tension as never before in this first person horror adventure.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rA-4xKxgjoM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_Pz_g3gTfo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qojp8MgnSgk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u2EibS_vXOQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X-bSIYHJ2eI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rise-of-Nightmares/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rise-of-nightmares/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rise-of-nightmares"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1213,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft"],
			"synopsis":"Self-Defense Training Camp helps players develop the self-confidence they need to react more efficiently when facing troublesome situations, and allows players to discover ways of protecting themselves from various forms of physical assault. The game combines fitness workouts and self-defense drills into four primary categories critical to successful self-protection: technique, stamina, composure and reflexes. Kinect's innovative tracking technology provides players with immediate feedback on their movements, helping to make the basics of self-defense easy regardless of the player's skill level. These self-defense techniques are taught by an experienced, real-life self-defense coach.<br><br>Players will get in shape as they learn new skills with fitness routines inspired by both kickboxing and martial arts. They will also improve their reflexes with a collection of fun mini-games. To help players sharpen their minds as well as their bodies, Self-Defense Training Camp also incorporates meditative forms of exercise helping users learn how to remain calm and composed in stressful situations.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ecjtw61R8_A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_yDdMJnTIf4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/SelfDefense/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/self-defense-training-camp/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/self-defense-training-camp"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1214,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Double Fine Productions"],
			"synopsis":"In a truly original interactive experience, young players join Cookie Monster, Elmo and other Sesame Street characters as they explore a living storybook titled Once Upon a Monster.<br><br>In the book, they make new zany monster friends from the Once Upon a Monster world and share in their adventures, solving problems, forging friendships and learning key life skills along the way. Parents and children literally become part of the whimsical storybook adventure by getting active together through dancing, jumping, flying and more.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"New Chapter!",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/22",
				"achievements":105,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Download a brand new chapter of Sesame Street: Once Upon a Monster! In this new chapter of gameplay, meet new alien monster friends and use the skills you've learned to help them accomplish their mission! From innovative game developer Double Fine Productions comes a storybook adventure of whimsical discovery and outrageous fun, featuring popular Sesame Street characters and quirky, new monsters! This Controller-free gaming experience is perfect for kids, and fun for the entire family! Drop-in/drop-out co-op gameplay is ideal for parent/child or sibling play. Join the fun!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YTiPmery4fI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M6PkLyict68"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B4-qC6V5dyY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sesame-Street-Once-Upon-a-Monster/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sesame-street-once-upon-a-monster/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sesame-street-once-upon-a-monster"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1215,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Magic Pockets"],
			"synopsis":"True to classic TMNT-style gameplay and atmosphere, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles is an energetic, blazing beat 'em up with four-person, local, drop-in/drop-out co-op (Wii system from Nintendo, Xbox 360 video game and entertainment system only) and features character upgrades, secondary items, and multiple gameplay modes. It offers an authentic Turtles storyline, encompassing franchise-favorite characters and locations from the animated series, unfolding through animated cut scenes and in-game events.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tpoNs8bU3uw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n-0BfibMcQw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HnNH3F8u58Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/723581-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Teenage-Mutant-Ninja-Turtles/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Turtlepedia",
				"url":"http://turtlepedia.wikia.com/wiki/Teenage_Mutant_Ninja_Turtles_(2013_video_game)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1216,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Games Studios"],
			"synopsis":"In SpongeBob Surf & Skate Roadtrip, hit the sand and surf with SpongeBob and Patrick, for some super boarding escapades. Ride waves and winding waterways, and skate seaside streets and ramps for hours of challenges that'll test your boarding skills.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LL03td2D1_Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QUerIwYC-Yc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/SpongeBob-Surf--Skate/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/spongebobs-surf-skate-roadtrip"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Encyclopedia Spongebobia",
				"url":"http://spongebob.wikia.com/wiki/SpongeBob's_Surf_%26_Skate_Roadtrip"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1217,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FromSoftware"],
			"synopsis":"Capcom's incredibly realistic action game Steel Battalion comes to Xbox 360, with Kinect motion control to allow players to place themselves inside the mech cockpit.<br><br>Set in 2082, Steel Battalion Heavy Armor depicts a world devoid of semiconductors, where war is waged with rudimentary weapons as new superpowers struggle for dominance. In a twist of fate, the U.S. army has been forced to begin major landing operations on what was once its own soil. In this low-tech era, there is one weapon class that will determine the course of the war -- the Vertical Tank (VT). Playing as pilot Lt. Powers, players control one such VT as he embarks on a mission that will see the action shift from North America to battlefields and war-torn streets across the globe.<br><br>Work together with your in-game crew or team up online with your friends on a variety of maps to destroy a set amount of enemies and unlock new items to customize your VT with. Steel Battalion Heavy Armor delivers an unprecedented level of control and interaction. VT movement, aiming and firing of the main guns are undertaken using the Xbox 360 controller. A wide variety of other combat-crucial actions are done through Kinect for Xbox 360 with upper body gestures -- from starting the engine, to operating the scope or manning the turret-mounted machine gun. Kinect for Xbox 360 also provides a means of interacting with your fellow crew members, from ensuring a panicked crew member stays focused, to a high five for successfully completing a mission.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Emblem Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/06/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A pack of emblems that can be affixed to your Vertical Tank. Includes the top user-created emblems as well as many others. Find one that suits your personality."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Map Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2012/07/03",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Map Pack 1 for Steel Battalion: Heavy Armor. Includes two new co-op missions. \"Fuel Requisition\": Secure fuel tanks without triggering a massive explosion. \"Mountain Sentinels\": Attempt to destroy a large enemy cannon located in the mountains. Each mission has three new items for you to find."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Map Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2012/07/17",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Map Pack 2 for Steel Battalion: Heavy Armor. Includes two new co-op missions. \"Ammo Dump Jump\": Attempt to destroy the enemy ammo dump. \"The Champ-de-Mars\": Take out the enemy's searchlight. Each mission has three new items for you to find."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Camouflage Pack 1: Chrome Blitzer",
				"releaseDate":"2012/07/31",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Camouflage Pack 1: Chrome Blitzer. Includes two camouflage skins for your vertical tank. \"Tiger Pattern\": Increases destructive force of ammo. Use it to increase your attacking power. \"Impact Pattern\": Increases turn speed. Use it to increase your agility. Change your camouflage to gain an advantage in battle and defeat the Empire!"
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Camouflage Pack 2: Iron Guardian",
				"releaseDate":"2012/07/31",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Camouflage Pack 2: Iron Guardian. Includes two camouflage skins for your vertical tank. \"Rock Pattern\": Increases armor durability. Use it to increase your defensive guard. \"Jaguar Pattern\": Increases movement speed. Use it to increase your mobility. Change your camouflage to gain an advantage in battle and defeat the Empire!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Camouflage Pack 3: Carbon Assassin",
				"releaseDate":"2012/07/31",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Camouflage Pack 3: Carbon Assassin. Includes two camouflage skins for your vertical tank. \"Savannah Pattern\": Increases ammo velocity. Use it to increase your ability to hit speedy targets. \"Storm Pattern\": Increases main armament range. Use it to increase your attacking range. Change your camouflage to gain an advantage in battle and defeat the Empire!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bVkUZbJm9vE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DBj59ASyH1Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EpfjSfs6kfE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RbGt_oP0pQE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 5",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CNPHbePsGok"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4JhJFwc1z0I"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/606289-steel-battalion-heavy-armor/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Steel-Battalion-Heavy-Armor/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/steel-battalion-heavy-armor"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1218,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Naked Sky Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"A brand new way to play Twister is coming to Kinect for Xbox 360 -- it's Twister Mania, the interactive digital Twister experience that allows up to eight players to twist into the action. Twister Mania offers 16 fun, unique ways to play in a Twister-inspired environment filled with iconic, colorful flair.<br><br>This outrageous fast-paced party game offers over-the-top hilarity - so don't hold back as you get your body moving and twisting to fit through cutouts, bend into thousands of forms, mirror your friend's image, and even clear stacked shapes lightning fast! Play solo to earn the fastest time or team up in co-op for laugh-out-loud tangled-up fun with your family and friends. Twist into wild and crazy fun with Twister Mania!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7xO7flwsVts"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x2V2Ok8q1oU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Twister-Mania/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/twister-mania"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1219,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Heavy Iron Studios"],
			"synopsis":"UFC Personal Trainer: The Ultimate Fitness System delivers a challenging and motivating UFC fitness experience that includes the best and most effective exercises utilized by today's renowned UFC fighters.<br><br>Users will learn over 70 MMA and NASM-approved exercises, including moves from disciplines such as wrestling, kickboxing and Muay Thai, that are designed to improve strength, endurance and conditioning through use in a variety of routines. All 51 routines, along with nine exclusive bonus routines on Kinect for Xbox 360, will be specialized to target specific muscle groups, as well as factor individual skill levels and fitness goals. In addition, users may focus on specific fitness objectives by building personalized routines with up to 12 different exercises. Each of the custom routines can be modified to increase or decrease intensity of the product's pre-set pace, enabling users to fully maximize their training experiences based on individual preferences.<br><br>Across the training experience, users will punch and kick virtual authentic MMA training gear, with Kinect for Xbox 360 users having access to exclusive branded equipment.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Urijah Faber Workout Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/07/01",
				"achievements":10,
				"type":0
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c0S_Hjy9QtY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2LVe_mnj4PM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/UFC-Personal-Trainer/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ufc-personal-trainer/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ufc-personal-trainer-the-ultimate-fitness-system"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1220,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["High Voltage Software"],
			"synopsis":"In Victorious: Time to Shine, players can partner up with friends in co-op or competitive gameplay to create a Hollywood Arts talent show where they can act, direct, sing, dance and more, all to the soundtrack of hit songs from the series.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yqx94BVPDW4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SeScoNnGB1k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Victorious-Time-to-Shine/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/victorious-time-to-shine/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1221,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ludia"],
			"synopsis":"You take the hot seat in the all new Who Wants to be a Millionaire video game. Win $1,000,000 by correctly answering 15 multiple choice questions, each worth an increasing amount of money. Just like on TV show, players can seek help for the super stumper questions via lifelines like \"Ask the Audience\", \"Double Dip\" or \"Phone a Friend\". Can you stand the pressure, or will you walk away? Who Wants To Be A Millionaire 2012 Edition features over 3000 randomized questions allowing players to either call out their answer as they would on the television show, or gesture with their hand to make their answer selection by using and the Xbox 360 Kinect. Players can also place themselves into the game by using their custom Xbox 360 avatar.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CMYPZ7rZx9k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Who-Wants-to-Be-a-Millionaire-2012/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/who-wants-to-be-a-millionarie-2012-edition/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/who-wants-to-be-a-millionaire-2012-edition"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1222,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["49Games"],
			"synopsis":"Winter Stars, developed by 49 Games, entices gamers off their sofas with its high quality and easy-to-learn, exhilarating motion controls. The unique \"family mode\" allows each participant to choose his or her own individual difficulty level, thus making for a fun multiplayer experience with even chances for everyone. In single player mode, Winter Stars offers a campaign full of variety that allows players to experience all aspects of an athlete's career.<br><br>Winter Stars is a breath of fresh air for the genre, enabling sports fans of all ages and abilities to compete with one another or against virtual opponents in no less than eleven disciplines: snowmobiling, bobsledding, downhill skiing, figure skating, biathlon, free ride skiing, snowboard cross, ski jumping, paraskiing, curling, and short-track. In thrilling multiplayer action, up to four players can engage in dynamic online or offline competitions for championship titles, or simply enjoy the variety of winter sports themed mini-games on offer. The story-driven single player mode not only features an extensive career system and character development, but also a number of special challenges such as training sessions that provide arcade-style enjoyment in between events. Console athletes can use the experience points they earn to purchase new equipment and improve their skills in preparation for the diverse challenges ahead, and to support their team on its path to victory.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=acOlKXwkvSg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4m8bPFKeNFI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Winter-Stars/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/winter-stars"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1223,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Behaviour"],
			"synopsis":"Wipeout In the Zone will have players running, ducking, dodging and wiping out using Kinect for Xbox 360's full-motion capabilities right in their own living room.<br><br>Wipeout In the Zone features over thirty outrageous obstacles that will test players' limits in more ridiculous ways than ever. Players can try to run the entire course in one shot, conquering one challenge after another, such as leaping over a pool of water using the infamous \"Big Balls\" and maneuvering their players to avoid being pummeled by the \"Smack Wall Sweeper\". Once again featuring the talents and hilarious commentary of the show's hosts, John Anderson, John Henson and co-host Jill Wagner, Wipeout In the Zone will bring hours upon hours of fun and laughter for the entire family.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YzqX00rmCEA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tfUoRzAKDW4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iiv_r5w373M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wipeout-In-The-Zone/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wipeout-in-the-zone/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wipeout-in-the-zone"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1224,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Atlus", "ARC System Works"],
			"synopsis":"A few days after the P-1 Grand Prix concludes in the first Arena title, the city of Inaba gets enveloped in a thick red fog and Mitsuru, Akihiko, Fuuka, and Aigis are shown as prisoners on the Midnight Channel. The Investigation Team from Persona 4 and former SEES from Persona 3 must once again fight to their limits in the new P-1 Climax tournament to rescue them and finally uncover the true culprit behind the deadly tournaments.<br><br>Persona 4 Arena Ultimax will improve on the award-winning fighting game formula with battle-altering 1-hit special attacks and new characters, including Yukari Takeba and Junpei Iori from Persona 3 and a brand new character, Sho Minazuki. Not a lot is known about Sho other than his goofy nature and being an unstoppable force in both puns and combat. Two swords, two scars on his face, red hair and red mist in Inaba? Surely it can't be coincidence that he's standing in the way of the Investigation Team. And to make matters worse, it seems he can control a Persona...",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Additional Character 1: Tohru Adachi",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/30",
				"achievements":110,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Adds Tohru Adachi to the roster of playable fighters and makes Episode \"Adachi\" available in Story Mode. This DLC also includes Glasses and 6 colors + 2 offline-only colors for Adachi. The icons \"Tohru Adachi C\", \"Tohru Adachi D\" and \"Magatsu-Izanagi\" will also be available under P-Card Edit. NOTE: Episode \"Adachi\" is unlocked after completing Episode \"P4.\" NOTE: Downloading this will change certain BGM tracks into the full-length versions."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Additional Colors Full Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Additional colors for all 19 characters. Each character will have 6 new colors + 2 offline-only colors. NOTE: This DLC contains all of the individual Additional Colors Packs."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Additional Character 2: Marie",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/30",
				"achievements":70,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Adds Marie to the roster of playable fighters. This DLC also includes Glasses and 6 colors + 2 offline-only colors for Marie. The icons \"Marie D\", \"Marie E\" and \"Kaguya\" will also be available under P-Card Edit. NOTE: Downloading this will change certain BGM tracks into the full-length versions."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"P4A Story",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/30",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Enables you to play through the story of the original Persona 4 Arena."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Glasses Full Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Glasses for all characters. You can select different glasses colors for each character to wear during battle. NOTE: This DLC contains all of the individual \"Glasses Pack\" DLC."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Additional Character 3: Margaret",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/07",
				"achievements":70,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Adds Margaret to the roster of playable fighters. This DLC also includes Glasses and 6 colors + 2 offline-only colors for Margaret. The icons \"Margaret B\", \"Margaret C\", \"Cu Chulainn\", \"Ardha\" and \"Yoshitsune\" will also be available under P-Card Edit. NOTE: Downloading this will change certain BGM tracks into the full-length versions."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Additional BGM #1",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/07",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Makes \"Persona Invocation\" available as BGM for battles and the main menu."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Additional BGM: P3P Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/07",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Makes \"Soul Phrase -long ver.-\", \"Wiping All Out\" and \"Sun\" available as BGM for battles and the main menu."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Additional BGM #2",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/07",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Makes \"Persona\" available as BGM for battles and the main menu."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Additional BGM: P3 Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/07",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Makes \"Burn My Dread\", \"Memories of You\" and \"Deep Mentality\" available as BGM for battles and the main menu. NOTE: If you download \"System Data ver. 1.30\" or \"Additional Character 1, 2 or 3\", some BGM tracks will become the full-length versions."
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Additional BGM: P3F Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/07",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Makes \"P3 FES\", \"Brand New Days\" and \"Darkness\" available as BGM for battles and the main menu. NOTE: If you download \"System Data ver. 1.30\" or \"Additional Character 1, 2 or 3\", some BGM tracks will become the full-length versions."
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Additional BGM: P4A Arranged Pack #1",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Makes \"The Arena -Naked Mix-\", \"The Hero from Junes -Electro Mix-\" and \"Like a Dragon -Girl Pop Mix-\" available as BGM for battles and the main menu. NOTE: If you download \"System Data ver. 1.30\" or \"Additional Character 1, 2 or 3\", the BGM tracks will become the full-length versions."
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"Additional BGM: P4A Arranged Pack #2",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Makes \"Princess Amagi -Traditional Taste Mix-\", \"The Wandering Wolf -Electro Mix-\" and \"Missions for the Brilliant Executioner -2K Mix-\" available as BGM for battles and the main menu. NOTE: If you download \"System Data ver. 1.30\" or \"Additional Character 1, 2 or 3\", the BGM tracks will become the full-length versions."
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"Additional BGM #3",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Makes \"Someone Else's Man\" available as BGM for battles and the main menu."
			},
			{
				"id":15,
				"name":"Additional BGM: PQ Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Makes \"MAZE OF LIFE\", \"Light the Fire Up in the Night DARK HOUR\" and \"Light the Fire Up in the Night MIDNIGHT\" available as BGM for battles and the main menu. NOTE: If you download \"System Data ver. 1.30\" or \"Additional Character 1, 2 or 3\", some BGM tracks will become the full-length versions."
			},
			{
				"id":16,
				"name":"Additional BGM #4",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Makes \"Reach Out to the Truth -Instrumental Ver.-\" available as BGM for battles and the main menu."
			},
			{
				"id":17,
				"name":"Additional BGM: P4 Pack #1",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Makes \"Pursuing My True Self\", \"Heaven\" and \"Quelorie Magic!\" available as BGM for battles and the main menu."
			},
			{
				"id":18,
				"name":"Additional BGM: P4 Pack #2",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Makes \"Never More\", \"Time to Make History\" and \"It's SHOW TIME!\" available as BGM for battles and the main menu."
			},
			{
				"id":19,
				"name":"Additional BGM: P4 Pack #3",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Makes \"Shadow World\", \"Let's Hit the Beach\" and \"True Story\" available as BGM for battles and the main menu. NOTE: If you download \"System Data ver. 1.30\" or \"Additional Character 1, 2 or 3\", some BGM tracks will become the full-length versions."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zD1Ea7satoQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JVmZiNMmK3g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0PY__iDJyhk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BtbsLd_OB30"
			},
			{
				"type":"All Character Trailers",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qObt0cnIXvE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aKRatGWaBFw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/763478-persona-4-arena-ultimax/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Persona-4-Arena-Ultimax/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/persona-4-arena-ultimax"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Megami Tensei Wiki",
				"url":"http://megamitensei.wikia.com/wiki/Persona_4_Arena_Ultimax"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1225,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Keen Games"],
			"synopsis":"After decades of peace, a new shadow is cast over the world of Ancaria. They say that whoever possesses the Heart of Ancaria will decide the fate of the world. Zane Ashen, ruler of the corrupt Ashen Empire, will do everything in his power to obtain the Heart; however, the Seraphim have hidden it away in a secure and secret place. Only when a group of heroes combine their powers to oppose Zane Ashen's reign of terror does the world have a chance of escaping utter destruction.<br><br>Sacred 3 reinvigorates this Action RPG franchise with accessible yet sophisticated gameplay. Up to four players can join the battle against the Ashen Empire in a unique and engaging co-op mode in which they will not only fight against the Imperial aggressors but also compete between each other in friendly rivalry. Choose between several character classes -- the Safiri Warrior and Ancarian Lancer being just two of these options. Each of these classes offers a specific skill set -- players must choose their Combat Arts, perks and equipment wisely in order to stand a chance against the Ashen Empire.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Z4ngr13f Weapon Spirit",
				"releaseDate":"2014/08/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Z4ngr13f, aka John, was busy pwning mobs in Sacred during a speedrun when lightning struck and he got sucked into the world of Ancaria. With the expertise of Z4ngr13f sealed into your weapon of choice, those Ashen troops stand no chance! This pack contains the exclusive Z4ngr13f Weapon Spirit."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Malakhim Hero",
				"releaseDate":"2014/08/05",
				"achievements":45,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Play as Kython the Malakhim, a mysterious dark assassin from unknown origins. Use powerful blood magic to reinforce the resistance, and protect Ancaria. This pack contains Kython the Malakhim as a fully playable character."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Underworld Story",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/07",
				"achievements":45,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Venture into the Underworld through a newly-discovered portal and find the mysterious tower guarded by the Black Seraphim. This pack contains 4 all-new missions set in the Underworld of Ancaria."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Orc of Thrones",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/14",
				"achievements":45,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Play as Garok the Orc, the true heir of the Orc Throne. Betrayed by his brother Gragon, he sets out to kill him and return his tribe back to the ways of nature. This pack contains Garok the Orc as a fully playable character."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Orcland Story",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"achievements":45,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Gragon has taken the Orc Throne, corrupted Orcland and turned its Orcs into Grimmocs. Fight your way through the homeland of the Grimmocs and defeat the wrongful king Gragon. This pack contains 4 all-new missions set in the canyons of Orcland."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WBI4BWtBAtE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mwS-2xSBuxI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TFCURzNgCYo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KO0dRv7NQsw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sacred-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sacred-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sacred-3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1226,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Piranha Bytes"],
			"synopsis":"Risen 3: Titan Lords is a hand-crafted role-playing world full of rugged charm where every decision changes the course of the story and your fate.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Adventure Garb",
				"releaseDate":"2014/08/12",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Adventure Garb not only protects you from the elements, it also helps you to defy the dangers found in the unknown wilderness or shady harbour taverns."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Uprising of the Little Guys",
				"releaseDate":"2014/08/12",
				"achievements":20,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Goblins and Gnomes are fighting for supremacy on the Isle of Thieves. Save the Gnomes and their culture from impending annihilation."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Fog Island",
				"releaseDate":"2014/08/12",
				"achievements":20,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"A stranded Inquisition raiding party is searching for new territory in a world where madness seems to spread. Help them unveil the deadly secret found on this island."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ilvyZH1zwVk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XEAKktXT1Dw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rySgkSMU2aw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LFXK_MXW2BM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zEy2_7m8BGU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Risen-3-Titan-Lords/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/risen-3-titan-lords"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Risen Wiki",
				"url":"http://risen.wikia.com/wiki/Risen_3:_Titan_Lords"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1227,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bungie Software"],
			"synopsis":"From the creators of Halo and the publisher of Call of Duty comes Destiny. With an unprecedented variety of FPS gameplay, Destiny promises to deliver an incredible story set within a newly-imagined, always-connected universe filled with action and adventure.<br><br>Everything changed with the arrival of the Traveler. It sparked a Golden Age when our civilization spanned the solar system ... but it didn't last. Something hit us, knocked us down. The survivors built a city beneath the Traveler, and have begun to explore our old worlds, only to find them filled with deadly foes. In Destiny, you are a Guardian of the last safe city on Earth, able to wield incredible power. Defend the City. Defeat our enemies. Reclaim all that we have lost.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=clRpcIHpmoY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jv7vqCmt6wY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y2Jx5__c1lY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Live Action Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9ZyQK6kUdWQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LlyyO9EcJdg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/952149-destiny/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Destiny/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/destiny/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/destiny"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Destinypedia",
				"url":"http://destiny.wikia.com/wiki/Destiny_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1228,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Creative Assembly"],
			"synopsis":"Discover the true meaning of fear in Alien: Isolation, a survival horror set in an atmosphere of constant dread and mortal danger. Fifteen years after the events of Alien, Ellen Ripley's daughter, Amanda enters a desperate battle for survival, on a mission to unravel the truth behind her mother's disappearance. As Amanda, you will navigate through an increasingly volatile world as you find yourself confronted on all sides by a panicked, desperate population and an unpredictable, ruthless Alien. Underpowered and underprepared, you must scavenge resources, improvise solutions and use your wits, not just to succeed in your mission, but to simply stay alive.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Crew Expendable Bonus Content",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/07",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"This additional content sees the original crew reunited aboard the Nostromo. Brett and Kane are dead; alongside Ash and Lambert, it is now down to you as Dallas, Parker or Ellen Ripley, to find a way to isolate the Alien and overcome the terror that confronts them."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Last Survivor Bonus Content",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/14",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"As Ellen Ripley, it is down to you to complete the last mission on board the Nostromo. The rest of the crew are dead. In a desperate bid to survive you must set the ship's self-destruct and attempt to reach the escape shuttle."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Corporate Lockdown",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/28",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Welcome to Corporate Lockdown, the first expansion pack for Alien: Isolation. This pack features three all-new maps for Survivor Mode, a time-based challenge to test your skills. Can you evade the Alien for long enough to survive or will you try to take the Alien head-on? - Three new maps, stretching from the Corporate Penthouse to the Medlabs. - New playable character Ransome gives you the firepower to take the fight to your enemies. - Upload your best times to the Alien: Isolation leaderboards and challenge the world."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Trauma",
				"releaseDate":"2014/12/02",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Welcome to Trauma, the second add-on content pack for Alien: Isolation. This pack features three all-new maps for Survivor Mode, a time-based challenge to test your skills. Face off against a range of enemies across the medical bays of Sevastopol station. Will you evade, distract or confront them? You'll have to act fast if you want to survive. - Three new maps, including a claustrophobic scramble through the Sevastopol vents. - Play as Chief Medical Officer Lingard and get faster access to Medikits and distraction IEDs. - Destroy any trace of your research and save the survivors on the station."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7h0cgmvIrZw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1BRz_s3Zvaw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uqmlNjPWNXA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mT6UQrmTzLk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MHF_SH8BtGU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/751157-alien-isolation/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Alien-Isolation/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Alien Anthology Wiki",
				"url":"http://alienanthology.wikia.com/wiki/Alien:_Isolation"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Xenopedia",
				"url":"http://avp.wikia.com/wiki/Alien:_Isolation"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1229,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Monolith Productions"],
			"synopsis":"Middle-earth: Shadow of Mordor is an action-packed adventure-RPG inspired by J.R.R. Tolkien's The Hobbit and The Lord of the Rings. Exploring an original story of vengeance and redemption, the game puts players in the role of Talion, a valiant ranger whose family is slain in front of him the night Sauron and his army return to Mordor -- moments before his own life is taken. Resurrected by a Spirit of vengeance and empowered with Wraith abilities, Talion ventures into Mordor and vows to destroy those who have wronged him. Through the course of his personal vendetta, Talion uncovers the truth of the Spirit that compels him, learns the origins of the Rings of Power and ultimately confronts his true nemesis.<br><br>Every enemy that players face is a unique individual, differentiated by their personality, strengths and weaknesses. Through the Nemesis System, enemy relationships and characteristics are shaped by player actions and decisions to create personal archenemies that remember and adapt to the player and are distinct to every gameplay session. Gamers are able to craft their own battles, enemies and rewards within the dynamic world that remembers and adapts to their choices, delivering a unique experience to every player.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=leaYw-7Fgxg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4rbOTQhasnM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X8hoTfZ3vUc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=apqeGvr2m6A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jYsK_K0AhIM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/739524-middle-earth-shadow-of-mordor/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Middle-earth-Shadow-of-Mordor/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/middle-earth-shadow-of-mordor/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Shadow of Mordor Wiki",
				"url":"http://shadowofmordor.wikia.com/wiki/Shadow_of_Mordor_Wikia"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1230,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["2K Australia", "Gearbox Software"],
			"synopsis":"Borderlands: The Pre-Sequel launches players to Pandora's moon to experience wild, gravity-bending gunfights in zero-atmosphere environments using an array of all-new weaponry. For the very first time, fans play on the other side as four new playable characters contributing to the rise of the Hyperion Corporation. Fighting alongside Handsome Jack, players witness his transformation into the megalomaniacal tyrant that fans loved to hate in Borderlands 2.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Handsome Jack Doppelganger Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/11",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Play as everyone's favorite maniacal tyrant-in-training... or at least his body double. With the Handsome Jack Doppelganger Pack, use the power of your good looks and charm to distract your enemies into submission. Or, just cut them down to size with your witty banter. Or just shoot them. That works too. Play as the hero(?) that Pandora and Elpis deserve."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"The Holodome Onslaught",
				"releaseDate":"2014/12/16",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"With all new narrative content, this add-on begins as Vault Hunters Axton and Gaige catch up on the story thus far via The Holodome Onslaught, a new challenge arena that lets players fight through wave after wave of exciting enemies and bosses to earn awesome, new weapons and gear along with radical new heads and skins! As bonus content, this download also includes the Ultimate Vault Hunter Upgrade Pack, which raises the level cap and gives your characters 10 new levels plus 10 new skill points to earn!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Shock Drop Slaughter Pit",
				"releaseDate":"2014/12/16",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Enter the Shock Drop Slaughter Pit and face off against the toughest Scavs on Pandora's moon, Elpis! Survive the battle and you'll be feared and respected by the few left alive... not to mention the experience and gear you'll earn!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=77IR2fjgMBU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1tcGpsNvALI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ze7BrRNaBSM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0YjCis2yJJ0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/783734-borderlands-the-pre-sequel/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Borderlands-The-Pre-Sequel/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/borderlands-the-pre-sequel"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Borderlands Wiki",
				"url":"http://borderlands.wikia.com/wiki/Borderlands:_The_Pre-Sequel"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1231,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tango Gameworks"],
			"synopsis":"While investigating the scene of a gruesome mass murder, Detective Sebastian Castellanos and his partners encounter a mysterious and powerful force. After seeing the slaughter of fellow officers, Sebastian is ambushed and knocked unconscious. When he awakens, he finds himself in a deranged world where hideous creatures wander among the dead. Facing unimaginable terror, and fighting for survival, Sebastian embarks on a frightening journey to unravel what's behind this evil force.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zc-jvqJV4SI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nxlo67zhOWc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vIDpby6NNGk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VnYGJc7dwxA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T0Uy4Xevz1A"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/711438-the-evil-within/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Evil-Within/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-evil-within"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Evil Within Wiki",
				"url":"http://theevilwithin.wikia.com/wiki/The_Evil_Within_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1232,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["High Moon Studios", "Sledgehammer Games"],
			"synopsis":"Call of Duty: Advanced Warfare envisions the powerful battlegrounds of the future, where both technology and tactic have evolved to usher in a new era of combat for the franchise. Delivering a stunning performance, Academy Award winning actor Kevin Spacey stars as Jonathan Irons -- one of the most powerful men in the world -- shaping this chilling vision of the future of war. The game takes place in a plausible future in which technological progress and today's military practices have converged with powerful consequences. In this carefully researched and crafted vision of the future, Private Military Corporations (PMCs) have become the dominant armed forces for countless nations outsourcing their military needs, redrawing borders and rewriting the rules of war. And Jonathan Irons, the founder and president of the world's largest PMC, Atlas Corporation, is at the center of it all.<br><br>Suit up for combat in exoskeletons that evolve every aspect of a soldier's battle readiness, enabling combatants to deploy with an advanced lethality and eliminating the need for specialization. Players experience enhanced player movement and verticality through boost jumps and grappling, covert cloaking abilities, and biomechanics that provide unparalleled strength, awareness, endurance, and speed. With the advent of the exoskeleton and newly advanced armor and weaponry, every soldier commands tactical freedom in any terrain unlike ever before, fundamentally changing the way gamers play Call of Duty across all modes.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0C2cG30FBas"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YSp8ZqIKEIM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Live Action Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GccGbdLqTmQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Campaign Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pUysNWHffWg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bj3-RsyJKfA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Campaign Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KN6vS32iHJ4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3HdTrrFzi9I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Exo Survival Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ytgn9AYJl0I"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/792621-call-of-duty-advanced-warfare/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Call-of-Duty-Advanced-Warfare/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Call of Duty Wiki",
				"url":"http://callofduty.wikia.com/wiki/Call_of_Duty:_Advanced_Warfare"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1233,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"Step into a vast, unknowable land once again in this fourth game in the Far Cry franchise. Players find themselves in Kyrat, a wild region of the Himalayas struggling under the regime of a despotic self-appointed king. Using a vast array of weapons, vehicles and animals, players will write their own story across an exotic open-world landscape. Built from the legendary DNA of its award-winning predecessor, Far Cry 4 delivers the most expansive and immersive Far Cry experience ever in an entirely new and massive open world with a new weapons, vehicles, wildlife and more.<br><br>In Far Cry 4, you'll conquer fortress outposts from the back of a six-ton elephant and take to the skies as you rain down explosives from the seat of your gyrocopter. The vertical landscape of the Himalayas isn't just a pretty backdrop, but a playground that encourages the player to fight, hunt and explore, grappling up cliffs or launching into the air, plummeting to the valley below in a controlled free fall with your wing suit. You'll carry with you a truly unique arsenal of weaponry that lets you play your way, whether it's sniping, sneaking or all-out assault. When all else fails, animals can be your biggest allies or your greatest danger, as Kyrat's wilderness delivers on the promise of a true open world anecdote factory.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6d60v1OErEY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PLt6T-WeToI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=egrtMng83RU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QRdqiaB3J0I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Far-Cry-4/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Far Cry Wiki",
				"url":"http://farcry.wikia.com/wiki/Far_Cry_4"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1234,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"Building on years of legacy as a top-ranked basketball video game, NBA 2K15 returns with more modes, new features and the incredibly realistic on-court and off-court action fans have come to expect. The game features 2013-14 NBA Most Valuable Player Kevin Durant on the cover, and an eclectic soundtrack curated by internationally renowned artist Pharrell Williams.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Spanish Commentary Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/07",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Enjoy in-game NBA commentary in Spanish from three of Spain's most prominent basketball journalists - Antoni Daimiel and Sixto Miguel Serrano from Canal+ along with Jorge Quiroga of Marca - with this Spanish Commentary Add-On pack."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WStjzy1fOwo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5Z3BgacJoH4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-2K15/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1235,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blizzard Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Diablo III picks up the story twenty years after the events of Diablo II. Mephisto, Diablo, and Baal have been defeated, but the Worldstone, which once shielded the inhabitants of the world of Sanctuary from the forces of both Heaven and Hell, has been destroyed, and evil once again stirs in Tristram. Take on the role of one of six powerful character classes -- Barbarian, Demon Hunter, Monk, Witch Doctor, Wizard, or the all-new Crusader -- and embark on a dark journey through Acts I-V to save the world of Sanctuary from ancient and sinister forces. Players will acquire powerful items, spells, and abilities as they explore new and familiar areas of Sanctuary and battle hordes of demons to safeguard the world from the horrors that have arisen.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Infernal Pauldrons",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This game add-on package includes unique items not found elsewhere in the world of Sanctuary:<br><br>- Infernal Pauldrons: Give your Heroes starter bonuses with this exclusive item.<br>- Spectral Hound: Summon a companion for your Heroes.<br>- Arma Mortis: Teach the Mystic seven new weapon appearances.<br>- Arma Haereticorum: Teach the Mystic three new helmet appearances.<br>- Three additional character slots."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Diablo 3 Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=de2KlsLnIVU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reaper of Souls Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-_jBcYhpvA4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n2XDnSQC6Q8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/794726-diablo-iii-ultimate-evil-edition/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Diablo-III-Reaper-of-Souls-Ultimate-Evil-Edition-Xbox-360/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/diablo-3-ulimate-evil-edition/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/diablo-iii-ultimate-evil-edition"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Diablo Wiki",
				"url":"http://diablo.wikia.com/wiki/Diablo_III:_Ultimate_Evil_Edition"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1236,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"The 26th edition of EA Sports venerable pigskin game, Madden NFL 15 delivers everything fans need to own their rivals on both sides of the field, including the most immersive defensive gameplay control in franchise history. Like the Super Bowl XLVIII champion Seattle Seahawks, you can win championships and bask in the glory of success by building a great defense fit to challenge the best offenses in the game. Fans will also experience an entirely new broadcast presentation that delivers Madden NFL game day like never before with dramatic all-new camera angles, as well as dynamic pre-game and halftime features. It's not just football, it's Madden Season.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RYIeJ5H8oe0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cyxSifdeDWw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Madden-NFL-15/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1237,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Toys for Bob"],
			"synopsis":"In Skylanders Trap Team, Kaos continues his ongoing quest to rule over Skylands. He has discovered the location of the legendary Cloudcracker Prison -- a fortress built entirely out of the magical substance Traptanium and home to Skylands' most nefarious baddies. In an attempt to build his own army of foes, Kaos blows up the prison, releasing the most wanted villains and blasting shards of Traptanium to Earth in the form of Traps. Now it's up to Portal Masters to recapture all of the escaped villains using powerful Traptanium Traps and defeat Kaos before it's too late!<br><br>Skylanders Trap Team lets Portal Masters \"trap\" the most wanted villains in Skylands and then play as them in the game in the battle for good. The game offers an unprecedented new addition to the game's play pattern in the form of Traptanium Traps. When this new type of toy is placed directly into the Traptanium Portal. Portal Masters can \"capture\" a variety of special villains from the game and magically transport them from Skylands into the real world. Skylanders Trap Team also will reverse the magic of bringing toys-to-life, letting kids take characters out of the digital world and bring them into the physical world, pulling villains out of the game and into living room. Players can then send them back into the game where they play as them to fight for good.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E8T78t9iRjs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vbc7E9t9le8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ujemdA0I2GE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qwEup6jJMCg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Skylanders-Trap-Team/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Skylanders Wiki",
				"url":"http://skylanders.wikia.com/wiki/Skylanders:_Trap_Team"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1238,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Kalypso Media"],
			"synopsis":"Packed with a whole host of new gameplay features and all new artwork designed from scratch, Tropico 5 takes the strategy series into a new and exciting direction -- dynasties! You, as El Presidente, will first take control of the infamous island of Tropico during early colonial times and then guide it through the centuries as the world changes and moves ever forward. You must tackle the changing needs of your people, as well as opposing governments and factions, and thus lay the foundations for your own dynasty. As you move through your years in office you can promote members of your extended family on the island to positions of power: such as ambassador, commanding general or even Supreme Ruler, to ensure your legacy thrives through the eras. As your influence and wealth grows, so do the threats to your burgeoning island superpower. Can you survive both World Wars, prosper through the Great Depression, rule as an iron-fisted dictator through the Cold War and advance your country to modern times and beyond? From the 19th to the 21st century, each era carries its own challenges and opportunities.<br><br>As well as a wealth of other new features, including advanced trading mechanics, technology, scientific research trees and island exploration, Tropico 5 will add cooperative and competitive multiplayer for up to four players for the first time in the series' history! Viva El Presidente!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Big Cheese",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/11",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"It's all about cheese in El Presidente's latest venture. Create and promote an artisan cheese brand by introducing a new production chain with the Creamery: a new building that enables you to make the most of Tropico's local goats and llamas. Face international competition in an epic quest to create the best cheese in the world and put on the chef's hat! This add-on includes two all-new sandbox maps, a new task, a standalone scenario including additional voiceovers, building, avatar accessories and music track!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j1BDJkYxsCc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FbxwlkfJADs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8RomdpZXQAA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8WZmyCvuPR8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tropico-5/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tropico-5"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tropico Wiki",
				"url":"http://tropico.wikia.com/wiki/Tropico_5"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1239,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Yuke's Media Creations"],
			"synopsis":"WWE 2K15 aims to usher in a new era of WWE video games with 2K Showcase Mode, improved graphics, top commentary talent, and more. Relive the groundbreaking rivalries of John Cena vs. CM Punk and Triple H vs. Shawn Michaels in a new single player campaign told through your gameplay and historic WWE footage. Create your own Custom Superstar, or customize WWE Superstars and Divas, Move-Sets and entrances. Take control of WWE as your actions shape your Universe: storylines, schedule, rivalries, alliances and more! Listen to Jerry Lawler and Michael Cole call the action with authentic WWE blow-by-blow commentary.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aTmXBBj6PMQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ilTC7xtTDtE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/WWE-2K15/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wwe-2k15"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1240,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"In NHL 15, you see realistic looking and skating hockey players, along with detailed and authentic representation of the game of hockey itself. 12 Player NHL Collision Physics and Real Puck Physics capture the hard hitting chaos and unpredictability of the sport, while the Superstar Skill Stick and Vision AI put the flow and finesse of the game in your hands.<br><br>Witness the sights and sounds of authentic arenas across the National Hockey League, as 9.000 individual crowd models - the most ever in a sports videogame - hang on every play called by an all-new three man commentary team. In addition, a new partnership with NBC Sports brings, a world class broadcast package to the game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0jEgFzpsPMA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9OR4XZ7M6wU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NHL-15/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1241,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"Disney Fantasia: Music Evolved is a breakthrough musical motion video game inspired by Disney's classic animated film, Fantasia. In the game, players enter the magical realm of Fantasia, selected by the legendary sorcerer Yen Sid, to hone their musical and magical prowess as his new apprentice. Fantasia: Music Evolved takes players on an interactive and immersive motion-controlled journey through worlds of music and magic.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Pop Expansion Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Add additional Pop mixes to enhance the following core game songs: \"Blue Monday\" by New Order, \"Forget You\" by Cee Lo Green, \"Levels\" by AVICII, \"Super Bass\" by Nicki Minaj, \"Seven Nation Army\" by The White Stripes and \"Bohemian Rhapsody\" by Queen."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Dance Expansion Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Add additional Dance mixes to enhance the following core game songs: \"Some Nights\" by Fun., \"Get Ur Freak On\" by Missy Elliott, \"In Your Eyes\" by Peter Gabriel, \"Rocket Man\" by Elton John, \"Take Care\" by Drake (feat. Rhianna) and \"The Real Me\" by The Who."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Rock Expansion Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Add additional Rock mixes to enhance the following core game songs: \"Applause\" by Lady Gaga, \"Feel Good Inc.\" by Gorillaz, \"Galang\" by M.I.A., \"Locked Out Of Heaven\" by Bruno Mars, \"Royals\" by Lorde and \"Message In A Bottle\" by The Police."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"\"Spoonman\" - Soundgarden",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/11",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Remix new tracks and build your song library by purchasing \"Spoonman\" by Soundgarden."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"\"Paradise\" - Coldplay",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/11",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Remix new tracks and build your song library by purchasing \"Paradise\" by Coldplay."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"\"Try It Out\" - Skrillex & Alvin Risk",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/11",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Remix new tracks and build your song library by purchasing \"Try It Out\" by Skrillex & Alvin Risk."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"\"Lucky Strike\" - Maroon 5",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/25",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Remix new tracks and build your song library by purchasing \"Lucky Strike\" by Maroon 5."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"\"Burn\" - Ellie Goulding",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/25",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Remix new tracks and build your song library by purchasing \"Burn\" by Ellie Goulding."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"\"Just Like Heaven\" - The Cure",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/25",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Remix new tracks and build your song library by purchasing \"Just Like Heaven\" by The Cure."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"\"Burning Down The House\" - Talking Heads",
				"releaseDate":"2014/12/04",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Remix new tracks and build your song library by purchasing \"Burning Down The House\" by Talking Heads."
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"\"Stay The Night\" - Zedd (feat. Hayley Williams)",
				"releaseDate":"2014/12/04",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Remix new tracks and build your song library by purchasing \"Stay The Night\" by Zedd (feat. Hayley Williams)."
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"\"DONE\" - The Band Perry",
				"releaseDate":"2014/12/04",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Remix new tracks and build your song library by purchasing \"DONE\" by The Band Perry."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kq0_dGKx4Os"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d784iuJCihM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lzSlL03KRtc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Disney-Fantasia-Music-Evolved/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1242,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["BioWare"],
			"synopsis":"In Dragon Age: Inquisition the world of Thedas is being torn apart by a massive, mysterious breach in the sky. Players must assume the role of the Inquisitor and lead a team of legendary heroes to uncover the truth behind the impending devastation.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xnXlKrBItc0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jJqxfkgSUog"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SmdnRfeH0p8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qzRjfkXW9Lo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 5",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yHeWOQvVRd8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 6",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1HY2bOdzVD0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 7",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uO2h4qUNJ60"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U_s4uZBiapk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dragon-Age-Inquisition/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dragon Age Wiki",
				"url":"http://dragonage.wikia.com/wiki/Dragon_Age:_Inquisition"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1243,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["CyberConnect2"],
			"synopsis":"Naruto Shippuden: Ultimate Ninja Storm Revolution brings back the ultimate anime fighting game from famed developer CyberConnect2. Stunning anime visuals and fluid 3D ninja fighting action come together once again for the largest and most explosive Ultimate Ninja Storm game yet. Naruto Shippuden: Ultimate Ninja Storm Revolution features brand new gameplay mechanics including devastating Combination Ultimate Jutsu attacks, allowing characters to combine their honed powers to create powerful techniques to bring opponents to their knees. With a roster reaching 100 playable characters spanning the entire Naruto and Naruto Shippuden anime arcs, there are sure to be characters that fit everyone's play style. A brand new character designed by Naruto manga creator Masashi Kishimoto also makes an appearance in Naruto Shippuden: Ultimate Ninja Storm Revolution.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Jinchuriki Costume Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The following characters' costumes will be available in Free Battle and Online Battle of Naruto Shippuden: Ultimate Ninja Storm Revolution: Naruto (White Robe) Killer Bee (White Robe) Fuu (White Robe) Utakata (White Robe)"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Jinchuriki Costume Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The following characters' costumes will be available in Free Battle and Online Battle of Naruto Shippuden: Ultimate Ninja Storm Revolution: Gaara (White Robe) Yugito (White Robe) Yagura (White Robe) Roshi (White Robe) Han (White Robe)"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Summer Cloth Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The following characters' costumes will be available in Free Battle and Online Battle of Naruto Shippuden: Ultimate Ninja Storm Revolution: Sakura (Summer Clothes) Ino (Summer Clothes) Hinata (Summer Clothes) Tenten (Summer Clothes)"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Suit Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The following characters' costumes will be available in Free Battle and Online Battle of Naruto Shippuden: Ultimate Ninja Storm Revolution: Naruto (Suit) Sasuke (Suit) Shikamaru (Suit) Gaara (Suit) Sai (Suit) Minato (Suit)"
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Variety Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/07",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The following characters' costumes will be available in Free Battle and Online Battle of Naruto Shippuden: Ultimate Ninja Storm Revolution: The Third Hokage (Hokage Costume) Itachi (w/o Cloak) Kakashi (Kakuzu Battle Costume) The First Hokage (Hokage Costume) Zabuza (Hidden Mist Costume)"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Variety Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/14",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This pack contains the following costumes: Madara (Black Robe) Karin (Taka) Jugo (Taka) Suigetsu (Taka) Mifune (Five Kage Summit) Part 1 Naruto (Pajamas)"
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Variety Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The following characters' costumes will be available in Free Battle and Online Battle of Naruto Shippuden: Ultimate Ninja Storm Revolution: Kushina (ROAD TO NINJA) Nagato (First Akatsuki Outfit) Konan (First Akatsuki Outfit) Pain (First Akatsuki Outfit)"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Reanimation-Before Death Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The following characters' costumes will be available in Free Battle and Online Battle of Naruto Shippuden: Ultimate Ninja Storm Revolution: Sasori (Reanimation) Chiyo (Reanimation) Kimimaro (Reanimation) Hanzo (Before Death) The Fourth Kazekage (Before Death) The Third Raikage (Before Death) The Second Tsuchikage (Before Death) The Second Mizukage (Before Death)"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8UlY3qvjFQs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gX1HHpekhRk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j3jHdov98zc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TC2yGKoB-b4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Naruto-Shippuden-Ultimate-Ninja-Storm-Revolution/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/naruto-shippuden-ultimate-ninja-storm-revolution"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Narutopedia",
				"url":"http://naruto.wikia.com/wiki/Naruto_Shipp%C5%ABden:_Ultimate_Ninja_Storm_Revolution"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1244,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"FIFA 15 brings football to life in stunning detail so fans can experience the emotion of the sport like never before. Witness the intensity of crowds chanting and cheering like on match day, and listen to commentators guide fans through the story of the game with Dynamic Match Presentation.<br><br>For the first time ever, all 22 players on the pitch are connected with Emotional Intelligence - now players will react to opponents and teammates within the context, and relative to the narrative of the match. Authentic Player Visuals make players lean, athletic, and true to their real-life appearance. Player Control heightens the responsiveness of player movement, gives athletes more control and personality on the ball, and makes Man-to-Man Battles more rewarding than ever before.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TnTYVT6lwBc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LY3Y_hhRCLQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/FIFA-15/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1245,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Playground Games", "Sumo Digital", "Turn 10 Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Race through a massive wide-open world featuring dramatic weather and day-to-night cycle in Forza Horizon 2. Instantly connect with friends in the ultimate celebration of speed, style, and action-packed driving. Explore beautiful and exotic locations in more than 200 of the world's greatest cars, all created with precise detail in stunning 1080p.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AX7r61fyltc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KSgyJqecz-4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9OTSj-vzkRA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hvv96IjpLk0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Forza-Horizon-2/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1246,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Sofia"],
			"synopsis":"18th century, North America. Amidst the chaos and violence of the French and Indian War, Shay Patrick Cormac, a fearless young member of the Brotherhood of Assassins, undergoes a dark transformation that will forever shape the future of the American colonies. After a dangerous mission gone tragically wrong, Shay turns his back on the Assassins who, in response, attempt to end his life.<br><br>Assassin's Creed: Rogue is the darkest chapter in the Assassin's Creed franchise yet. Follow your own creed and set off on an extraordinary journey through New York City, the wild river valley, and far away to the icy cold waters of the North Atlantic in pursuit of your ultimate goal -- bringing down the Assassins for good. For the first time ever, experience the Assassin's Creed universe from the perspective of a Templar. The acclaimed naval components from previous Assassin's Creed games have been enhanced in Assassin's Creed Rogue. The game also gives players new weapons to use on both land and sea in pursuit of taking down the Assassins, including a new ship called the Morrigan.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bjSy5kF6io0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rJ5JTk1K60A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RDeyI31pG8A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tUdU5ogSwtg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/826287-assassins-creed-rogue/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Assassins-Creed-Rogue/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/assassins-creed-rogue"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Assassin's Creed Wiki",
				"url":"http://assassinscreed.wikia.com/wiki/Assassin's_Creed:_Rogue"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1247,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bandai Namco Games"],
			"synopsis":"Following the colorful characters and world of the animated series, Pac-Man and the Ghostly Adventures 2 will feature Pac, Spiral and Cylindria in an all-new storyline as they defend PacWorld from the ghoulish army of Lord Betrayus. Players will be able to explore the lands of PacWorld far beyond the bustling streets of Pacopolis and the Netherworld through the depths of the ocean floor and into space.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qdcdl2asm0s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BjDzYm9jzxo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UPZ8zwyYh9k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9_c7RzMHuTk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=smQ0HrVpkrc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4h0sw6pT8lk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/PAC-MAN-and-the-Ghostly-Adventures-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pac-man-and-the-ghostly-adventures-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pac-man-and-the-ghostly-adventures-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Pac-Man Wiki",
				"url":"http://pacman.wikia.com/wiki/Pac-Man_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1248,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Little Orbit"],
			"synopsis":"When aliens invade the Earth, who will rise up to save humankind?Lead the revolution in this tactical strategy RPG set in the tense, gritty world of the critically acclaimed sci-fi TV series. Players will dive into a world gone wrong and command a squad of recently-rescued survivors who have been recruited into the human resistance fighting to save the planet. The team will engage in covert tactical operations against the Espheni fighting to survive against alien invaders while also rescuing and recruiting survivors to the join the 2nd Mass. With addictive strategy-based gameplay, players will be immersed into the unique story line with all their favorite heroes from the show.<br><br>With engaging tactical combat and an immersive story driven experience, Falling Skies will offer players a never-ending list of missions as they join the 2nd Mass and fight the alien invasion including Mechs, Skitters and Harnessed Humans. With hundreds of character skills and equipment upgrades to unlock, players can engage in tactical combat and take different approaches to achieve game-changing objectives. Falling Skies will also feature dynamic enemy AI and map randomization designed to make every mission feel new and fresh.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AmX8MqFC02w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iLlDvdxSp_A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xTNqxF-A6H4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Falling-Skies/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/falling-skies-the-game"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Falling Skies Wiki",
				"url":"http://fallingskies.wikia.com/wiki/Falling_Skies_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1249,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Frogwares"],
			"synopsis":"Experience the adventures of the great detective Sherlock Holmes like never before with Sherlock Holmes: Crimes & Punishments, the first game in the series designed in Unreal Engine 3 for an evolutionary leap in graphic detail. Environments is more realistic and finely detailed with dynamic lighting and shadows. Powerful new visual systems allow for smooth movement and motion transitions, real-time shaders and a particle system, and advanced post-processing effects.<br><br>Unlike the previous adventures of Sherlock Holmes, in Crimes and Punishments you will not be a mere spectator during the detective's investigation. It is now your turn to truly become Sherlock Holmes and lead your own investigation-actually, your investigations, as 8 captivating cases await you! Murders, disappearances, spectacular thefts, and other investigations will bring you to the cutting edge of the detective genre. Each case, written in the pure tradition of Conan Doyle's novels, offers real freedom to players, who will have to make important moral choices instead of simply enforcing justice by the book. All decisions have an influence in the game and affect your character's reputation in addition to having realistic, sometimes unexpected, consequences. You will have to bear the weight of your choices, as Crimes and Punishments offers an exciting system of actions/consequences that forces players to think before acting by giving true depth to every decision they make.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0UqKRpr-duQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rHIkWwOwzzQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8_HwkgY0D5A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gwfzSI9Nn5U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sherlock-Holmes-Crimes-and-Punishments/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Baker Street Wiki",
				"url":"http://bakerstreet.wikia.com/wiki/Sherlock_Holmes:_Crimes_%26_Punishments"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1250,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Nordic Games Publishing"],
			"synopsis":"Marking the revival of the best-selling MX vs. ATV racing series, MX vs. ATV Supercross is centered around the high-flying, mud-churning Supercross sport.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iu_o-tISARk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=109GCjd-arw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iBhbPtRibaI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MX-vs-ATV-Supercross/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mx-vs-atv-supercross"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1251,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["MileStone"],
			"synopsis":"Sakura Flamingo Archives is a Miscellaneous game, developed by MileStone Inc. and published by Klon Co., Ltd., which was released in Japan in 2014.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q-Bea_E3Gxs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sakura-Flamingo-Archives/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1252,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["WayForward Technologies"],
			"synopsis":"Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Danger of the Ooze brings together new locations, allies and threats! The game quickly heats up as Shredder, Tiger Claw and a new army of mutants threaten the streets of New York, forcing Leonardo, Raphael, Donatello and Michelangelo to take action into their own hands. The game's distinguishing feature is its vast, interconnected, non-linear game world, which rewards exploration and creative thinking. Powers, upgrades and equipment scattered across New York and Dimension X opens up new environments to traverse, secrets to discover and bosses to battle.<br><br>All four Turtles can be swapped between freely throughout the adventure, and each has his own unique rhythm, with specialized stats, strengths and skills. Combat is fast-paced, emphasizing the gang's martial arts prowess through attack and item combos, counters and finishers, but also provides tools for stealth-based approaches to avoid or tackle enemies.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=56Y8UDkc3wA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VB5J0RvGs5E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Teenage-Mutant-Ninja-Turtles-Danger-of-the-Ooze/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-danger-of-the-ooze"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Turtlepedia",
				"url":"http://turtlepedia.wikia.com/wiki/Teenage_Mutant_Ninja_Turtles:_Danger_of_the_Ooze"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1253,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft"],
			"synopsis":"Ubisoft and Aardman join together for this animated series based on the popular Rabbids video game characters. Originally developed as a TV series, Rabbids Invasion instead goes beyond just TV to deliver interactive sequences for use with Kinect that play over the show!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IEOaBIoFL1I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XYA3jEc3ALM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rabbids-Invasion-The-Interactive-TV-Show/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Raving Rabbids Wiki",
				"url":"http://ravingrabbids.wikia.com/wiki/Rabbids_Invasion:_The_Interactive_TV_show"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1254,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["TT Games"],
			"synopsis":"In LEGO Batman 3: Beyond Gotham, the Caped Crusader joins forces with the super heroes of the DC Comics Universe and blasts off to outer space to stop the evil Brainiac from destroying Earth. Using the power of the Lantern Rings, Brainiac shrinks worlds to add to his twisted collection of miniature cities from across the universe. Now the greatest super heroes and the most cunning villains must unite and journey to different Lantern Worlds to collect the Lantern Rings and stop Brainiac before it's too late.<br><br>Players will unlock more than 150 unique characters from the DC Comics universe, including members of the Justice League and LEGO big figures such as Killer Croc, Solomon Grundy and many more. Fans of all ages will be able to control their favorite heroes and villains with new gadgets and abilities. Brainiac's mind controlling abilities and the power of the Lantern rings bring unexpected twists to the classic characters' personalities.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Man of Steel Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/11",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Help Jor-El, his wife Lara and their robot Kelex send the infant Superman \"Kal-el\" into space towards the safety of Earth as Krypton falls into chaos. Find a way inside Jor-El's home, fight General Zod's invading forces and battle against Zod himself to save Superman."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Dark Knight Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/11",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Experience the heart-pounding chase scene from the iconic film complete with cool vehicles and explosive action. Play as the legendary Dark Knight and Commissioner Gordon, as well as the Joker and his goons as they chase down Harvey Dent's police escort. Bane and Catwoman from the third film are also playable."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"75th Anniversary Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/11",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Play as Joker and Harley Quinn, setting up a variety of celebration set pieces. Be the Dark Knight and play as some of the most iconic faces of Batman through the years, including his first appearance in Detective Comics #27."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TWbhbOgEtl4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7bsHsp2WXUI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1jkbBA27zSs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J95z43E3WfY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/LEGO-Batman-3-Beyond-Gotham/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lego-batman-3-beyond-gotham"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Brickipedia",
				"url":"http://lego.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Batman_3:_Beyond_Gotham"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Batman Wiki",
				"url":"http://batman.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Batman_3:_Beyond_Gotham"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1255,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Fatshark"],
			"synopsis":"Explore the quarantined island of Narapela and get to the bottom of the sinister zombie virus plaguing humanity in Escape Dead Island, a survival mystery game set in the Dead Island universe. In this action-packed single-player game, fans will take on the role of ambitious Cliff Calo, son of a wealthy media empire mogul with a chip on his shoulder and something to prove, as he traverses across the globe to Banoi after hearing about the gruesome events that took place in the original global best-seller, Dead Island. Can Cliff uncover the clandestine origins of the virus and get out before it's too late?<br><br>Splashed across your screen in a bold comic-vignette art style, Escape Dead Island emphasizes a story driven plot which pits players against their own psyche as they try to escape the island and the cryptic, looping horrors that lurk there. Penned by Emmy award-winning author Anne Toole, Escape Dead Island catapults Dead Island fans onto a lush tropical island infested with brutal zombies where only cunning stealth can help players retain their sanity.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L51ipbzVhNU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CpaXg1p-yoA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Escape-Dead-Island/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/escape-dead-island"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dead Island Wiki",
				"url":"http://deadisland.wikia.com/wiki/Escape_Dead_Island"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1256,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Avalanche Software"],
			"synopsis":"Heroes and villains. Sorcerers and superheroes. Princesses and pirates. Disney Infinity invites you and your family to enter those worlds in game experiences only Disney, Marvel - and your imagination - can bring to life. With the new Toy Box 2.0, players can mix, match and mash up characters and worlds to create any adventure they can imagine! Use the new Creator tool to quickly build your worlds with ease. Create and share Toy Boxes online. Connect your Toy Box creations with friends. Play without limits!<br><br>Disney Infinity: Marvel Super Heroes will take players deep into the Marvel Universe with classic characters and original storylines - all while offering players more opportunity for unprecedented freedom and endless possibilities to create new adventures. Fans will also have hundreds of Marvel-themed items, locations, props, and characters at their disposal to create their own stories or even re-create their favorite comic book moments. Players use real-world interactive Marvel figures to activate original storylines (Play Sets) in the Disney Infinity virtual game worlds of some of Marvel's most popular franchises. In the Play Set - penned by award-winning Marvel comic writer Brian Michael Bendis - players will be able to take on the role of more than 20 Marvel character, including Captain America, Black Widow, Thor, Hulk, and Hawkeye, as they battle enemies, complete challenging missions, solve puzzles, and ultimately save the world from destruction.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W1P3b4YU8so"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=26eN6jxdK5g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WtiVKvdfh0I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f8UHRDPQYac"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/792569-disney-infinity-20-edition/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Disney-Infinity-Marvel-Super-Heroes-2-0-Edition/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/disney-infinity-20-edition"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1257,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["WayForward Technologies"],
			"synopsis":"What time is it? It's time for an Adventure Time video game! The third installment in the mathematical Adventure Time video game franchise, Adventure Time: The Secret of the Nameless Kingdom introduces a classic top-down action adventure experience and puzzle-solving element to the franchise.<br><br>Players take on the personas of both Finn and Jake as they navigate through the eponymous kingdom - a mysterious unexplored region in the Land of Ooo. They will discover hidden secrets by exploring all corners of a new kingdom created exclusively for the game and encounter never-seen-before characters and creatures.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n8wyM4nH2p4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n4CNDof1ou0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bj3LiXsZdO4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Adventure-Time-The-Secret-of-the-Nameless-Kingdom/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/adventure-time-the-secret-of-the-nameless-kingdom"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Adventure Time Wiki",
				"url":"http://adventuretime.wikia.com/wiki/Adventure_Time:_The_Secret_of_the_Nameless_Kingdom"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1258,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Reflections", "Ivory Tower", "Asobo Studio"],
			"synopsis":"Take part in a relentless ride to infiltrate and overtake the 510s, a gang grown around Detroit's illegal street racing scene. Your plan? Get a rep on the underground-racing scene and sabotage their activities city-by-city all across the United States. Maneuver through the bustling streets of New York City and Los Angeles, cruise down sunny Miami Beach or trek through the breathtaking plateaus of Monument Valley. Each locale comes with its own set of surprises and driving challenges to master. On your journey you will encounter other players on the road - all potentially worthy companions to crew up with, or future rivals to compete against. This is driving at its most exciting, varied and open.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ISys5W-WOM8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d4JnshyKOOQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LVDUbfdfBPk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WibVKyF78RE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-yMd4Oj1-wo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Crew-Xbox-360/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Crew Wiki",
				"url":"http://thecrew.wikia.com/wiki/THE_CREW_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1259,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Winning Eleven Productions"],
			"synopsis":"PES 2015 elevates on-field realism with the aim of recreating the drama and tension associated with vital matches. PES 2015 marks a concerted return to core PES values of total control, utterly responsive controls and unrestricted gameplay, where the user has complete control over how they play. Evert pass, shot or run is finely balanced to give maximum player satisfaction within PES 2015's on-field action.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PdZTnek1ZAw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vq1XRbds4uo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pro-Evolution-Soccer-2015-Xbox-360/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pro-evolution-soccer-2015"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1260,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Paris"],
			"synopsis":"The world's top selling dance video game and a mainstay of popular culture is back again with Just Dance 2015, bringing hot moves and new features to 40+ current hit songs and throwback favorite tunes. Let loose with friends and family by dancing to hit songs like \"Happy\" by Pharrell Williams and \"Burn\" by Ellie Goulding. Staying true to the Just Dance personality, there are also legendary favorites like \"Walk This Way\" by Run DMC & Aerosmith and a chance to dance to Tetris moves! Get ready for this year's fun and quirky dance moves that have something for everyone in your family or group of friends.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"\"One Way Or Another (Teenage Kicks)\" by One Direction",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download all-new moves from \"One Way Or Another (Teenage Kicks)\" by One Direction!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"\"Roar\" by Katy Perry",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download all-new moves from \"Roar\" by Katy Perry!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"\"I Need Your Love\" by Calvin Harris Ft. Ellie Goulding",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download all-new moves from \"I Need Your Love\" by Calvin Harris Ft. Ellie Goulding!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"\"I Luh Ya Papi\" by Jennifer Lopez Ft. French Montana",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download all-new moves from \"I Luh Ya Papi\" by Jennifer Lopez Ft. French Montana!"
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"\"Break Free\" by Ariana Grande Ft. Zedd",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download all-new moves from \"Break Free\" by Ariana Grande Ft. Zedd!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"\"Wake Me Up\" by Avicii",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download all-new moves from \"Wake Me Up\" by Avicii!"
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"\"Papaoutai\" by Stromae",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download a brand new choreography for \"Papaoutai\" by \"Stromae\"!"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"\"Moves Like Jagger\" by Maroon 5 Ft. Christina Aguilera",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download all-new moves from \"Moves Like Jagger\" by Maroon 5 Ft. Christina Aguilera!"
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"\"Beauty and a Beat\" by Justin Bieber Ft. Nicki Minaj",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download all-new moves from \"Beauty and a Beat\" by Justin Bieber Ft. Nicki Minaj!"
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"\"Gangnam Style\" by PSY",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download all-new moves from \"Gangnam Style\" by PSY!"
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"\"Don't You Worry Child\" by Swedish House Mafia",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download a brand new choreography for \"Don't You Worry Child\" by \"Swedish House Mafia\"!"
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"\"Just Dance\" by Lady Gaga Ft. Colby O'Donis",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download all-new moves from \"Just Dance\" by Lady Gaga Ft. Colby O'Donis!"
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"\"Die Young\" by Ke$ha",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download all-new moves from \"Die Young\" by Ke$ha!"
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"\"Sexy And I know It\" by LMFAO",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download all-new moves from \"Sexy And I know It\" by LMFAO!"
			},
			{
				"id":15,
				"name":"\"Funhouse\" by P!nk",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/25",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download a brand new choreography for \"Funhouse\" by \"P!nk\"!"
			},
			{
				"id":16,
				"name":"\"Kiss You\" by One Direction",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/25",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download a brand new choreography for \"Kiss You\" by \"One Direction\"!"
			},
			{
				"id":17,
				"name":"\"We Can't Stop\" by Miley Cyrus",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/25",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download a brand new choreography for \"We Can't Stop\" by \"Miley Cyrus\"!"
			},
			{
				"id":18,
				"name":"\"C'mon\" by Ke$ha",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/25",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download a brand new choreography for \"C'mon\" by \"Ke$ha\"!"
			},
			{
				"id":19,
				"name":"\"Want U Back\" by Cher Lloyd Ft. Astro",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/25",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Share the power of dance and download a brand new choreography for \"Want U Back\" by \"Cher Lloyd Ft. Astro\"!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RNv9ekQfHxM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pc2XBLLr9s4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TczCbjuux5M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QPqOWA2GyBc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vz3Bb-E0pyI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Just-Dance-2015/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Just Dance Wiki",
				"url":"http://justdance.wikia.com/wiki/Just_Dance_2015"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1261,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FUN Labs"],
			"synopsis":"Hunt, race and prank to become a Robertson! Interact with Willie, Uncle Si, Jase and the rest of the family from the hit TV show Duck Dynasty. Take on the role of Willie's son John Luke as he learns how to become one of the Robertson men! Go duck hunting, varmint shooting, off-roading and play office pranks in the Robertson's hometown of West Monroe, LA. Will you learn the way of the beards?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XZjUyR26KKs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LpRS__8LiaQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/847457-duck-dynasty/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Duck-Dynasty/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1262,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Codemasters Studios Birmingham"],
			"synopsis":"F1 2014 recreates this year's racing season and features new turbocharged cars, new circuits plus all the driver moves.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EDkvNrQpLeg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mQhodi6z3Tg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/F1-2014/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/f1-2014"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1263,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["bitComposer Games"],
			"synopsis":"Take the stage and be heard with The Voice, a single and multiplayer singing video game based on the Emmy Award-winning music competition TV series. Impress the coaches and watch them compete for you to join their team! From the Blind Auditions to the Battle Rounds, all the way to the Finale, experience the show with the ultimate goal of being named \"The Voice\". In Party Mode, battle together or against seven of your friends singing chart-topping hits spanning Rock, R&B, Pop and Country genres! Singers can also practice real-world techniques in Voice Coach Mode like singing runs and harmonizing, with the game offering neat tips and tricks to help with each performance like breathing, harmonizing and singing on perfect pitch. The Voice features different popular music genres - Rock, R&B, Pop and Country - including chart-topping hits from your favorite acts!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LfsAbhRW4JM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CtZFz2RWExE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Voice/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1264,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Milestone"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the Official MotoGP World Championship motorcycle racing series, MotoGP 14 features more than 100 available riders, all the official manufacturers, all racing classes and 18 tracks. The game allows you to customize your racing experience by creating your own unique rider and selecting your race options. Whether it is a quick race or a full-weekend event tearing through the tracks, the choice is yours. By changing teams, landing supporting sponsors, and growing a loyal fan base, you are able to manage your very own racing career. MotoGP 14 gives you the chance to live the dream of being in the shoes of a real rider.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Donington Park British Grand Prix",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/04",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"The MotoGP 14 Donington Park British Grand Prix pack adds this sensational circuit to the game. Take on your opponents in Grand Prix and Championship modes!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Laguna Seca Red Bull US Grand Prix",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/04",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"The MotoGP 14 Laguna Seca Red Bull US Grand Prix pack adds this sensational circuit to the game. Take on your opponents in Grand Prix and Championship modes!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Red Bull Rookies Cup",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/04",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"The Red Bull Rookies Cup will add the game this exciting competition."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Moto2 and Moto3",
				"releaseDate":"2014/11/04",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Enhance your game experience with this free additional content, completing the rosters for the Moto2 and Moto3 classes, updated for the 2014 season. Immerse yourself even more deeply into the world of the MotoGP!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8nQiqyUd5oA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=equNpCSGuaM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MotoGP-14/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/motogp-14"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1265,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Prope"],
			"synopsis":"In Digimon All-Star Rumble, the Digital World enjoys a time of restored peace after overcoming numerous wars and crises. However, Digimon must battle to Digivolve, so the restless Digimon propose to hold their first ever \"Digimon Evolution Tournament\" to determine who is the strongest of them all.<br><br>In the vivaciously competitive tournament, up to four players will be able to select from a roster of 12 popular base Digimon characters and play as a total of 32 Digimon forms pulled from every Digimon series ranging from Digimon Adventure to Digimon Fusion. By powering up in battle, players can Digivolve into a much more powerful form, creating a unique combat atmosphere where players must balance attacking and simultaneously attempt to Digivolve and gain the upper hand. Utilizing special techniques during matches such as activating a Digimon's \"Evolution\" power-up along with employing an aggressive attack or defensive strategy will provide colorful and exciting party-arena gameplay so that Digimon fans of all ages can face-off against rivals and become a true Digimon hero!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tB4Boq48uAA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cdf30O8BjTQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wehO247xV1o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Digimon-All-Star-Rumble/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Digimon Wiki",
				"url":"http://digimon.wikia.com/wiki/Digimon_All-Star_Rumble"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1266,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Milestone"],
			"synopsis":"Dust, emotion, simulation, authenticity, amazing jumps and the fight to the first position. These are the key elements of MXGP, The Official Motocross Videogame, based on one of the most adrenaline filled and challenging Championship events ever. The aim? Win the World championship title match by match. Authentic racing features have been included into the game that will inspire Motocross lovers and race fans. MXGP features all the riders, teams, bikes and rules from the official MXGP 2013 calendar including a redesigned career mode for living the feelings of the Motocross.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=abEj7oZVO6A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cucBxPpvzio"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZpxJNeSACvE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MXGP-The-Official-Motocross-Videogame/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mxgp/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mxgp-the-official-motocross-videogame"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1267,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["HB Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Take the helm of official teams and clubs from the most prestigious leagues: the Aviva Premiership Rugby, the PRO 12 and, in a world exclusive, the TOP 14 and PRO D2! In addition to being able to play friendly matches either solo or with other players, rugby fans will also be able to take part in the official championships of 4 major European leagues: TOP 14, Aviva Premiership Rugby, PRO 12 and PRO D2. All of the teams and rules for each of these championships are faithfully respected, and players will have to battle in order to raise the Brennus Shield or to become champions of England. For this first in the series, Rugby 15 also includes 20 of the major national teams and 15 southern hemisphere teams, although without the official licences. There is an editor mode as well, so the most dedicated fans can find the most famous names in these teams. Finally, 'Custom tournament' mode lets players create their own competitions by setting the rules (number of participants, type of competition, playoff, knock-out...) and giving you the chance to mix and match all of the teams in the game. Give full rein to your imagination and create the league of your dreams!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-_uxWuhrhyc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BLGzV3pwusQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/RUGBY-15/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1268,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1269,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1270,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1271,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1272,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1273,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1274,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1275,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1276,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1277,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1278,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1279,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1280,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1281,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1282,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1283,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1284,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1285,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1286,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1287,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1288,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1289,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1290,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1291,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1292,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1293,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1294,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1295,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1296,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1297,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1298,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1299,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1300,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":[""],
			"synopsis":"",
			"links":[
			{
			}]
		}
	}]
}