{
	"catalog": [
	{
		"id":601,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts", "Kush Games"],
			"synopsis":"In NBA 2K11, players can experience what it's like to play in Michael Jordan's shoes! Relive 10 different legendary games from Michael Jordan's career and replicate in NBA 2K11 what MJ did on the court, and even unlock MJ: Creating a Legend, a special mode where you get to take control of a newly drafted rookie Michael Jordan and craft your own version of Michael's career in the NBA. Players can also experience what it's like to be part of some of the greatest teams in NBA history as the 1985-86, 1989-90, 1990-91, 1991-92, 1994-95, 1995-96, 1996-97, and 1997-98 Chicago Bulls.<br><br>NBA 2K11 features IsoMotion Dribbling Controls, Shot Control, a deeper My Player mode, NBA Today 2.0 (which now includes a halftime show recapping not only your in-game highlights but also real NBA scores and player stats from around the league) and much more.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lo9nlAveToc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aIy9_558v3k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a9mtAHiSj2E"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/987827-nba-2k11/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-2K11/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-2k11/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-2k11"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":602,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Spellbound"],
			"synopsis":"Arcania is a Fantasy Action game set in a rich world where an entire kingdom's future is at stake Build your strength and learn the skills needed to become a hero as you challenge a mighty king and uncover his dark secrets. Travel through a land of different climate zones, abundant flora and fauna, subterranean vaults, and unique towns and castles where clouds darken the skies, weather effects such as wind and heavy rain influence an endlessly fascinating game world, day and night cycles, and a stunning display of light and shadow. As you battle the monsters and villains of the land and meet a host of unique characters, will you be able to right the King's wrongdoings and, above all, what choices will lead you there?",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Fall of Setarrif",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/03",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Argaan's fate teeters on the edge of your sword! A mysterious demon roams the east, threatening the coastal city of Setarrif. At the same time King Rhobar III orders his armies to attack this last stronghold of the rebels. To top it all off, a volcano erupts near the troubled region. All this can't be coincidence: only the unnamed Hero and his strongest allies can decide the upcoming struggle in the East. Immerse yourself into an exciting adventure amidst demonic powers, political intrigue and inscrutable incidents! - Follow a new, compelling story for more than 10 hours. - PLAY as each of your 4 famous allies and use their unique skills! - All new enemies & monsters as well as items  & weapons to further expand and hone your combat skills. - Meet new, lively characters when exploring the unknown regions & dungeons. - The time for true heroes has finally come!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_kqSKQbEFz4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_kqSKQbEFz4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Obk64H0-BIs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/ArcaniA-Gothic-4/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/arcania-gothic-4/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/arcania-gothic-4"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":603,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Immersion Games"],
			"synopsis":"Lucha Libre AAA: H&eacute;roes del Ring is a sports-wrestling game where up to four players can experience the world of Mexican Lucha Libre style wrestling from the perspective of luchadores from Mexico's AAA wrestling league. Whether playing as part of the online Lucha Libre community or against friends at home, each action-packed match features all of the colorful characters, acrobatic moves and dynamic popularity-based combat style which differentiates Lucha Libre from its American counterparts.<br><br>Featuring high quality graphics and game mechanics developed in conjunction with Lucha Libre legend El Apache, AAA Lucha Libre: Heroes del Ring captures the essence of this new style of sports entertainment in culturally rich environments representative of Mexican culture.<br><br>It's Not Wrestling. It's Lucha Libre.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Khez7NjvW8c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qyhImrpPV5Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/995068-lucha-libre-aaa-heroes-del-ring/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lucha-Libre-AAA/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lucha-libre-aaa-heroes-of-the-ring/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lucha-libre-aaa-heroes-del-ring"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":604,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Danger Close", "DICE"],
			"synopsis":"Medal of Honor leaves the WWII theater and enters the modern day setting of war-torn Afghanistan seen though the lens of a small band of fictional characters.<br><br>The new Medal of Honor introduces players to the Tier 1 Operator, an elite warrior and relatively unknown instrument of the U.S. Military that operates under the National Command Authority, taking on missions no one else can handle. In addition to a full single-player campaign mode, developer EALA has enlisted Battlefield creator EA DICE to supply the multiplayer experience of Medal of Honor. The game features a weapon customization system and a range of tactical and team-based modes for up to 24 players, including Team Assault, Combat Mission, and more.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Clean Sweep Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/02",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Download the Multiplayer Mode, Clean Sweep, along with two brand new maps called Bagram Hangar and Khyler Caves. Put your skills to the test in this last-man-standing game mode."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Hot Zone Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/02",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Download the completely new mode, Hot Zone which includes 2 brand new maps, Hindukush Pass and Korengal Outpost, as well as 2 resdesigned original maps. Hotzone is as intense as it gets with coordinated all-out annihilation followed by strategic dug-in defense. Your mission is simple, control the area."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HigXVoGpU24"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jbfNiDdnVYA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XtuYkPBzxwE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/980769-medal-of-honor/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Medal-of-Honor/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/medal-of-honor/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/medal-of-honor"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Medal of Honor Wiki",
				"url":"http://medalofhonor.wikia.com/wiki/Medal_of_Honor_(2010)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":605,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Papaya Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Ben 10 Ultimate Alien: Cosmic Destruction allows players to wield the power of the Ultimatrix, the strongest Omnitrix to date, to transform Ben into more powerful, hyper-evolved alien forms and experience impressive battles as the most ultimate aliens. Take control of Ben Tennyson and his many alien forms as they journey to iconic worldwide locales, including Paris, Tokyo, China, and Rome, in search of an ancient alien artifact that will help save humanity from a mysterious cosmic storm.<br><br>Players will wield the power of the all-new Ultimatrix, an upgraded alien watch that transforms Ben into the most powerful, hyper-evolved alien forms ever available in the series. All-new ultimate events will empower players to defeat bosses through stylized cut-scenes and hard-hitting combat interactions, and the upgrade system will allow players to enhance their favorite alien character's strength, speed, defense, and special attacks.<br><br>As a bonus, players will receive the quick and fiery Rath with the Xbox 360 version.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gjhXu1q4RYw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F6ALOnBn4sU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/995982-ben-10-ultimate-alien-cosmic-destruction/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ben-10-Ultimate-Alien/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ben-10-ultimate-alien-cosmic-destruction/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ben-10-ultimate-alien-cosmic-destruction"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Ben 10 Planet",
				"url":"http://ben10.wikia.com/wiki/Ben_10_Ultimate_Alien:_Cosmic_Destruction"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":606,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FreeStyleGames"],
			"synopsis":"Picking up where the award-winning DJ Hero soundtrack left off, DJ Hero 2 spins together the hottest tracks blazing up the charts and legendary club anthems from the biggest artists in pop, dance and hip hop including Dr. Dre, The Chemical Brothers, Kanye West, Metallica, Lady Gaga, Rihanna and over 85 others.<br><br>Fueling the party will be a host of social multiplayer game modes and innovative freestyle gameplay giving virtual DJ's the ability to crossfade, scratch and sample in over 70 speaker-blowing mashups from the hottest DJ's and Producers around the world, including Deadmau5 - part of dance music's elite - who will be starring as an in-game playable character.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QQoQQegxthk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tj9gcdUD2zM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1YmVRPmP5VQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/DJ-Hero-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dj-hero-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dj-hero-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"DJ Hero Wiki",
				"url":"http://djhero.wikia.com/wiki/DJ_Hero_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":607,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"In EA Sports MMA, choose from the world's top fighters or climb the ranks of the worldwide circuit with your created prodigy to become the ultimate MMA champion.<br><br>Travel the globe and learn a multitude of fighting techniques and skills from masters in each discipline. Select from various weight classes, rule sets, and take on all challengers in multiple cage types or a ring. The challenge continues online with the ability to create and share custom fighters, prize fights, and more. Are you ready? Let's get it on.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w7d965LFgsQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KvGGSY5bNLs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/EA-Sports-MMA/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ea-sports-mma/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ea-sports-mma"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":608,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Obsidian Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Experience all the sights and sounds of fabulous New Vegas, brought to you by Vault-Tec, America's First Choice in Post Nuclear Simulation. Explore the treacherous wastes of the Great Southwest from the safety and comfort of your very own vault: Meet new people, confront terrifying creatures, and arm yourself with the latest high-tech weaponry as you make a name for yourself on a thrilling new journey across the Mojave wasteland.<br><br>From Bethesda Softworks and the veteran RPG designers at Obsidian Entertainment (a team which includes members of the original Fallout and 2 teams) comes Fallout: New Vegas, a thrilling and chilling episode in the Fallout saga.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Courier's Stash",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/27",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Wake up in the Mojave Wasteland with an edge. Courier's Stash gives players immediate access to four content bundles previously available only through pre-ordering Fallout: New Vegas. The Caravan Pack, Classic Pack, Mercenary Pack and Tribal Pack each offer unique weapons, apparel and aid advantages that will help you throughout your journey."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Gun Runners Arsenal",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/27",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The famous weapons manufacturer, Gun Runners, has opened up their exclusive cache of armaments, including new weapons, weapon mods, ammo types and recipes. Their inventory doesn't come without a price, though. Trek far and wide throughout the Mojave Wasteland in search of this elite class of weapons that range from the outrageously potent to the bizarrely impractical."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Dead Money",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/22",
				"achievements":140,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Welcome to the Sierra Madre Casino! The casino's mythical contents are lusted after by desperate wasteland scavengers, who tell stories of intact treasure of the old world buried deep within its vault. Lured here by a mysterious radio signal advertising the long-awaited grand opening of the casino, you are thrown into a high stakes game where you'll have to work with three other lost souls if you want to survive."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Honest Hearts",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/17",
				"achievements":140,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"In Honest Hearts, an expedition into the unspoiled wilderness of Utah's Zion National Park goes horribly wrong when your caravan is ambushed by a tribal raiding band. As you try to find a way back to the Mojave you become embroiled in a war between tribes and a conflict between a New Canaanite missionary and the mysterious Burned Man. The decisions you make will determine the fate of Zion."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Old World Blues",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/19",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"In Old World Blues, you are transported to the Big MT research crater and find you're the only hope of saving the Think Tank - the strange group of post-human researchers who inhabit the facility. Recover all the weapons, armor, and tech of the Pre-War era and use them to help save all of Science!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Lonesome Road",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/20",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"In Lonesome Road you are contacted by the original Courier Six. He promises to answer why he refused to deliver the Platinum Chip--but only if you make one last journey into the canyons of the Divide. Bring all your gear and weapons but leave your companions behind...this is one road you must walk alone."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l-x-1fm2cq8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5MJLFcqrC8w"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/959557-fallout-new-vegas/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fallout-New-Vegas/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fallout-new-vegas/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fallout-new-vegas"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Fallout Wiki",
				"url":"http://fallout.wikia.com/wiki/Fallout:_New_Vegas"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":609,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["CyberConnect2"],
			"synopsis":"Naruto: Ultimate Ninja Storm 2 faithfully recreates the anime series and envelops players into the mythical world of ninja with expansive environments, missions, battle systems and gameplay modes. While there are two sides to every story, Naruto: Ultimate Ninja Storm 2 has three, that have players living different as well as daring ninja lives through the eyes of Naruto, Sasuke and Jiraya.<br><br>With more than 40 characters to choose from, engaging in bigger and more epic cinematic boss battles has never been this explosive. The game also delivers an improved Support Character system which allows players to link jutsus for wild ninja punishment and awards compatibility bonuses according to the strategic selection of ally recruits. To provide a true ultimate experience, the game also offers various online features where players can sharpen their skills or flex their fighting muscle to defeat rival ninja from around the world.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r5F-BLLChoM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jXgyqPFcXjc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/982705-naruto-shippuden-ultimate-ninja-storm-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Naruto-Ultimate-Ninja-Storm-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/naruto-shippuden-ultimate-ninja-storm-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/naruto-shippuden-ultimate-ninja-storm-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Narutopedia",
				"url":"http://naruto.wikia.com/wiki/Naruto_Shipp%C5%ABden%3A_Ultimate_Ninja_Storm_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":610,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Seven45 Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Power Gig: Rise of the SixString will transport players to an entirely new universe, with its own mythology, politics, settings, heroes and villains, where music rules all.<br><br>On the gameplay front, Power Gig uses technology that represents the next evolution of music performance games to provide all players - from casual gamers to the hardcore, from those who have never before picked up a guitar to those who play guitar on a regular basis - with a more authentic and fun experience. The game offers two overarching modes of play. In addition to traditional beat-matching that will be familiar to fans of the band game genre, Power Gig also introduces the option to switch on chording, or chord play.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YrGS_RJhN-I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3n78JbMe_wM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/PowerGig/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/power-gig-rise-of-the-six-string/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/power-gig-rise-of-the-sixstring"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":611,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Winning Eleven Productions"],
			"synopsis":"Pro Evolution Soccer 2011 reinvigorates the series with the most advanced set of improved gameplay additions, control options and to catch up with the evolution of the real-life soccer. Central to its total freedom of play, the game introduces a power bar for each player that allows the user to determine the exact strength and placement of every pass and shot. Balls can now be spread absolutely anywhere with surgical precision, with long balls into space, short passes to feet, and intricate one-twos allowing the player to dictate play and control the tempo of a match.<br><br>This freedom of play is also extended via AI routines designed to place every move and decision into the player's hands. No longer will assisted AI intervene during matches; users will now need to sense and react to threats intuitively as opposed to chasing the ball; and passes will not automatically reach the nearest player. Instead, routines facilitate complete control both of the player and their chosen actions in every respect to give the player sublime control over every movement.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FrAtq0LDG-g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U-oF-L5AwjY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/995948-pro-evolution-soccer-2011/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pro-Evolution-Soccer-2011/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pes-2011/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pro-evolution-soccer-2011"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":612,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Epicenter Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Grab your axe and jump off stage as you transcend from aspiring musician to global rock god! The planet is under attack, and the only chance we have is through the power of rock! Use rippin' riffs to unleash sonic blasts on hordes of flesh eaters! Grab a buddy and play through the story-based campaign in two-player competitive co-op with guitars, drums or both! Rock out to a soundtrack featuring metalized versions of Bach, Brahms and other classical pieces as well as Rob Zombie and White Zombie hard-hitting tracks. With a cast of characters voiced by Neil Patrick Harris, Felicia Day and Rob Zombie, huge boss battles and dozens of unlockables and upgradeable special attacks, the fate of the planet is in your hands!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=biO5HhxHXOc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dix6GCop1fg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8n9G-0DOK5g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rock-of-the-Dead/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rock-of-the-dead/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rock-of-the-dead"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":613,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Zombie Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Step into the dark and tormented world of Saw 2 and experience the gruesome traps that Jigsaw has created to test your will to survive. With new traps, puzzles, and combat system players will need to think fast and act quick to pass the rigors of the tests Jigsaw has engineered. Set between the Saw and Saw II movies, the game follows Detective Tapp's estranged son Michael, who become Jigsaw's next subject while he is investigating father's recent death.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J2sQniAvvqw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CzoeSRQBeRc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/995071-saw-ii-flesh-and-blood/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Saw-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/saw-2-flesh-and-blood/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/saw-ii-flesh-blood"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":614,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Omega Force"],
			"synopsis":"No synopsis available.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dynasty-warriors-4-special/achievements/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dynasty-warriors-4-special/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":615,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Platinum Games"],
			"synopsis":"The story of Vanquish is set in the near future. Russia and the United States are vying for ownership of the world's fast-depleting energy resources and the US has constructed a space station in order to harness energy from the sun. Russian forces capture this space station and divert its harvested solar energy into a blast wave that destroys San Francisco, aiming to force the US into a total and unconditional surrender. In response, the US tasks its armed forces with recapturing the space station before the Russians can annihilate their next target - New York.<br><br>Players take the role of Sam, a government agent who must stop the threat before it is too late. Armed with a special suit and a plethora of weapons, Sam also has an array of martial arts skills that he can use to take down his robot enemies.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Tri-Weapon Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This exclusive three weapon download pack adds to your arsenal of weaponry and awesome firepower. The Tri-Weapon Pack contains: BOOST MACHINE GUN: A conversion of the Heavy Machine Gun carried by space-based troops into an assault weapon for use against light armour. LASER CANNON: This miniaturised spaceship cannon is the most powerful portable weapon available to infantry soldiers under Joint Space Operations Command. ANTI-ARMOUR PISTOL: A next-gen anti-armour gun. Due to its heavy weight and unique ammunition, military operators put its further development on hold."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wT5wg51JB8w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nr1RzIr0Rzc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C9UrXYGraYQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/987823-vanquish/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Vanquish/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/vanquish/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/vanquish"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":616,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Qute"],
			"synopsis":"Eschatos is a vertical 2.5D shoot 'em up for the Xbox 360 developed by Qute.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IKHGwMYGtw0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TG10TZYYNaM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fja7eiOyGqE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fja7eiOyGqE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Eschatos/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":617,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bright Light Productions"],
			"synopsis":"The Hasbro Family Game Night 3 collection of titles will appeal to the entire family with versions of their favorite game brands brought to life in a new theme park setting with the loveable Mr. Potato Head returning as the host and park guide. Featuring both classic and remixed versions, players can spin the wheel of fate in The Game of Life, find out \"whodunit\" in Clue, tie themselves in knots with Twister, trigger crazy chain reactions in Mouse Trap, and try their hand at Yahtzee Hands Down.<br><br>Hasbro Family Game Night 3 will also crank up the fun factor with local multiplayer capability and full avatar integration to add a personal touch to the experience. Fans will also be able to take the gameplay online by challenging opponents around the globe via the online play features.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2l79wMEoj5I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lCvh73Lyiik"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=03uGC8ZJ0OM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Family-Game-Night-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/family-game-night-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hasbro-family-game-night-3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":618,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["HB Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Go long! Backyard Sports: Rookie Rush offers kids the opportunity to get in the huddle with fan-favorite characters Pablo, Dmitri, and Joey as they block and tackle their way through energetic, kid-friendly football games on 12 interactive, neighborhood fields many representing each character's home turf and also a \"My Backyard\" field mode in which players can unlock items and populate their unique backyard. With hard hitting power-ups, imaginative new fields, stylized graphics, exciting new array of super-charged gameplay options and a compelling story mode, Rookie Rush is well trained and ready to take down the competition.<br><br>Kids can play pick-up football games with their Backyard Sports neighborhood friends in both single game and tournament options, or play the game in Backyard Sports' inventive new story mode. The Backyard Sports: Rookie Rush storyline centers on the Backyard kids who must come to terms with the new kid on the block, combine their unique talents, overcome egos and the odds in order to win a tournament and a big grand prize.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BKL3SzBNOv0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dK4hGea46rg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=igWJyqd8CoE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i4tXigmTyus"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VWwQQAJh9K4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rookie-Rush/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/backyard-sports-rookie-rush/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":619,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Now Production"],
			"synopsis":"In Bakugan Battle Brawlers: Defenders of the Core, players will create a new hero and lead the brawlers on an epic adventure to save Earth's cities from Spectra and his Vexos minions.<br><br>Players will discover a whole new aspect of Bakugan by being given complete control over their creatures when taking on their opponents as Bakugan transform from small balls into towering creatures. In the midst of intense battles, players will find themselves bravely exploring dangerous and dark areas to stop the evil spirits that are sucking the life force from the world. Players will unlock all-new levels and characters as they unearth hidden clues and defeat opponents in the quest to save the world from ultimate destruction.<br><br>Bakugan Battle Brawlers: Defenders of the Core also features split-screen multiplayer action in three different game modes. Coupled with real-time battle gameplay, this game marks the first time that players can duke it out with their Bakugan in head-to-head duels, free for all, and strategic destruction battles.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JigpLgGT24g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=npyFqVLddRo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bakugan-DOTC/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bakugan-defenders-of-the-core/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bakugan-defenders-of-the-core"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Bakugan Wiki",
				"url":"http://bakugan.wikia.com/wiki/Bakugan:_Defenders_of_the_Core"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":620,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cauldron"],
			"synopsis":"Dangerous becomes deadly in Cabela's Dangerous Hunts 2011, where the player steps into the boots of American marksman Cole Rainsford, who has joined his estranged father on an African safari to hunt savage animals that have been terrorizing remote villages. Soon finding themselves stranded, their survival depends on cunning instinct and expert skill to make it out alive.<br><br>Scripted by renowned scriptwriter and creative director Brad Santos (Resistance: Fall of Man, Tomb Raider: Legacy, The Saboteur) Cabela's Dangerous Hunts 2011 is a story of suspense, drama, and survival as the player faces tense, action packed kill-or-be killed scenarios.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gU-uU4Pfgo8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_JPrKM3R098"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c1r0INTWvoA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cabelas-Dangerous-Hunts-2011/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cabelas-dangerous-hunts-2011"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":621,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Telltale Games"],
			"synopsis":"CSI: Fatal Conspiracy features five connected cases that will allow players to experience an authentic crime-solving video game with real CSI characters, heart-pounding interrogations and enhanced graphics.<br><br>Partner with FBI agent Gene Huntby Cases to take down the Queen of the Hive. Be Prepared to Work with your CSI Partners, including the returning Sara Sidle, to solve murder cases and uncover the Fatal Conspiracy behind the crimes you investigate",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LEv2Ty-hspM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IKYZlJh38Mo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c-T0WMG7lH0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9f2TERnBKV0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/605047-csi-crime-scene-investigation-fatal-conspiracy/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/CSI-Fatal-Conspiracy/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/csi-fatal-conspiracy/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/csi-crime-scene-investigation-fatal-conspiracy"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":622,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Lionhead Studios"],
			"synopsis":"The fables of Fable continue to be told with this third series entry -- a revolution for the series that gives you power over your character and environment like never before. In this new adventure, players will witness tyranny, poverty and injustice plague their land. They will see a people divided, and they will be compelled to stand up for change. They will also be forced to answer a question: What would you sacrifice to secure the crown of Albion? Will you uphold the values and principles that led to your ascension, or will you be corrupted by the station you've strived to acquire? Will you be a monarch of the people, or bring the entirety of Albion to the brink of collapse?<br><br>The journey to rule the throne of Albion begins five decades after the events of the last chapter, and you play as the child of your hero from Fable II. As you rule your kingdom as king or queen, you will be called upon to make choices and sacrifices that will test your morality and can affect your entire kingdom. Themes of heroism, leadership and consequence are taken to a grand scale as you fight to unite a divided people.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Free Weapons",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"In-game content. Communication is very important in Fable III, and what better way to communicate with the world than to bash it in the head with the new hammer, Bloodstone Bludgeon, and shoot it in the face with the brand new rifle, Gusket's Musket? These items will be added to your gift queue in the Sanctuary, and will be available when weapons are unlocked in the storyline."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Dog Outfit",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Your dog is your best friend, always there for you when you need him. Isn't it time you gave something back? Now you can dress up as a dog yourself and turn Fable III into an all-canine adventure. The outfit comprises a head piece, body piece and front and back paws. This items will be added to your gift queue in the Sanctuary, and will be available when clothes are unlocked in the storyline."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Female Highlander Outfit",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Summon the spirit of the highlands with this new outfit, perfect for charging into battle with a rebellious roar. The outfit comprises a bonnet, bracers, boots, bodice and kilt. These items will be added to your gift queue in the Sanctuary, and will be available when clothes are unlocked in the storyline. Please be aware that retail copies of Fable III contain a code to receive this outfit and you may already own it."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Male Highlander Outfit",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Summon the spirit of the highlands with this new outfit, perfect for charging into battle with a rebellious roar. The outfit comprises a bonnet, bracers, boots, top and kilt. These items will be added to your gift queue in the Sanctuary, and will be available when clothes are unlocked in the storyline. Please be aware that retail copies of Fable III contain a code to receive this outfit and you may already own it."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Highlander Tattoo Set",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Summon the spirit of the highlands with this new tattoo set, perfect for charging into battle with a rebellious roar. This item will be added to your gift queue in the Sanctuary, and will be available when tattoos are unlocked in the storyline. Please be aware that retail copies of Fable III contain a code to receive this set and you may already own it."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Industrial Knight Outfit",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Always wanted to be an industrial age cyborg? Well, now you can at least look like one. The outfit comprises a helmet, gloves, boots, gauntlets and armour. These items will be added to your gift queue in the Sanctuary, and will be available when clothes are unlocked in the storyline."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Dye Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Breathe new life into your hair and clothes with this collection of dyes, including the long-awaited black dye. Those preferring lighter colours will make good use of the cream, hot pink and turquoise dyes. These items will be added to your gift queue in the Sanctuary, and will be available when dyes are unlocked in the storyline."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Red Setter Dog Potion",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Transform your faithful collie into a red setter with this amazing potion. Just let your dog have a sip when he's lying in his basket in the Sanctuary. This item will be added to your gift queue in the Sanctuary, and will be available when it's unlocked in the storyline. Please be aware that retail copies of Fable III contain a code to receive this potion and you may already own it."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Understone Quest Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/23",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Discover a whole new town built beneath the streets of Bowerstone. This full size region contains new houses and stalls to own, new creatures to fight and a major mystery to solve. As a special bonus, you will also receive two extra quests for free: the Mercenary Shooting Range, where you can earn prizes by hitting a variety of targets, and the Wheel of Misfortune, which gives you a chance to return to Reaver's manor and participate in his insane combat arena."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Hair Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Some people like to express themselves through speech, others through song, and yet others find that their hair-style does all the talking. Here are three brand new hairstyles to give your Hero a truly unique look: cornrows, afro and asymmetrical bob. These items will be added to your gift queue in the Sanctuary, and will be available when clothes are unlocked in the storyline."
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Five Star Dog Potion",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Teaching your dog to be a better fighter, treasure hunter and trick performer can be hard laborious work. So why not cheat and bypass all that fancy book-learning by giving him a swig of this potion? He will immediately maximise all his abilities. To use it press up on the D-Pad while facing your furry little friend. This item will be added to your gift queue in the Sanctuary, and will be available when it's unlocked in the storyline."
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Dog Breed Set",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/14",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Transform your faithful dog into a poodle, doberman or alsatian with this amazing set of potions. Just let your dog have a sip when he's lying in his basket in the Sanctuary. This item will be added to your gift queue in the Sanctuary, and will be available when it's unlocked in the storyline."
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"Free Yule Hat",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Bring cheer to the people of Albion with this extravagant hat. Whether you want to give them any gifts as well is entirely up to you."
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"Channeler Sword & Crystal Tattoo",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"In-game content. The Channeler is a powerful conduit for the magic in all Heroes, and it makes for a mean sword too. And it looks even better if you're wearing the Crystal tattoo set."
			},
			{
				"id":15,
				"name":"Clockwork Tattoo Set",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"In-game content. In this day of industry, magical symbols have lost some of their power, but this tribute to all things mechanical will mark you out as a thoroughly modern Hero."
			},
			{
				"id":16,
				"name":"The Champion Hammer & Balance Tattoo",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"In-game content. In ancient times, a great Hero would be chosen to protect the balance of the universe until his death. This Hero would wield The Champion Hammer and wear the Balance tattoo set."
			},
			{
				"id":17,
				"name":"Collector's Edition In-Game Content",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/24",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Move into Hunter's Lodge, a beautiful new home in the snowy Mistpeak Valley. Go on a new quest to find a powerful, unique weapon in The Silverpines Curse. Dress up as an Auroran. And even transform your dog into a boxer with a magical potion!"
			},
			{
				"id":18,
				"name":"Tattoo Set",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"In-game content. The Swirlwing tattoos reflect the ever-changing nature of the world and all living things in it."
			},
			{
				"id":19,
				"name":"Sword & Industrial Tattoo",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"In-game content. Keep Albion's factory workers in line with The Inquisitor, a sword inspired by the age of industry. Complete your modern look by wearing industrial tattoos."
			},
			{
				"id":20,
				"name":"Absolver Hammer & Dragonbreath Tattoo",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"In-game content. The Absolver is the weapon of choice for warrior monks and angry priests. The Dragonbreath tattoo set will ensure your holy fury is aesthetically pleasing too."
			},
			{
				"id":21,
				"name":"The Shardborne Sword",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"In-game content. Said to have been forged from a piece of Shard, this weapon is imbued with the power of the Tattered Spire itself."
			},
			{
				"id":22,
				"name":"Free Soldier Outfit",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/01",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Join the ranks of the Bowerstone army with this dashing military uniform. Albion needs you! The outfit comprises boots, hat, top and trousers. These items will be added to your gift queue in the Sanctuary. This package also contains the necessary data to play coop with players who own Fable III Traitor's Keep Premium game add-on."
			},
			{
				"id":23,
				"name":"Traitor's Keep Quest Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/01",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Experience your first grand adventure as the ruler of Albion, visiting the kingdom's secret prison and tracking down the most dangerous criminals in the land. You may have led a rebellion once, but can you survive your encounters with a new wave of revolutionaries? To help you on your way, this pack also includes a Clockwork Dog Potion. Just let your dog have a sip when he's lying in his basket in the Sanctuary."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QJnT3u01k18"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_3DYxsNC4gU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lpR2Uy2VLMc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d7pC8-xm3pM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/971431-fable-iii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fable-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fable-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fable-iii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Fable Wiki",
				"url":"http://fable.wikia.com/wiki/Fable_III"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":623,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Electronic Arts"],
			"synopsis":"Monopoly Streets has everything you love about the board game, presented as a street level tour of Mr. Monopoly's fully animated world. Players can experience Monopoly, one of the world's favorite family game brands, as a fully dynamic, living, 3D world that continuously evolves with the videogame action.<br><br>Monopoly Streets comes loaded with an array of imaginative twists such as the ability to establish house rules where players can save their own set of customized rules tailored to their group of friends. In addition, players are able to create and play as their own Xbox 360 avatar, and have the city populated by their friend's Xbox 360 avatars.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KEu0VOwtqf0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yw-5lWnn1kw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Monopoly-Streets/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/monopoly-streets/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/monopoly-streets"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":624,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"Rock Band 3 is the ultimate social and interactive music game. Featuring innovative game modes and instruments, Rock Band 3 will change the way fans think about and play music games.<br><br>Rock Band 3 has something for everyone. Master an instrument through the gameplay fun of Rock Band Pro, add another member to your band with a keyboard controller, or experience 83 new hits from 83 unique bands, along with your current library of songs from the over 1,500 songs available to date and counting.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable tracks",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/26",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"More than 1000 tracks available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nmWJNidyqKM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Pro Guitar Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QWVo7FNWQlc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kIPGnzBVKds"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_unJdDDXHQk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/971478-rock-band-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rock-Band-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rock-band-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rock-band-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Rock Band Wiki",
				"url":"http://rockband.wikia.com/wiki/Rock_Band_3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":625,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["The Sims Studio", "Edge of Reality"],
			"synopsis":"The Sims return yet again in this third full evolution of the long-running and always-expanding sim series. In this home console version of The Sims 3, players will be able to create Sims with unique personalities, fulfill their desires (...or not) and control their lives within a living neighborhood. Additionally, all-new features make it easier than ever to mess with life as players can unlock the ultimate \"Karma Powers\" for instant control and unleash them on their Sims. Players can help their Sim \"get lucky\", bless them with \"instant beauty\" or be deviant and curse them with an \"epic fail\". But players should use these powers wisely-they may have unexpected results and karma may come back to bite.<br><br>Rich, immersive gameplay is complimented with a seamlessly integrated exchange system, and gamers will be more connected than ever before as they design, build, and share their creations and download content from other players around the world without ever leaving the game. Facing short and long term challenges, players will reap rewards and trophies and can even share achievements with friends by connecting to Facebook.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Toyota Prius + Toyota Prius Eco Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Now your Sims can enjoy the newest member of the Toyota Prius family with this cool new pack! The pack includes environmentally conscience items so Sims can reduce their global footprint and feel good about it at the same time. Celebrate a greener tomorrow today!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Ultra Lounge Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Chic and sleek but always keeping comfort in mind, the Ultra Lounge set updates the jet set 70's look for today. Strong lines, curves, and an eclectic mix of metals and woods are the hallmarks of this daring design."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Hairstyles Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The latest trends in Moonlight Bay hairstyles are now available. These new haircuts will transform your Sims!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Ultra Lounge Kids Bedroom Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Nothing says I've got more style than years like these ultra-hip bedroom sets. From high-tech fabrics and floral mirrors, to bunny clocks and robots on the wall, there is something for every boy and girl in this collection of fashionable furniture."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Ultra Lounge Teens Set",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Too cool for school? You bet. Too cool for the rest of the house? Yep. This teenage haven has personality, spunk, and way too much style for its own good. Best of all this bedroom set has its very own TV for the teen who wants to watch their favorite shows in their own style."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y1U-b9QEXyY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vuvwMvmURgc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/995669-the-sims-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sims-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-sims-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-sims-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Sims Wiki",
				"url":"http://sims.wikia.com/wiki/The_Sims_3_(console)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":626,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["LucasArts"],
			"synopsis":"Explore more of the hidden shadows of the Sith with this sequel to the hit game Star Wars: The Force Unleashed. Starkiller, Darth Vader's apprentice, returns with over-the-top Force powers and embarks on a journey to discover his own identity and to reunite with his one true love, Juno Eclipse. In Star Wars: The Force Unleashed II, Starkiller is once again the pawn of Darth Vader -- but instead of training his prot&eacute;g&eacute;e as a ruthless assassin, the dark lord is attempting to clone his former apprentice in an attempt to create the Ultimate Sith warrior. The chase is on -- Starkiller is in pursuit of Juno and Darth Vader is hunting for Starkiller.<br><br>With all-new devastating Force powers and the ability to dual-wield lightsabers, Starkiller cuts a swath through deadly new enemies across exciting worlds from the Star Wars films -- all in his desperate search for answers to his past.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Endor",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/14",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Continue your adventure as the Dark Apprentice, where you can forever change the history of the Star Wars Universe by executing Darth Vader's orders to crush the Rebels as they mount their assault on Endor."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Character Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/14",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download additional content for Star Wars: The Force Unleashed II in this new character costume pack that will allow you to play as your favorite Star Wars characters, including Luke Skywalker in Dagobah Training Gear, Obi-Wan Kenobi in Clone Wars Battle Armor, Darth Malak, Han Solo, Lando Calrissian, Admiral Ackbar as well as new costumes for Starkiller."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MmZbV6uN6qY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-AWhJqCwZOI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2h8HAT4tLyU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KFRuUYJ_zNk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/981370-star-wars-the-force-unleashed-ii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Star-Wars-the-Force-Unleashed-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/star-wars-the-force-unleashed-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/star-wars-the-force-unleashed-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wookieepedia",
				"url":"http://starwars.wikia.com/wiki/Star_Wars:_The_Force_Unleashed_II"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":627,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Milestone"],
			"synopsis":"Licensed by the Italian Championship racing league, Superstars V8 Racing gets you out on the track to test your skills with V8 engines! Powered by some of the most important car manufacturers in the whole world, such as BMW, Audi and Jaguar, and sporting top class production cars, Superstars V8 Racing offers the utmost realistic impression of the Championship. From car design to technical engine features, from the setting of the races to the turns of the tracks, everything has been designed in great detail. Every single car behaves in a complete different way accordingly to its real technical features and the settings tuned by each team competing for the title in order to get the best performance out of the powerful engine.<br><br>Game play mode variety is enriched by each cars' peculiarity and it can be appreciated for the pick-up-and-play game mechanics, thought for the casual gamers, as well as for the top notch quality of the most experienced ones.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vb9OX3640aM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j51of72OhUA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qyviYs2ovLI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960192-superstars-v8-racing/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Superstars-V8-Racing/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/superstars-v8-racing/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/superstars-v8-racing"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":628,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Robomodo"],
			"synopsis":"A skateboarding experience created for a younger audience, Tony Hawk: Shred allows players to GO BIG and feel the exhilaration of supersized skate and snowboarding using the game's innovative, motion-sensing board controller right at their feet. Featuring an arcade style look and feel, where the bigger the feat the better the fun, Shred is packed to the brim with larger-than-life moments and a veritable assortment of jaw-dropping tricks -- enticing kids to get off the couch and into the action. Players will be on the deck mastering over-the-top tricks, massive drops, awesome grabs and super long grinds in no time.<br><br>Whether riding on cement or snow, Tony Hawk: Shred has it covered. In addition to skateboarding, aspiring snowboarders can jump on Shred's amazing board controller and go crazy in a completely new way - feeling the ultimate rush of shredding down the steep mountain peaks of Whistler, the French Alps and Beijing, China as they launch off huge kickers and pull off crazy spins, flips and grabs.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A0d31xR6MQk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Uul0jnLDEow"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5skkLAFvWBo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tony-Hawk-Shred/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tony-hawk-shred"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tony Hawk's Games Wiki",
				"url":"http://tonyhawkgames.wikia.com/wiki/Tony_Hawk's_Shred_Session"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":629,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Yuke's Media Creations"],
			"synopsis":"WWE SmackDown vs. Raw 2011 empowers players more than ever to to define their gameplay experiences in a dynamic and ever-changing WWE. Along the way, gameplay scenarios change based on player decisions, allowing for more spontaneous WWE action in and out of the ring. Players can also enjoy a greater level of interactivity and have increased control of their destinies in the game's popular Road to WrestleMania story-driven mode.<br><br>WWE SmackDown vs. Raw 2011 has more creative tools than ever to customize their Superstars, finishing moves and story designs. In addition, searching and sharing content are greatly simplified with improvements to the highly regarded WWE Community Creations feature, which generated nearly 10 million downloads, including more than 7.5 million Created Superstars, 500,000 story designs and 500,000 finishing moves in its franchise debut.<br><br>WWE SmackDown vs. Raw 2011 also features more than 70 of today's prominent WWE Superstars and Divas. In addition, a new physics system will ensure all matches and object interactions look and feel unique, dynamic and unpredictable to capture the full essence of the WWE Universe.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SMcQrqbcLYs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ky2Qvq2rmys"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g7P__VVJxBw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u8yy1WsQ_jk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fYD-JGVE38s"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/996718-wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-2011/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/WWE-SmackDown-vs-RAW-2011/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-2011/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-2011"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":630,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Propaganda Games"],
			"synopsis":"Transport into a high-tech and action-packed world of Tron in the prequel to the thrilling 2010 film. Explore vast cities and fight high-tech enemies as you try to save a world on the brink of totalitarian domination. Gamers explore Tron's cities using the free running phenomenon Parkour, navigate among unique rebel factions, and fight an epic battle against a dictator's seemingly unstoppable army.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Bonus Multiplayer Skin - Sam Flynn",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/14",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download the Sam Flynn multiplayer skin for TRON: Evolution. The only son of Kevin Flynn-the adventurous and rebellious 27-year-old who has turned away from the ENCOM money and is haunted by his father's disappearance."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Tron Multiplayer Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/28",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Tron multiplayer map pack contains 5 NEW and mind blowing maps. This pack contains a classic light bike map inspired from the Original 1982 Tron movie. The other 4 maps provide new, never before seen, ways to play the game. Enjoy!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5ZLONRreKAI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iMWuTMTZvEE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=153aHwf0vBg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/981378-tron-evolution/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tron-Evolution/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tron-evolution/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tron-evolution"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tron Wiki",
				"url":"http://tron.wikia.com/wiki/TRON:_Evolution"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":631,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sidhe"],
			"synopsis":"In Blood Drive, contestants must use their motorized death steeds of steel in a televised game show where drivers battle each other and hordes of revolting flesh eaters in an all-out fight to the death.<br><br>Face undead frat boys, cops, strippers and bachelorette partiers, each with their own special brand of death and devastation - and ways to die! While these rotting monsters wander the streets of a desert sin city craving sweet, succulent brains, your enemies have come equipped battle hardened armed vehicles, including heavily weaponized muscle cars, hot rods, and more. Amidst this gore-drenched mayhem contestants must use their head or lose it.<br><br>Blood Drive features several gruesome events set up as tournaments in the game's six unforgiving environments. Battling for top position is even more satisfying in multiplayer modes where up to four friends can drop in and drop out of the bloodbath at any time. With such a target rich environment, it won't take you long before you send the endless mass of blood-thirsty zombies and battle hardened maniacs back to hell, one bloody tire-tread at a time.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-za5gGEgGao"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N-BAl77tYkk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Blood-Drive/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/blood-drive"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":632,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Spike"],
			"synopsis":"The second game in this high-flying, fast-hitting, and intense versus battles series, Dragon Ball: Raging Blast 2 promises over 90 characters from the massively popular anime franchise. Dragon Ball Z fans can rest assured that the destructible environment, and character trademark attacks and transformations will be true to the series. These include signature Pursuit Attacks which enable players to initiate attack combo strings, juggling your opponent in a string of devastating strikes throughout the environment. Additionally, Dragon Ball: Raging Blast 2 sports the new Raging Soul System which enables characters to reach a special state, increasing their combat abilities to the ultimate level. Featuring more than 90 characters, 20 of which are brand new to the Raging Blast series, new modes, and additional environmental effects, Dragon Ball: Raging Blast 2 is the next evolution in the home console series.<br><br>As a bonus for Dragon Ball fans, Raging Blast 2 contains the exclusive new feature entitled \"Dragon Ball: Plan to Eradicate the Super Saiyans\" -- a completely reconstructed, re-scripted and re-edited version of an original Japanese episode that has never been released in the U.S or Canada, offering something unique to fans of the series. Everyone who buys the game can watch this exclusive anime straight out of the box.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZUeLR5t0OOI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AYeYL3UoFsc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LTwDsGtyFAw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/996390-dragon-ball-raging-blast-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dragon-Ball-Raging-Blast-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dragon-ball-raging-blast-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dragon-ball-raging-blast-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dragon Ball Wiki",
				"url":"http://dragonball.wikia.com/wiki/Dragon_Ball:_Raging_Blast_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":633,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Dimps"],
			"synopsis":"The Dragon Ball Z Budokai HD Collection includes two blockbuster fighting games based on the Dragon Ball Z anime series. Included are Dragon Ball Z Budokai and Dragon Ball Z Budokai 3.<br><br>Dragon Ball Z Budokai -- Fight to the finish against the deadliest fighters in the universe and take on the most powerful heroes and the most evil villains in Dragon Ball Z. The more you win, the more difficult it gets. Can you survive?<br><br>Dragon Ball Z Budokai 3 -- A \"Hall of Fame\" cast of warriors from Dragon Ball Z, Dragon Ball GT, and DBZ movies come together for a tournament of champions. With the power of the new Saiyan Overdrive Fighting System, players have unprecedented gameplay control and Dragon Ball Z authenticity.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rlEpm7mDfHM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_zznqf1L9jY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/676304-dragon-ball-z-budokai-hd-collection/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dragon-Ball-Z-Budokai-HD-Collection/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dragon-ball-z-budokai-hd-collection/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dragon-ball-z-budokai-hd-collection"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dragon Ball Wiki",
				"url":"http://dragonball.wikia.com/wiki/Dragon_Ball_Z:_Budokai_HD_Collection"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":634,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tecmo KOEI"],
			"synopsis":"In Fist of the North Star: Ken's Rage, players assume the role of Ken, a man with seven scars on his chest and the chosen successor of the legendary assassin's art known as Hokuto Shinken. Sworn to protect the weak and innocent from malicious gangs roaming the post-apocalyptic planet, players use Ken's trademark moves to decimate enemies on his quest to find his long-lost love.<br><br>Tearing through the scorched landscape, manga and action fans will pummel their way through dozens of enemies at once and crush obstacles in their path, using them against their foes. They will execute blistering finish attacks in faithfully recreated environments ripped straight from the comic legend. But Ken doesn't need to fight alone - he's joined by an unforgettable cast of playable characters from the Fist of the North Star universe, including Mamiya and Rei, among others.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Playable character 'Heart' and 2 new missions",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/02",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"A huge (literally) new playable character, Heart, will allow you to plow a giant path through the battlefield. Use Heart or any other playable character in 2 new missions where you must defeat 5 bosses on your own, or team up to battle 3 bosses and take ownership of a new food supply."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Kenshiro - Original costume",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Kenshiro has returned, in all his glory! Kenshiro, master of the post-apocalyptic wasteland, is now playable in his costume from the original comic book!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Playable character 'Outlaw' and King survival mission",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/02",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"You've fought against them, now fight as one of them with this Outlaw playable character. Play as the Outlaw or any other playable character in a new"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Rei, Mamiya & Raoh - Original costumes",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Fight as Rei with the elegant yet deadly Nanto Suichoken, glide gracefully through the battlefield as Mamiya, or conquer the Post-War World as Raoh in their original comic book costumes."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Jagi - Original costume and 2 new missions",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/30",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Fight as Jagi, the twisted Hokuto fighter impersonating Kenshiro, in his original comic book costume. Battle through 2 new missions, one pits you against Jagi's forces, and the other will test your skills against the four mighty heroes: Ryuga, Fudo, Juza and Toki."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Toki - Original costume and 2 new missions",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/28",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Experience the legendary warrior, Toki, in all his former glory his pre-apocolyptic costume from the flashback sequence in the original comic book. Two new missions have you battling to escape Amiba grasp, and fighting to escape a deadly trap set by Thouzer and Juda."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Shin & Thouzer - Original costume and 2 new missions",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/11",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Instill terror in the hearts of your enemies with Shin and Thouzer, two mighty Nanto masters, in their original comic book costumes. Two new missions will have you facing off against the most powerful fighters in the world, or choosing sides with either Hokuto or Nanto forces for an epic final"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GnorSW9w9PE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=INDFC85jKYs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=faWWBrE7fCs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/976862-fist-of-the-north-star-kens-rage/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fist-of-the-North-Star-Kens-Rage/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fist-of-the-north-star-kens-rage/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fist-of-the-north-star-kens-rage"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Koei Wiki",
				"url":"http://koei.wikia.com/wiki/Fist_of_the_North_Star:_Ken's_Rage"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":635,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bizarre Creations"],
			"synopsis":"An international conspiracy has placed the UK's most secretive bio-chemical project into deadly hands, and only Her Majesty's most lethal agent, James Bond, can unravel the mystery. To navigate through layers of corruption, you, as Bond, will embark on a global chase that will have you battling on land, sea and air through Athens, Istanbul, Monaco, and Bangkok. Nothing is what it seems as each adventure reveals a deeper and more sinister conspiracy.<br><br>A mix of third-person gunplay, hand-to-hand combat and the driving action, James Bond 007: Blood Stone features Daniel Craig, Judi Dench and Joss Stone. The game features various modes and multiplayer mode for up to 16 people. Engage in precise cover-based gameplay and tactical firefights, and speed your way through explosive, adrenalin-fueled driving sequences. Become Bond as he engages in intense hand-to-hand combat and uses his environment to finish off enemies.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ebOerQRntHQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gIxdjIbkw-k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PNxdaJ61Av0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BO7oE4MsTQs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/995481-james-bond-007-blood-stone/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Blood-Stone/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/james-bond-bloodstone/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/james-bond-007-blood-stone"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"007 Wiki",
				"url":"http://jamesbond.wikia.com/wiki/Blood_Stone"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":636,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["THQ Studio Australia"],
			"synopsis":"Just as Megamind has become our new Mega Hero, a sudden crime wave hits the city. The Doom Syndicate & their Doom Goons have emerged and are looking to take over! Only Megamind and his arsenal of gadgets can stop them! Now, in three unique game play experiences, players can be the ultimate Mega Hero!<br><br>Picking up right after the events of the movie, MegaMind: Ultimate Showdown is an action-packed game for up to two players (playing as Megamind and Brainbot) to take on the vile villains of the Doom Syndicate.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DhioYvmKRVo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PPPlsZf-MHs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8o_Hz2josFc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Megamind/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/megamind/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/megamind-ultimate-showdown"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":637,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Activision"],
			"synopsis":"Monster Jam 2011 is all about authenticity, personality, and fun, with 30 officially licensed Monster Jam trucks, including fan-favorites Grave Digger, Maximum Destruction, and Grinder. Players can also create and customize their own trucks with thousands of options, unlocking new parts and upgrades as they progress through the game.<br><br>Eight real life stadiums from the Monster Jam circuit help bring the live atmosphere to the living room, with explosive truck introductions, pyrotechnics and lighting, and a roaring crowd. In single player mode the goal is the same as for real life drivers - rise through the ranks of ruthless competitors to ultimately battle against the best at the Monster Jam World Finals! Head-to-head multiplayer modes take the heart-pounding competition to another level.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=auX8nL2-yCo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fuwYiJX9F3M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Monster-Jam-Path-of-Destruction/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/monster-jam-path-of-destruction/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/monster-jam-path-of-destruction"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":638,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Treyarch"],
			"synopsis":"Hear the call of duty once again with this seventh entry in this blockbuster first-person shooter franchise. Call of Duty: Black Ops takes you deep behind enemy lines into the world of deniable operations as a member of an elite special forces unit engaging in covert warfare, classified operations, and explosive conflicts across the globe. With access to a variety of exclusive weaponry and equipment, your actions will tip the balance during the most dangerous time period mankind has ever known.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"First Strike Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/01",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"First Strike contains 5 all-new maps including \"Berlin Wall\", the Arctic \"Discovery\", Hong Kong's \"Kowloon\", the sports complex \"Stadium\" and the new Zombies level \"Ascension\"."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Escalation Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/03",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Escalation contains 5 all-new maps; featuring 4 Multiplayer maps and an epic, star-studded Zombies experience with new playable characters. Battle it out in \"Hotel\" on the roof of a luxury hotel & casino in old Havana; \"Convoy\" delivers close-quarters combat near an ambushed US military convoy; \"Zoo\" takes you on a wild ride in an abandoned Soviet Russian Zoo; \"Stockpile\" is set in a Russian farm town housing secret WMDs. For Zombies fans, \"Call of the Dead\" features a cast of iconic horror film stars battling zombies on a Siberian island."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Annihilation Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/28",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Obliterate the competition with 4 unique Multiplayer Maps and a wild new locale for the latest in Zombies action. Jump into battle with \"Hangar 18\", located in the classified military base of Area 51; \"Drive-In\", close quarters combat through a 60's American Drive-In theater; \"Silo\", a secret Soviet nuclear missile site in this multilevel battleground; and \"Hazard\", a coastal golf course on the cliff sides of Cuba. Zombies are back in \"Shangri-La\", a legendary shrine lost in an exotic jungle."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Rezurrection Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/23",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Lift off into the latest Zombies epic with \"Rezurrection\", the new content pack for \"Call of Duty: Black Ops\", and the first to launch players into space! Old school Zombies strategies get blown out of the airlock in \"Moon\", where armed with new perks and a space-age arsenal of weapons, our heroes must overcome undead astronauts and fluctuating gravity as they unearth conspiracies that began in 1943. Rounding out Rezurrection are the 4 maps that spawned the Zombie phenomenon: \"Nacht der Untoten\", \"Verr&uuml;ckt\", \"Shi No Numa\" and \"Der Riese\"."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OtRnpC7ddv8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OPTOVQFRggI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_maBGM-i8OQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S79tB1bapy8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T3iPr-c8Rwk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Nazi Zombies Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tBLiWxaCNuE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960189-call-of-duty-black-ops/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Call-of-Duty-Black-Ops/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/call-of-duty-black-ops/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/call-of-duty-black-ops"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Call of Duty Wiki",
				"url":"http://callofduty.wikia.com/wiki/Call_of_Duty:_Black_Ops"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":639,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Pipeworks Software"],
			"synopsis":"Discover your inner artist with uDraw Studio. Utilizing the uDraw GameTablet, players can finally express their own individual artistic creativity on their game console. Featuring versatile and easy-to-use tools, users can paint, draw, and color anything from simple doodles to intricate masterpieces. uDraw Studio offers the freedom to create spectacular works of art without the hassle of clean-up.<br><br>This enhanced version of the artistic software package uDraw Studio brings the core functions of the uDraw GameTablet to life on your television. uDraw Studio: Instant Artist offers expansive guided tutorials to teach many of the basics of art and design, as well as a more intuitive interface that keeps art tools right on screen at all times. Using the new uDraw Studio: Instant Artist on uDraw, artists will be able to more easily send and share images online.<br><br>The uDraw GameTablet has also been redesigned, with a sleek design that incorporates console controls direction into the tablet. Enhanced capabilities include high-definition art creation and gameplay, a stylus with greater sensitivity for more detailed results, motion features, longer drawing time, and direct touch-screen control that incorporates pinch-and-stretch & rotation features.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FVgqZ0_k-jo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XPFe4dteppw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CTh3DWfqLko"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=goz_TdALt_Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/uDraw-Instant-Artist/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/udraw-studio-instant-artist/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/udraw-studio-instant-artist"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":640,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gaijin Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Apache: Air Assault is a modern combat flight simulation game where players control a variety of lethal Apache attack helicopters outfitted with cutting-edge military weaponry. The goal is to prevent terrorist attacks by raining down destruction from above in the world's most volatile warzones.<br><br>The game can be played based on the player's tastes - Arcade Mode allows players to easily pick up the controls and jump right into the combat. The Realistic mode showcases the real depth of the title, where the dedication to realism and precision shines through. The local Co-op Campaign Mode lets two players team up in the same Apache with one as the pilot and the other as the co-pilot in a joint effort for a truly authentic combat flight experience. For those that want to go even further, Apache: Air Assault includes competitive online multiplayer matches such as Team Deathmatch, Ground Attack, Capture the LZ, and Ground Strike.<br><br>Apache: Air Assault features more than 16 multi-stage missions involving air and ground strike operations off the coast of Africa, the mountains of the Middle East and the jungles of Central America, each meticulously created using high resolution map data from real-world satellite photography.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HnPr2V0sqTA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ooN7_EdDhXY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mnDgLdlJNuU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Rk4wf4t2o1A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Apache-Air-Assault/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/apache-air-assault/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/apache-air-assault"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":641,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"The critically acclaimed single-player experience of Assassin's Creed is back and better than ever as Ezio returns in an epic struggle against the powerful Templar Order.<br><br>Now a legendary Master Assassin, Ezio must journey into Italy's greatest city, Rome, center of power, greed and corruption to strike at the heart of the enemy. Defeating the corrupt tyrants entrenched there will require not only strength, but leadership, as Ezio commands an entire Brotherhood that will rally to his side. Only by working together can the Assassins defeat their mortal enemies.<br><br>Assassin's Creed Brotherhood offers a never-before-seen multiplayer layer. Players can help the Templars by using Abstergo to train in the art of Assassination to eliminate the Assassins once and for all. Players can choose from a wide range of unique characters, each with their own signature weapons and assassination techniques, and match their skills against other players from all over the world in different game modes.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Animus Project Update 1.0",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/14",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Abstergo rewards its recruits and enhances its Training Program with the all new free DLC featuring the new map 'Mont Saint-Michel' and one new mode 'Advanced Alliance'. Located on the rocky tidal island of Normandy in France, Mont Saint-Michel offers a breathtaking scenery sure to enchant all. Its particular topography of narrow streets, high perched bell-tower and multi-leveled architecture is perfect for hunters and predators alike to surge from nowhere and execute their prey. To survive, recruits will need to use free-running and narrow roads to their advantage. Description of \"Advanced Alliance\" Mode - Six Players with 3 teams comprised of 2 - Each match consists of 2 four minute rounds - Target identification and engagement are more difficult than in the basic Alliance Mode, players will need to maximize their skills and use caution to survive."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Animus Project Update 2.0",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/18",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The new Pienza Map is set against central Tuscany's background and landmarks such as the Palazzo Piccolimini and Palazzo Comunale provide the perfect free-running playground where predator and targets can blend and disappear. To dominate, employees must master the town's layout as it's free-running routes can become the recruit's ally or doom.<br>- New Chest Capture Multiplayer Mode<br>- Six Players with two teams comprised of three players each<br>- Player's objectives are to partner with fellow Templars to either defend or capture Chests.<br>- Defenders will receive points for assassinating and defending the chests. Capturors will earn points by capturing the chests. Defenders will receive points for assassinating and defending the chests. Capturors will earn points by capturing the chests.<br>-New Templar Score Feature. Updated weekly and based on users scores of the previous four weeks, it splits recruits in 10 specific slices - each representing part of the hierarchy of the community. The goal is to reward diligent work by Abstergo recruits."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"The Da Vinci Disappearance",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/08",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"After the fall of the Borgias in Rome, Leonardo Da Vinci is kidnapped by an underground cult dedicated to transforming mankind. Ezio will embark on a relentless quest to recover stolen paintings in order to find Leo before it is too late, discovering two new locations and two new gameplay features along the way. The multiplayer addition is the biggest expansion to the award-winning multiplayer yet, including one new map, four new characters and two new game modes. The new multiplayer map, Alhambra, provides multileveled indoor and outdoor areas perfect for predators to lurk in the dense crowd for unsuspecting targets. The four new characters include the Dama Rossa, the Knight, the Marquis and the Pariah. In Escort mode, two teams of four players compete to protect their VIP target or assassinate the other team's VIP target. In Assassinate mode six to eight players are pitted against each other deathmatch-style in one ten-minute round."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_p7l1l_rlE0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jCD0LmXrkm8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K9N_25wRKdY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4y7FTOcXrWg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Rome",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O1L4uKIvYw0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/996093-assassins-creed-brotherhood/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Assassins-Creed-Brotherhood/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/assassins-creed-brotherhood/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/assassins-creed-brotherhood"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Assassin's Creed Wiki",
				"url":"http://assassinscreed.wikia.com/wiki/Assassin's_Creed:_Brotherhood"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":642,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Bright Light"],
			"synopsis":"Create is a game powered by imagination, a title for the whole family that rewards players for being creative. The game presents imaginative gameplay challenges where the solutions are fueled by the creativity of the player. The more players explore the game, solve level-based challenges, and customize their world, the more rewards will be unlocked. Creativity will be unleashed as players design environments with easy-to-use brushes and tools, including textures, props and animating objects that bring the scene to life. Players can share any of their creations, solutions or challenges with the community through the console and also via the official Create website at www.create.ea.com. Friends can download and remix solutions and set challenges for other players to download and complete.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vb9JQYUjL6c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WMEcSujE9VI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Create/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/create/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/create"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":643,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Bright Light"],
			"synopsis":"In Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, players will be on the run, fighting for survival on a desperate and dangerous quest to locate and destroy Voldemort's Horcruxes, engaging with Death Eaters and Snatchers in epic battle sequences at every turn.<br><br>To amplify the action, players will encounter ferocious creatures from the previous films in addition to the adversaries Harry faces in the seventh film. They will need to muster their most powerful magic against relentless assaults from all sides. There are no more lessons, no more training. This time the danger is real. It's time for players to fight for their lives.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uRaNtJNs9RA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rAZyBtCelnU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pJ2X8mhqA28"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/997203-harry-potter-and-the-deathly-hallows-part-1/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Harry-Potter-and-the-Deathly-Hallows/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/harry-potter-and-the-deathly-hallows/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/harry-potter-and-the-deathly-hallows-part-1"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Harry Potter Wiki",
				"url":"http://harrypotter.wikia.com/wiki/Harry_Potter_and_the_Deathly_Hallows:_Part_1"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":644,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Griptonite Games"],
			"synopsis":"In Marvel Super Hero Squad: The Infinity Gauntlet, players can \"Hero Up\" with friends in cooperative play master the unique Factor Power of each of the Marvel heroes in three game modes: Story Mode, Freeplay Mode and Challenge Mode. The game also boasts a brand new puzzle component, in which players will need to utilize the characters' unique abilities to move or destroy objects, traverse through certain environments, and summon specific strengths to overcome obstacles.<br><br>With new adventures, tricky puzzles, an expanded selection of Marvel Super Hero Squad members to unlock and play as, Marvel Super Hero Squad: The Infinity Gauntlet is set to thrill gamers from here to Super Hero City.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Captain America Collection",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/16",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":8
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"The Thanos Throwdown",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/16",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":8
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Doom on the Loose",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/16",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":8
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vABPybwM_8k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2Ww9lbOIAzU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/999434-marvel-super-hero-squad-the-infinity-gauntlet/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Marvel-Super-Hero-Squad-the-Infinity-Gauntlet/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/marvel-super-hero-squad-the-infinity-gauntlet/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/marvel-super-hero-squad-the-infinity-gauntlet"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":645,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Criterion Games"],
			"synopsis":"Need for Speed Hot Pursuit brings the franchise back to its roots with intense cops vs. racer chases.<br><br>The game features Need for Speed Autolog where players compare racing stats and automatically get personalized gameplay recommendations from their friends. Need for Speed Hot Pursuit players can also experience the thrill of the chase and the rush of the escape as they play through full careers as both a cop and a racer - solo or connected. The high speed busts and heart-stopping getaways are all connected via Need for Speed Autolog.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Super Sports",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/21",
				"achievements":195,
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Pairing the fastest production car in the world, the Bugatti Veyron 16.4 Super Sport with the unbelievably capable GUMPERT apollo s, this pack continues the Hyper Series (Racers) and the Special Response Deployment Unit (Cops). In addition you'll get access to the incredible Porsche 911 GT2 RS - pound for pound one of the greatest cars ever created. These new vehicles are available to both Racers and the Cops, decked out in the SCPD's most current liveries and come with three brand new solo events each to go put them through their paces. This collection includes four exclusive solo events and will give you a great saving over purchasing these cars individually."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Armed and Dangerous",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/22",
				"achievements":45,
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":" Be the Most Wanted; the SCPD's Number One target. Try to escape from a whole squad of Cops with only a handful of fellow Racers to protect you. Your team of Racers are free to drive anywhere in Seacrest County while the Cops must work together to bring the Most Wanted player to justice. Arms Race. Racers get dirty as they turn their weapons on each other. In a no-holds-barred trail of destruction, the Racers stop at nothing to take each other out and get to the finish line first."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Lamborghini Untamed",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/01",
				"achievements":75,
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"The Countach LP5000QV has to be the most iconic Supercar of the 80's. It has the power and the looks, do you have the skill? The Diablo SV is a rear-wheel-drive beast powered by a monstrous V12 engine that must be tamed and driven on the edge. The Sesto Elemento is a futuristic super-light-weight capable of reaching a speed of 100 kph in just 2.5 seconds. These new vehicles are available to both Racers and Cops, decked out in SCPD's most current liveries and come with a total of six new events to test your Racer and Cop abilities to the limit. This collection includes four exclusive solo events and will give you a great saving over purchasing these cars individually."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Porsche Unleashed",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/08",
				"achievements":75,
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"The Porsche Unleashed Pack includes three very special Porsches, each one created to fulfil a very specific purpose - the power of the 1982 Porsche 911 Turbo, the speed of the 1988 Porsche 959, and the style of the 2011 Porsche 911 Speedster. It also includes ten new events to drive them in that will test your Racer and Cop abilities to the limit."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D6ouHWP0KrY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DAI2D_yfMm0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KOd5DDGI8_4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/997658-need-for-speed-hot-pursuit/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NFS-Hot-Pursuit/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/need-for-speed-hot-pursuit/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/need-for-speed-hot-pursuit"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Need for Speed Wiki",
				"url":"http://nfs.wikia.com/wiki/Need_for_Speed:_Hot_Pursuit_(2010)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":646,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"Boomshakalaka! EA Sports NBA Jam revives the classic franchise with vintage NBA Jam gameplay, all-new features, and, for the first time ever for the arcade classic, in high definition and featuring online play. Shoves, spins and, of course, backboard smashing dunks take center stage with Classic 2 vs. 2 gameplay that lies at the core of NBA Jam. Play with a roster of current NBA players, NBA legends and a few special appearances on the hardwood.<br><br>For the first time ever play the arcade classic online. Gamers can take on all rivals playing Classic 2-on-2 online, measuring their success on Friends and Global Leaderboards. Connected fans will be able to team-up locally to compete online in Remix Games, including Backboard Smash, Domination Free-for-All, Elimination, and 21. Fans will also be able to make it a Jam Party online by inviting up to 3 friends on separate consoles to play. Plus, gamers will be able to take on the world in Online Progression, leveling up through a series of challengers and secret online JAM Challenges to unlock online exclusive rewards and hidden content in the ultimate quest for global bragging rights.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LxF8BnyfDbk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oBJSko9V2ss"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-Jam/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-jam/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-jam"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":647,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Game Republic"],
			"synopsis":"Wrapped in an emotional journey of courage and respect, Majin and the Forsaken Kingdom takes players on a majestic adventure as a cunning individual who must rely on his agility to triumph over increasing obstacles. What he lacks in might, his AI-controlled companion makes up for with his towering size and brawn.<br><br>Majin and the Forsaken Kingdom redefines co-op AI gameplay by delivering an accessible experience that offers the perfect mix of stealth, action, platform navigation and combat that is designed to keep the journey gripping and immersive. Though each character has their own objective, teamwork is essential for survival as the hero and Majin must fight in tandem to persevere over any challenge that lies in their path. This complementary relationship will only continue to deepen and evolve as the story unfolds.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Challenge Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/07",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"The Majin and the Forsaken Kingdom Challenge Pack features three new exciting game play styles: Battle Challenge, Sneak Challenge and Puzzle Challenge. Each challenge includes four different levels of play and a unique costume for Tepeu and Majin. All costume sets come with their own abilities and powers allowing players to customize their gaming experience."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dIE3eV8HFPk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iizuEKdBvAw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P5Y1_PxNcgE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/988808-majin-and-the-forsaken-kingdom/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Majin-and-the-Forsaken-Kingdom/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/majin-and-the-forsaken-kingdom/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/majin-and-the-forsaken-kingdom"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":648,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bandai Namco Games", "BottleRocket Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Follow Rick and his mysterious Terror Mask as he unmercifully tears, cuts and beats his way through denizens of unearthly creatures in an epic adventure to rescue his girlfriend from the clutches of deranged occult figure Dr. West. Embodying the unfiltered, primal aggression of its namesake, Splatterhouse combines visceral, adrenaline-soaked combat with horror elements to deliver an original gaming experience that defies the boundaries of the traditional action category with over the-top gore and shocking new gameplay mechanics.<br><br>Featuring an original storyline by critically-acclaimed comic book writer Gordon Rennie (Necronauts, Judge Dredd), Splatterhouse takes Rick beyond the mansion as he scours the ends of the world to rescue his beloved Jennifer.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Dia de Los Muertos Mask",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Inspired by the artwork of Dia De Los Muertos, Rick can wear this mask throughout Story Mode and the Survival Arenas."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"The Retro Hockey Mask",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A Retro Hockey Mask inspired by the classic games of yesteryear. Rick can wear this throughout Story Mode and the Survival Arenas."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"The Skull Mask",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Inspired by the love of a good skull, Rick can wear this mask throughout Story Mode and the Survival Arenas."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"The Killing Floor",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/23",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Can you survive the madness of the white room? Turn the white room red. This exclusive content opens up a brand new survival arena accessible in Splatterhouse. Endure wave after wave of increasingly difficult enemy combinations and open up new unlockables."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"The Corrupted Mask",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Corrupted by the power of the Abyss, Rick can wear this mask throughout Story Mode and the Survival Arenas."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Lost Islands",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/23",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"On the Lost Islands, in the halls of the Thule, an ancient terror stirs... This exclusive content opens up a brand new survival arena accessible in Splatterhouse. Endure wave after wave of increasingly difficult enemy combinations and open up new unlockables."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nGF2qavLYFU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WOdVE-k1fyQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GDMUj8jVlr4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w7vWdFPaRhk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FWCJOztN5-s"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/946605-splatterhouse/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Splatterhouse/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/splatterhouse/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/splatterhouse"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Splatterhouse Wiki",
				"url":"http://splatterhouse.wikia.com/wiki/Splatterhouse_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":649,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["DoubleTap"],
			"synopsis":"Capturing the drama and excitement of the Discovery Channel's Emmy-winning TV series Deadliest Catch, this game challenges players to take on the world's toughest job, crab fishing. Deadliest Catch: Sea of Chaos combines strategy and action as players chart a course through the unforgiving Bering Sea on a quest for Opilio and King Crab. To begin, players choose a boat to command for a season and strategically decide where and when to harvest the crab. The action comes when it is time to successfully retrieve crab pots from an angry sea. Players will test their skills in the real-life situations that captains and crew encounter daily, including setting pots, repairing the ship, sorting the catch, breaking the ice and even rescuing men overboard.<br><br>Deadliest Catch: Sea of Chaos also provides plenty of ways to connect with the TV show and loyal fans, including competing with the other captains from the show and comparing their in-game crab \"takes\" with actual takes as documented in seasons of Deadliest Catch on TV. Players will also compete in online \"leagues\", which pit virtual captains against other fans and players.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BqbNolx3-uE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qh31pdO5Gxg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lTn60n5L8LQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QzP8Z7dfexs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Deadliest-Catch-Sea-of-Chaos/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/deadliest-catch-sea-of-chaos/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/deadliest-catch-sea-of-chaos"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":650,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Techland"],
			"synopsis":"Nail'd is a racing game that is all about eschewing boring realism for over the top arcade fun. It's a racer that challenges everything from player reflexes through to the rules of physics. Riding on ATVs and motocross bikes with powerful boost controls, players will race down near-vertical courses of incredible jumps, stunts and obstacles. The brutal challenge of the Yosemite National Park is but one of the places they'll learn the meaning of verticality.<br><br>Nail'd's single-player campaign features various configurable modes and races including Tournament, Time Attack and Quick Event. The multi-player mode allows players to compete head to head in a range of race-types with multiple mutators, locally or online. Earned points will determine a player's position on leader boards and based on the player's performance and ability to pull off stunning feats of speed and glory during each race, they'll unlock exciting new components to customize their vehicle.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Detonator Mode and Track Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/30",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Nail'd is getting even more extreme! Check out the brand spanking new Detonator Mode for the ultimate in racing thrills, where you can perform the wildest jumps and extreme maneuvers to get rid of the ticking bomb and blow up your opponents. Includes four additional and insanely vertical tracks set in the Andes, Arizona and the Yosemite environments, which each challenge you to race at even more ridiculous speeds. To stand a chance, customize your ride with fresh and exclusive parts and give it one of the numerous custom paint jobs. But don't forget to jump into a fresh driver outfit of your own!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a4HRXjyAjE4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3uIHAOwemmU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G6MNtjVIs1Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RW2HaxVu39g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/naild/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/naild"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":651,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Deck 13"],
			"synopsis":"In the era of Venetica, Death walks among the living as a flesh & blood being, carrying out the deeds of an ancient council known by a few as Corpus. Each generation of the Corpus is set with the task of selecting the next predecessor of the bringer of death. Unfortunately, the most recent council had unwittingly selected a crafty necromancer who is determined on bringing death and destruction to the world.<br><br>This conniving imposter has managed to transform into an undead fiend, which no mortal man can kill. This power-crazed necromancer is hell-bent on destroying the reinstated Death and the council of Corpus. Only one person stands in his way, Scarlett, the daughter of Death.<br><br>Up to now she has known nothing of her origins, her powers and the capabilities that she possesses - now she is challenged to learn how to develop and use her powers to save her father and curse the necromancer and his henchmen to the eternal hereafter.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M_zkvnS7HjU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cF0ksHgz3g0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T9pSWmi86_c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ISDjt0iqtAU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Venetica-NA/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/venetica/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/venetica"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Venetica Wiki",
				"url":"http://venetica.wikia.com/wiki/Venetica_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":652,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Feel Plus"],
			"synopsis":"A new era. Sophisticated and complex technologies are now contributing to the advancements of mankind. However, the world's governments are crumbling, new corrupt powers arise and conspiracies proliferate. The truth behind the proscribed technology could destroy the very core of humanity. Join a rogue team of agents as they fight for survival and entangle themselves deeper into the mystery.<br><br>Drawing upon the graphics and storytelling mastery of both Square Enix and developer feelplus, Mindjack offers a distinctive experience that throws players into a revolutionary playing field where an engaging solo campaign transitions seamlessly to thrilling, cooperative multiplayer gameplay. Expand your mind's reach by \"hacking\" into enemies, vehicles or civilians and enjoy the freedom to control almost any character. Each bystander becomes an active combatant in this new urban warfare. Your \"state of mind\" is your only limitation!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Extra Map Pack 01",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/28",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Extra Map Pack 1 Includes: Airport Shootout: Defend yourself against a raid of Nerkas soldiers coming from every direction at the San Mira Airport. Construction Carnage: Take cover behind make-shift barricades to battle against countless waves of enemies. Container Maze: Survive through a maze of shipping containers and snipers waiting behind every corner."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Extra Map Pack 02",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/28",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Extra Map Pack 2 Includes: Neon Nightmare: Encounter waves of soldiers and enemies in a fierce battle at an old downtown alley. Look Up, Look Down: Defend yourself from enemies attacking you from every direction on a vertical battlefield. Truth at Nerkas HQ: Fight your way through a labyrinth of structures inside Nerkas Laboratories. Utilize its hidden corners to gain the most advantageous position against your enemies."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cGhfRu9V8ik"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m1yKDRsQBq8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DlJbDmR27-4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mindjack/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mindjack/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mindjack"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":653,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visceral Games"],
			"synopsis":"Engineer Isaac Clarke returns for another blood-curdling adventure in Dead Space 2, the sequel to the critically acclaimed horror adventure. After waking from a coma on a massive space city known as \"The Sprawl\", the lone survivor of a horrific alien infestation finds himself confronting a catastrophic new nightmare. Battling dementia, hunted by the government and haunted by visions of his dead girlfriend, Isaac will do whatever it takes to save himself and rid the city of the gruesome, relentless Necromorphs. Equipped with a new arsenal of tools to dismember the Necromorphs, Isaac will face the challenge head-on.<br><br>In Dead Space 2, Isaac brings the terror to space. Players will take on bigger, scarier and more epic battles that will keep them on the edge of their seats. Delivering a sensory overload of sound, visuals and action sequences, Dead Space 2 will bring the psychological thrills of deep space to a terrifying new level.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Supernova Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Gain the upper hand with this collection of stress-tested tools and suits approved by the CEC for deep space operations."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Hazard Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A collection of powerful new suits and weapons built for the most demanding jobs on the Sprawl."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Martial Law Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Stack the odds in your favor with this collection of battle-hardened weapons and tools."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Severed",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/01",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Severed adds two new chapters to Dead Space 2 that focus on Gabe Weller and Lexine Murdoch and gives you access to a unique security suit and a supercharged pulse rifle & seeker rifle. The DLC has you playing as Gabe in the infected Sprawl as the events of the main game begin to unfold."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Outbreak Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/07",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"This free map pack adds 2 new mutliplayer maps: The Academy and The Concourse."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z7Qy_4sWs3I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=776fi2I8e6U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qSIUYgH4LEs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vDaXowMbEnE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/975303-dead-space-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dead-Space-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dead-space-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dead-space-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dead Space Wiki",
				"url":"http://deadspace.wikia.com/wiki/Dead_Space_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":654,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["TopWare Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Two Worlds II expands the RPG adventure by introducing new game content, extending gameplay and providing you with the answers to many questions and mysteries which arose in the main story. Besides several well-known regions of Antaloor, there are also completely new territories to explore. The combat system has been further enhanced too, with an active blocking system, a completely new means of transport, a much-enhanced reaction system from NPCs, and other tweaks.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Pirates of the Flying Fortress",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/27",
				"achievements":215,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The lands of Two Worlds II: Pirates of the Flying Fortress are teeming with betrayal and trickery as adventurers take to the high seas. Venture forth on an all-new quest to explore a vaguely familiar, yet vastly different and forgotten corner of the world. While abundant in exotic new creatures, enemies, and settings, it is trust that has become the rarest of elements in the world of Antaloor..."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Multiplayer Map Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/27",
				"achievements":35,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"For those seeking new thrilling multiplayer adventures with friends in the \"Two Worlds\" universe, look no further - team up in the new Multiplayer Map Pack! It includes hours and hours of co-op and vs experiences: 7 Duel maps, 4 Adventure maps, 3 Deathmatch maps and 3 Crystal Hunt maps. Besides, what are friends for?"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Defense",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/10",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"See the world of Antaloor from a brand new perspective, as a valued enforcer of Emperor Gandohar and Lord Sordahon, in this latest gaming mode for the acclaimed RPG blockbuster! Defend the Dark Lords with your skills and your life from the incoming waves of hundreds of faithless fiends across 5 newly designed maps. From cursed catacombs, to an abandoned cemetery, to Gandohar's gilded fortress, recruit your friends, stand at the ready, and earn gold and precious magical crystals, as you cut down the enemies. Do you have what it takes to become the Emperor's Sentinel?"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9LJGD-ni7-4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1lrzAoXLXno"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944163-two-worlds-ii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Two-Worlds-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/two-worlds-ii/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/two-worlds-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Two Worlds Wiki",
				"url":"http://twoworlds.wikia.com/wiki/Two_Worlds_II"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":655,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eden Games"],
			"synopsis":"Test Drive Unlimited 2 aims to transform the driving genre, adding the persistency, progression and customization of the latest multiplayer games to the racing experience. Test Drive Unlimited 2 blends single player and multiplayer sxperiences seamlessly, creating a dynamic world of evolving content and challenges. Players define their online persona through unparalleled customization of their avatars and vehicles, and the acquisition of property, clothing and other accoutrements of a luxurious international lifestyle. The challenge comes to life with refinement and balance of the core Test Drive driving experience. All-new race types, vehicle classes, environmental challenges, locations and much more push this epic franchise to new levels of performance.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Explorer Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/21",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"20 new missions including 2 all-new mission types: Extreme Convoy and Timed Convoy. 20 new wrecks to find which give you access to 2 new cars: Lancia Stratos Version Rallye and Dodge charger 1969. 3 additional Discovery levels. 2 new Multiplayer Races for the Stratos Other Enhancements. Help channel added to TDU media. Construction has begun on several new retail locations, Grand Openings coming soon!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Casino Online",
				"releaseDate":"2012/05/29",
				"achievements":195,
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Test your luck on Roulette and several different types of Slot machines. Confront other players at Poker Texas Hold'em and participate in tournaments. Be the best driver on the Casino Island races! Compete to unlock TWO EXCLUSIVE CARS: an Audi R8 Spyder 5.2 FSI quattro and a Spyker C8 Aileron Spyder. Win other exclusive prizes: furniture for your house, stickers for your car and clothes for your avatar. This game gives access to 10 new levels of progression."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"15 Car Bundle",
				"releaseDate":"2013/03/12",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"This special offer delivers all 15 cars released prior to DLC2 at a special low price. If you're looking to access all the content in the game, this is the best value to complete your collection (now you just need that 15 car garage!). Bundle includes Audi Q7 V12 TDI Quattro, Audi RS 5 Coup&eacute;, Bugatti Veyron 16.4 Centenaire, Bugatti Veyron 16.4 Grand Sport Sang Bleu, Bugatti Veyron 16.4 Super Sport, Chevrolet Camaro Synergy Special Edition, Ford Shelby GT500. Aston Martin DBS Carbon Black,Aston Martin V12 Vantage Black, Ferrari 599 GTB Fiorano China Edition, Ferrari 612 Sessanta, Jaguar XKR Speed Pack and Black Pack, Pagani Zonda Tricolore,Caterham Superlight R500 and Nissan 370Z. Cars Sold Separately!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8JaJ1c2AQfE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JkrUnTSby8s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oNApB8c3FvU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b7IMBdCONtM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/990995-test-drive-unlimited-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Test-Drive-Unlimited-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/test-drive-unlimited-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/test-drive-unlimited-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":656,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Jellyvision"],
			"synopsis":"The award-winning You Don't Know Jack trivia franchise is now playable on your Xbox 360! The pioneer of the interactive game show format, You Don't Know Jack returns with all-new questions and classic features such as Screw Your Neighbor and commercial parodies. Filled with more than 15 hours of game play, You Don't Know Jack offers multiplayer action and online challenges via Xbox Live. Along with classic quiz modes such as the DisOrDat and the Jack Attack, You Don't Know Jack offers features like the Wrong Answer of the Game and collectible prizes, with more than 70 full episodes of trivia quiz show.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"JACK Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/08",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"10 brand new episodes."
			},
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"JACK Pack 2: Best of the Webshow",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/29",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"A pack of the best content from the You Don't Know Jack web game."
			},
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"JACK Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/17",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Another 10 new episodes."
			},
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"JACK Pack 4",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/21",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"10 more new episodes."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dUX_4zxkxp0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/You-Dont-Know-Jack/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/you-dont-know-jack/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/you-dont-know-jack"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":657,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Crave Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"It's time to bowl! Brunswick Pro Bowling features a realistic and authentic bowling experience while showcasing jaw-dropping ball and pin physics. Strap on the wrist guard and roll on accurate oil patterns, earn tons of trophies, and unlock hidden items on your way to winning the world championship. Customize your bowler with genuine Brunswick equipment from bowling balls, shoes, and clothing. Whether you're a casual player or a bowling fanatic, Brunswick Pro Bowling provides hours of entertainment for the whole family!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bvy4cCXRgEw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=130GHlSrNuM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Brunswick-Pro-Bowling/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/brunswick-pro-bowling/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/brunswick-pro-bowling"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":658,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Traveller's Tales"],
			"synopsis":"LEGO Star Wars III: The Clone Wars includes all the characters from both seasons of the hugely popular animated television series, Star Wars: The Clone Wars, as well as some fan-favourite characters from the beloved theatrical Star Wars Saga. The game features brand new battle modes, giving players unique, head-to-head combat and an upgraded level builder, allowing the creation of customized bases and in-game battlefields.<br><br>Play either as a Jedi or Separatist with all-new character abilities, such as Squad command, Lightsaber slicing, Lightsaber jumps, long distance Jedi attacks and Grapple Tie-Ups, all within a new, easy-to-navigate hub.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s3pxs81xuTg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ugjd5QmIJJQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FwUkYTqJviw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/988767-lego-star-wars-iii-the-clone-wars/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/LEGO-Star-Wars-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lego-star-wars-iii-the-clone-wars/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lego-star-wars-iii-the-clone-wars"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Brickipedia",
				"url":"http://lego.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Star_Wars_III:_The_Clone_Wars"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wookieepedia",
				"url":"http://starwars.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Star_Wars_III%3A_The_Clone_Wars"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":659,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Capcom"],
			"synopsis":"Marvel Vs. Capcom 3 is an explosive showdown between the heroes of the Capcom universe and the superheroes of the Marvel universe. After a decade of waiting, iconic Marvel and Capcom characters join forces again in team fighting action. Fill the shoes of legendary characters from both the Marvel and Capcom Universes -- including massively popular characters such as Ryu, Wolverine, Iron Man, and Morrigan, as well as fan favorites such as Trish from Devil May Cry and the wise-cracking Deadpool. They all come to you battle in a living comic book art style powered by Capcom's MT Framework, an advance version of the graphics engine used for Resident Evil 5.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Shadow Battle 01",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/01",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Shadow Battle 01 allows the player to battle against AI based off of the developers of Marvel vs. Capcom 3."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Jill Valentine",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/15",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Resident Evil major character Jill Valentine is one of the latest characters available as downloadable content."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Shuma Gorath",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/15",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Marvel character Shuma Gorath is one of the latest characters available as downloadable content."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MCxjuXre3Dw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XdXjZ9xqVT4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/995376-marvel-vs-capcom-3-fate-of-two-worlds/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Marvel-vs-Capcom-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/marvel-vs-capcom-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/marvel-vs-capcom-3-fate-of-two-worlds"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Marvel vs Capcom Wiki",
				"url":"http://marvelvscapcom.wikia.com/wiki/Marvel_vs._Capcom_3%3A_Fate_of_Two_Worlds"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":660,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["People Can Fly", "Epic Games"],
			"synopsis":"Bulletstorm brings new furor to first-person shooter action thanks to its signature 'kill with skill' gameplay. The game tells the story of a futuristic confederation protected by an elite band of mercenaries: Dead Echo. When Dead Echo members Grayson Hunt and Ishi Sato learn they've been working for the wrong side, they're betrayed by their commander and exiled to the far reaches of the galaxy. In Bulletstorm, Grayson and Ishi find themselves surrounded by hordes of mutants and flesh eating gangs in an abandoned paradise. They have two objectives: get off the planet alive, and exact revenge on the man who sent them there.<br><br>Players step into the role of Grayson Hunt complete with an arsenal of over-the-top combat moves and outrageously large guns. Bulletstorm's array of distinct 'skillshots' produces unprecedented levels of frantic gameplay and yell-inducing satisfaction. The skillshot system rewards players for inciting mayhem in the most creative way possible. The more insane the skillshot, the more points players collects to upgrade their character and unlock weapons, which then allows them to execute even more creative moves and exaggerated skillshots.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Gun Sonata DLC Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/12",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The Bulletstorm Gun Sonata DLC pack includes 2 new Echoes maps - Guns of Stygia and Crash Site within which to creatively dispose of your enemies and climb those leaderboards. You'll also be able to jump online with your friends in 3 brand new Anarchy maps: Hotel Elysium, Villa and Sewers, all of which provide unique and brutal opportunities for you to work together and kill with some skill."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Blood Symphony DLC Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/10",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The 2 new Echoes maps included in this pack are: Monorail factory, which has you annihilating your foes through the hallways of a monorail transport hub. Secondly we have Mean Streets, which tasks you with destroying a medley of different enemy types through the streets of Elysium. The Anarchy mode maps allow you and your friends to kill with skill in 3 new areas, including: Mini-City, here enemies can be thrown into miniature skyscrapers as well as sent into the path of a rampaging Mechaton. Rock Quarry, which will see players fighting at night by a cliffside waterfall next to a mining facility and features a number of environmental hazards such as runaway minecarts and furnaces. Finally, we have Ulysses, this map takes place in and furnaces. Finally, we have Ulysses, this map takes place in the jail hub of the ship and, again, offers some 'unique' opportunities for creative players to dispatch their enemies."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CAzdMjP39eg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gjNEKnifT5M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DAF_waUaERQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Halo Parody",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sgWoXu5fhn0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Call of Duty Parody",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uvOGVfqJcUs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tM1Gdp8Yr9k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pk67_UqDpZw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/952598-bulletstorm/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bulletstorm/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bulletstorm/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bulletstorm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Bulletstorm Wiki",
				"url":"http://bulletstorm.wikia.com/wiki/Bulletstorm_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":661,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blue Tongue"],
			"synopsis":"In de Blob 2, Comrade Black is back and so is his war on color. Disguised as Papa Blanc, Comrade Black rigs the city's election in order to win and take control of Prisma City with his brainwashing new cult. That is, until de Blob bounces back in full color-spreading force with his revolution to restore color and life back to the city and its residents.<br><br>In the colorful sequel, de Blob will paint his way through the enormous and pollution-filled Prisma City accompanied by an interactive soundtrack and an arsenal of new tricks to confound his enemies. Joining de Blob will be a new robot sidekick, named Pinky, who will help him blast enemies, disable traps, and negotiate the challenging levels of Prisma City. The game will also present players with new side quests, which allow players to upgrade de Blob's abilities.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j_5cc0dQavg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q9doF72JvZg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_quNLVnv5_M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZcFjs_2X1HI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 5",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LTGtbMwyYSM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 6",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sUoY4LyHXR0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 7",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7_Y8AfDxadQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rF-Q36loVrg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/de-Blob-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/de-blob-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/de-blob-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"De Blob Wiki",
				"url":"http://deblob.wikia.com/wiki/De_Blob_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":662,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Kaos Studios"],
			"synopsis":"The year is 2027. The world has suffered a decade-long energy crisis, and economies have crumbled. Reduced to a mere shadow of the super power it once was, the United States became the target of a North Korean takeover. American malls, suburbs and city streets are now battlegrounds as the civilian resistance fights for freedom. Featuring a compelling single player story crafted by John Milius (Apocalypse Now, Red Dawn), Homefront immerses gamers in an interactive and cinematic FPS experience where they will assume an infantry role or take command of a wide variety of aerial and ground vehicles. In addition to the single-player experience, Homefront will deliver a robust multiplayer experience. In a land stripped of freedom, the brave will fight for their home.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Fire Sale Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/07",
				"type":1
			},
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Rock Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/30",
				"type":1
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4x_-KVooUKQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UYQNcz_MhB0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Campaign Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CEGfBwygaKA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7LVkU3C_xRw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960374-homefront/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Homefront/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/homefront/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/homefront"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Homefront Wiki",
				"url":"http://homefront.wikia.com/wiki/Homefront_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":663,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bandai Namco Games"],
			"synopsis":"In a time of swordsmen and magic, Knights Contract follows the twisted tale of Heinrich, an immortal executioner, and Gretchen, a resurrected witch. Once the victim of Heinrich's blade by the order of the game's antagonist, Dr. Faust, Gretchen now has him under her control as the two must work together to rid the land of the supernatural foes who are cursing its people with the black spell of death.<br><br>Armed with a razor sharp scythe and explosive witchcraft, players will use these tools with spectacular effects in order to return civility to the land. As players succeed in their journey, they can deal tremendous damage to their on-comers or unleash a gruesome finisher by coordinating the efforts of Heinrich and Gretchen. However, players must also keep a close eye on Gretchen as her mortality is the key to the duo's survival as Heinrich can never be vanquished. It's time to let the combos fly and lay waste to the hordes of darkness with a liberal dose of medieval panache.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LHcJYxWZvbA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yQZW31wV3kY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b-iChHIsiwA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/996557-knights-contract/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Knights-Contract/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/knights-contract/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/knights-contract"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":664,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"Step into the ring for this 2011 entry in the knockout king boxing franchise. Fight Night Champion sets out to define a new standard in sports videogames by delivering the most dynamic simulation fighting experience to date, pushing visual boundaries and redefining the single player journey for the category.<br><br>Featuring a refined physics-based animation system that incorporates improved locomotion, punching and stamina mechanics, Fight Night Champion will enable users to move, attack and dodge with the speed and power of the best champions, contenders and pretenders in the world of boxing. In addition, an all-new control scheme (dubbed Full Spectrum Punch Control) will deliver the most realistic punching system ever seen in a simulation fighting game, while still delivering an accessible experience for all players. And Fight Night Champion breaks the mold of what is expected in a single-player sports game. Players will be introduced to an entirely new way to step between the ropes and experience the drama, emotion, excitement and tragedy of world championship boxing.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Heavyweight Legends Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/01",
				"achievements":105,
				"type":4
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Alternate Weight Class Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/01",
				"achievements":45,
				"type":4
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nepBG1PtFd0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7sN8iVSbnnk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PWTLyGrsIxY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nPVW-tZNqWE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jqh9KdioasA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/996445-fight-night-champion/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fight-Night-Champion/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fight-night-champion/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fight-night-champion"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":665,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Behaviour Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Rango The Video Game invites players to continue on Rango's wild journey through new adventures inspired by the movie. Set in a gritty, pint-sized, Wild West World filled with off-color characters, wild rides and frantic shoot-outs, Rango invites players of all ages to meet the residents of the town of Dirt and play through Rango's whacky Tall Tales of Adventure, brimming with intense action and outlandish scenarios.<br><br>Explore a variety of environments featured within and beyond the film, and achieve near impossible feats while working to uncover a plot that threatens the entire population of Dirt. Along the way, Rango will encounter all the trappings of an adventure set in the Old West -- ridin', jumpin', brawlin', and shootin' -- that are crafted from the film's pint-sized desert scene.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4gjeoIvX5HA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7W8lRne81ek"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rango/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rango/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rango"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":666,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["BioWare"],
			"synopsis":"Dragon Age II thrusts players into the role of Hawke, a penniless refugee who rises to power to become the single most important character in the world of Dragon Age. Known to be a survivor of the Blight and the Champion of Kirkwall, the legend around Hawke's rise to power is shrouded in myth and rumor.<br><br>Featuring an all-new story spanning 10 years, players will help tell that tale by making tough moral choices, gathering the deadliest of allies, amassing fame and fortune, and sealing their place in history. The way you play will write the story of how the world is changed forever.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Black Emporium",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/01",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Come one, come all to the Black Emporium! There, nestled deep under Kirkwall, you'll find a curious collection of items-some for sale, some for free, and ranging from the mundane to the mysterious! One artifact can even transform your very body, face, hair, eyes-all new! Act now to receive your very own mabari war hound that you can call to your side with a whistle-a boon in battle and a beloved pet at home. Purchase the Black Emporium today, or download it for free as part of your Online Pass, and you'll be the envy of adventurers everywhere! Once you've escaped imminent danger, return home."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"The Exiled Prince",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/01",
				"achievements":130,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Sworn to the priesthood as a boy, the noble archer Sebastian Vael is thrust back into the viper's nest of princely politics when his family is brutally murdered, leaving him as the sole surviving heir. Adventure together through three new missions as you choose to either avenge Sebastian's murdered family and reclaim his title or direct his holy vengeance on your enemies in Kirkwall. Purchase The Exiled Prince today to employ this full Dragon Age II follower's unshakable loyalty and excellent aim. "
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Mage Item Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The story of the Hawke family began with the forbidden love of a fugitive mage hiding from the Chantry, and the noblewoman who abandoned her life of power and privilege to flee across Thedas with the man she loved. These mementos of Malcolm and Leandra Hawke's adventures have now passed to their children. Take up the family legacy, and write your own chapter of the Hawke family tale. This item pack includes relics and mementos of untold power for use by your Mage and Mage followers."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Warrior Item Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The original owner of this priceless collection was an Orlesian chevalier who was stabbed in the heart thirteen times. His prized possessions were taken from him at the time of his death, and since then, anyone who has claimed a piece of his stolen property has met a gruesome and untimely end. Each piece of this collection would make a princely gift for a warrior in your company. But would you tempt fate, and risk the wrath of a man murdered in cold blood? This item pack includes a collection of arms, armor and accessories for your Warrior and Warrior followers."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Rogue Item Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Collected here are the storied items of the greatest scoundrels the Dragon Age setting has known. Dashing liars and murderous shadows-the best and worst that rogues offer. Add to the legacy, or just enjoy the fact that as good as they were, you have their stuff. This item pack includes new armor, weapons, and accessories for use by your Rogue and Rogue followers."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Legacy",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/26",
				"achievements":120,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"A vicious criminal cartel is hunting \"the blood of the Hawke\". To end their attacks, you must venture outside Kirkwall to investigate a prison constructed by the Grey Wardens in ages past. You will uncover the harsh truths about the Hawke lineage as your journey brings you face to face with an ancient horror. Includes: (1) Hours of adventuring spread across several brand-new areas. (2) New enemies to battle including genlocks, brontos, and an epic boss fight. (3) A powerful class-specific weapon to which you can apply upgrades of your choice. To begin, return to your house in Kirkwall and look for the Memento of Legacy."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Rogue Item Pack II",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"For decades, Ferelden was held captive. The land's freedom was secured in time, but the rebel king did not act alone. Many scoundrels worked to free the kingdom, and then to shape it. Loghain was a notorious bandit before he turned general. Duncan was little better before he joined the Wardens. Now, their powerful relics can be yours! This item pack includes new armor, weapons, and accessories for use by your rogue Hawke and rogue party members."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Warrior Item Pack II",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"From the frozen heights of the Frostbacks to the murky swamps of the Korcari Wilds, there the barbarians of Ferelden dwell. They have fought off empires, led holy wars, and conquered Blights. Contained within are the strongest arms and armors of their stalwart heroes. Take their might for your own as you carve out your destiny in Kirkwall! This item pack includes new armor, weapons, and accessories for use by your warrior Hawke and warrior party members."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Mage Item Pack II",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"When tales are told of the greatest mages who ever lived, one is always mentioned - Aldenon the Wise. With magic and guile, he helped guide Calenhad, a young squire, to be crowned first king of united Ferelden. Later he nearly brought the newly formed Circle Tower to its knees. His mystic artifacts are only given to those worthy of his legacy. Now it is your turn. This item pack includes new armor, weapons, and accessories for use by your mage Hawke and mage party members."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Mark of the Assassin",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/11",
				"achievements":120,
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"mbark on a thrilling adventure of deception and intrigue alongside a mysterious assassin. Infiltrate an estate far from Kirkwall and battle deadly new enemies with the help of Tallis, a new party member voiced by Felicia Day. Includes: (1) Hours of adventuring spread across several brand-new areas. (2) Impressive new equipment for every member of your party. To begin, return to your house in Kirkwall and look for the Memento of Mark of the Assassin"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jlACgYHtWCI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Rh43mO4Huds"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K8mn1rVakZg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2MXY1uCV6LY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HbewMIBdS70"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/988966-dragon-age-ii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dragon-Age-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dragon-age-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dragon-age-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dragon Age Wiki",
				"url":"http://dragonage.wikia.com/wiki/Dragon_Age_II"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":667,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["CyberConnect2"],
			"synopsis":"Inspired by Asian mythology and fused with science fiction, Asura's Wrath aims to redefine the action genre by delivering unprecedented levels of dynamism, drama and interaction. Once a revered deity, Asura was betrayed by his fellow gods and stripped of all his powers. Consumed by anger at the injustice he has suffered and swearing vengeance, Asura discovers he can use this fury to his advantage and turn it against his enemies. By channelling his inner rage, Asura is now able to unleash devastating attacks and wreak havoc as he battles against the deities who have wronged him and their earthly forces. Inspired by episodic dramas, Asura's Wrath is split into distinct sections with gameplay and narrative unfolding as one and building to a final climatic conclusion.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Episode 11.5",
				"releaseDate":"2012/03/27",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Asura narrowly defeats his former mentor in a climactic battle. But the clash between student and master has disturbed the planet, waking an endless sea of Gohma. Realizing that they are headed straight for a nearby village, Asura charges in their direction... Don't miss this fully-animated episode revealing the mysterious explosion between episodes 11 and 12!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Episode 15.5",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/03",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Having lost himself to his wrath, Asura exchanges fists with his eternal rival, Yasha. In the midst of their battle, Yasha discovers a new power within him. It is in this moment that he decides to pursue their cause through a different means -- through this newfound power. But before he can do this, he must confront the leader of the Seven Deities. Don't miss this fully-animated episode revealing Yasha's defiance between episodes 15 and 16!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Episode Pack: Part IV",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/24",
				"achievements":165,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"It was not the end. The cries that echo across the planet have yet to cease. But why? Why does the world still suffer? Asura and Yasha take on the one who has been manipulating even the demigods themselves in \"Part IV: Nirvana\", the epic four episode conclusion to Asura's Wrath!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Lost Episode 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/08",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"One of the world's greatest warriors appears before Asura... His name is Ryu. He challenges Asura to a duel and they exchange punches in an intense battle. Ryu is then suddenly consumed by the Satsui no Hado... The characters appearing in this episode are voiced only in Japanese."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Lost Episode 2",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/15",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"After his battle with Ryu, Asura is confronted by Akuma, the fighter who seeks to surpass all. They clash in a fierce battle that escalates into both of their transformations: Akuma into Oni, and Asura into Mantra Asura. No one knows how far their battle will take them past the limits of their sanity. The characters appearing in this episode are voiced only in Japanese."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YJ30HjDBngw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RR_NkqleMfw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_O9KYmvHZ80"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/605975-asuras-wrath/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Asuras-Wrath/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/asuras-wrath/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/asuras-wrath"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Asura's Wrath Wiki",
				"url":"http://asuraswrath.wikia.com/wiki/Asura%27s_Wrath_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":668,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"Swing for the fences with the 2011/2012 edition of 2K Sports' acclaimed baseball franchise. This year's edition offers improvements in the fielding system to ensure better control of the ball against the advancing runners. Each player has been re-created in the game down to the last detail, with performance stats based on live data to match the realistic looks. And with My Player Mode, gamers can look beyond the league and their team to focus on just one player that they guide through a Minor League career all the way through the ranks to step out on the field as a big league star.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HMArort_jTU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S95yeWL0hAU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sH4LeeO77SE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MLB-2K11/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/major-league-baseball-2k11"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":669,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Slightly Mad Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Need for Speed Shift 2 Unleashed builds on the true driving experience that the NFS franchise is renown for by introducing the driver's battle, an even more authentic and primal feeling of power and speed which elevates the fundamental competitive race into a struggle for supremacy against other drivers and even the track itself. In Shift 2 Unleashed, players' hands sweat and ache as they clutch onto the controller, their pulse races from the break-neck speeds experienced through the first-person cockpit view.<br><br>Shift 2 Unleashed features an all-new rendering engine with a massive graphics overhaul that puts the player in the heart of the racing action. With an innovative helmet camera view simulating the physical experience of driving at 200mph, the thrilling experience of night racing and authentic degradation of tracks and cars, this is tomorrow's sim for today's adrenaline fueled racer. Shift 2 Unleashed also incorporates the next generation of Need for Speed Autolog -- the groundbreaking network that connects friends for epic head-to-head races and compares player stats for the ultimate social racing competition.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Legends",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/26",
				"achievements":35,
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"There has never been a better representation of racing's golden age than the Legends Pack for Shift 2 Unleashed. In the pack, you'll get access to 13 of racing's most legendary cars, including the Porsche 911 Carrera RSR 3.0 and BMW 3.0 CSL Gr.5, and 5 of the most treacherous tracks you'll ever race on, including the classic configurations of Rouen and Monza."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Speedhunters Edition",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/17",
				"achievements":80,
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"The Speedhunters Edition Pack for Shift 2 Unleashed includes 12 unique cars with their own special updates, tuning and liveries, as well as 2 exciting new race modes: Drag and Standing Mile, so if you like tuning a beast to generate 1600 horsepower and go 250 mph, this pack is a must!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=21bg2moGRU8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MOyMxfxUct8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xfpNzKjPBP4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BHtCrQXKw44"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wmwG2ix87-s"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/604347-shift-2-unleashed/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Need-for-Speed-Shift-2-Unleashed/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/need-for-speed-shift-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/shift-2-unleashed"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Need for Speed Wiki",
				"url":"http://nfs.wikia.com/wiki/Shift_2:_Unleashed"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":670,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["KOEI Canada"],
			"synopsis":"In the age when Zeus Almighty ruled over immortals and men, what begins as a truce between two cities quickly erupts into a massive war that will shake the very foundations of Olympus. Two great armies clash not over home and country, but for the love of a single woman. The fates of these civilizations now stand upon the razor's edge...<br><br>From the creators of Dynasty Warriors comes an unbelievable game that tells the tale of the epic Trojan War. In this ancient time, men and gods fought alongside one another for eternal glory. Carve your name into history as you experience amazing action and incredible mythology.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=41VyuZTGBM0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U-3GjOC6Uvc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fZapXLTn47w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aFDQbaAueZg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Legends-of-Troy/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/warriors-legends-of-troy"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Koei Wiki",
				"url":"http://koei.wikia.com/wiki/Warriors:_Legends_of_Troy"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":671,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["2K Czech"],
			"synopsis":"Top Spin 4 redefines the way you experience the game of tennis. Intuitive controls make gameplay immediately accessible yet deep and rewarding for the tennis experts who want to plan their strategy, target their opponent's weaknesses and become an unstoppable force on the court. The most feature-rich title of the Top Spin franchise, Top Spin 4, puts you front and center of the professional tennis experience with the deepest player roster to date complete with 2K's Signature Style, an enhanced Player Creator with new Coaching and Development systems, an incredibly immersive Career mode, all-new visually stunning TV Broadcast presentation elements, and a fully online World Tour Mode. Do you have what it takes to rise above the competition and become #1 in the world?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1AD7o4z48LM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aoEA8sW_aRU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EIzP25Irvrk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Top-Spin-4/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/top-spin-4/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/top-spin-4"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":672,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eutechnyx"],
			"synopsis":"NASCAR The Game 2011 completely redefines what fans can expect from a NASCAR racing game. Players can choose to play as themselves or as one of the sport's real-world drivers as they battle it out for the NASCAR Sprint Cup Series Championship. Each pro driver has the AI characteristics of his or her real world counterpart, setting the stage for intense rivalries played out on the track. From the 22 real world tracks to full pit stop strategy action, NASCAR The Game 2011 captures the real atmosphere, sense of speed and spectacle that embodies NASCAR. Players can even feel the thrill of a win with the interactive celebration mode.<br><br>The game also includes multiplayer modes which allow up to 16 players to battle it out for the win online. In both online and offline races, players earn NASCAR experience points which help unlock rewards such as decal packs or special car designs, as well as career sponsorships and special races throughout career mode. Everything you do on the track counts.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cgkEcv1yXos"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z-lAWZEI2f0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NASCAR-The-Game-2011/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nascar-2011-the-game/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nascar-2011-the-game"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":673,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Crytek Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Whether played in 3D or standard 2D, Crysis 2 drops players into a devastated New York in the midst of an attack by a frightening alien species. The alien enemies are armed with deadly weaponry and exceptional sensory abilities that test players' skill and push them to the limit. These terrifying invaders stalk the streets of New York, leaving the streets in chaos and the skyline in flaming ruin.<br><br>Surrounded by catastrophic destruction, players harness the superhuman abilities of the Nanosuit to level the playing field, becoming the ultimate weapon on a mission to save New York.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Retaliation Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/17",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"In the Retaliation Pack the multiplayer battlefield is expanded with 4 brand new maps supporting all game modes - Park Avenue, Transit, Shipyard, and Compound. Adapt. Upgrade. Dominate. Be The Weapon."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Decimation Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/14",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Decimation Pack upgrades the multiplayer experience with 5 new battle-torn maps supporting all game modes - 5th Avenue, Chasm, Plaza, Prism, Apartments; and 2 new equipment items - the FY71 Assault Rifle and M18 Smoke Grenade. Adapt. Upgrade. Dominate. Be The Weapon"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=laIghwTFdqg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YUhXKUEtyHs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oBwReBKYs2s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Campaign Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VJvpTd-Oo9M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fBXVyPgoIgE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960491-crysis-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Crysis-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/crysis-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/crysis-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Crysis Wiki",
				"url":"http://crysis.wikia.com/wiki/Crysis_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":674,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Omega Force"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the epic novel, Romance of the Three Kingdoms, the genre-defining Dynasty Warriors series depicts the massive battles ignited by the fall of the Han Dynasty when three rebellious states moved to overthrow the Emperor of China.<br><br>Incredible might and power of warriors is born again in this seventh chapter of the dynasties with Shu, Wei, Wu and the new Kingdom of Jin, the state that superseded the Three Kingdoms period. Dynasty Warriors 7 will embrace new technology with full stereoscopic 3D.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"New Stage & BGM Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/03",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This pack features a brand new stage for Conquest Mode: Sanjiang Castle! Three distinct scenarios are available to be played out on this stage, the home of the King of Nanzhong, Meng Huo. Additionally, two sets of BGM music are included, featuring tracks from Dynasty Warriors 5 and Dynasty Warriors 6."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Costume Pack 0",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Use the original costumes from the first Dynasty Warriors for Zhao Yun, Xiahou Dun, Lu Bu, Diao Chan and Taishi Ci."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Costume Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Use costumes from Dynasty Warriors 6 for all 42 characters who appeared in the game. In addition, costumes for Da Qiao, Jiang Wei, Xing Cai, and Zhu Rong are also included."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"New Weapon Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Attack your enemies with two new weapons, the Dagger-axe and the Bomb. Grab and slam nearby enemies or perform multi-level attacks with the Dagger-axe, or set the Bomb to explode and cause massive damage! Both weapons will be added to your inventory, but you can also create them at the Blacksmith or earn more powerful versions of each weapon by clearing each weapon scenario in Conquest Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Japanese Voice Option",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/03",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Play Dynasty Warriors 7 with voices in the original Japanese. After downloading the Japanese Voice Option, go to the \"Options\" menu under \"Sound Settings\" - \"Voice Language\" and select \"Japanese\" to switch to Japanese voices."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Stage Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/24",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Play the 'Yellow Turbans' and 'Hulao Gate' stages in Conquest Mode, with 3 scenarios remastered from Dynasty Warriors 2 for each stage. The 'Yellow Turbans' stage includes the 'Yellow Turban Rebellion', 'Fall of the Han' and 'Test of Faith' scenarios. The 'Hulao Gate' stage includes the 'Battle of Hulao Gate', 'Allied Invasion Resistance' and 'Sishui Gate Defensive Battle' scenarios."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Original Costume Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/24",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Use original costumes for the 13 Wei officers including uniforms, suits, high school club outfits, etc. Experience a battlefield like you've never seen with these unique costumes!"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Costume Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/24",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Use costumes from Dynasty Warriors 5 for all 46 characters who appeared in the game."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"New Weapon Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/24",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Attack your enemies with two new weapons, the Short Pike and the Mace. The Short Pike is the perfect balance of range and speed and allows counterattacks, and the Mace is very powerful with a wide attack range! Both weapons will be added to your inventory, but you can also create them at the Blacksmith or earn more powerful versions of each weapon by clearing each weapon scenario in Conquest Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Original Costume Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Experience a battlefield like you've never seen with these unique and original costumes for the 16 Wu officers!"
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Original Costume Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Use original costumes for the 17 Shu officers including uniforms, suits, high school club outfits, etc. Experience a battlefield like you've never seen with these unique costumes!"
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"New Weapon 'Great Axe'",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Attack your enemies with new weapon, the Great Axe. Mow all your enemies down with ease with the Great Axe! This weapons will be added to your inventory, but you can also create at the Blacksmith or earn more powerful versions of weapon by clearing weapon scenario in Conquest Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"Stage Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/16",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Play the 'Changban' and 'Guandu' stages in Conquest Mode, with 3 scenarios remastered from Dynasty Warriors 2 for each stage. The 'Changban' stage includes the 'Battle of Changban', 'Destruction of Changban' and 'Escape from Changban' scenarios. The 'Guandu' stage includes the 'Battle of Guandu', 'Capture of Guandu' and 'Invasion of Guandu' scenarios."
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"New Stage & BGM Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/16",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This pack features a brand new stage for Conquest Mode: Ji Castle! Three distinct scenarios are available to be played out on this stage, the home of the King of Nanzhong, Meng Huo. Additionally, 8 BGM music are included, featuring tracks from Dynasty Warriors 4 and Dynasty Warriors 5."
			},
			{
				"id":15,
				"name":"Costume Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Use costumes from Dynasty Warriors 4 for all 42 characters who appeared in the game, plus 4 additional character costumes."
			},
			{
				"id":16,
				"name":"Weapon Rank pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Complete new scenarios in Conquest Mode to acquire new versions of 35 different weapons from the game, and 5 downloadable weapons for players who have downloaded those weapons."
			},
			{
				"id":17,
				"name":"Weapon Rank pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Complete new scenarios in Conquest Mode to acquire new versions of 35 different weapons from the game, and 5 downloadable weapons for players who have downloaded those weapons."
			},
			{
				"id":18,
				"name":"Stage Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/13",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Play the 'Chibi' and 'Hefei' stages in Conques Mode, with 3 scenarios remastered from Dynasty Warriors 2 for each stage. The 'Chibi' stage includes the 'Battle of Chibi', 'Assault at Chibi' and 'Fire Attack at Chibi' scenarios. The 'Hefei' stage includes the 'Battle of Hefei', 'Defense of Hefei', and 'Grand Battle at Hefei' scenarios."
			},
			{
				"id":19,
				"name":"BGM Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/13",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Listen to classic Dynasty Warriors BGM in the Conquest/Sound Test game modes. This pack includes some of the most popular BGM tracks from Dynasty Warriors 3 through Dynasty Warriors 6."
			},
			{
				"id":20,
				"name":"Original Costume Pack 4",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Use original costumes for the 16 Jin and Other officers including uniforms, suits, high school club outfits, etc. Experience a battlefield like you've never seen with these unique costumes!"
			},
			{
				"id":21,
				"name":"New Stage & BGM Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/11",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This pack features a brand new stage for Conquest Mode: Jianye! Three distinct scenarios are available to be played out on this stage. Additionally, 8 BGM music are included, featuring tracks from Dynasty Warriors 3, Dynasty Warriors 4 and Dynasty Warriors 6."
			},
			{
				"id":22,
				"name":"Stage Pack 4",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/11",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Play the 'Yiling' and 'Wuzhang Plains' stages in Conquest Mode, with 3 scenarios remastered from Dynasty Warriors 2 for each stage. The 'Yiling' stage includes the 'Battle of Yiling', 'Assault at Yiling' and 'Defend Yiling' scenarios. The 'Wuzhang Plains' stage includes the 'Battle of the Wuzhang Plains', 'Dreams of Conquest', and 'Brawl at the Wuzhang Plains' scenarios."
			},
			{
				"id":23,
				"name":"Costume Pack 4",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/11",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Use costumes from Dynasty Warriors 3 for all 39 characters who appeared in the game. 4 BGM tracks from Dynasty Warriors 4 and Dynasty Warriors 6 are included in this pack too."
			},
			{
				"id":24,
				"name":"Excel Stage Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/20",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The following four additional stages will become available to play in Conquest Mode: Brawl at Taoshui, Siege of Nanpi, Chaos at Puyang, Siege of Mt. Dingjun."
			},
			{
				"id":25,
				"name":"Original Costume Pack 5",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Fantasy-style costumes for the 16 characters who debuted in Dynasty Warriors 7 will become available for selection under Change Outfit. Experience a fresh take on battlefield action with these new and unique outfits."
			},
			{
				"id":26,
				"name":"New Weapon Pack 4",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"New models for each weapon type will become available to be equipped under Weapons. A total of 41 new weapons are included."
			},
			{
				"id":27,
				"name":"Xtreme Stage Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/17",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The following four additional stages will become available to play in Conquest Mode: Melee at Mt. Xingshi, Siege of Liaodong, Advance upon Luo Castle, Xtreme Family Feud."
			},
			{
				"id":28,
				"name":"Legend Stage Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/14",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Play the Guandu and Yiling stages in Conquest Mode, with 3 scenarios remastered from Dynasty Warriors 5 for each stage. The Guandu stage includes the Battle of Guandu - Cao Cao's Forces, Battle of Guandu - Yuan Shao's Forces and Chaos at Guandu scenarios. The Yiling stage includes the Battle of Yiling - Wu Forces, Battle of Yiling - Shu Forces, and Breakthrough at Yiling scenarios."
			},
			{
				"id":29,
				"name":"Xtreme Stage Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/14",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The following four additional stages will become available to play in Conquest Mode: Chaos at Nanjun, Siege of Yangping Gate, Dongxing Battle of Wits, Struggle for Tong Gate."
			},
			{
				"id":30,
				"name":"New Weapon Pack 5",
				"releaseDate":"2012/03/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"New models for each weapon type Pugil Stick and Spiked Shield will become available to be equipped under Weapons."
			},
			{
				"id":31,
				"name":"BGM Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2012/03/13",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Listen to classic Dynasty Warriors BGM in the Conquest/Sound Test game modes. This pack includes some of the most popular BGM tracks from Dynasty Warriors 2: Xtreme Legends, Dynasty Warriors 5, Dynasty Warriors 6 and Dynasty Warriors 6 Special."
			},
			{
				"id":32,
				"name":"Legend Stage Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2012/03/13",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Play Changban and Wuzhang Plains stages in Conquest Mode, with 3 scenarios remastered from Dynasty Warriors 4 for each."
			},
			{
				"id":33,
				"name":"Xtreme Stacke Pack 4",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/17",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The following four additional stages will become available to play in Conquest Mode: Breakthrough at Hefei, Family Matters, Paradise Lost, Life of the Party."
			},
			{
				"id":34,
				"name":"Xtreme Stacke Pack 5",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/17",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The following four additional stages will become available to play in Conquest Mode: Rivalry at Qing Province, Breakthrough at Jiangdong, Dragon versus Phoenix, Glorious Leaders."
			},
			{
				"id":35,
				"name":"Legend Stage Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/17",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Play the Nanzhong and Hefei stages in Conquest Mode, with 3 scenarios remastered from Dynasty Warriors 3 for each stage. Added scenarios: Pacification of Nanzhong - Shu Forces, Pacification of Nanzhong - Nanzhong Forces, Fire at Nanzhong, Battle of Hefei - Wei Forces, Battle of Hefei - Wu Forces, Chaos at Hefei."
			},
			{
				"id":36,
				"name":"New Weapon Pack 6",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"New models for the weapon types Lightning Sword and Arm Blade will become available to be equipped under Weapons."
			},
			{
				"id":37,
				"name":"Wallpapers 1",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/17",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"New wallpapers for all 16 officers of the Wei Kingdom will become available for selection under Wallpaper."
			},
			{
				"id":38,
				"name":"Wallpapers 2",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/17",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"New wallpapers for all 16 officers of the Wu Kingdom will become available for selection under Wallpaper."
			},
			{
				"id":39,
				"name":"Wallpapers 3",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/17",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"New wallpapers for all 17 officers of the Shu Kingdom will become available for selection under Wallpaper."
			},
			{
				"id":40,
				"name":"Wallpapers 4",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/17",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"New wallpapers for all 16 Jin Kingdom and unaffiliated officers will become available for selection under Wallpaper."
			},
			{
				"id":41,
				"name":"Wallpapers 5",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/17",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"New wallpapers for all 5 Kingdoms and unaffiliated officers will become available for selection under Wallpaper."
			},
			{
				"id":42,
				"name":"Wallpapers 6",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/17",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"New wallpapers for all 16 officers of the Wei Kingdom will become available for selection under Wallpaper."
			},
			{
				"id":43,
				"name":"Wallpapers 7",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/17",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"New wallpapers for all 16 officers of the Wu Kingdom will become available for selection under Wallpaper."
			},
			{
				"id":44,
				"name":"Wallpapers 8",
				"releaseDate":"2012/05/08",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"New wallpapers for all 17 officers of the Shu Kingdom will become available for selection under Wallpaper."
			},
			{
				"id":45,
				"name":"Wallpapers 9",
				"releaseDate":"2012/05/08",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"New wallpapers for all 16 unaffiliated and Jin Kingdom officers will become available for selection under Wallpaper."
			},
			{
				"id":46,
				"name":"New Weapon Pack 7",
				"releaseDate":"2012/05/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The new weapon types Boomerang and Circle Blade will become available to be equipped under Weapons."
			},
			{
				"id":47,
				"name":"Original Costume Pack 6",
				"releaseDate":"2012/06/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Fantasy-style costumes for the 13 characters from the kingdom of Wei will become available under Change Outfit."
			},
			{
				"id":48,
				"name":"Original Costume Pack 7",
				"releaseDate":"2012/06/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Fantasy-style costumes for the 16 characters from the kingdom of Wu will become available for selection under Change Outfit."
			},
			{
				"id":49,
				"name":"Original Costume Pack 8",
				"releaseDate":"2012/06/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Fantasy-style costumes for the 17 characters from the kingdom of Shu will become available for selection under Change Outfit."
			},
			{
				"id":50,
				"name":"Original Costume Pack 9",
				"releaseDate":"2012/06/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Fantasy-style costumes for the 16 unaffiliated and Jin Kingdom characters will be available for selection under Change Outfit."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TzEAkeHuPvU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t3rhK1ROVoA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rT_sp6k96VA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bnZ7eqW2tRk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/606311-dynasty-warriors-7/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dynasty-Warriors-7/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dynasty-warriors-7/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dynasty-warriors-7"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Koei Wiki",
				"url":"http://koei.wikia.com/wiki/Dynasty_Warriors_7"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":675,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Left Field Productions"],
			"synopsis":"Featuring a distince noir comic book aeshetic, Mayhem challenges players to crush or be crushed in a white-knuckle racing and car destruction game.<br><br>Highly customizable for hours of opponent pummeling entertainment, the fast-paxced arcade racing video game features realistic 3D action.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XlmaN7AEyLk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vI-Egy-Eiwg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mayhem-3D/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mayhem/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mayhem-3d"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":676,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"For the first time in the history of this award-winning sports franchise, players are able to step onto the hallowed grounds of Augusta National, experience the rich history and tradition of the Masters Tournament and begin their own journey to capture the most sought-after prize in professional golf -- the Green Jacket.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable courses",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/29",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"New courses available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DDHDGoUVATM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aNVuq32KQLI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PvK9dFurBJQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/618274-tiger-woods-pga-tour-12-the-masters/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tiger-Woods-PGA-TOUR-12/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tiger-woods-pga-tour-12/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tiger-woods-pga-tour-12-the-masters"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":677,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["THQ San Diego"],
			"synopsis":"WWE All Stars is an over-the-top, arcade-style beat-down featuring the WWE's past and present superstars of the ring. WWE All Stars delivers one of the greatest rosters ever assembled in a wrestling-centric videogame. Renowned WWE Legends will align with today's most prominent WWE Superstars, inviting players to generate fantasy matches and ultimately determine the greatest competitors of all time. In addition, each WWE Legend and WWE Superstar will boast a distinctive and highly stylized appearance, adding to the overall atmosphere and intrepid attitude exuding from the on-screen action.<br><br>WWE All Stars encompasses a fluid, intuitive and original gameplay style, creating a highly competitive environment and an engaging spectacle. Packed with high-flying, hard hitting and over the top action, players will explore a variety of responsive quick grapples, strong grapples, standing and running attacks, as well as combination sequences. Every WWE Legend and WWE Superstar on the power-packed roster will be equipped with individual abilities, signature moves and renowned finishers to create the ultimate in-ring experience.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Compatibility Pack 1 featuring Honky Tonk Man",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Don't be cruel! Download and play as the Greatest Intercontinental Champion of all-time, the Honky Tonky Man, in WWE All Stars! Please Note: This pack also contains a compatibility update."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"American Dream Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get funky like a monkey if you will and download the American Dream Pack, featuring 2 new downloadable characters for WWE All Stars: WWE Hall of Famer Dusty Rhodes and his son, \"Dashing\" Cody Rhodes."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Million Dollar Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/29",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Everybody's got a price! Download the Million Dollar Pack and bring one of the greatest father and son pairings in WWE history to WWE All Stars! The Million Dollar Pack includes two bonus downloadable characters for your roster: WWE Legend and Hall of Famer, the Million Dollar Man and his son, current RAW Superstar, Ted DiBiase."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Compatibility Pack 2 featuring R-Truth",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"What's up? It's R-Truth! Download now to add one of WWE's premier rising stars to WWE All Stars. Please Note: This pack also contains a compatibility update. Please download prior to playing WWE All Stars multiplayer on Xbox LIVE."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"All-Time Greats Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"What a rush! Download this pack to add some of the greatest Superstars of all-time to WWE All Stars. This pack features Hawk and Animal, the legendary Road Warriors, Chris Jericho, and Jerry 'The King' Lawler!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Southern Charisma Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Have you ever taken a trip down to Cobb County, Georgia? How about Badstreet, Atlanta G.A? Some of the greatest Superstars in WWE history have called the South 'home'. Download this pack to play as - 'The Fabulous Freebird', Michael Hayes, 'The World's Strongest Man', Mark Henry, and the Big Boss Man!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QE6azcSC-ms"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uQMO_coTFJY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_kiiB_HcoiM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=riXEaeKxF4U"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/997443-wwe-all-stars/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/WWE-All-Stars/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wwe-all-stars/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wwe-all-stars"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":678,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Larian Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Divinity II - The Dragon Knight Saga includes the original adventure \"Ego Draconis\", and \"Flames of Vengeance\", the Dragon Knight's new adventure that continues the epic story and adds dozens of hours of additional gameplay.<br><br>Divinity II - The Dragon Knight Saga offers an epic total of over 60 hours of gameplay and more than 180 original quests that combine into a fantastic role playing experience.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nzsg_WkSI6s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rAajB7x9QIk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/998545-divinity-ii-the-dragon-knight-saga/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Divinity-2-Dragon-Knight-Saga/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/divinity-2-the-dragon-knight-saga/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/divinity-ii-the-dragon-knight-saga"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Divinity Wiki",
				"url":"http://divinity.wikia.com/wiki/Portal:Divinity_II:_Dragon_Knight_Saga"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":679,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Scientifically Proven"],
			"synopsis":"Man vs. Wild captures the heart-pounding excitement and realistic nature of the Discovery Channel's top-rated television series. The game offers five authentic situations in a role play-style adventure, featuring seasoned survival expert Bear Grylls.<br><br>The action begins when players are dropped into extreme conditions and forced to demonstrate indigenous survival techniques such as escaping quicksand in the desert, exploring dangerous jungles, traversing ravines in the mountains and navigating some of the world's most treacherous waters.<br><br>The core gameplay of Man vs. Wild is a dynamic mix of exhilarating action adventure, role playing and puzzle solving tasks throughout five extraordinary expeditions. Players gather materials to accomplish tasks such as building fires, catching food, and creating the necessary tools for survival while traveling across miles of diverse landscapes.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jywCoytchDg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iJ5EXDg_QrY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Man-vs-Wild/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/man-vs-wild/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/man-vs-wild-with-bear-grylls"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":680,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eurocom"],
			"synopsis":"Birds of a feather party together in this party adventure based on the hit animated movie Rio! In this multiplayer video game, Blu goes on the adventure of his life, with the help of his female counterpart, Jewel, and a group of wise-cracking and smooth-talking city birds. Blu and his new friends journey through Rio, dodging soccer balls, collecting tropical fruits and soaring across the beach. He participates in amazing games and ultimately, forms a conga line and dances his way to first place at the Carnaval ceremony. While the main character is Blu, players will also have a chance to play as the other characters from the movie!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P89_GCUAFUs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AVq2yboD_1Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/621457-rio/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rio/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rio/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rio"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Rio Wiki",
				"url":"http://rio.wikia.com/wiki/Rio_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":681,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Nuclear Monkey Software", "Valve"],
			"synopsis":"Portal 2 is a hilariously mind-bending adventure that challenges you to use wits over weaponry in a funhouse of diabolical science.<br><br>Using a highly experimental portal device, you'll once again face off against a lethally inventive, power-mad A.I. named GLaDOS. And this time you won't be alone. Meet an expanded cast of characters as you think your way through dangerous, never-before-seen areas of Aperture Laboratories.<br><br>Break the laws of spatial physics in ways you never thought possible, with a wider variety of portal puzzles and an expansive story that spans a single player and co-operative game mode.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Peer Review",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/04",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Featuring a devious new co-op track that continues the story of Atlas, Peabody and GLaDOS, the DLC also includes both single and multiplayer challenge modes, plus leaderboards so you can compare your portal placement and time scores with the Portal community."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"All Trailers",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dWTqylt3JQQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Campaign Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ix_YE7vx0hU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Co-Op Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YiXFDtPCETM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/991101-portal-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Portal-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/portal-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/portal-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Portal Wiki",
				"url":"http://theportalwiki.com/wiki/Portal_2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Half-Life Wiki",
				"url":"http://half-life.wikia.com/wiki/Portal_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":682,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["NetherRealm Studios"],
			"synopsis":"After centuries of Mortal Kombat, Emperor Shao Kahn has finally defeated Raiden and his allies. Faced with extinction, Raiden has one last chance to save Earthrealm. To undo the Emperor's victory, he must strike Shao Kahn where he is vulnerable...the Past.<br><br>Driven by an all new graphics engine, the fan favorite series is back and presented in more gory detail than ever before. Mortal Kombat (known as Mortal Kombat 9 by the fans) introduces a number of game-play features including tag team and the deepest story mode of any fighting game. Players can choose from an extensive lineup of the game's iconic warriors and challenge their friends in traditional 1 vs. 1 matches, or take on several new game modes.<br><br>Introducing a number of game modes as well as an online experience, Mortal Kombat allows up to 4 players can battle \"tag-team\"- 2 players can team up in the new \"Co-op Arcade Mode\" or compete against another team online.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Klassic Skins Pack #1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/07",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Relive the Klassic days of Mortal Kombat just the way you remember. Download the Klassic Skins Pack #1 and receive 7 Klassic Character Skins (Scorpion, Sub-Zero, Reptile, Ermac, Kitana, Mileena, Jade) and 3 Klassic Fatalities (Scorpion, Sub-Zero, Reptile)."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Skarlet",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Warrior blood gathered from countless battlefields, fused with sorcery, produced Shao Kahn's most effective enforcer yet: Skarlet. During kombat, Skarlet gains strength from her opponent's blood, absorbing it through her skin."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Warrior Kenshi",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download and play as the Warrior Kenshi. For years the swordsman Kenshi traveled the world in search of worthy opponents. A mysterious man offered to show him the location of Sento, an ancient sword worthy of his abilities. When Kenshi retrieved the sword, spirits of ancient warriors spewed forth, blinding him."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Rain",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download and play as the Warrior Rain. A refugee orphaned by Shao Kahn's conquest, Rain grew up under the protection of the Edenian Resistance. An exceptional fighter, he soon rose through their ranks. As his reputation grew, so did his arrogance. When Rain demanded leadership of the Resistance forces, he was refused. Infuriated, he turned against his rebel comrades and betrayed them to their sworn enemy."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Freddy Krueger",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A malevolent spirit of the Dream Realm, Freddy Krueger preys on souls of the living as they sleep. When Shao Kahn stole Earthrealm's souls, Freddy battled him in the Dream Realm. But Shao Kahn pulled Freddy into the waking world, to do battle where Freddy was mortal once more."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o00-MspCacs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SfqmGy98Mw4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EocP7bJO5VU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_GJfKDacr_E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Arcade Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sqfF9V_qQ0o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Story Mode Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6ScfdZSgWbc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Challenge Tower Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QvzXw1FkMlw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/961032-mortal-kombat/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mortal-Kombat/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mortal-kombat/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mortal-kombat"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Mortal Kombat Wiki",
				"url":"http://mortalkombat.wikia.com/wiki/Mortal_Kombat_(2011)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":683,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Haemimont Games AD"],
			"synopsis":"The First Templar follows the story of two characters -a French Templar, and his companion, a noble lady who has been proclaimed a heretic. Taking control over these two unlikely allies, the player must uncover the mysteries behind the Templar Order, play a role in a grand conspiracy, and discover the secret of the Holy Grail.<br><br>The First Templar features both single player and co-op modes. When playing solo, the player can switch between the two characters, leaving the control of the second hero to the game's AI. At any moment a second player can join in and take control of the AI controlled hero.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Arena",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/03",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Caught by the vile Byzantine, you have to survive the perils of the Arena. Fight for your life, face the Gauntlet and stage your escape. Chose who will stand beside you as you confront the Byzantine and his minions."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ie-eJRcGTMo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dFVAhRqIHv0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dK8MvyciPY8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/997308-the-first-templar/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-First-Templar/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-first-templar/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-first-templar"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":684,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Liquid Entertainment", "Marvel Studios"],
			"synopsis":"In Thor: The Video Game game, Thor battles through the numerous worlds of Norse mythology to save Asgard, the capital city of the Norse Gods.<br><br>Thor must overcome monstrous foes lifted from the pages of the comics including Ulik, Ymir, and Surtur, as well as other monstrous denizens. Players will wield the iconic Mj&ouml;lnir, Thor's legendary hammer, to fight enemies on an immense scale while controlling the elemental storm powers of lightning, thunder, and wind to vanquish enemies. As Thor earns Valor points through his exploits, players can acquire new abilities, powers, and weapon upgrades.<br><br>The Xbox 360 version features cinematic, third-person action gameplay with melee combos, ranged hammer throws, tide-turning elemental powers, and an upgrade system to bolster Thor's powers as gamers progress. Players will take on enemies up to four times as large as Thor, with multiple grappling points and a variety of strategies for taking them down: go toe-to-toe with a 25 foot tall, 12 ton Ice Trolls for a truly heart-pumping experience.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Prologue Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TLjhR4agnGU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dj9dFgsmh_8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7e1eQIsaDt0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/978622-thor-god-of-thunder/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Thor-God-of-Thunder/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/thor-the-video-game/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/thor-god-of-thunder"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":685,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Slitherine Software"],
			"synopsis":"The History Channel: Great Battles - Medieval is set against the background of the historic Hundred Years' War, spanning various conflicts between England and France in the 14th and 15th centuries. History -- Great Battles Medieval allows players to assume complete control of huge armies with more than 40 different units. From knights on horseback to infantry, French crossbowmen and English longbow archers, all units of the two warring factions are represented in the game, historically correct. Whether in campaign mode, a brief skirmish, or multiplayer mode, History -- Great Battles Medieval offers precise, realistic recreations of medieval battles.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UKU4HqFcif4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nhfkeLR7Azc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Great-Battles-Medieval/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/history-channel-great-battles-medieval/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-history-channel-great-battles---medieval"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":686,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Splash Damage"],
			"synopsis":"A man-made floating city called the Ark, made up of hundreds of separate floating islands, is on the brink of all-out civil war. Originally built as an experimental self-sufficient and 100 percent \"green\" habitat, the reported rapid rise of the Earth's oceans has forced the Ark to become a refuge for humanity. With 25 years of social unrest, the inhabitants of the Ark have reached their breaking point. It's up to you to decide the future of the Ark and the human race.<br><br>Brink is an immersive shooter that blends single-player, co-op, and multiplayer gameplay into one seamless experience, allowing you to develop your character across all modes of play. You decide the role you want to assume in the world of BRINK as you fight to save yourself and mankind's last refuge for humanity. Brink offers a compelling mix of dynamic battlefields, extensive customization options, and an innovative control system.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Agents of Change",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/03",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The battle spreads to two all-new districts of the Ark - the futuristic, underwater Labs facility and Founders' Tower, the iconic spire housing the island's elite. Unleash new abilities on your enemies and customize your character with new outfits and weapon attachments."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Doom/Psycho Combo Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Extend your customization options even further with the exclusive Doom/Psycho combo pack."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Fallout/SpecOps Combo Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Extend your customization options even further with the exclusive Fallout/SpecOps combo pack."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s-kVnw4RA80"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NrqhykRsKVI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Id47IE8P5jw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960407-brink/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Brink/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/brink/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/brink"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Brink Wiki",
				"url":"http://brink.wikia.com/wiki/Brink_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":687,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["TT Games"],
			"synopsis":"LEGO Pirates of the Caribbean: The Video Game re-creates the action, adventure and memorable moments of the Pirates of the Caribbean mythology in LEGO form, incorporating the humor of LEGO minifigures and fantastic worlds built from LEGO bricks and elements for players to explore.<br><br>Players can take on the roles of more than 70 characters and experience the pirate adventure, irreverent humor and amazing creatures of the Pirates of the Caribbean films, through action-adventure gameplay and hilariously quirky LEGO cut scenes. Throughout the game, players will also have the freedom to explore environments from the highly acclaimed movie series in more than 20 levels. The game features two-player cooperative mode, in which players each control a character to experience the story together, and freeplay mode, which lets players return to levels to discover new items.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M9UGtnXF-tY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8VqBd_DujrE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qMniSLgR_eQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/612246-lego-pirates-of-the-caribbean-the-video-game/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/LEGO-Pirates-of-the-Caribbean/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lego-pirates-of-the-caribbean/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lego-pirates-of-the-caribbean-the-video-game"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Brickipedia",
				"url":"http://lego.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Pirates_of_the_Caribbean%3A_The_Video_Game"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Pirates of the Caribbean Wiki",
				"url":"http://pirates.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Pirates_of_the_Caribbean:_The_Video_Game"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"LEGO Pirates of the Caribbean Wiki",
				"url":"http://legopiratesthevideogame.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":688,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SEGA"],
			"synopsis":"Get a grip on your racquet like never before in the first Virtua Tennis game made compatible with the Kinect accessory.<br><br>Boasting its strongest ever player line-up, Virtua Tennis 4 features the world's top stars such as world No.1 Rafael Nadal, 16-time major champion Roger Federer and UK No.1 Andy Murray. Joining them for the first time are seven new champions making their debut to the series, enabling players to take on the likes of Juan Mart&iacute;n Del Potro, Fernando Gonzalez, Caroline Wozniacki and Laura Robson.<br><br>In addition, Virtua Tennis 4 sees a new World Tour career mode designed to encourage replay value with an element of off-court fame. Each decision affects a player's career path meaning no two careers will ever be the same, while a brand new on-court feature makes for even more dramatic singles and doubles matches. Players can build up their Match Momentum gauge over the course of a match and revel in their improved ability as their players grow in confidence.<br><br>The new Online Mode offers an invigorating experience with the choice of a competitive and casual area to suit all players. This new hub will be the most engaging online experience for tennis gamers ever, promising a more competitive matchmaking system and online tournaments geared to seeking out the ultimate Virtua Tennis Champion.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KHXHNbbAFWk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x5Qkc39VPvs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5U0kjh5zy2c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=usz4kFFVvdQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Virtua-Tennis-4/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Virtua-Tennis-4/walkthrough.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/virtua-tennis-4"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":689,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Team Bondi"],
			"synopsis":"Set amid the violence and corruption of post-World War II Los Angeles, L.A. Noire is a crime thriller that seamlessly blends crime-solving, clue-finding, car chases and shoot-outs with revolutionary new interrogation-based gameplay that will allow players to read characters' emotions in order to reveal the truth. Players will take on the role of Cole Phelps, a decorated war veteran, who rises through the ranks of the LAPD by solving a series of gruesome murders and other crimes that bring him face-to-face with the dark heart of Los Angeles during Hollywood's Golden Age.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"\"The Naked City\" Vice Case",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/31",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"This L.A. Noire Add-on content is included in the L.A. Noire Rockstar Pass. If you have purchased the L.A. Noire Rockstar pass please do not purchase this content as you will be charged again. Julia Randall, a stunning young fashion model with the world at her feet, is found dead, floating in her own bathtub. To the Homicide Squad it looks like a textbook society suicide - a glamorous life come to a nasty end - but coroner Malcolm Carruthers remains unconvinced. It falls to Detectives Phelps and Earle to work the scene, and determine which of Miss Randall's many vices finally killed her."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"The Chicago Piano",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/31",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Chicago Piano, used by both law enforcement officers and criminals, was favored for its reliability, ergonomics, compact size, large 45-round cartridge, and high rate of automatic fire. This bonus weapon will be stored in the trunk of Detective Cole Phelps' car throughout L.A. Noire, ensuring that extra firepower is always close at hand."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"The Broderick Detective Suit",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/31",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Broderick unlockable suit boosts Cole Phelps' fist-fighting abilities and resilience to damage. Throughout L.A. Noire, Phelps will inevitably encounter suspects or persons of interest who prove resistant to arrest. Phelps' hand-to-hand fighting skills could be called into action in these cases and the Broderick suit, which enhances his fighting abilities, will help give Cole the edge in making that collar."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"The Badge Pursuit Challenge & Button Man Suit",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/31",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Hidden around L.A. Noire's beautiful recreation of 1947 Los Angeles are 20 police badges to find and collect. Find all 20 of these badges to unlock the dapper Button Man Detective suit which provides extra ammo for all weapons. Each badge also provides 5 additional XP which will help further unlock Intuition Points - special credits that can be used to give Phelps a key investigative insight when he needs it most."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"The Sharpshooter Detective Suit",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/31",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Sharpshooter unlockable suit enhances your aim with rifles and pistols. Always a worst case scenario for any Detective working a case, there are inevitably occasions when pursuing or confronting a suspect escalates to gunfire. In these shootout situations, the Sharpshooter suit gives Cole extra aiming precision to take criminals down."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"\"A Slip Of The Tongue\" Traffic Case",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/31",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"When a suspect caught behind the wheel of a stolen car claims to have bought the vehicle fair and square, Detectives Phelps and Bekowsky are unimpressed. When he produces a pink slip and bill of sale as proof, they sit up and take notice. There follows an investigation that will throw up bumbling car thieves, double talking auto dealers, and a theft racket that stretches across Los Angeles and the state line."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"\"Nicholson Electroplating\" Arson Case",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/21",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"At 9.45 in the morning, a thunderous explosion rocks Los Angeles. City blocks are flattened and smoke and ash fill the air. Detectives Phelps and Biggs race to the site of the former Nicholson Electroplating plant to find a pile of unanswered questions. What caused the explosion? What were Nicholson's employees working on? And where are chief chemist Dr Harold McLellan and his mysterious female assistant?"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"\"Reefer Madness\" Vice Case",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/12",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Vice Narcotics receives a tip from one Freddie Calhoun, junkie, snitch and all around no-hoper. Freddie seems to be playing it straight for once, sharing information on a city-wide marijuana distribution ring. Detective Phelps and Earle will search, question and raid their way to the top of the operation, and in the process learn how the crooks could be smuggling fifty pound shipments of dope in plain sight."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xk69qfTRIgY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jeYym1U226M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D_vLxAI5rII"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a4lJSg3bTvo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bf_5J82pQ-Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/988983-la-noire/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/LA-Noire/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/la-noire/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/la-noire"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"L.A. Noire Wiki",
				"url":"http://lanoire.wikia.com/wiki/L.A._Noire_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":690,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Codemasters"],
			"synopsis":"The acclaimed off-road racing franchise returns in this third series entry. DiRT 3 delivers mud, sweat and gears the world over: from the intense weather-beaten rally stages of Europe, Africa and the US, to executing performance driving showcases and career challenges where car control is pushed to spectacular limits. The game boasts more cars, more locations, more routes and more events than any other game in the series, including over 50 rally cars representing the very best from five decades of the sport.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Colin McRae Vision Charity Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/31",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Download the Colin McRae Vision Charity Pack and receive the Ford Escort Mk II, a 70s Rally car with five liveries. All Codemasters' profits from this pack will go to the Colin McRae Vision Charity."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Power and Glory Car Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/14",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Download the Power and Glory Car Pack to gain access to 5 new cars available for singleplayer, splitscreen and online multiplayer events. Race the BMW M3 Rally, Lancia Delta S4, Ford Focus ST Rallycross, Scion tC and Chevrolet Camaro SSX Concept, each with a range of liveries."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Monte Carlo Track Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/28",
				"achievements":75,
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Download the Monte Carlo Track Pack and take on 8 breathtaking Rally stages featuring the dramatic climbs, descents and hairpins of snowy mountain roads. Race through the Alps and conquer the legendary Col de Turini pass in singleplayer, splitscreen and online multiplayer."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Mini Gymkhana Special Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/28",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Download the Mini Gymkhana Special Pack and receive the mid-engined Mini Cooper S Gymkhana, customised and tuned to become an outrageously responsive gymkhana car."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Horn Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download 6 new Horns and let your rivals know you're coming for them!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Mud and Guts Car Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/12",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Download the Mud and Guts Car Pack to gain access to 5 new cars available for singleplayer, splitscreen and online multiplayer events. Race the Lancia Stratos, Peugeot 205 T16 Evo 2, Citro&euml;n C4 Rallycross, Saturn Sky and Ford Mustang GT, each with a range of liveries."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"X Games Asia Track Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/26",
				"achievements":75,
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Download the X Games Asia Track Pack to go for the win in Japan. The X Games Asia Track Pack includes four routes set across two new tracks in Shibuya, the neon heart of central Tokyo. These spectacular mud-spattered Rallycross circuits weave beneath towering skyscrapers in front of thousands of cheering fans."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Ken Block Special Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/02",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Download the Ken Block Special Pack and receive a customised and upgraded Ford Escort Mk II, an Open Class Rally car sporting a killer Ken Block livery."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aqRafZz6Y7o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wZ0TOjomgt4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cRtCQ2yPLWo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z1Y6_N23tJo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k59A0c5w0-c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aprARssIR_s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/DiRT-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dirt-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dirt-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Colin McRae DiRT Wiki",
				"url":"http://dirt.wikia.com/wiki/DiRT_3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":691,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["InXile Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"The dark ages have become corrupted. Heinous creatures have emerged from underground. Townsfolk across the land are disappearing. Upon the promise of their fortune in gold, mercenaries E'lara and Caddoc take on the daunting task of discovering where the innocent villagers have been taken. Their journey will lead them on a dark and twisted path where they will encounter death, slavery, and sacrifice. Travel deep within the world of Kala Moor... and to the secrets of The Demon's Forge.<br><br>Set in a dark fantasy world, Hunted: The Demon's Forge is a cooperative action game, pitting you and your partner against waves of vicious enemies. Taking control of either E'lara, a ranged weapon expert, or Caddoc, a master swordsman, you must use a variety of weapons, powerful spells, and cover tactics to battle your way through menacing dungeons, overgrown ruins, and downtrodden towns. Discover secrets and complete co-op-based puzzles whilst exploring the sinister world to discover answers to the game's deep, dark mysteries.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4bsiaHggwD0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TeKlGrtbkEI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0TAfVwpmqV4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3vuO51bJojo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/991429-hunted-the-demons-forge/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hunted-Demons-Forge/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hunted-the-demons-forge/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hunted-the-demons-forge"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Hunted: The Demon's Forge Wiki",
				"url":"http://hunted.wikia.com/wiki/Hunted_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":692,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Double Helix"],
			"synopsis":"Green Lantern: Rise of the Manhunters is inspired by the feature film, which brings the enduringly popular DC hero to the big screen. Playing as gifted pilot Hal Jordan -- the first human Green Lantern -- gamers create an arsenal of ring constructs and take flight in outer space and beyond to restore intergalactic order. Use the Power Ring to build an array of weapons from green energy to defeat the Manhunters -- an evil android race bent on destroying the Green Lantern Corps.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fxfDKR7m00U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Osko13AiBIQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HnV3Y3p15MA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/999483-green-lantern-rise-of-the-manhunters/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Green-Lantern-Rise-of-the-Manhunters/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/green-lantern-rise-of-the-manhunters/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/green-lantern-rise-of-the-manhunters"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Green Lantern Wiki",
				"url":"http://greenlantern.wikia.com/wiki/Green_Lantern:_Rise_of_The_Manhunters"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":693,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Codemasters"],
			"synopsis":"Delivering an authentic and intensely personal US Marine Corps infantryman experience, Operation Flashpoint: Red River offers an epic campaign played out on a deadly new battlefield set in the remote yet beautiful country of Tajikistan along the Vakhsh River.<br><br>Red River depicts a fictional conflict with contemporary geopolitical themes, unfolding over three distinct acts in both single player and drop-in-drop-out co-operative play for up to four players online. Faced with new counter-insurgency combat and the returning threat of the Chinese PLA, players will feel the tension, brutality and carnage of modern conflict from the perspective of a marine fireteam on deployment in a hostile country.<br><br>Building extensively on the successes of Operation Flashpoint: Dragon Rising, Red River brings wide-ranging advancements including a deeper narrative-led campaign, streamlined inventory and control system, a refined enemy and squad AI system, player class roles including customizable XP upgrades and loadout choice, close-quarters combat, new air support options and comprehensive tutorials. Players will also be able to team up with their friends to play through additional co-operative game modes. Whether escorting a convoy to safety under heavy fire, or falling back from the enemy against almost insurmountable odds, each unique mode will test players' tactics and teamwork in distinct ways.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Valley of Death",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/28",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The Valley of Death Pack features 8 new Fireteam Engagements set across 2 stunning new locales. Fight through the warehouses and factories of a former Soviet manufacturing town on the outskirts of an abandoned Tajik settlement, and carry out operations in a riverside mudbrick village set beneath foreboding hilltop ruins - an intimidating overwatch position. The Valley of Death Pack features 2 new Combat Sweep missions, 2 new CSAR missions, 2 new Last Stand missions and 2 Rolling Thunder missions. Play these new Fireteam Engagements in single player, or stand together in 4 player online co-op play."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8aRbR8xv8m4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xdXPXIMumcw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W-ICq-1Nc1E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EJpFcowDu6Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1Fl6-mZpDVY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/604137-operation-flashpoint-red-river/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Operation-Flashpoint-Red-River/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/operation-flashpoint-red-river/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/operation-flashpoint-red-river"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":694,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Volition"],
			"synopsis":"Half a century after the Red Faction resistance freed Mars, the red planet again becomes a battleground. Colonists struggle for survival in the underground mines after the surface is rendered uninhabitable. When Darius Mason, grandson of revolution heroes Alec Mason and Samanya, unknowingly releases a long-dormant evil, Armageddon is unleashed on Mars. As settlements are torn asunder, only Darius and the Red Faction can save mankind. The battle will take them to the core of the storm-blasted planet through ice caves and lava flows until they are face to face against the unspeakable threat.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Ruin Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/07",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Red Faction: Armageddon's Ruin Mode is all about one thing: destruction. In \"Free Play\" you'll wreak havoc on a variety of maps with unlimited time and infinite ammo. \"Challenge\" is a race against the clock to do as much damage as possible in a limited time. Earn extra points and bonus minutes for extreme annihilation. Break the high score to unlock new maps. Afterwards, flaunt your catastrophic conquests on the Leaderboards by comparing your ranking with friends or every player worldwide!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Path to War",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/02",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The Earth Defense Force has been defeated, and after centuries of oppression, Mars is finally free. For a time, there was peace. Yet from the forgotten ashes rose Adam Hale, scarred from years of struggle, seeking ultimate revenge against the Red Faction. His target, the one thing that keeps the surface of Mars habitable for thousands of colonists, is the Terraformer. Relive the battle for the Terraformer through four incredible new missions featuring aerial flyers, orbital strikes, and the Red Faction armored surface tank. Unlock two destructive new weapons, the Sharpshooter Gun and Shard Cannon, while earning ten new achievements in this thrilling new mission pack for Red Faction: Armageddon!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Recon Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Suit up in the Recon uniform and add two new weapons to your arsenal with the Red Faction: Armageddon Recon Pack. The Arc Welder immobilizes and electrocutes clusters of enemies. The XNG-5000 launches devastating Nanite-filled projectiles that seek out targets and dissolves them. Pick these up from any weapons locker in the campaign or deal death from their barrels to the merciless hordes in Infestation Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Commando Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Throw on the Commando uniform and add two new weapons to your arsenal with the Red Faction: Armageddon Commando Pack. The Plasma Thrower sprays an unforgiving stream of destruction that lays waste to enemies and obstacles. Dual wield two Laser Pistols to decimate the plague. Pick these up from any weapons locker in the campaign or deal death from their barrels to the merciless hordes in Infestation Mode."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XjxMuMOH08s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Of4rAZlIL2I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0l2MAkvo9Tk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NFJ791W3vzs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KsLHwxMi7aY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/988573-red-faction-armageddon/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Red-Faction-Armageddon/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/red-faction-armageddon/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/red-faction-armageddon"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Red Faction Wiki",
				"url":"http://redfaction.wikia.com/wiki/Red_Faction:_Armageddon"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":695,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Spicy Horse"],
			"synopsis":"The Wonderland that you knew from childhood has gone horribly wrong ... again. This is the follow-up to designer American McGee's twisted take on the classic Lewis Carroll tale. Designed with the same dark style of the original, but now featuring entirely new visuals, story and game design, Alice: Madness Returns follows Alice on a journey through a wildly corrupted and shattered Wonderland to uncover the truth behind her haunted past and tortured psyche.<br><br>Alice: Madness Returns takes place 10 years after the conclusion of the original game, with Alice struggling to recover from the emotional trauma of losing her entire family in a fatal fire. After spending a decade institutionalized in an insane asylum, she is finally released to the care of a psychiatrist who just may be able to help her conquer the nightmarish hallucinations that still haunt her. Alice embarks on a mission to root out the true cause of her family's mysterious death, jumping from a gloomy and stark London to a rich and provocative Wonderland.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"American McGee's Alice",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/14",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Play through the cult classic and relive Alice's battle against the Queen of Hearts as she fights to regain control of her Wonderland."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Weapons of Madness and Dresses Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/14",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Return to Wonderland and battle the corruption with all new weapon upgrades as well as 6 new collectible dresses. The new fourth tier of weapons tips the scales into Alice's favor by unlocking a whole new level of destruction."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D1X1C333nN8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VR8wXsvUrBg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cFrs5UGB-ns"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o51Nen1nfug"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kfr3coP4ie4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958269-alice-madness-returns/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Alice-Madness-Returns/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/alice-madness-returns/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/alice-madness-returns"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Alice Wiki",
				"url":"http://alice.wikia.com/wiki/Alice:_Madness_Returns"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":696,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Q Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Child of Eden thrusts the player into the center of a battle to save Project Lumi, a mission to reproduce a human personality inside Eden, the archive of all human memories. As the project nears completion, the archive is invaded by an unknown virus. The player's mission is to save Eden from the virus, restoring hope and peace.<br><br>This game is a collaboration between publisher Ubisoft and acclaimed videogame creator Tetsuya Mizuguchi -- the mastermind behind the acclaimed game Rez. The player becomes truly immersed in the game, with no physical barriers between him and the game world.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xuYWLYjOa_0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZCb6CyATEuk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3PR6ECqi110"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Child-of-Eden/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/child-of-eden/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/child-of-eden"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":697,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Triptych Games", "3D Realms"],
			"synopsis":"Put on your sunglasses and prepare to step into the boots of Duke Nukem, whose legend has reached epic proportions in the years since his last adventure. The alien hordes are back and only Duke can save the world, again. Pig cops, alien shrink rays and enormous alien bosses won't stop our hero from accomplishing his one and only goal: to save the world, save the babes and to be a bad-ass while doing it.<br><br>The King of All Shooters is back with over-the-top weapons, massive aliens and unprecedented levels of interactivity. This game puts pedal to the metal and tongue firmly in cheek, among other places. Shoot hoops, lift weights, read adult magazines, draw crude messages on whiteboards or ogle one of the many beautiful women that populate Duke's life; that is if you can pull yourself away long enough from kicking ass and taking names. Duke Nukem was and will forever be immortalized in gaming history, and this is his legend.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Hail to the Icons Parody Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/11",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Cocked and Reloaded, Duke Nukem Forever's First Add-On Content, Hail to the Icons Parody Pack, parodies some of gaming's most iconic battlegrounds and includes four all-new multiplayer maps, each with its own unique weapons and three new game modes."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"The Doctor Who Cloned Me",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/13",
				"achievements":205,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Duke Nukem Forever's new Add-On Content, Duke Nukem: The Doctor Who Cloned Me is bursting with all of the over-the-top Duke goodness fans love. Deep in the heart of Area 51, Dr Proton has been hatching his evil plan. Fueled by new ego boosts, Duke is ready to take on evil clones, aliens queens and anything else that comes his way in order to save the world and his babes!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wVuuyRGB_BA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p35Kg-1JnKw"
			},
			{
				"type":"2001 Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TDlB2P1leRM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UGHGogRZ80k"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944794-duke-nukem-forever/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Duke-Nukem-Forever/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/duke-nukem-forever/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/duke-nukem-forever"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Duke Nukem Wiki",
				"url":"http://dukenukem.wikia.com/wiki/Duke_Nukem_Forever"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":698,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Idea Factory"],
			"synopsis":"Record of Agarest War Zero is a prequel that tells the story of what happened in the age before Record of Agarest War, detailing the rise of some to glory, and the fall of others, into darkness.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Extra Dungeon 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/15",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"I can see it... With this, you will receive the additional dungeon \"Fohites Ruins\", which is playable during the first generation. In order to get there, you must proceed through the game to a certain point, and view a certain event. Brand-new adventures await you..."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Extra Dungeon 2",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/21",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"I can see it... With this, you will acquire the additional dungeon \"Neige Snow Field\", which is playable during the second generation. In order to get there, you must proceed through the game to a certain point, and view a certain event. Now your journey into the frontier begins..."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Additional Costume 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Something new to dress one of the women up in during Free Intention! Why don't you go put it on someone now?"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Additional Costume 2",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Something new to dress one of the women up in during Free Intention! Why don't you go put it on someone now?"
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Forbidden Book Volume 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/05",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"This will give you the 6th Forbidden Tome. To be reunited with the people it contains, you must proceed through the game to a certain point, and view a certain event."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Forbidden Book Volume 2",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/05",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"This will give you the 7th Forbidden Tome. To be reunited with the men it contains, you must proceed through the game to a certain point, and view a certain event."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Forbidden Book Volume 3",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/05",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"This will give you the 8th Forbidden Tome. To be reunited with the women it contains, you must proceed through the game to a certain point, and view a certain event."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=luH14T6HXRY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n7DEIWgmdKs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Record-of-Agarest-War-Zero/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/record-of-agarest-war-zero/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/record-of-agarest-war-zero"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Record of Agarest War Wiki",
				"url":"http://agarest.wikia.com/wiki/Record_of_Agarest_War_Zero"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":699,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Avalanche Software"],
			"synopsis":"Cars 2: The Video Game brings players inside the international training center CHROME (Command Headquarters for Recon Operations and Motorized Espionage), where they choose from more than 20 different characters and train to become world class spies. As part of their international training, they will participate in simulated hazardous missions using high-tech gadgets to evade and slow down adversaries.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"C.H.R.O.M.E. Agent Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/21",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Four pack of playable cars Rod Redline joins C.H.R.O.M.E. in sharing some of their all-time greatest disguises - Airport Security Finn, Cherry Blossom Holley,  Undercover Rod Redline and Rod Redline."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Tall Tales Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/28",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Jump into the action of Cars 2: The Video Game with the newest agents of C.H.R.O.M.E. (Command Headquarters for Recon Operations and Motorized Espionage) - Mater the Greater, Tokyo Mater, Dragon Lightning McQueen and Daredevil Lightning McQueen!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Cars 2 Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/05",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Jump into the action of Cars 2: The Video Game with the newest agents of C.H.R.O.M.E. (Command Headquarters for Recon Operations and Motorized Espionage) - Uncle Topolino, Mater as Ivan, Kabuki Mater, and Victor Hugo!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"The Queen",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/05",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Jump into the action of Cars 2: The Video Game with the newest agent of C.H.R.O.M.E. (Command Headquarters for Recon Operations and Motorized Espionage) -The Queen!"
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Radiator Springs Bundle",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/01",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Jump into the action of Cars 2: The Video Game with the newest agents of C.H.R.O.M.E. (Command Headquarters for Recon Operations and Motorized Espionage) - Ramone, Flo, Sheriff, and Chick Hicks"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Road Hazards Bundle",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/01",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Jump into the action of Cars 2: The Video Game with the newest agents of C.H.R.O.M.E. (Command Headquarters for Recon Operations and Motorized Espionage) - Wingo, Snot Rod, Boost, and DJ!"
			},],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S8q4YB4l-Tk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nyv3zBczUw8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cars-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cars-2-the-video-game/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cars-2-the-video-game"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":700,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Obsidian Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Torn asunder, the delicate balance of power between the kingdom of Ehb's powerful factions has fallen apart. As one of the few remaining members of the disgraced protectors of the land, the 10th Legion, it is up to you to rebuild the once great Legion and stop Ehb from falling into darkness. Joined by a group of unique companions, you will travel through the striking land of Ehb defeating all manner of villains and beasts through a combination of heroic abilities, screen shaking magic and pure cunning.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Treasures of the Sun",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/25",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Travel beyond the borders of Ehb in Dungeon Siege III's downloadable content pack, Dungeon Siege III: Treasures of the Sun. Your search for a lost Legion hero will take you to the Aranoi Desert, where a forgotten abbey hides a long-lost secret - the \"greatest treasure of the Azunite faith\". Explore an accursed desert and an ancient underground vault, while battling sand hulks, skeletal giants, blood worms, mummies, and more. Unlock divine abilities that can be used to empower yourself or devastate your opponents. Upgrade your legionnaire with an increased level cap, a hoard of new loot, and an item-enchanting system... or reinvent your character with the new respec pool!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ayal7xCxl2k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q_yyg0WCnTw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CNM2ZF1V-2s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eD3ytW2fGgA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/997432-dungeon-siege-iii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dungeon-Siege-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dungeon-siege-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dungeon-siege-iii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dungeon Siege Wiki",
				"url":"http://dungeonsiege.wikia.com/wiki/Dungeon_Siege_3"
			}]
		}
	}]
}