{
	"catalog": [
	{
		"id":1101,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Telltale Games"],
			"synopsis":"On the stormy night when Jurassic Park fell apart, a desperate smuggler infiltrates Isla Nublar, hunting the precious canister containing the contraband dinosaur embryos. She collides -- literally -- with park staff trying to evacuate, and they become stranded amidst the collapsing park ruins, with the newly-freed dinosaurs on the loose. When InGen launches a perilous rescue operation, mercenaries, saboteurs, and survivors are thrown together in the struggle to escape the island.<br><br>In this intense adventure game based on the blockbuster film franchise, the survivors' agendas clash, secrets of the park are exposed, and a new threat emerges: an eerie, nocturnal predator stalking the group, hunting them relentlessly across the island.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q7G94FZIoao"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xawBCUhHOw8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZrgDuLdHxxY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Jurassic-Park/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/jurassic-park/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/jurassic-park-the-game"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Jurassic Park Wiki",
				"url":"http://jurassicpark.wikia.com/wiki/Jurassic_Park:_The_Game"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1102,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Griptonite Games"],
			"synopsis":"Marvel Super Hero Squad: Comic Combat puts the artist's pen in players' hands, enabling them to draw directly into the game world and determine the fate of the Squaddies.<br><br>For the first time ever, players will use the uDraw stylus to command Captain America, Thor, Iron Man and seven other Marvel Super Heroes in the battle against Doctor Doom and his evil cohorts. The uDraw GameTablet allows players to direct attacks, wield weapons and build barricades in the Marvel Super Hero Squad universe. Players can even shake the uDraw GameTablet to create an in-game earthquake!<br><br>Marvel Super Hero Squad: Comic Combat also features a distinctive cel-shaded comic book art style that brings the characters to life, as well as a variety of challenging new stages, including The Helicarrier, Baxter Building, The Vault and Sanctum Sanctorum.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=leOHZhKI8X8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6VLVWxGMKm0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2f0lUAtNS1U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ClpcDZsjTN4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Marvel-Super-Hero-Squad-Comic-Combat/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/marvel-super-hero-squad-comic-combat/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/marvel-super-hero-squad-comic-combat"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1103,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Black Box"],
			"synopsis":"Adrenaline junkies and speed fiends will find themselves on the wrong side of the law when they race for their lives in Need for Speed: The Run. This game takes players on a heart-pounding cross-country race from San Francisco to New York. Players are lured into an underground world of illicit, high-stakes racing. The heat is on -- and it isn't just the fuzz who are after you. Entering the race is just the beginning as you blow across borders, weave through dense urban traffic, rocket down icy mountain passes and navigate narrow canyons at breakneck speeds.<br><br>Powered by DICE's state-of-the-art Frostbite 2 engine, Need for Speed: The Run takes the action racing genre to new heights with stunning visuals and car physics that hug the road even at top speeds all built around a gripping storyline. The cars are hot, the racing is intense and the story will have you at the edge of your seat ... all the way from the Golden Gate Bridge to the Empire State building.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Signature Edition Booster Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/20",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"The Signature Edition Booster Pack includes the following custom-style 'Signature' edition cars: 'Puppet' Chevy El Camino SS 'Fatlace' Nissan Skyline 2000GT-R (C10) 'Venom' Nissan 370Z (Z34) 'Scoundrel' Subaru Impreza WRX STI 'Victory' BMW M3 Sport Evolution 'Nicholas' Mazda RX-7 RZ 'Mega' Nissan GT-R (R35) 'Falken' Porsche 911 GT3 RS 4.0 Ford GT 'CONROY' These vehicles can be used in The Run, Challenge Series and Multiplayer modes."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Italian Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/02",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Experience The Run with a collection of cars from the most prestigous Italian manufacturers! The Italian Pack includes the following: 1995 Lamborghini Diablo SV 2010 Lamborghini Gallardo LP 570-4 Superleggera 2009 Pagani Zonda R 2010 Alfa Romeo 8C Competizione 2005 Maserati MC12 1993 Lancia Delta HF Integrale Evoluzione Italian Motor Racing Playlist Italian Challenge Series Italy vs. World Challenge Series."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Heroes & Villains Plus Limited Edition Upgrade",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/28",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"If you missed out on the Limited Edition of The Run or any exclusive pre-order content, this pack is for you! This pack contains the following: Limited Edition Challenge Series Chevrolet Camaro ZL1 Porsche 911 Carerra S Lamborghini Aventador LP 700-4 Underground Challenge Series Underground-themed Nissan 370Z (Z34) Nissan Skyline GT-R (R32) Most Wanted Challenge Series Most Wanted BMW M3 GTS Razor's Ford Mustang Boss 302 Carbon Challenge Series Cross' Chevrolet Corvette Z06 Carbon Limited Edition Darius Audi R8 Coup&eacute; 5.2 FSI quattro Autolog Profile Items."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Supercar Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/15",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Drive 7 of the world's fastest and sexiest supercars in Need For Speed The Run! The Supercar Pack includes the following cars: Bugatti Veyron 16.4 Super Sport Lamborghini Countach QV500 Lexus LFA Porsche Carerra GT GUMPERT apollo s Hennessey Venom GT Koenigsegg Agera R."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v-4msZsoe18"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3h1QaFzcJXU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JfhWV8-Kc2g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N3at_oqTLRY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZPZ6Rwi2hrI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/628144-need-for-speed-the-run/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Need-for-Speed-The-Run/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/need-for-speed-the-run/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/need-for-speed-the-run"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Need for Speed Wiki",
				"url":"http://nfs.wikia.com/wiki/Need_for_Speed:_The_Run"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1104,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ludia"],
			"synopsis":"Feel the thrill of being called to \"COME ON DOWN!\" in the ultimate multiplayer The Price Is Right Decades game featuring Kinect for Xbox 360! Compete with friends and family as you bid on thousands of products in 40 different pricing games from all four decades of the TV show. The game features all your favorite elements including Contestant's Row, the Big Wheel and Showcase, plus rare pricing games taken from The Price Is Right TV show \"vault\" and all-new pricing challenges not included in any previous The Price Is Right video game. For the first time ever, you can play pricing games simultaneously with up to 4 players in multiplayer modes. Authentic stages and theme music from the 70s, 80s, 90s and 00s increase the fun!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aI4vicgIS7M"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/640801-the-price-is-right-decades/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Price-is-Right-Decades/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-price-is-right-decades"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1105,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Volition"],
			"synopsis":"Years after taking Stilwater for their own, the Third Street Saints have evolved from street gang to household brand name, with Saints sneakers, Saints energy drinks and Johnny Gat bobble head dolls all available at a store near you. The Saints are kings of Stilwater, but their celebrity status has not gone unnoticed. The Syndicate, a legendary criminal fraternity with pawns in play all over the globe, has turned its eye on the Saints and demands tribute.<br><br>Refusing to kneel to the Syndicate, you take the fight to a new city, playing out the most outlandish gameplay scenarios ever seen in Saints Row: The Third, the third chapter in the blockbuster open-city action series. Strap it on.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Shark Attack Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/15",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Add to your wardrobe and weapon cache with the Shark Attack Pack. The Shark-O-Matic shoots out a steady stream of slimy fish guts, attracting whatever may lurk under the streets of Steelport. And if that isn't enough, the Shark Bite Hat allows you to experience the feeling of being caught in the jaws of a great white."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Z Style Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/06",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Live the high life of Zimos himself by adding a weapon to your arsenal and an outfit to your wardrobe with the Z Style Pack. You won't go unnoticed in the bold and pimpalicious outfit good enough to be called The \"Z\". Arm yourself with the super flashy Bling Shotgun and your bullets won't be the only thing that makes an impact."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Explosive Combat Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/06",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Throw on your combat gear and add a weapon to your arsenal with the Explosive Combat Pack. The M2 Grenade Launcher sends a plethora of mass explosions right at your enemy, and the Future Soldier Outfit is perfect for any battle."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Warrior Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/20",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Warrior Pack adds four combat-ready outfits to your wardrobe. Antiques never go out of style with the Knight of Steelport Armor, or go for something a little more revealing with the Warrior Princess outfit. Bring out your inner samurai with the Kabuki Warrior Outfit or choose the Intergalactic Warrior Outfit for an out of this world look."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Genkibowl VII",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/17",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Professor Genki invites you to be the main contestant on Genkibowl VII! Featuring games themed by the Genki Girls Angry Tiger, Sexy Kitten and Sad Panda, see if you can beat Genkibowl and gain them and reporter Tammy Tolliver as homies!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Money Shot Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/14",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Looks can kill...and so do you. With the Money Shot pack, you can transform yourself into one of Ultor's elite femme fatales. Don your high-heeled tactical catsuit and take to the skies on a custom Ultor jet bike. Then when the time comes to execute your target, do so with unprecedented style with your fully automatic sniper rifle."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Funtime! Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/14",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Go super ballistic with the FunTime! Pack which gives you a new weapon, vehicle, and outfit. Terrorize your enemies by sucking them up and shooting them out with the Genki Man-A-Pult! Pull the trigger on the Mollusk Launcher and unleash the power of an exploding, mind-controlling octopus! And make sure you put on your FunTime! Outfit, because who doesn't want to look like Professor Genki!"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Gangstas In Space",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/21",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"A new movie is being shot in Steelport and you're the star! Join with your co-star, Jenny, to fight the alien invasion for the film Gangstas In Space. With spaceships and alien weaponry, this retro-style film is sure to be a hit!"
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Bloodsucker Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Keep the cash flowin' with the Bloodsucker Pack. You'll earn respect and get cash bonuses but it doesn't stop there! You also get payments, money drop, and the ability to regain health through your human shields with The Dracula skill."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"The Trouble With Clones",
				"releaseDate":"2012/03/20",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Help the Saints' biggest fan, Jimmy Torbitson, stop his Saints clone from terrorizing the city by using the new Bee Gun and unlocking the true power in Saints Flow. In the end, maybe even save a lost friend in the process."
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Nyte Blayde Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The ultimate collection of goods for Nyte Blayde fans! Look just like a Nyte Blayde star with exact replicas of the Altar Boy and Bloody Cannoness Outfits. Experience the excitement of Nyte Blayde's adventures as you get behind the wheel of the Nyte Blayde Mobile vehicle. Top off your full Nyte Blayde experience by zipping around town on the Bloody Cannoness Bike!"
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Special Ops Vehicle Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A collection of fully equipped military vehicles for your garage. The Saints VTOL features jet and hover modes making airborne attacks easy and stylish. The Saints Tank and the Saints N-Forcer are the ultimate in armored warfare, showing your opponents the Saints aren't to be messed with."
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"Steelport Gangs Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/05/01",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get some new gangwear for your wardrobe with six new outfits. Disguise yourself as a Morningstar Soldier or blend in with the Luchador Specialist crowd. You can even try out the Decker cyberpunk style and get in touch with your inner techno-goth!"
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"Penthouse Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/05/22",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Ass kicking just got a whole lot better looking. Introducing the Saints Row: The Third Penthouse Pack, featuring Penthouse Pets Nikki Benz, Justine Joli, Ryan Keely, and Heather Vandeven. Add these well-dressed Pets to your gang and call them into combat anytime to do battle against the Syndicate. For the first time in your life, when you call Penthouse Pets, they'll actually answer."
			},
			{
				"id":15,
				"name":"Witches & Wieners",
				"releaseDate":"2012/06/12",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"For those who wish to be more than they are, there's the Witches & Weiners Pack. Now dress yourself as the best mascot in town, the Hot Dog. Just hope your enemies aren't hungry. Or sneak around and shoot people in the back as a Ninja. A halo and horns shows who's naughty or nice. Want to channel your inner witch? Go ahead and dress the part while riding your broomstick through the air!"
			},
			{
				"id":16,
				"name":"Genki Girl Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/07/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Drive in Genki Girl style with this assortment of vehicles. Sad Panda sports a dune buggy, Angry Tiger has her motorcycle, and Sexy Kitten drives a special sports car. Each of these rides is themed after the girls themselves, and pack a deadly surprise!"
			},
			{
				"id":17,
				"name":"Horror Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/07/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Join the ranks of the most terrifying dreams with these horrific costumes. The flesh-eating Zombie Outfit will have everyone you meet running for their lives. Even more horrifying is the Slasher Outfit--it's all of your worst nightmares rolled into one. And no Horror Pack would be complete without a full Werewolf Outfit that might just have you howling at the moon."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=csTf2Z7xlQ0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Aqg2PUEyBFA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P-4ECYsOBDA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fsPHoYqNXjE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cixm2hdMigE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gCa1ut77I84"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eN2-WSyRuO0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/954855-saints-row-the-third/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Saints-Row-The-Third/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/saints-row-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/saints-row-the-third"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Saints Row Wiki",
				"url":"http://saintsrow.wikia.com/Saints_Row:_The_Third"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1106,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Capcom"],
			"synopsis":"In Ultimate Marvel Vs. Capcom 3, fill the shoes of legendary characters from both the Marvel and Capcom Universes --including massively popular characters such as Ryu, Wolverine, Iron Man, and Morrigan, as well as fan favorites such as Trish from Devil May Cry and the wise-cracking Deadpool. They all come to you battle in a living comic book art style powered by Capcom's MT Framework.<br><br>Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3 prepares to take the battle to all-new heights in a updated version of the original hit fighting game Marvel Vs. Capcom 3. With brand new iconic characters from the Marvel and Capcom universes -- now with 48 characters on the disc -- a refined fighting system and new modes, Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3 continues the Capcom fighting game legacy.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=usu7jXBkXpg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aLmCVGgD9jY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=usu7jXBkXpg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ivf0eGEN6tA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/637241-ultimate-marvel-vs-capcom-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ultimate-Marvel-vs-Capcom-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ultimate-marvel-vs-capcom-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ultimate-marvel-vs-capcom-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Marvel vs. Capcom Wiki",
				"url":"http://marvelvscapcom.wikia.com/wiki/Ultimate_Marvel_vs._Capcom_3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1107,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SNK Playmore"],
			"synopsis":"With the triumphant return of fan favorite characters like Mai, K', and Vice, extensive refinement of the core fighting engine based on community feedback, and vastly improved network functionality, The King of Fighters XIII represents the HD entry in the series that fans have been waiting for.<br><br>Painstaking effort has been made to address every last concern following the last entry: fights play faster; the addition of over a half dozen play modes offers variety and replayability; the game's beautifully rendered and animated character sprites are better distinguished from the backgrounds--which happen to be richer and more detailed; the camera perspective is less restricted; fighters have more moves, including new supers and the all-new Neomax supers; and much, much more.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Additional Character \"Iori with the Power of Flames\"",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/06",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"\"Iori with the Power of Flames\" is available as an additional playable character. How to use \"Iori with the Power of Flames\":<br>1. At the character select screen, move the cursor over \"Iori Yagami\".<br>2. Then, press \"BACK\" in order to reveal \"Iori with the Power of Flames\" character portrait.<br>3. Press \"A\" to confirm."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Additional Character \"NESTS style Kyo\"",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/20",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"\"NESTS style Kyo\" is available as an additional playable character. How to use \"NESTS style Kyo\":<br>1. At the character select screen, move the cursor over \"Kyo Kusanagi\".<br>2. Then, press \"BACK\" in order to reveal \"NESTS style Kyo\" character portrait.<br>3. Press \"A\" to confirm."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Additional Character \"Mr. Karate\"",
				"releaseDate":"2014/03/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"\"Mr.Karate\" is available as an additional playable character. How to use \"Mr.Karate\":<br>1. At the character select screen, move the cursor over \"Takuma Sakazaki\".<br>2. Then, press \"BACK\" in order to reveal \"Mr.Karate\" character portrait.<br>3. Press \"A\" to confirm."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kKZk8ULvlAQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h2vwdAXQcjU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XJxFduVMDbw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/632924-the-king-of-fighters-xiii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/King-of-Fighters-XIII/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-king-of-fighters-xiii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"SNK Wiki",
				"url":"http://snk.wikia.com/wiki/The_King_of_Fighters_XIII"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1108,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["HB Studios"],
			"synopsis":"NBA Baller Beats challenges players using a real basketball to master ball-handling skills by dribbling and performing moves to the beats of an eclectic soundtrack. Train alongside your favorite NBA franchise unlocking songs, difficulty levels, environment accessories, and over 100 posters and Panini's 2012 NBA Hoops trading cards that showcase NBA players' greatest moves. The music is your guide as the Kinect motion sensor captures every movement of both player and ball to create an entirely new basketball gaming experience. Master crossovers, pump fakes, behind-the-back, around-the-world and more as you bounce the ball to the beat of 30 licensed tracks that span across decades and genres including hip-hop, rock and old school classics. Today Majesco Entertainment officially announced 15 of the 30 songs featured in-game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E_ifGC7Gvpw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FLA6bPy_kXQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fN8qgEKnzDE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-WzJ2-LrY-8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tlBikXpskzw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-Baller-Beats/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-baller-beats"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1109,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tamsoft"],
			"synopsis":"Aya and her little sister Saki once again stand up to evil and shake their stuff with style in this entry for the sexy zombie-slaying Onechanbara series.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Aya and Saki Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/15",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":2
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V9KwBDYLHR4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y7MvFT2HFVU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hgkub17y7BE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Onechanbara-Z-Kagura/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1110,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Behaviour Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the ABC hit show Wipeout and continuing the tradition of wickedly entertaining family fun, Wipeout 2 offers updated, outrageous course designs across all platforms with obstacles and effects taken straight from the show's summer and winter seasons. Players must navigate around snow, ice, foam, and fan-favorite obstacles like the Sucker Punch Wall and Big Balls; which are making their triumphant returns alongside more than 50 others. Extended gameplay on all systems encourages even more interaction and participation with family and friends. Once again, all the wild and crazy action is narrated by the show's hosts John Anderson and John Henson.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Vn5kJO0N_k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wipeout-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wipeout-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1111,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"Face off against opposing crews online using your MyPLAYER. Create your logo and face off in 5v5 battles with other crews featuring leaderboards and stats. Play with 14 of the top European teams, featuring authentic uniforms and players. Player attributes and tendencies automatically update daily to reflect true life hot and cold streaks. Now, each game played in the NBA can have an effect on your game.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Spanish Commentary Add-On",
				"releaseDate":"2013/10/01",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Enjoy in-game NBA commentary in Spanish from three of Spain's most prominent basketball journalists - Antoni Daimiel and Sixto Miguel Serrano from Canal+ along with Jorge Quiroga of Marca - with this Spanish Commentary Add-On pack."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Gold Jewelry Collection",
				"releaseDate":"2013/10/01",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Unlocks a gold jewelry set for your MyPLAYER that provides a +3 boost to all attributes.  Collection includes gold watch, bracelet, earrings and rings.  Attribute boosts are applied upon ownership, and jewelry items need not be worn to receive boosts.  Collections do not stack, and if multiple collections are owned, only the highest boost will be applied to your MyPLAYER."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Platinum Jewelry Collection",
				"releaseDate":"2013/10/01",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Unlocks a platinum jewelry set for your MyPLAYER that provides a +6 boost to all attributes.  Collection includes platinum watch, bracelet, earrings and rings.  Attribute boosts are applied upon ownership, and jewelry items need not be worn to receive boosts.  Collections do not stack, and if multiple collections are owned, only the highest boost will be applied to your MyPLAYER."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Blue Diamond Jewelry Collection",
				"releaseDate":"2013/10/01",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Unlocks a diamond jewelry set for your MyPLAYER that provides a +10 boost to all attributes.  Collection includes diamond watch, bracelet, earrings and rings.  Attribute boosts are applied upon ownership, and jewelry items need not be worn to receive boosts.  Collections do not stack, and if multiple collections are owned, only the highest boost will be applied to your MyPLAYER."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bQlyBeh-FCk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oI-N7L3mA08"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-rtONLEAWzQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/713752-nba-2k14/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-2K14/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-2k14"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1112,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Big Ant Studios"],
			"synopsis":"World of Outlaws: Sprint Cars 2009 features twelve popular dirt tracks, including Knoxville Raceway and Eldora Speedway. In addition to this, there are five specially made Arenas created exclusively for the multiplayer matches (2-player split screen and up to eight players online.)",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L0m2EyPGgd0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=llC-8bLEucY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6KXU3LF2HJY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/World-of-Outlaw-Sprint-Cars/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/world-of-outlaws-sprint-cars/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/world-of-outlaws-sprint-cars"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1113,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Quebec City"],
			"synopsis":"The skrulls have landed and now it is up to you to embody your favorite Marvel superheroes and save the planet in Marvel Avengers: Battle for Earth, a game built around adrenaline-pumping motion control gameplay and featuring interactive environments inspired by iconic Marvel comic artwork and the Secret Invasion storyline.<br><br>Marvel Avengers: Battle for Earth features 20 different characters, including Avengers such as Iron Man, Hulk, Captain America and Thor, as well as other fan-favorite Super Heroes and Super Villains from the Marvel Universe. Use motion to trigger unique super attacks and hone special moves. Feel powerful as you unlock special content and rise to the top of the online leaderboards. Play with friends or against the AI in a wide variety of game modes including arcade, campaign and coop and vs.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"X-Men Costume Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/10/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this pack now and get 5 all-new Costumes for X-Men Characters."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Avengers Costume Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/10/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this pack now and get 5 all-new Costumes for Avengers Characters."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Captain America Costume Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/10/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this pack now and get 2 all-new Costumes for Captain America."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Spider-Man Costume Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/10/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this pack now and get 2 all-new Costumes for Spider-Man."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y5EJnrbI9P8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6V-G5Ykian0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lilm7nBHyLA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Marvel-Avengers-Battle-for-Earth/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/marvel-avengers-battle-for-earth/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/marvel-avengers-battle-for-earth"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1114,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"Experience the emotion of scoring great goals in FIFA 14. The game plays the way great football matches are contested, with innovations to the gameplay that inspire fans to build play through midfield, dictating the tempo of a match.<br><br>Feel the tension as chances are created, and experience the thrill of hitting the back of the net. A new feature called Pure Shot and a brand-new ball physics system will transform shooting, making every shot attempt feel real. FIFA 14 delivers online features and live services that connect fans to the heartbeat of the sport-and to each other-through EA Sports Football Club. FIFA 14 is football's social network, where fans connect, compete and share with millions of others around the world.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Ultimate Team Legends Bonus Commentary",
				"releaseDate":"2013/11/20",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"EA Sports brings 42 legendary footballers like Pel&eacute;, Viera, and Gullit, to FIFA 14 Ultimate Team. The FIFA 14 Ultimate Team Legends Bonus Commentary DLC is completely free and enhances the Legends content with additional colour commentary and more! This DLC is not required to play with Legends in FIFA 14 Ultimate Team."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=APMrtUd4WW8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZVx7vqtzACE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=beQzwszgTUA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/711401-fifa-14/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/FIFA-14/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fifa-14/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fifa-14"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1115,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"Pro Evolution Soccer 2014 marks a new beginning for Konami's blockbuster soccer series, with an all-new engine allowing for every aspect of Pro Evolution Soccer 2014 to be totally reworked to produce a game much closer to the excitement and variety of a top-level match.<br><br>The central theme of fluidity is based on the constant moving of players and switching positions which mirrors the modern approach to football. Producers looked at how the matches ebb and flow, with player individuality key to a team's success, and well-drilled tactics helping underdogs produce giant-killing feats. In addition to noticeably improved graphics and seamless animation, the thrust of the new engine's power has been used to redefine the way football is played as a video game. Gone are the limitations imposed by dated animation systems and AI elements, and instead PES 2014 boasts a central core that perfectly mimics the skill and awareness that elevates the world's greatest players above their peers.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"South American Classic Kit",
				"releaseDate":"2013/09/20",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this DLC to get kits from legendary Latin American club teams. - Santos FC 1968 - Boca Juniors 1997 - Racing Club 1967 - Colo Colo 1992 - Universidad de Chile 1996 - Sao Paulo FC 1993 Choose these classic kits and relive the glory days as you bring home the cup."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"3rd Kit",
				"releaseDate":"2013/09/20",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this DLC and get the 3rd colors for three of Europe's star studded teams: - Manchester United - Inter Milan - Juventus"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"European Classic Kit",
				"releaseDate":"2013/12/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this DLC to get kits from legendary European club teams: - Manchester United FC 1998-1999 - AS Roma 1982-1983 - AC Milan 1989-1990 - S.L. Benfica 1961-1962"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"World Challenge DLC",
				"releaseDate":"2014/03/25",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Compete for the ultimate football trophy, leading your International team or player to glory in new World Challenge DLC for PES 2014. As manager take control of your team from qualification stage with new menus. As a player fulfil your dreams and take your 'Become A Legend' character or current star on the ultimate career journey to global success. The World Challenge mode comes complete with official Brazil National Team adding a fresh feel to the ultimate football simulator."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EO1EFKRdJd8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bksw2NeH558"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pro-Evolution-Soccer-2014/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pro-Evolution-Soccer-2014/walkthrough.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pro-evolution-soccer-2014"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1116,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Team Ninja"],
			"synopsis":"Dead or Alive 5 Ultimate is the definitive DOA 5 package, with new content and additional fighters. This version ushers in the addition of modes from Dead or Alive 5 Plus, including \"Move Details Plus\" and a tutorial mode, will allow novice and expert fighters to refine their fighting style with razor-fine precision.<br><br>Dead or Alive 5 marries its signature fighting style with MMA fighting techniques to deliver a major kick for players new and old. Visually striking scenes from around the world blended with a hard-hitting cast puts players in the roles of the cast of Dead or Alive fighters once again. In DoA 5, stages act not only as visual backdrops to accompany a fight but instead play to a fighter's strengths. As a fight progresses, the backdrop will change and interact with players. Skilled fighters will be able to utilize these dynamic stages to execute hard hitting blows, pitting their opponents against new obstacles creating a unique experience that will leave you breathless.<br><br>With each battle executing a new level of involvedness, the fighters themselves have become more complex in their design. In Dead or Alive 5 players will be able to feel more involved in the action as they see their fighters sweat as they exert more energy. Players can also kick up the competition in online multiplayer modes where fighters must learn to utilize their strength and weaknesses to K.O. challengers.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable costumes",
				"releaseDate":"2013/10/22",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"More than 100 costumes available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SgMQQZCD5fs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tru02cd64AU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B9p_6DMcmRk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aXu1KG-HT5Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 5",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KCh_KwOInZc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-3oLQr5etQ4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/714711-dead-or-alive-5-ultimate/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dead-or-Alive-5-Ultimate/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dead-or-alive-5-ultimate/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dead-or-alive-5-ultimate"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dead or Alive Wiki",
				"url":"http://deadoralive.wikia.com/wiki/Dead_or_Alive_5_Ultimate"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1117,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SEGA"],
			"synopsis":"This compilation will feature the best first-party games from SEGA's venerable 16-bit Genesis years as well as feature bonus content from its 8-bit Master System and 1980's arcade era games library. Developed by Backbone Entertainment, Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Collection contains over 40 classic SEGA games in one package; making it the largest collection of SEGA first party games ever offered.<br><br>Featured games include Sonic the Hedgehog 1, 2 and 3, Columns, Ecco the Dolphin, Shinobi III, Space Harrier, and fan favorite Streets of Rage. The games in the collection have been reproduced with the utmost detail and accuracy to the original games. In addition, Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Collection can output the games in 720p with higher resolution graphics for HD televisions, bringing a new visual richness to playing these classic titles.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nc0qIv0oZ78"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qw9XfjfoNOs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-NL0r1zVaSU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/954264-sonics-ultimate-genesis-collection/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sonics-Ultimate-Genesis-Collection/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sonics-ultimate-genesis-collection/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sonics-ultimate-genesis-collection"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sonic News Network",
				"url":"http://sonic.wikia.com/wiki/Sonic's_Ultimate_Genesis_Collection"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1118,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sonic Team"],
			"synopsis":"In Sonic Free Riders, full-motion body control allows you to twist and turn your way through a range of courses in an action-packed Sonic experience.<br><br>Kinect's unique motion sensor means Sonic Free Riders will see family and friends controlling their fully customisable hover board or bike by twisting, turning and jumping in an exhilarating race to be the first to cross the finish line.<br><br>Choosing from one of your favorite Sonic characters, or your own Avatar, you can reach out and grab a variety of pickups along the course. By throwing, shaking, or swinging your arms to launch your items, you can gain the competitive edge over your rivals in high octane single or multiplayer races.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NWewtY3cDng"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uCicnIDjCsM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sonic-Free-Riders/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sonic-free-riders"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sonic News Network",
				"url":"http://sonic.wikia.com/wiki/Sonic_Free_Riders"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1119,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bongfish GmbH"],
			"synopsis":"Developed in conjunction with world-renowned snowboarding movie creator Absinthe Films, Stoked captures the pioneering spirit of professional back country riders. Exhilarating snowboarding experiences are born from dynamic backcountry conditions. The riders who brave and master these conditions are the stuff of legend in Absinthe videos and on the pages of snowboarding magazines. The look and style of these riders are emulated across the world. In Stoked, it's your turn to become a legendary rider and wow the world on the Xbox Live online entertainment network by becoming an absolute snowboarding phenomenon.<br><br>Upgraded with enhanced graphics and features, the Big Air Edition of Stoked features marked trails that make it easy to find great runs, lots of park objects to use for tricks, two new mountains, better visuals, and faster and smoother riding.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cdEIoK6izf4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g8CfY9weKUw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mfAhzroklNg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Stoked-Big-Air/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/stoked-big-air/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/stoked-big-air-edition"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1120,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tose"],
			"synopsis":"Champion Jockey uses motion control functionality to simulate the jockey experience to a degree of accuracy beyond anything you've ever played in a horse racing game. Players will learn how to use the horse's reins and whip as well shifting their body-weight to ride their thorough-bred to victory. In addition to controlling their horse, players must understand its unique rhythm, potential, stamina and preferred racing style to truly master the game.<br><br>Champion Jockey reproduces the European and Japanese horse racing world, incorporating both flat and jump racing. Players will feel the unique thrill of competing in detailed realizations of the European and Japanese horse racing worlds. The game also supports a host of online features -- a large step-forward for horse racing video games. Online Multiplayer Races, Live Jockey Rankings and a range of DLC will be available to players.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Variety Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Additional horses. Get four different unique horses and use their skins on your favorite horses at the paddock."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Music Pack 1 (G1 Jockey selection)",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/06",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"First batch of race BGM. Listen to four tracks from the G1 Jockey series with one brand new track for your racing enjoyment!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Music Pack 2 (Gallop Racer selection)",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/20",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Second batch of race BGM. Listen to four tracks from the Gallop Racer series with one brand new track for your racing enjoyment!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Comedy Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/27",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This pack offers additional riders and horses. Use two new unique riders or one new horse to cross the finish line in style."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Music Pack 3 (Sound Director's selection)",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/04",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Third batch of race BGM. 4 tracks from the Gallop Racer series with 1 new BGM selected by the Gallop Racer Sound Director."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Special Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/11",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This pack offers additional \"racehorses\". Play as a male or a female rider and use the roadbike or motoskates to ride to victory!"
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Music Pack 4 (Director's selection)",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/18",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Fourth batch of race BGM. 4 tracks from the GR and G1 Jockey series hand-picked by the sound directors!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e8sFAoclqsA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=23V0PhONNS4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vI3gnTMD71Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QrEc1k884Qk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/632138-champion-jockey-g1-jockey-and-gallop-racer/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Champion-Jockey-G1-Jockey-Gallop-Racer/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/champion-jockey-g1-jockey-gallop-racer"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1121,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"Take your alma mater to another bowl trophy in the 2014 edition of EA Sports' college pigskin game series.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cTklaI3EAm0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=92aMMtDf4lU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H07nWRF4H3A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NCAA-Football-14/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ncaa-football-14/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ncaa-football-14"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1122,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"DanceDanceRevolution for the Xbox 360 marks its long awaited return to the console complete with the engaging, physical, and interactive gameplay fans have come to love.<br><br>DanceDanceRevolution on Xbox 360 features two new gameplay modes filled with non-stop dancing action, comes fully equipped with the Visual Jockey, a feature which awards dancing pros with new on-screen graphics for a more engaging gameplay experience, and boasts a vast song roster with 20 licensed tracks spanning decades of hits from \"Celebration\" by Kool and the Gang to \"crushcrushcrush\" by Paramore and \"Bad Romance\" by Lady Gaga. DanceDanceRevolution also includes more than 30 original songs by Konami's original artists, and players can download new songs and add them to their playlist through Xbox LIVE.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"DanceDanceRevolution Premium Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/12",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Celebrating the first release of \"DanceDanceRevolution\", 3 of the most popular tracks have been selected from the game to provide the full-length version of the songs to you for free! Recorded Songs - Let's Get Away (Full Version) / NAOKI feat. Brenda Burch - dreaming can make a wish come true (Full Version) / jun & NRG Factory feat. Anna Kaelin - Private Eye (Full Version) / atomsoak ft. cerol."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"DanceDanceRevolution Greatest Hits",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/12",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"\"Dance Dance Revolution\" was the first release of the DDR series in 2001. 5 songs from the game have been recorded with new step sequences! Be sure to try out these tracks. Recorded Songs - PARANOiA / 180 - BRILLIANT 2U / NAOKI - AM-3P / KTz - TRIP MACHINE / DE-SIRE - PUT YOUR FAITH IN ME / UZI-LAY "
			},
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"DDRMAX2 Greatest Hits",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/12",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"5 hit songs from \"DDRMAX2 Dance Dance Revolution\", released in 2003 are included in this song pack with brand new step sequences! Dance the night away to this hot line-up. Recorded Songs - STILL IN MY HEART / NAOKI - KAKUMEI / dj TAKA with NAOKI - D2R / NAOKI - SUPER STAR / D.J.RICH feat. TAILBROS. - rain of sorrow / NM feat. EBONY FAY."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"DDR SuperNOVA Greatest Hits 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/12",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"5 songs from \"DanceDanceRevolution SuperNOVA\", released in 2006 are included with new step sequences! \"DDR SuperNOVA Greatest Hits 1\" includes the most popular and greatest tracks! Recorded Songs - My Only Shining Star / NAOKI feat. Becky Lucinda - RED ZONE / Tatsh&NAOKI - Mugen / T&euml;ra - Gamelan de Couple / TOMOSUKE - TRUE LOVE / jun."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"DDR SuperNOVA Greatest Hits 2",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/12",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"5 smash hit tracks from \"DanceDanceRevolution SuperNOVA\", released in 2006 are included with new step sequences! Try out this song pack with challenging dance steps. Recorded Songs -CAN'T STOP FALLIN' IN LOVE -super euro version-/NAOKI with Y&Co. -INNOCENCE OF SILENCE/nc ft NRG Factory -Star Gate Heaven/SySF. feat. Donna Burke -Flow(True Style)/Scotty D. revisits U1 -Fascination MAXX/100-200-400."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"DDR SuperNOVA2 Greatest Hits",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/12",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"5 hit songs from \"DanceDanceRevolution SuperNOVA2\", released in 2007 are included in this song pack with all new step sequences! Anybody can have fun dancing to this line-up! Recorded Songs - KISS KISS KISS/NAOKI feat. SHANTI - Raspberry Heart(English version)/jun feat. PAULA TERRY - Music In The Rhythm/nc ft. Electric Touch - BALLAD FOR YOU/NM feat. Thomas Howard - Arrabbiata/Reven-G alterative."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"DDR KONAMIX Greatest Hits",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/12",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"5 smash hit songs from \"Dance Dance Revolution KONAMIX\", released in 2002 are included in this pack with new step sequences! Try these 5 representative songs from the DDR series! Recorded Songs - B4U / NAOKI - HIGHER / NM feat. SUNNY - BURNIN' THE FLOOR / NAOKI - HYSTERIA / NAOKI 190 - TRIP MACHINE~luv mix~"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=len-36qxifQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WqcEyCyAJoM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dance-Dance-Revolution/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dance-dance-revolution/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dancedancerevolution"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"DanceDanceRevolution Wiki",
				"url":"http://dancedancerevolutionddr.wikia.com/wiki/Dance_Dance_Revolution_(DDR)_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1123,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["High Moon Studios"],
			"synopsis":"The Transformers: Dark of the Moon video game allows players to fight through the epic battles on Earth that will shape the events of the movie. Armed with a brand-new gameplay mechanic, fans will harness the power of Stealth Force to instantly convert to a third, hybrid state that combines the weapons and firepower of robot mode with the agility and maneuverability of vehicle mode. Set in unique environments around the world such as the Jungles of South America, Siberian military facilities, Detroit Cityscapes and more, the game lets players assume the roles of a diverse roster of everyone's favorite Transformers from the movie through a heart-pounding campaign to save mankind. Additionally, fans can play the game with or against their friends through intense, online multiplayer game modes as their favorite iconic characters.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Sideswipe - Playable Multi-Player Character",
				"releaseDate":"2011/07/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Sideswipe lives to fight, and while he generally prefers his swords, recently, Ironhide has convinced him to give blasters another chance. He hunts the Decepticons around the world, destroying them wherever he can find them. With his blades extended and his wheels on the ground, no one can stop him! Sideswipe is an original Autobot, one with a long legacy in the Transformers universe. With a role in Revenge of the Fallen, he showcased his melee skills and agility. In the Dark of The Moon game, he is now armed with a Scoped Burst Rifle for ranged combat as well as his powerful Cybertanium arm blades that allow for a powerful whirlwind attack. He compliments the other Autobot Scouts as Mirage and Bumblebee are geared towards short and mid-range combat whereas Sideswipe can be dangerous from any range. Sideswipe is a scout character, quick on his feet (wheels) and ready to mix it up with Decepticons. He excels at hit and run tactics, and can effortlessly move in and out of fights in both robot and vehicle form. Gamers who prefer speed and melee capabilities should look to Sideswipe as a class-A specimen."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WojGd2_wrCg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u2omskGit8Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Transformers-Dark-of-the-Moon/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/transformers-dark-of-the-moon/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/transformers-dark-of-the-moon"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Transformers Wiki",
				"url":"http://transformers.wikia.com/wiki/Dark_of_the_Moon_(game)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1124,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Monumental Games"],
			"synopsis":"MotoGP 10/11 will bring fans the most authentic and realistic MotoGP experience of the series. Gamers will get all of the 2010 MotoGP season content and downloadable updates for the 2011 MotoGP championship shortly after the season starts.<br><br>The all new handling system and improved physics in MotoGP 10/11 will deliver a level of authenticity never seen before in the GP series. The inclusion of the brand new customizable player assists feature allows fans of both simulation and arcade racing to alter their racing style. Those wanting to take less of a risk with their riding technique will be able to switch on the player assists for a more forgiving style of racing. For players who want to feel the full intensity of MotoGP racing, all the in-game player assists can be turned off delivering challenging and realistic gameplay that emulates the MotoGP experience.<br><br>Career mode will be complemented with the addition of brand new co-op play. Through local split-screen gameplay a second player can jump into the race and become a team mate, helping to take your team to pole position. The classic Championship and Time Trial modes are back along with a revised 'Challenge' mode. This year fans of the MotoGP will be able to play as their racing hero from the start in all three of these game modes. And as with MotoGP 09/10, MotoGP 10/11 will continue to offer the most robust online mode in a racing title, allowing up to 20 players to compete in a Championship race.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fZD-44cyUc8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aBILlWMCVHc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FQ2Kc2smBN8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_-s3X1Y9BL8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MotoGP-10-11/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/motogp-1011"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1125,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Milestone"],
			"synopsis":"The popular racing franchise is back! Speed. Emotion. Skill. These essential elements mixed with an adrenaline-fuelled experience immerse you into the world of MotoGP like never before. With genre-leading graphics, MotoGP 2013 will bring players into the 2013 championship through the eyes of a real MotoGP rider. MotoGP 13 features a career mode, online multiplayer, and full use of the MotoGP license, including the new Moto2 and Moto3 classes. The game includes all the official tracks and riders of the 2013 MotoGP season. Utilizing a brand new game engine buily from the ground up, MotoGP 2013 brings a whole new level of realism to elements such as graphics, physics, bikes, environments and in-game sound.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"2012 Top Riders",
				"releaseDate":"2013/06/21",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"For the download the 8 riders and 4 bikes from 2012 season to your MotoGP13 are Stoner and Pedrosa in Repsol Honda Team, Rossi and Hayden in Ducati Team, Lorenzo and Spies in Yamaha Factory Racing, Dovizioso and Crutchlow in Yamaha Monster Tech 3. These 2012 riders are available in single player quick race, race weekend and online multiplayer modes."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Moto2 and Moto3",
				"releaseDate":"2013/07/03",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Additional riders, bikes and teams are going to be made available to expand your gaming experience by completing the in-game rosters of the Moto2 and Moto3 categories. This free of charge add-on is totally updated for the 2013 season, for a comprehensive immersion in MotoGP world."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Red Bull Rookies Cup",
				"releaseDate":"2013/09/18",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"The Red Bull Rookies Cup will add the game this exciting competition."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"MotoGP Champions",
				"releaseDate":"2013/11/06",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"MotoGP Champions gives you the opportunity to race as, and against, legendary riders of the past, including Doohan, Schwantz, Rainey, Spencer, Gardner, Capirossi and many others. Ride their historical 2 stroke 500 CC bikes and experience all the excitement of being a Motogp legend."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F3YThppLrJw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xtUF1Ocxu2E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wjT4V0Gsa90"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9pPtlhxECOQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MotoGP-13/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/motogp-13"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1126,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Milestone"],
			"synopsis":"MotoGP 14 features more than 100 available riders, all the official manufacturers, all racing classes and 18 tracks in a brand new racing chapter based on the Official MotoGP World Championship.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Laguna Seca Red Bull US Grand Prix",
				"releaseDate":"2014/06/20",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"The MotoGP 14 Laguna Seca Red Bull US Grand Prix pack adds this sensational circuit to the game. Take on your opponents in Grand Prix and Championship modes!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Moto2 and Moto3",
				"releaseDate":"2014/06/20",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Enhance your game experience with this free additional content, completing the rosters for the Moto2 and Moto3 classes, updated for the 2014 season. Immerse yourself even more deeply into the world of the MotoGP!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8nQiqyUd5oA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Pmp_IVxPt4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=equNpCSGuaM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MotoGP-14/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/motogp-14"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1127,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Liar Soft"],
			"synopsis":"In 1907, the advent of steam power and excessive use of it caused the air around New York to turn dark. There was an unexplained disaster called the \"great disappearance\" 5 years ago and the government blocked off the city. Now, there's only one girl who walks in the ruins of the city: Elicia. Meanwhile, down below the ruins, Lily looks at the 'sky' which is stained purple. She doesn't have any memories, but she knows that she has a mission to reach the edge of the purple sky, Manhattan. A mysterious boy A accompanies her and along the way, they learn more about the truth from others and are attacked by monsters on their journey. What is her true purpose? What actually happened 5 years ago to New York?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W2QBzMSEwLA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay (PSP)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0DG0aalT6is"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Refrain/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1128,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Alchemist"],
			"synopsis":"An upgraded XBox 360 version of 2010's Ogon Musokyoku (\"Golden Fantasia\") with Rosa Ushiromiya, Jessica Ushiromiya and George Ushiromiya added to the game's roster of selectable characters.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t9-Keu3ZZMA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9Vcqt9ah5Xc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Golden-Fantasia-X/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/golden-fantasia-x/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1129,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["THQ Digital Studios Phoenix"],
			"synopsis":"Own the competition as you wrestle for position with tightly contested racing in the fifth iteration of the MX vs ATV franchise. Feel the realism of the revolutionary real-world physics engine which has defined the genre. MX vs ATV Alive captures the spectacle of motocross and the essence of competitive racing while providing the best riders and gear from the latest manufacturers, letting players live the sport.<br><br>MX vs ATV Alive employs the franchise's acclaimed physics engine while utilizing a new game structure that caters to the fans via a robust offering of DLC content. As you get deeper and deeper into the game, a player can add more content of your favorite modes and features in, catering the game to your likes and your style of play.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2SqXihhT5aM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W3ZzVmjOIFA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MX-vs-ATV-Alive/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mx-vs-atv-alive/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mx-vs-atv-alive"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1130,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rebellion"],
			"synopsis":"Sniper Elite 3 sees American OSS agent Karl Fairburne on assignment in North Africa during WWII to assist intelligence efforts and provide sharpshooter skills to Allied forces within exotic, rugged and open land. As part of his mission, Karl learns of a secret \"wonder weapon\" tank program which, should it become a reality, has the potential to crush any Allied force in its path and turn the tide of the war.<br><br>With an emphasis on player choice, Sniper Elite 3 features non-linear gameplay across varied North African terrain such as mountain ranges and sprawling plains, allowing for a greater range of motion and the ability to take longer-ranged shots with customizable weapons. In addition, bustling cities and remote villages greatly assist in planning relocation tactics. An all-new vehicle kill-cam lets gamers take out armored cars and tanks and wreak massive destruction with one shot into vehicles' gas tanks. In addition, the infamous X-Ray kill-cam is back with greater graphic detail including circulatory system and muscle layer. Sniper Elite 3 also features co-op and competitive multiplayer.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Hunt The Grey Wolf",
				"releaseDate":"2014/07/16",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Hitler, Allied code name \"Grey Wolf\", and his double have embarked upon a secret trip to the town of Tobruk in 1942. In order to prepare for the crucial final shot, you must infiltrate the ancient streets and crumbling rooftops using stealth and distraction. With an expansive open environment, and randomized target identities, journals and locations, no two playthroughs will be the same. Can you tell fact from fiction, the real target from the double?"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Camouflage Weapons Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/07/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Camouflage Weapons Pack includes 3 weapons - Rifle: Mosin Nagant (camo), SMG: MP44 (camo), Pistol: High Standard HDM (silenced). 3 weapons for Sniper Elite 3 usable in single and multi-player."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"US Infantry/Allied Outfits Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/07/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"US Infantry/Allied Outfits Pack includes three characters for use in Sniper Elite's competitive multi-player modes - Allied Urban Sniper, US Army Rifleman, and Indian Division Soldier."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Hunter Weapons Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/07/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Hunter Weapons pack includes 3 weapons - SVT-40, Shotgun: Trenchgun, Pistol: Revolver M1917. High power hunting weapons for Sniper Elite 3 usable in single and multi-player."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Save Churchill - Part 1: In Shadows",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/10",
				"achievements":70,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The first part of the 'Save Churchill' mini-campaign for Sniper Elite 3. Intelligence has learned about rumours of a plan to assassinate Winston Churchill. Can you find the assassins and stop them before it's too late?"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Patriot Weapons Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Patriot Weapons Pack includes 3 weapons - the Springfield rifle, M3 Grease Gun, and M1911 Pistol. A combination of three all-American favourites into one powerful pack for use in all modes."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Save Churchill - Part 2: Belly of the Beast",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/29",
				"achievements":70,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The second part of the 'Save Churchill' mini-campaign for Sniper Elite 3. Karl has managed to track the assassins down to their secret mountain base. Find out what they're up to and where they plan to kill the British Prime Minister."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Axis Weapons Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/29",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Axis Weapons Pack includes 3 weapons - the Type 99, MAB 38, and Army Pistol 38. Use your enemies' weapons against them. Usable in all modes."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Eastern Front Weapons Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/29",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Eastern Front Weapons Pack includes 3 weapons - the Mosin-Nagant, Blyskawica, and Tokarev TT-33. Wield iconic guns from the Eastern Front. Usable in all modes."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Sniper Rifle Weapons Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/09/29",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Sniper Rifle Weapons Pack includes 3 rifles - the Kar 98k, M1917 Enfield and Springfield (Tuned). Keep your foes at a distance with this pack. Usable in all modes."
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Multiplayer Expansion Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/02",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Free downloadable content required to play Sniper Elite 3 online, includes new multiplayer maps in all modes!"
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Save Churchill - Part 3: Confrontation",
				"releaseDate":"2014/10/06",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The final part of the 'Save Churchill' mini-campaign for Sniper Elite 3. The assassins plan to attack Winston Churchill on the outskirts of Casablanca. Stop them and square off against their mysterious leader."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UgTLk8duMNU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nsHcLZGQ81s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=leZV-a_8ugs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JVUhVJmSBH8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/733722-sniper-elite-iii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sniper-Elite-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sniper-elite-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sniper-elite-iii"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1131,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Hydravision"],
			"synopsis":"Invisible, silent, deadly Let confrontations lead you to victory, get promoted and make your avatar's skills evolve. Purchase new weapons you can improve and new equipment to trap your enemies or hide (hologram projectors, thermal glasses, drones, etc.). Discover the first online multiplayer FPS exclusively developed for snipers!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DPifA6Rb-dg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B7raL07Ka38"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Snipers/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1132,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["City Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"When millions of soldiers and thousands of tanks clashed on the fronts of World War II, an even more dramatic battle was being fought above the blood soaked earth. All across the globe, heroic allied pilots desperately tried to gain air dominance.<br><br>Defend Great Britain against the German Luftwaffe, take part in the monumental efforts of the Red Army on the east, or exact revenge on the Japanese air forces as an American pilot over the Pacific. Stay focused, as split-seconds decide victory or death.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FIA4tShQryE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-TDWfBRMzjE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ojniQTEE8dk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o8sn3rtdLAE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Combat-Wings/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1133,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tradewest Games"],
			"synopsis":"This 2010 edition of the classic sports franchise has been carefully tailored for modern consoles and offers a realistic simulation of the Olympic Winter Games. Winter Sports 2010 offers 8 disciplines based on winter sports popular which the break to ski, the skating, snowboard cross or even the biathlon.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UVEppoC57B8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DvRm2ldQvT0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Winter-Sports-2010/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1134,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["RTL Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Winter Sports 2011 is the ultimate challenge for casual gamers and sport fans, that includes the nine most exciting winter sport disciplines. Thanks to improved multiplayer mode it offers more direct interaction with the player's opponents. Thus, there are several disciplines, like snowboard cross, in which all players can participate simultaneously. In each competition - whether multiplayer or single player - players can choose from a variety of tactical possibilities, as for example skating in slipstreams, turbo or hard physical impacts. Moreover, every fair or unfair behavior affects the qualities and the appearance of the players.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sn-nvcOJzxU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DIV6V3cPpiA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Winter-Sports-2011/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1135,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cave"],
			"synopsis":"DeathSmiles II X is a horizontal scrolling shooter with updated visuals, two new characters, two new stages, and selectable difficulties that builds on the original game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tbm3JWU2Q3Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L0XVuRfQZpI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Deathsmiles-2-X/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/deathsmiles-ii-x"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1136,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Milestone"],
			"synopsis":"Superstars V8 Next Challenge will offer you access to a fast and exciting new racing experience! The game has been developed with the expert advice of race veteran and champion of the Superstars competition, Gianni Morbidelli. Gianni made it possible to make multiple improvements and integrate many real world features, regarding the fine tuning of each car performance.<br><br>Superstars V8 Next Challenge will have countless improvements to discover, from new gameplay modes & online experiences to all new realistic 3D environments. The 2010 edition is enriched with new licensed cars from top tier manufacturers, new tracks and some of the world's best known and challenging circuits.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AOpLG9R5CH4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iY3kHzeX1YA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Superstars-V8-NC/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/superstars-v8-next-challenge/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1137,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Studio9"],
			"synopsis":"SuperStar is a Korean karaoke game from Studio9.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/SuperStar/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/superstar-karaoke/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1138,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sidhe"],
			"synopsis":"Rugby Challenge is a rugby union-based title that includes the All Blacks, ITM Cup, and Investec Super Rugby amongst other licensed teams and competitions, and will feature multiplayer online play, a multi-year franchise mode, extensive customisation options, and dynamic real-time commentary.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tRPadakmZKY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tT-q2vCCfCA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Jonah-Lomu-Rugby-Challenge/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rugby-challenge/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/jonah-lomu-rugby-challenge"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1139,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Home Entertainment Suppliers"],
			"synopsis":"Rugby League Live brings all the hard hitting action and excitement of the greatest game of all to your lounge room. Featuring: 40+ licensed teams from competitions such as the NRL, Super League, State of Origin, City v Country and International teams. 30+ realistic stadia from around the world. Bone crunching tackles. Field and uniform degradation. Multiple replay angles and commentary by Andrew Voss. Xbox Live.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u4GzFAfcSbo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FhW8aPhLfgY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rugby-League-Live/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rugby-league-live/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1140,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Big Ant Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Rugby League Live 2 promises to deliver the hard-hitting action and excitement of the greatest game of all, accurately capturing the speed, creativity and strategy of today's Rugby league. The sequel features a multitude of licensed leagues & teams to choose in single matches or a massive 10-Year Career Mode. The game also boasts improved graphics that detail everything down to the grass tearing up on the field and the mud and sweat that cling to players' bodies.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d4a7qQKyers"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mGyrRunFSyI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4MsuZXjyFAs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rugby-League-Live-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rugby-league-live-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1141,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tamsoft"],
			"synopsis":"A mahjong game based on the hostess-club/dating simulator series Dream C Club.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vBFD84sudC4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=039ElN0tpCM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/653723-mahjong-dream-c-club/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mahjong-Dream-C-Club/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1142,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Boost On"],
			"synopsis":"Love Training is a gal-training / love sim created for use with the Kinect motion sensor. Players are in charge of the activities in dance club at school, and must get to know the girls as well as demonstrate great timing and skillful moves in order to help the club do its best!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CBxxb3qb0u8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bL2CTlMiQZ8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Love-Tore-Bitter/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1143,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Boost On"],
			"synopsis":"Love Training is a gal-training / love sim created for use with the Kinect motion sensor. Players are in charge of the activities in dance club at school, and must get to know the girls as well as demonstrate great timing and skillful moves in order to help the club do its best!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GVs0nKXgaG8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JpQZn2IqRHM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FKTQWy3210c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zhvouLk462M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Love-Tore-Mint/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1144,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Boost On"],
			"synopsis":"Love Training is a gal-training / love sim created for use with the Kinect motion sensor. Players are in charge of the activities in dance club at school, and must get to know the girls as well as demonstrate great timing and skillful moves in order to help the club do its best!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ca9TGFoy1QI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9BY5snYqTIc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Love-Tore-Sweet/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1145,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Lightning Fish"],
			"synopsis":"Adidas MiCoach brings the popular miCoach interactive athletic training system to video game consoles. Many of the world's most well-known adidas athletes are featured in the game, including Dwight Howard, Kak&aacute;, Tyson Gay, Jessica Ennis, Ana Ivanovic and Eric Berry, and they will guide users through a wide selection of sport-specific personalized training programs. Users will also receive real-time feedback on their actual in-game performance during their workouts when wearing a miCoach heart rate monitor (or any ANT+ compatible monitor).<br><br>For an even more connected gaming experience, the miCoach hardware interacts with the game, allowing users to wirelessly synchronize a miCoach Pacer and miCoach mobile app to their game console, incorporating workout data gathered while away from the game. Utilizing advanced video game console technology, users will be able to create profiles, set fitness goals and get instant analyses of workout regimens. They will choose from several sports, such as running, tennis, football (soccer), American football and basketball, as well as the athletes who guide them through hours of on-screen training and motivating game experiences.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Rugby Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/08/07",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"A full rugby training program to add to your miCoach living room experience - train with the best! Train in the comfort of your own home with an all-star rugby training team - Ma'a Nonu and Will Genia. Earn Fit Points and awards for every bit of exercise you do. Train at home, in the gym and outdoors, tracked by the latest motion tracking technology and portable fitness hardware. Wake up to a whole new community of friends and social network updates. It's your exercise world, perfectly synced from your console, via the web or via your smartphone."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Manuel Neuer",
				"releaseDate":"2012/08/07",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Add football superstar Manuel Neuer to your miCoach football training team - train with the best! Train in the comfort of your own home with an additional football star for your all-star football training team. Earn Fit Points and awards for every bit of exercise you do. Train at home, in the gym and outdoors, tracked by the latest motion tracking technology and portable fitness hardware. Wake up to a whole new community of friends and social network updates. It's your exercise world, perfectly synced from your console, via the web or via your smartphone."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Hp-u7LVXPQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lFLJW9A7QbY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/miCoach/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/adidas-micoach"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1146,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"Crossboard 7 thrusts gamers into 7 unbelievable fantasy worlds with exciting boarding battles in amazing environments played with the Kinect sensor. Compete in cross boarding action through freestyle, time and collection challenges against boss characters each with unique abilities. Battle Boss' from around the world growing your abilities and gaining more impressive boards each with their own special features. Win a race, steal that boss' board and do battle to collect all 60. Kinect controls mean anyone can play because your body is the controller. The Kinect camera reads your body's natural motions converting them into character actions on screen. It's not just a race, it's a battle!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Moss's Board",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This will allow you to use Moss's Board, which cannot be obtained within the game."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Fridge's Board",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This will allow you to use Fridge's Board, which cannot be obtained within the game."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Blaizer's Board",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This will allow you to use Blaizer's Board, which cannot be obtained within the game."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Pestor's Board",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This will allow you to use Pestor's Board, which cannot be obtained within the game."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Krystale's Board",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This will allow you to use Krystale's Board, which cannot be obtained within the game."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Ricky Jr.'s Board",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This will allow you to use Ricky Jr.'s Board, which cannot be obtained within the game."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Glop'Ee's Board",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This will allow you to use Glop'Ee's Board, which cannot be obtained within the game."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Sabre's Board",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This will allow you to use Sabre's Board, which cannot be obtained within the game."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KrOsGn1JQDY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wm_Dsp7nQ6s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Adrenalin-Misfits/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/crossboard-7/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/adrenalin-misfits"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1147,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Behaviour Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Dance and sing along with Alvin and the Chipmunks in this motion-based experience that lets you perform for the crowd as one of your favorite singing Chipmunks or sassy Chipettes. Dance to classic Chipmunk hits as you play in environments right from the big screen. Unleash your 'Munk Power' to perform ultra-cool finishing dance moves while following an exciting story based on the movie. Get the party started in the exciting musical adventure that is Alvin and the Chipmunks: Chipwrecked!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VBG1NwjWBxc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VQCq-pGoEfE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Alvin-and-the-Chipmunks-Chipwrecked/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/alvin-and-the-chipmunks-chipwrecked/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/alvin-and-the-chipmunks-chipwrecked"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1148,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Robomodo"],
			"synopsis":"Big League Sports for Kinect offers instant access to the most action-packed moments in sports. The result is a title with a singular focus on putting players in the most thrilling situations while competing in their favorite sports.<br><br>Big League Sports for Kinect brings together the six most popular sports in the world: football, soccer, baseball, hockey, basketball and golf. Big League Sports offers 18 accessible yet competitive skills challenges to master. The single player mode tracks stats with a real-time leaderboard and multiple multiplayer modes means there is no shortage of ways to show off abilities. Controls are refined for maximum fun on Kinect and are unique to each sport.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y6DuPvvqIU4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7-mV57ZUjac"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Big-League-Sports/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1149,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Games Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the hit television show, The Biggest Loser Ultimate Workout comes to Kinect offering the ultimate workout experience. Complete your fitness program using the interactive motion control sensors providing real-time feedback. From a body analyzer and recipes to personalized tips and a video diary to track your journey, The Biggest Loser Ultimate Workout fitness game has it all to drop the weight and change your life.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-eipeLPuBqg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MQGYBydJHTk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Biggest-Loser-UW/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-biggest-loser-ultimate-workout/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-biggest-loser-ultimate-workout"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1150,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["iNiS"],
			"synopsis":"The Black Eyed Peas Experience dance game brings BEP's music, moves and style to gamers. It features fun dance moves as well as hit songs from The Black Eyed Peas multi-platinum selling albums. Players control their on-screen avatar via the Kinect while following the dance moves of 3D avatars, including each of The Black Eyed Peas: apl.de.ap, Fergie, Taboo and will.i.am.<br><br>The Black Eyed Peas Experience takes that concept even further, and features a comprehensive selection of The Black Eyed Peas' hit music tracks as well as dance routines arranged by the group's famed creative director and choreographer, Fatima Robinson.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Dance Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Keep the party moving and expand your library with three new songs. This pack includes two classic Black Eyed Peas hits, \"Where is the love\",\"Bebot\", and a killer track from LMFAO, \"Party Rock Anthem\"."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Dance Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"This pack includes two classic Black Eyed Peas hits, \"They Don't Want Music\" and \"Do It Like This\"."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Dance Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"This pack includes two classic Black Eyed Peas hits, \"Light Up The Night\" and \"Someday\"."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Dance Pack 4",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"This pack includes two hits, \"Nothing Really Matters\" and \"Like a G6\"."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Dance Pack 5",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Keep the party moving and expand your library with three new songs. This pack includes: \"Don't hold your breath\" - Nicole Scherzinger, \"Mirrors\" - Natalia Kills and \"Pon De Floor\" - Major Lazer."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g_OsLv_tpm4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CvCuQS2W3xo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0ORQVAeoCA8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LRfw9iX2-ho"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Black-Eyed-Peas-Experience/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/black-eyed-peas-experience/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-black-eyed-peas-experience"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1151,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bandai Namco Games"],
			"synopsis":"From the originators of the video game brain training craze, Body and Brain Connection challenges players to think on their feet in one of the most cerebral and energetic party games. Body and Brain Connection will test the whole family to think quickly and act even quicker as they compete in 20 unique activities ranging from math, logic, reflex, memory and physical-related exercises using the full-motion capabilities of the Kinect sensor. Players can track their daily brain age progress and complete a specialized set of single player exercises determined by the player's previous results.<br><br>Body and Brain Connection also supports up to four players in a fun and energetic multiplayer mode. Compete against friends and family to determine who has the youngest brain age, or who has the best score across any of the game's 20 exercises.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Higher Learning I",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/22",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Higher Learning I is bursting with all new exercises and game modes to help challenge your brain! -New Exercises- Hit & Step: Memorize movements to answer the problem! Figure It Out: Combine shapes to replicate the final figure! -New Modes- Endless Edition: See how long you can keep going without messing up in \"Traffic Control\" and \"Math Jock\"! Duel Mode: Train alongside another player in \"What Time Is It?\" and \"Touch 'n Go\" to add a new level of difficulty! With Body and Brain Exercises, training your brain has never been easier or more fun!"
			},
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Higher Learning II",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/26",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Higher Learning II adds even more fun and excitement with all new exercises and game modes to help challenge your brain! -New Exercises- Mime Games: Try to memorize a series of poses! Even Split: Split the Ferris Wheel into two equal halves! -New Modes- Endless Edition: See how long you can keep going without messing up in \"Touch 'n Go\" and \"Mouse Mayhem\"! Duel Mode: Train alongside another player in \"Strike a Pose\" and \"Follow the Arrows\" to add a new level of difficulty! With Body and Brain Exercises, training your brain has never been easier or more fun!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nivjpR_zGKI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PtvGpshGK2M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Body-and-Brain/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/body-and-brain-connection"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1152,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cat Daddy"],
			"synopsis":"Get ready for a dip in the Shark Tank, a raucous ride on Coin Coaster Mountain or a Cotton-Eyed Joe dance-off with the Monkey Barker. Carnival Games:Monkey See, Monkey Do was made specifically to take full advantage of the innovative Kinect technology, offering easy access to all the thrills and fun of Carnival Games. Corner to Whirligig Way -- set the stage for gamers to swing away in the batting cage, avoid twisting tornadoes in the Hot Air Balloon Race, take a galactic journey to the red planet in Rocket to Mars and much more.<br><br>Classic games like Alley Ball, Milk Bottle Throw and Wheel of Chance add to the family fun. All manner of interactive prizes and surprises abound, including pet dragons, robot cowboys, flying bears and ninja masks.<br><br>In addition, Kinect for Xbox 360's voice recognition technology allows The Amazing Wodin, a wily wizard with a weakness for wit, to advise players of their future. Also making his debut appearance in a Carnival Games title, is the Monkey Barker. Smartly dressed and renowned for his dancing skills, he promises to bring a fair share of monkey mischief to the midway.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Monkey Dancin' Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/06/14",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Time to do the funky monkey in this new downloadable dance pack.  Get your groove on to Rock n Roll, Disco, Country and Hip-Hop! Sixteen new songs include \"Devil Went Down to Georgia\", \"Rock and Roll All Night\", \"Superfreak\", \"Mony Mony\", \"It Takes Two\", \"Jam on It\" and \"On the Road Again\". Now put your dancing shoes on and bust a move!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Coasterama Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2014/07/19",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Get more heart-pounding thrills, twists and turns in this new roller coaster downloadable pack. Grab gold coins as you race through ancient tombs and pyramids in Mummy Madness; get spaced out in Galactic Express; and dodge medieval mayhem in the fiery Dragon's Den!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gy-j9bAAk7Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NK-TssRiP7g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iGREfSPLyoQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1xMW0bZiW8M"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/621202-carnival-games-monkey-see-monkey-do/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Carnival-Games-Monkey-See-Monkey-Do/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/carnival-games-monkey-see-monkey-do/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/carnival-games-monkey-see-monkey-do!"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1153,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["High Voltage Software"],
			"synopsis":"Country Dance All Stars is the entertaining dance game that's packed with over 30 songs from country music's biggest artists. Country Dance All Stars was designed from the ground up for Kinect for Xbox 360 to bring a whole new hands-free experience to the dance party.<br><br>Your body becomes the controller as you kick up your boots and dance your way through over 30 hot routines and songs. Challenge a friend to a dance off with simultaneous competitive play or work together to pull off the moves and collectively build a top score. Boost your boot-scootin' skills with all new line-dancing routines, and don't be afraid to belt it out with scrolling sing-a-long lyrics. Share the fun with friends as the Kinect sensor snaps photos throughout each routine. Plus, all new downloadable content (DLC) support allows you to keep the party going with downloadable song packs featuring new choreography that will be released post launch.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BeEUvyXwHj8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_xJhajbKH3I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ID6bE3BBo6w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Country-Dance-AllStars/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/country-dance-all-stars"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1154,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"Featuring full-body tracking, the magic of Kinect for Xbox 360 allows you to experience real dance with your friends and family. Whether you're rehearsing in Break It Down! or owning the stage in Perform It, you'll be introduced to more than 600 moves in the game and more than 90 dance routines all created by professional choreographers.<br><br>The game features tracks from an amazing mix of pop, hip-hop and R&B artists including Lady Gaga, No Doubt, M.I.A., Bell Biv Devoe, and more. Take your moves to the next level while connecting with the music you love!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable tracks",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/04",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"32 tracks available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dkRiHMXq6nw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qIRK34wfCAY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T-EuAJwZoWo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dance-Central/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dance-central/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dance-central"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dance Central Wiki",
				"url":"http://dancecentral.wikia.com/wiki/Dance_Central"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1155,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"Dance Central 2 keeps the wildly addictive Dance Central experience going with a new focus on simultaneous multiplayer. Friends can now team up in Perform It or go head-to-head in a simultaneous dance off within Dance Battle. Additionally, players can seamlessly drop in or out at any point during a song, so the party never has to stop!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable tracks",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"67 tracks available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YQ2F3KogQrA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_EBtzfzNcJQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZA27ZjC3BrY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2E7hO7FmuuM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dance-Central-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dance-central-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dance-central-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dance Central Wiki",
				"url":"http://dancecentral.wikia.com/wiki/Dance_Central_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1156,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"In Dance Central 3, players get sent back in time to dance their way through the '70s, '80s, '90s, '00s and beyond - learning popular dance crazes like The Hustle, Electric Slide and The Dougie, alongside the hottest moves from today. The beat keeps rocking with an innovative new party mode for up to eight players, the ability to import your songs from previous Dance Central titles, and more! The best full-body dance experience on Kinect for Xbox 360 is better in every way with Dance Central 3!<br><br>Dance Central 3 features brand new ways to play with your friends, including the innovative Crew Throwdown mode. With support for up to eight players, Crew Throwdown pits two teams of up to four dancers head-to-head in a series of performances, dance battles, and fresh mini-games to prove who's the hottest crew on the dance floor! Crew Throwdown features innovative gameplay, including the all-new rhythm-tracking Keep the Beat mini-game and Make Your Move, which will have players competing head-to-head as they create fresh routines on the fly!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable tracks",
				"releaseDate":"2012/10/16",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"101 tracks available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hcFwIG5k3UM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x-_8_JSMOyg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ruv8HYZ-l28"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ObayN8kFKqY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WpcAqJzMn90"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jkOhuMg9EZg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dance-Central-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dance-central-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dance-central-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dance Central Wiki",
				"url":"http://dancecentral.wikia.com/wiki/Dance_Central_3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1157,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"DanceMasters will offer users the ultimate dance club vibe. Kinect for Xbox 360 allows players to watch their actions in real time and also save two of their original routines for use as back-up dancers in the game, no controllers required. As players dance in tune to the game's music, they can also take snapshots of their favorite dance poses, save to local albums and share the fun with friends. Utilising XboxLIVE for the Xbox 360 video game and entertainment system from Microsoft, players can also challenge up to four friends around the world and enhance their experience with dance sequences, theme packs and more.<br><br>Featuring 30 tracks spanning club music classics, Hip Hop, R&B, Pop, and Techno, DanceMasters dancers can groove to their favorite songs, creating non-stop set lists and can also download new songs via Xbox LIVE. The game also offers three gameplay modes for the ultimate dance experience: Dance, Lesson, and Status. In Dance Mode, users compete to become the Dance Master as they play and unlock their favorite songs and dance along with a friend. Lesson Mode offers a tutorial service, and Status Mode allows players to check their play records and review the titles they have earned. Players can also compete to determine the ultimate dancer with multiple difficulty levels including Light, Standard, Extreme and Stealth.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Master Level Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/21",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"This is the Master Level Pack. It adds the master level songs."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Outfit 1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"If this content is downloaded, the character costumes for the below songs will change. Brilliant 2U, We Can Win the Fight, Crazy Control. To change the costume back, please delete the downloaded data from the Xbox Dashboard."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Outfit 2",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"If this content is downloaded, the character costumes for the below songs will change. A Geisha's Dream, Kimono Princess, Sakura. To change the costume back, please delete the downloaded data from the Xbox Dashboard."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Outfit 3",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/01",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"If this content is downloaded, the character costumes for the below songs will change. Afronova Primeval, Burnin' the Floor, La receta. To change the costume back, please delete the downloaded data from the Xbox Dashboard."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Outfit 4",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/15",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"If this content is downloaded, the character costumes for the below songs will change. Still in my Heart, My Only Shining Star, Secret Rendez-vous, L'amour et la libert&eacute;(Darwin & DJ Silver remix). To change the costume back, please delete the downloaded data from the Xbox Dashboard."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Outfit 5",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/01",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"If this content is downloaded, the character costumes for the below songs will change. Lover's High, Mess With My Emotions, My Summer Love. To change the costume back, please delete the downloaded data from the Xbox Dashboard."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pkB4sg6wdyo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QTUIM4LNNbk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jLo0D8IYXXw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mUz3G8W7fxQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/997760-dancemasters/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/DanceMasters/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dancemasters"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1158,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Mindscape"],
			"synopsis":"Using Kinect's tracking detection and control-free technology, Dance Paradise gives players the chance to express themselves, move completely freely and dance without any restrictions. This is a dance game appealing to children, parents, fans of classic hits and even the most die-hard of clubbers. In fun, colorful settings including beaches, discos and casinos; dance floor kings and queens will be able to dance solo or challenge each other in different multiplayer modes. With the Kinect for Xbox 360 sensor technology, two dancers can play simultaneously and be scored individually.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6UPyP9cARIQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EXqvV-YY7AA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9XChUZcl9HQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dance-Paradise/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dance-paradise/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dance-paradise"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1159,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Hudson Soft"],
			"synopsis":"Deca Sports Freedom takes sports gaming to the next level with 10 sporting events designed especially for Kinect. Players can compete in Tennis, Boxing, Archery, Paintball, Beach Volleyball, Dodge Ball, Kendo, Mogul Skiing, Snowboard Cross and even more.<br><br>Deca Sports Freedom takes advantage of Kinect for Xbox 360's advanced technology and allows gamers to compete controller-free against friends and family, and even online against \"DECAthletes\" around the world through Xbox LIVE online entertainment network. Players' movements are mirrored by their avatars, which appear in the game as the athletes.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Aj4MzR1pHVo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lXVmSce9-ew"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Deca-Sports-Freedom/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/deca-sports-freedom/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/deca-sports-freedom"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1160,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Spike Chunsoft"],
			"synopsis":"Dragon Ball Z for Kinect used the unique gameplay abilities of the Kinect motion sensor to let gamers become part of the DBZ world. It features all the classic action and intensity of the Dragon Ball Z universe but with the unprecedented sense of immersion that only Kinect can deliver. Players will be able to unleash over 100 moves upon their enemies, including the legendary Kamehameha, with their very own fists as they battle their way to victory in this ultimate evolution of the unstoppable franchise.<br><br>Dragon Ball Z For Kinect also packs a double dose of exclusive content for Dragon Ball Z fans! The game includes the Dragon Ball Z anime episode \"Episode of Bardock\" and will feature Bardock Super Saiyan as a playable character for the first time ever in the history of Dragon Ball Z video games.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=umM0jivA4cw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uCapMnuSWf0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/667277-dragon-ball-z-for-kinect/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dragon-Ball-Z-for-Kinect/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dragon-ball-z-kinect/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dragon-ball-z-for-kinect"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dragon Ball Wiki",
				"url":"http://dragonball.wikia.com/wiki/Dragon_Ball_Z_For_Kinect"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1161,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"Continue to work on your shape and health with this 2010 entry into EA Sports' fitness franchise. The EA Sports Active 2 fitness program delivers true fitness results by featuring an innovative wireless control system, powered by new leg and arm straps with motion sensors, a heart rate monitor to capture intensity, and a new online hub to track and share workout data. The product will make working out simple, effective and will go with you wherever you are.<br><br>The new EA Sports Active 2 innovative wireless control system gives users complete freedom of motion, making it even easier to get a workout that delivers great results. Using innovative heart rate detection technology, the heart rate monitor will help users monitor intensity, providing constant on-screen monitoring throughout the workout and tracking user data over time to optimize performance.<br><br>Kinect for Xbox 360 tracks full body movement with true 1:1 motion that will register exercises never before possible and create seamless workout experiences, without ever having to use a controller. Users will also have the ability to navigate workouts with voice and gesture recognition, which allows for a seamless, fluid workout experience. Additionally, users also have the ability to download new workouts and exercises to their Xbox 360 console through Xbox LIVE online entertainment network to keep their workouts fresh and maintain motivation.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9mGP-36Val4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U3iz0wEbcR4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ks5LRAadl7M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rFrY9utGA88"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HM3yeGhoB9k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/EA-Sports-Active-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ea-sports-active-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ea-sports-active-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1162,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Lionhead Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Fable: The Journey offers a whole new way to experience the deep storyline and picturesque world of Albion that fans have come to know and love. Set 50 years after the events of Fable III, this new version asks you to come to the aid of the mysterious Theresa, who thrusts you into an action-packed adventure full of dangerous enemies, hair-raising chases and humorous characters. Built from the ground up for Kinect, Fable: The Journey gives you the power to wield magic as a deadly weapon, defend yourself in combat and solve puzzles on your journey to becoming a hero.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Fragment of the Spire",
				"releaseDate":"2012/12/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Spire looms over Albion, a focus for all the magic in the world. Adventurers have often made the dangerous voyage across the sea to capture fragments of the Spire for themselves, as such shards are rumoured to possess great power. This artefact will increase the magical charge of your gauntlets, allowing you to cast more Bolt spells in combat."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Non-Fluffy Dice",
				"releaseDate":"2012/12/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Need to make a big decision, but can't make your mind up? Desperately longing for some backgammon? Unsure if your sneak attack will be successful? Dice are the answer! As well as letting you resolve all manner of dilemmas through the art of cleromancy, these swinging D20s will also grant extra Experience while travelling."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Pet Cluckling",
				"releaseDate":"2012/12/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This tiny chicken always longed for a life beyond the coop, to stretch her wings and take flight across Albion. Unfortunately, chickens aren't particularly good at flying, so she's been reduced to the life of a hitchhiker. Fulfil her dream by hanging her in your cart and you'll make her so happy that she'll occasionally lay an egg that will grant you bonus Experience."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Gauntlets of Force",
				"releaseDate":"2012/12/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Gauntlets of Force grant one free upgrade to your Push spell."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Gauntlets of the Shard",
				"releaseDate":"2012/12/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Gauntlets of the Shard grant one free upgrade to your Shard spell."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Gauntlets of Wisdom",
				"releaseDate":"2012/12/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Gauntlets of Wisdom increase the Experience gained in combat."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Gauntlets of Flame",
				"releaseDate":"2012/12/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Gauntlets of Flame grant one free upgrade to your Fireball spell."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Dangly Gnome",
				"releaseDate":"2012/12/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Albion was once awash with aggressive porcelain gnomes that came to life. This plague was finally eradicated by the Hero of Brightwall, and Albion's gnomes have once again been restored to silence. Or have they? If you get lonely during your travels, hang this fellow in your cart and find out!"
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Gauntlets of Bolt",
				"releaseDate":"2012/12/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Gauntlets of Bolt grant one free upgrade to your Bolt spell."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Wisp-in-a-Jar",
				"releaseDate":"2012/12/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A wisp is a haunted, restless soul, cursed to remain in our world long after its mortal flesh has rotted. As such, it seems the perfect thing to hang from the side of your cart, with only fragile glass keeping it sealed away. There's literally nothing that could go wrong with that arrangement. Your reward for this bravery? Extra health."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MmM67e_YU0M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u33lL8A8uFI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-WhW8v2au-Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xzraQ--uw-Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/632872-fable-the-journey/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fable-The-Journey/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fable-the-journey"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Fable Wiki",
				"url":"http://fable.wikia.com/wiki/Fable:_The_Journey"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1163,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Games"],
			"synopsis":"Fantastic Pets brings a world of adventure into the living room. Players start with four domestic animals -dog, cat, horse and lizard - that can be morphed into imaginative creations from mystical unicorns to ferocious dragons.<br><br>Kinect for Xbox 360 technology enables players to step inside the world and onto the screen where they can play and care for their pets. Voice recognition allows players to command their pet throughout mini-games and Talent Shows to reach the professional ranks of a Pet Trainer. Players can unlock news items and activities, in addition to taking pictures of themselves and their pet to share with family and friends.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Fantastic Pets Flight Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/03",
				"achievements":235,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Take to the skies with new customization options and a brand new activity. This pack includes new wings and new patterns to customize your pet in the pet database, then guide your pet through the clouds in the new 'Take Off!' activity."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NHIk6lLPvVk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KpFHyQeOIrw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fantastic-Pets/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fantastic-pets/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fantastic-pets"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1164,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["AMA Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Fighters Uncaged deliver to players the excitement of real fighting competitions, in addition to teaching players mixed martial arts techniques. Leveraging the Microsoft Kinect technology, Fighters Uncaged delivers players an immersive total-body combat experience. Players will be able to create 70 different strikes inspired by martial arts and compete in 21 different fighting environments such as rooftops, dark alleys, gritty city docks and abandoned church. Included are diverse opponents with unique fighting styles, devastating combos with voice-activated super strikes, opportunities to upgrade your character by unlocking new skills and a jump-in multiplayer feature to take your enemies down with your friends.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=43CjayM9KKI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y-00YRZm8Dw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=snicJqGEKBw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fighters-Uncaged/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fighters-Uncaged/walkthrough.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fighters-uncaged"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1165,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FarSight Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Game Party: In Motion offers players full-body motion control of in-game or Xbox 360 Avatar characters, using the motion-sensing technology of Kinect for Xbox 360 in a collection of 16 games.<br><br>Game Party: In Motion lets players engage in true-to-life motions with games appealing to people of all ability levels, ranging from sports like Hoop Shoot and Darts to arcade and party games including Rootbeer Tapper, Table Hockey and more. Players mimic the actions and gestures of real-life activities allowing them to move their arms, legs or full bodies in natural motions to control the game.<br><br>Game Party: In Motion also allows players to challenge friends head-to-head online over Xbox LIVE. In addition to online gameplay, Game Party: In Motion offers integration with Facebook, including the ability to post in-game Achievements onto the player's Facebook Wall and set automatic notifications to Facebook friends when they have started a game. With full Xbox 360 Avatar support, players can get even closer to the game by using their own likenesses.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gEerJ1Alcag"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bo9q9OPz7RI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VkWwrY5oXHA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Game-Party-In-Motion/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/game-party-in-motion/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/game-party-in-motion"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1166,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Lightning Fish"],
			"synopsis":"In Get Fit With Mel, the former Spice Girl will bring you real-time advice and feedback on several disciplines like dance fit, cardio, step, pump and tone and kickboxing.<br><br>The game also delivers a personal nutritional program (six meals plans and 140 recipes) totally aligned to your fitness workout.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Latin Beats",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"'Latin Beats' consists of 15 challenging dance workouts, which don't require any fitness equipment. Similar to the core dance exercises already in the game, these more advanced exercises implement improvement in co-ordination as well as fitness."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Exotic Location Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Add a touch of tranquility to your workouts with these new exotic workout locations."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Boot Camp",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"'Boot Camp' consists of 15 tough fitness exercises, which don't require any equipment. An intensive workout which further enhances the users level of fitness and stamina."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gWuGt2mDgXo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PApbBHzXihQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sG6A0v7e7DU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Get-Fit-With-Mel-B/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/get-fit-with-mel-b"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1167,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Zoe Mode"],
			"synopsis":"Get ready for those Summer Nights with a return to Rydell High! Grease utilizes the Kinect's motion sensor technologies to deliver the ultimate Grease experience. Sing, dance and party with Barry, Sandy and the rest of the Grease gang. Grease delivers the movie's signature choreography and legendary songs combined with today's motion-sensor technology so fans can dance and sing along to their favorite Grease tunes including iconic anthems like \"You're the One That I Want\", \"Greased Lightning\" and \"Summer Nights\". Grease allows players to sing or dance as a solo act, in a duet or four players can team up to sing and dance together for a sensational musical performance.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8O5f8pd7BtE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PaGBHSB2urg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PVZ8orZ9XWE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Grease-Dance/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/grease-dance"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1168,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Twisted Pixel"],
			"synopsis":"Twisted Pixel Games, creators of The Maw, Splosion Man and Comic Jumper, proudly present The Gunstringer! This is an all-new type of Kinect game where you'll puppeteer a fiery gun-toting marionette through his adventures. The Gunstringer combines solo platforming and shooting mechanics into unique, competitive action with a full suite of collectables, unlockables, abilities, rewards and more.<br><br>Along with the disc for The Gunstringer, the retail package will include a token code for the full downloadable version of Fruit Ninja Kinect via Xbox Live. Fruit Ninja Kinect brings the worldwide mobile gaming phenomenon to Kinect so you can use your arms as blades in an epic battle against the world's most delicious produce.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Wavy Tube Man Chronicles",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/19",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"This completely live-action interactive shooter features Wavy Tube Man Jr., who has stolen a time machine to prevent his father's death at the hands of the Gunstringer. Shot on location with classic western and futuristic sets, this DLC pack features quick-drawing cowboys, heavily armed future warriors, and a final showdown against Wavy Tube Man Jr. himself. Players use Kinect-based targeting, shooting, and more to chase the villain through time, the fate of the world hanging in the balance."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Real Big Shootin'",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/15",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Git yer gun and ammo up for some Real Big Shootin'! Take your high-powered weaponry out on the range and get you some hunting, 'Merica-style. Each hunting round features different weapons, locations, and wildlife to splatter. Tally high scores on your own or grab a friend to compete in alternate round play. This DLC pack pays tribute to several shooting classics of yesteryear."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"El Diablo's 'Merican Adventure",
				"releaseDate":"2012/03/13",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"This shooting-gallery themed DLC pack features El Diablo, the Lady of the Dead's husband, as its hero marionette. El Diablo shoots his way through a wide variety of full pop-up gallery environments based on the retail game, along with all-new sets including the Baron's oil platform and the Madam's bedroom and ballroom. Players will need sharp reflexes and accuracy as they use a variety of weapons to blast and burn their way through El Diablo's adventure."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PGpVEruw3M4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7oqweiFsqrw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IomJRdijMYA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Gunstringer/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-gunstringer/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-gunstringer"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1169,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Heavy Iron Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Harley Pasternak's Hollywood Workout gives you direct access to the workout program that Hollywood celebrities use to get in shape! Harley Pasternak is a renowned fitness and nutrition expert, best-selling author, acclaimed celebrity trainer, and TV personality. And now Harley himself is your own personal trainer who will help you reach your fitness goals with his signature 5-Factor program. Run, jump, squat, and work out with Harley in just 25 minutes a day, five days a week. Monitor your progress with Harley's personalized feedback and nutritional tips. Get into red carpet shape with the Hollywood Workout that sculpts the bodies of the stars!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tPnDrWNKF0Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CyAfrmV4BFY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Harley-Pasternaks-Hollywood-Workout/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/harley-pasternaks-hollywood-workout/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1170,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eurocom"],
			"synopsis":"Based on all eight Harry Potter films, Harry Potter for Kinect allows players to join Harry Potter, Ron Weasley and Hermione Granger as they embark on an unforgettable journey through Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry and beyond. With Kinect's scanning technology, for the first time ever in a Harry Potter game, players will be able to scan in their own face to create a unique witch or wizard to journey through the adventures of the film.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OXizEuYzLRI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a0Dl-UQYeRw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rcgeEeD-REY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Harry-Potter-for-Kinect/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/harry-potter-kinect/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/harry-potter-for-kinect"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Harry Potter Wiki",
				"url":"http://harrypotter.wikia.com/wiki/Harry_Potter_for_Kinect"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1171,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["iNiS"],
			"synopsis":"Drop it like it's hot with hip-hop's hottest dance game. The Hip-Hop Dance Experience is the first authentic hip-hop game in the dance category. Dance to the most popular tracks of the genre with original moves designed by the most famous hip-hop choreographers in the industry. Trigger lavish visual effects worthy of the best music videos and avatar customization unique in the market. Experience the world of hip-hop through music, dance and design with The Hip-Hop Dance Experience.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q7slb288O34"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Aj7RCQMMR0Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Hip-Hop-Dance-Experience/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-hip-hop-dance-experience"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1172,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the global television game show phenomenon, Hole in the Wall Deluxe Edition is a game where players must contort their bodies to fit through bizarrely shaped holes in themed moving walls hurtling toward them. The video game will feature three different modes: practice alone on one of the 800 different walls in show mode, play survival mode and attack wall after wall until you drop, or compare your skills with other competitors in an online multiplayer \"Last-man standing\" mode where up to 10 players can put their skills to the test simultaneously.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hole-in-the-Wall-Deluxe-Edition/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hole-in-the-wall-deluxe/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hole-in-the-wall-deluxe-edition"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1173,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Panic Button"],
			"synopsis":"Utilizing the Kinect motion sensor, Hulk Hogan's Main Event is the first performance-based wrestling game, letting players train with mentor Hulk Hogan as they build their own wrestling personalities and learn the art of showmanship to win over the crowd. Players will learn the ropes from the man himself as Hulk Hogan schools them on delivering the best show for the crowd by emulating famous Hulk poses and performing more than 30 punishing combos. The Kinect sensor tracks players' every move; the more dynamic the motion, the more high impact the wrestler's performance is. Players will create their own unique wrestler personality through a robust create-a-wrestler feature including many choices for face, hair, tattoos, outfit, ethnicity, body type, and entrance music. Perform in nine different venues including the backyard brawl, local gym and giant stadium in front of a massive audience. Enter tournament mode for two player tag-team and take turns delivering extreme moves. Best of all, players can wield a variety of damaging objects including metal chairs and ladders to deliver bone-jarring hits to their opponents.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pgXyMDo_N1Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U_ynm-gZEPY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hulk-Hogan-Main-Event/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hulk-hogans-main-event/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hulk-hogans-main-event"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1174,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Behaviour Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Prepare for ice-cold competition in Ice Age: Continental Drift -- Arctic Games. A secret treasure has fallen into the hands of the Ice Age gang and trouble has stirred over the glaciers as to who will keep the prized riches. Naturally, the best way to settle the score is through a series of wintery sporting events! Join the jolly 'Herd' or the mischievous 'Pirates' to compete in the first ever Arctic Games to determine who can land their paws on the prize. Play as Manny, Diego, Sid, and other prehistoric pals in competitive games like glacier hopping, ski jumping, and squirrel cannon. Gamers can compete through story mode, free play, and tournament style games to reach for new records and earn gold, silver, and bronze acorn medals. Ice Age: Continental Drift -- Arctic Games is perfect for gamers of all ages to get together and laugh their way through silly competition. It's time to team up with your favorite sub-zero friend and go for the gold!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ilStCxz9-yU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZMA8wvdgdsA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ice-Age-Continental-Drift--Arctic-Games/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ice-age-continental-drift---arctic-games"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1175,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["n-Space"],
			"synopsis":"Get ready to use your entire body this time as players join Jillian Michaels on an interactive adventure, which of course is also filled with Jillian's trademark intensity! Using the Kinect motion sensor, Jillian Michaels' Fitness Adventure takes your fitness routine beyond a basic workout and turns it into a real adventure through a mission-based, thrill-seeking journey set in a lush jungle temple environment. The high-energy and fully customizable motion-based experience offers a results-oriented personal training experience that you can expect from teaming up with Jillian to achieve your fitness goals.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uYVlX-aqFsM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VNwQ3Cb8T0Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Jillian-Michaels-Fitness-Adventure/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/jillian-michaels-fitness-adventure"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1176,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Paris"],
			"synopsis":"The world's #1 dance game is back -- and now, you can play it with the Kinect! Just Dance 3 for the Kinect kick-starts the party with over 40 tracks from multiple genres and popular artists including today's hottest hits like \"Party Rock Anthem\" by LMFAO, \"California Gurls\" by Katy Perry featuring Snoop Dogg, and \"Forget You\" by Cee Lo Green. Also included are legendary favorites like \"I Was Made For Lovin' You\" by Kiss.<br><br>And for the first time ever, dance simultaneously with four players for the ultimate dance party experience! Not only does Just Dance 3 include everyone's favorite game modes, but it also offers several Kinect-exclusive features that take advantage of the unique Kinect technology: Just Create, Shout Out, Online Sharing, and more!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Heart of Glass",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/07",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Heart of Glass\" - Blondie. Written by Deborah Harry and Chris Stein."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Fame",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/07",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Fame\" In the Style of Irene Cara. Written by Michael Gore and Dean Pitchford."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"U Can't Touch This",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/07",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"U Can't Touch This\" - Groove Century. Written by Rick James, Alonzo Miller and Stanley Burrell."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Jin Go Lo Ba",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/08",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Jin Go Lo Ba\" - Fatboy Slim. Written by Michael Olatunji."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Satisfaction (Isak Original Extended)",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/08",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Satisfaction\" - Benni Benassi. Written by A.Benassi."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Jump in the Line",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/08",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Jump in the Line\" - The Sunlight Shakers. Written by Raymond Bell, Ralph de Leon, Gabriel Oller and Steve Samuel."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Cosmic Girl",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/08",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Cosmic Girl\" - Jamiroquai. Written by Jason Kay, Toby Smith, Stuart Zender,Derrick McKenzie, Wallis Buchanan and Simon Katz."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Jump",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/22",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Jump\" - Studio Allstars. Written by Deke Richards, Alphonso Mizell, Freddie Perren, Berry Gordy Jr., Jermaine Dupri, Marshall Jones, Leroy Bonner, Clarence Satchell, Norman Napier, Andrew Noland, Marvin Pierce, Gregory Webster, Walter Morrison and Ralph Middlebrooks."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Acceptable in the 80's",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/22",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Acceptable in the 80's\" - Calvin Harris. Written by Adam Wiles."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Proud Mary",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/22",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Proud Mary\" - Ike & Tina Turner. Written by John. C. Fogerty. "
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Toxic",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/22",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Toxic\" - The Hit Crew Written by Cathy Dennis, Christian Karlsson, Henrik Jonback and Pontus Winnberg."
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Baby Girl",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/06",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Baby Girl\" - Reggaeton. Written by Joachim Svare (ASCAP) and Carsten Lindberg (BMI)."
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"Walk Like an Egyptian",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/06",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Walk Like an Egyptian\" - Bangles. Written by Liam Sternberg."
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"Mashed Potato Time",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/06",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Mashed Potato Time\" - Dee Dee Sharp. Written by Robert Bateman, Kalman Cohen, William Garrett, Brian Holland, Freddie Gorman and Georgia Dobbins."
			},
			{
				"id":15,
				"name":"Iko Iko",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/06",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Iko Iko\" - Mardi Gras. Written by James Crawford, Barbara Hawkins, Rosa Hawkins and Joan Johnson."
			},
			{
				"id":16,
				"name":"Step By Step",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/20",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Step by Step\" - New Kids On The Block. Written by Larry Curtis Johnson."
			},
			{
				"id":17,
				"name":"Funplex (CSS Remix)",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/20",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Funplex (CSS Remix)\" - The B-52s. Written by Fred Schneider, Kate Pierson, Keith Strickland and Cindy Wilson."
			},
			{
				"id":18,
				"name":"Crazy Christmas",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/20",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Crazy Christmas\" - Santa Clones. Contains samples of \"Jingle Bells 2\" by O. Sieben and J. Pierpont, \"O Christmas Surf\" by R. Abernethy, \"We Wish U A Merry Skaristmas\" by D. Martin, \"Country Bells\" by R. Vilas and \"We Wish You An Indie Christmas\" by Backer, Taylor and Emanuel."
			},
			{
				"id":19,
				"name":"Louie Louie",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/20",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Louie Louie\" - Iggy Pop. Written by Richard Berry."
			},
			{
				"id":20,
				"name":"Dun N Dusted",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/03",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Dun N Dusted\" - Sweat Invaders. Written by Jason Creasey."
			},
			{
				"id":21,
				"name":"Beat Match Until I'm Blue",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/03",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Beat Match Until I'm Blue\" - Sweat Invaders. Written by Alan Hawkshaw (PRS) and Andrew Kingslow (PRS)."
			},
			{
				"id":22,
				"name":"Touch Me Want Me",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/03",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Touch Me Want Me\" - Sweat Invaders. Written by Chunky Nelson (PRS). "
			},
			{
				"id":23,
				"name":"Cardiac Caress",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/17",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Cardiac Caress\" - Sweat Invaders. Written by Richardson, Ford and Macklin. "
			},
			{
				"id":24,
				"name":"Who Let the Dogs Out?",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/17",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Who Let the Dogs Out?\" - Baha Men. Written by Anslem Douglas."
			},
			{
				"id":25,
				"name":"Boomsday",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/17",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Boomsday\" - Sweat Invaders. Written by Junkie XL."
			},
			{
				"id":26,
				"name":"Merengue",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/17",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Merengue\" - Sweat Invaders. Written by Chucho Merchan."
			},
			{
				"id":27,
				"name":"Why Oh Why",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/31",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Why Oh Why\" - Love Letter. Written by S. Huguenin, C. Padovan and Y. Sanna. "
			},
			{
				"id":28,
				"name":"Skin-To-Skin",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/31",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Skin-To-Skin\" - Sweat Invaders. Written by H. Langschwert."
			},
			{
				"id":29,
				"name":"Katti Kalandal",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/31",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Katti Kalandal\" - Bollywood. Written by Veilumuth Chitralekha (NS) and Tony Tape (GEMA)."
			},
			{
				"id":30,
				"name":"The Power",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/31",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"The Power\" - Snap! Written by Benito Benites, John \"Virgo\" Garrett III and Antoinette Colandreo."
			},
			{
				"id":31,
				"name":"That's the Way (I Like It)",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/14",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"That's the Way (I Like It)\" - KC and the Sunshine Band. Written by Harry Wayne Casey and Richard Finch."
			},
			{
				"id":32,
				"name":"Mugsy Baloney",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/14",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Mugsy Baloney\" - Charleston. Written by Gert Wilson."
			},
			{
				"id":33,
				"name":"Rasputin",
				"releaseDate":"2012/02/14",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Rasputin\" - Boney M. Written by Frank Farian, Fred Jay, George Reyam."
			},
			{
				"id":34,
				"name":"Dare",
				"releaseDate":"2012/03/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Dare\" - Gorillaz. Written by Damon Albarn, Jamie Hewlett and Brian Burton."
			},
			{
				"id":35,
				"name":"Professeur Pumplestickle",
				"releaseDate":"2012/03/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Professor Pumplestickle\" - Nick Phoenix and Thomas Bergersen."
			},
			{
				"id":36,
				"name":"Down By The Riverside",
				"releaseDate":"2012/03/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Down By The Riverside\" - The Reverend Horatio Duncan & Amos Sweets."
			},
			{
				"id":37,
				"name":"Kids in America",
				"releaseDate":"2012/03/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Kids in America\" - Kim Wilde. Written by Marty Wilde and Ricky Wilde."
			},
			{
				"id":38,
				"name":"Alright",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/24",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Alright\" - Supergrass. Written by Daniel Goffey, Gareth Coombes and Michael Quinn."
			},
			{
				"id":39,
				"name":"Dagomba",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/24",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Dagomba\" - Sorcerer. Composed by Tom Salta."
			},
			{
				"id":40,
				"name":"Futebol Crazy",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/24",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"Futebol Crazy\" - The World Cup Girls. Written by P. J. Borg."
			},
			{
				"id":41,
				"name":"It's Raining Men",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/24",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Download \"It's Raining Men\" - The Weather Girls. Written by Paul Jabara and Paul Shaffer."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I7v7_dbAqFw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RfjZiSNLEJc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F8lrwcDC75E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YZ6uFgegK4A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Just-Dance-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Just-Dance-3/walkthrough.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/just-dance-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Just Dance Wiki",
				"url":"http://justdance.wikia.com/wiki/Just_Dance_3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1177,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Land Ho!"],
			"synopsis":"For the first time Just Dance and Disney are bringing together the greatest dance game for the whole Family - Just Dance: Disney Party. Dance like the star of Disney Channel's hottest shows and beloved Disney Movie Classics. With a great selection of 25 including hits from Disney Channel's hottest shows and songs from beloved Disney Movie Classics, fun choreographies and a kid-friendly gameplay, children of all ages can Just Dance along with family and friends!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h4LnB47GPZE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QKWp3pXkCqI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Just-Dance-Disney-Party/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/just-dance-disney-party"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Just Dance Wiki",
				"url":"http://justdance.wikia.com/wiki/Just_Dance:_Disney_Party"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1178,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft"],
			"synopsis":"Experience Just Dance Greatest Hits, the only collection that includes the most popular tracks from the Just Dance franchise! Start the party, battle with friends, or even exercise in disguise to hit songs from Katy Perry, Rihanna, Beastie Boys, and Ke$ha - 35 tracks in all! Kinect for Xbox 360 players can dance along for the first time to classic hits from Just Dance and Just Dance 2. It's the ultimate way to discover - or rediscover - America's best-selling dance game brand.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iejeUfbi0FA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AaWSXierJsg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iKtPzamCMAE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Just-Dance-Greatest-Hits/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/just-dance-greatest-hits"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Just Dance Wiki",
				"url":"http://justdance.wikia.com/wiki/Just_Dance:_Greatest_Hits"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1179,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft"],
			"synopsis":"Just Dance, is now FOR KIDS! With a selection of over 40 of their favorite songs, crazy fun dance moves and all-new kid-friendly game play, children of all ages will get up and move to the beat. Dance to favorite nursery rhymes remixed to fun dance beats, popular songs from The Wiggles and Yo Gabba Gabba! TV shows, the biggest pop hits of today, and family dance favorites. Now everyone can Just Dance! Dances that KIDS of All Ages Will Love!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ej3pZWV8KOk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Just-Dance-Kids/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Just Dance Wiki",
				"url":"http://justdance.wikia.com/wiki/Just_Dance_Kids"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1180,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft"],
			"synopsis":"The coolest dance experience for kids is back -- Just Dance Kids 2, now for play with Kinect! Featuring 40 fun and crazy dance routines to kids favorite songs, including hits from today's most popular artists, TV shows and movies. Just Dance Kids 2 gets kids of all ages up and dancing with colorful graphics, super-fun dance moves, and kid-friendly gameplay!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OybOAWAFEg4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4eo-Y9xJmkA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Just-Dance-Kids-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/just-dance-kids-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Just Dance Wiki",
				"url":"http://justdance.wikia.com/wiki/Just_Dance_Kids_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1181,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Good Science Studio"],
			"synopsis":"Float in outer space. Experience the thrill of roaring rapids. Tackle mountaintop obstacle courses. And dive into the deep to explore a leaky underwater observatory -- all from your living room. With Kinect Adventures, you are the controller as you jump, dodge and kick your way through exciting adventures set in a variety of exotic locations.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K_4zx5af4C4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pwBQ7Fyw77c"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/997630-kinect-adventures/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kinect-Adventures/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kinect-adventures/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kinect-adventures!"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1182,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Frontier Developments", "Disney Interactive Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Harnessing the controller-free magic of Kinect for Xbox 360, Kinect: Disneyland Adventures allows children, families and Disney fans of all ages to explore Disneyland park, step into adventures based on attractions, engage in challenging quests and interact with beloved Disney characters using their full bodies and voices, no controller required. Kinect: Disneyland Adventures is your portal to a magical world of Disneyland park adventures through Kinect.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v7DXR_Y1UAE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Ohnv2cSFWA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_TZgexShoTA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hm8WGYeyD28"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/632874-kinect-disneyland-adventures/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Disneyland-Adventures/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kinect-disneyland-adventures/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kinect-disneyland-adventures"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1183,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["BigPark Inc."],
			"synopsis":"Kinect Joy Ride takes you and your friends on the ride of your lives -- no drivers license required. Kinect Joy Ride reinvents driving and Kart racing by adding massive jumps and full body stunts to the classic Kart racing action. With a host of cool features and game modes you can take off for the ride of your life by yourself, pick up a co-pilot or team up with your friends and family to take on the world.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Chevrolet Car Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/04",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Take your ride to the next level with the exclusive Chevrolet Car Pack for Kinect Joy Ride."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mbarl85A7NA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KZJKNU3eS5k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kinect-Joy-Ride/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kinect-joy-ride/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kinect-joy-ride"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1184,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Relentless Software"],
			"synopsis":"A ground-breaking interactive experience developed as part of Microsoft \"playful learning\" initiative, Kinect Nat Geo TV uses Kinect to combine motion-control with augmented reality. It mixes high-quality National Geographic television shows with fun-packed Xbox 360 Kinect motion-controlled game play.<br><br>With Kinect Nat Geo TV, you're not only gaming and you're not only watching TV -- living rooms are turned into animal habitats and players into a variety of animals! And all along, players are inspired to learn and care about the planet. Kinect Nat Geo goes beyond what a TV show can do: it is a totally immersive experience for parents and kids.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1LuNFlDl36Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vXSzo8hl8H0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kinect-Nat-Geo-TV/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kinect-nat-geo-tv/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kinect-nat-geo-tv"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1185,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Asobo Studio"],
			"synopsis":"Kinect Rush: A Disney Pixar Adventure invites families and fans of all ages to experience the worlds of five beloved Disney/Pixar films like never before! Through the magic of Kinect for Xbox 360, scan yourself into the game to become a unique character in five Pixar worlds. Team up with characters from The Incredibles, Ratatouille, Up, Cars and Toy Story to solve puzzles and uncover hidden secrets.<br><br>For the first time in Kinect history, you and your favorite Pixar character can interact on screen and play cooperatively to solve challenges. Use your voice and body to seamlessly move from fast-paced puzzle-solving to moments of pulse-pounding agility and speed.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b0T9ACRuLaM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZMgzZO0hGIk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kinect-Rush/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kinect-rush/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kinect-rush-a-disney-pixar-adventure"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1186,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Soho Productions"],
			"synopsis":"A ground-breaking interactive experience developed as part of Microsoft \"playful learning\" initiative, Kinect Sesame Street TV uses Kinect to combine motion-control with augmented reality. It mixes high-quality Sesame Street television shows with fun-packed Xbox 360 Kinect motion-controlled game play.<br><br>With Kinect Sesame Street TV, children are invited to experience the world of Sesame Street alongside their favorite characters such as Big Bird, Grover, Cookie Monster and Elmo like never before. The magic of Kinect for Xbox 360 lets you share in the experience through visual and physical interactions with characters of Sesame Street, placing you in the Sesame Street experience.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6yvZLsWdkUo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iSs2MYHATCI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kinect-Sesame-Street-TV/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kinect-sesame-street-tv/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kinect-sesame-street-tv"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1187,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rare"],
			"synopsis":"Turn your living room into a world-class stadium, bowling alley, soccer pitch or arena. With Kinect Sports you're not only the star player, you are the controller -- through the magic of Kinect for Xbox 360. See a ball? Kick it. Spike it. Even give it a little top spin.<br><br>Kinect Sports is so real, you will almost feel the wind in your hair as you fly over hurdles and the sand in your toes as you set, bump and spike your way to volleyball victory. The game features six full sports -- Soccer, Beach Volleyball, Track & Field, Boxing, Bowling and Table Tennis -- and boasts a Team vs. Team mode, allowing the whole family to play in a fast-paced tournament style competition.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Party Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/14",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Brought to you by Samsung! Shake your hips and move your feet with six brand new mini games: Super Striker, Pinvaders, Rapid Runner, Target Smash, Fruit Splatter and King of the Ring. Get the Kinect Sports party started with new Party Play games and three additional crazy mascots: Zippy Zombie, Champion Chicken and Sportastico!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Calorie Challenge Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/26",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Get fighting fit the Kinect Sports way! Hit calorie-loss targets by beating mascot rivals in the Calorie Challenge Pack: Steady Celery, Blazing Banana, Mighty Milk, Super Soda, Peppy Pizza and Chunky Chocolate. Also includes Free Play mode and 10 achievements for 250 gamerscore, with food mascots selectable in Party Play."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zw2Fo9k96hc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=clPu2b4qzfI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WT3tSU3nUxc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5H5BQlbrym0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b3n7VNezxqw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/997628-kinect-sports/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kinect-Sports/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kinect-sports/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kinect-sports"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1188,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rare", "BigPark Inc."],
			"synopsis":"Kinect Sports: Season Two sprints out the box with six new sports and exciting new features that take full advantage of the revolutionary Kinect technology. The second season brings families and the world together like never before with the addition of Challenge Play to Xbox LIVE and harnesses the power of friendly competition to provide a more immersive experience for everyone from casual players to top-notch athletes.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Challenge Pack #1",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/07",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Discover new ways to play Kinect Sports: Season Two with more game modes and challenges to send to friends. Each sport receives a standout new experience: Crazy Kicker (Football), Frantic Fielder (Baseball), Cool Ringings (Skiing), Champion Chip (Golf), Rapid Returner (Tennis) and Smart Shot (Darts)."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Two Maple Lakes Golf Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/20",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Double your Golf fun in Kinect Sports: Season Two with nine new holes, playable in all modes with achievements and new challenges to send to friends. Swing to win past forts, marinas, causeways and coves, finding hidden routes and hole-in-one opportunities. Attempt an 18-hole course match, the ultimate Golfing gauntlet!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Midnight Mountain Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/01/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"If throwing yourself downhill in broad daylight isn't exciting enough, this pack of floodlit Skiing runs for Kinect Sports: Season Two will get your heart racing. Midnight Mountain delivers three icy cool new slopes playable in all modes with new challenges to send to friends, plus all the trimmings!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Challenge Pack #2",
				"releaseDate":"2012/03/01",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Presented by Bengay. Kinect Sports: Season Two gets another free serving of fantastic new game modes and challenges to send to friends! Throw yourself headlong into Receiver Fever (Football), Top Jumps (Skiing), Darts Vs Zombies (Darts), Pitcher Perfect (Baseball), Prize Driver (Golf) and Red Rally, Yellow Rally (Tennis)."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Basketball Challenge Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2012/04/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Basketball fever takes hold of Kinect Sports: Season Two! Get a feel for the court with three fast-paced activities designed to hone your passing, shot timing and long-range basket skills: Alley-Oop Dreams, Shot Party and 3-Point Hero. All playable solo or in multiplayer, Quick Play or Challenge Play!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m2TB5YOKDyI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NhCvPlphtS0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YHDXc566vhU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iYs0VhdO6dA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kinect-Sports-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kinect-sports-season-two/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kinect-sports-season-two"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1189,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Terminal Reality", "LucasArts"],
			"synopsis":"Get ready to enter the Star Wars universe in an entirely new way. Featuring iconic settings, characters and action, Kinect Star Wars puts you in the Star Wars you know and love, and lets you unleash your inner Jedi -- with no controller in the way.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Aurra Sing",
				"releaseDate":"2012/07/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Play as Aurra Sing in Jedi Destiny mode."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Snow Rancor",
				"releaseDate":"2012/07/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Play as the Snow Rancor in Rancor Rampage."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Korriban Rancor",
				"releaseDate":"2012/07/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Play as the Korriban Rancor in Rancor Rampage."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Kit Fisto",
				"releaseDate":"2012/07/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Play as Kit Fisto in Jedi Destiny mode."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vrZN5K7JwVM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wWbQTBa5c2E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cb8-520zEhc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T6L8ieJ_cfo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/997652-kinect-star-wars/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kinect-Star-Wars/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/star-wars-kinect/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kinect-star-wars"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1190,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Frontier Developments"],
			"synopsis":"A wide-eyed Bengal tiger cub cocks its head to the side and playfully peers at you. Memories of your first trip to the zoo come rushing back. Through the magic of Kinect that furry tiger cub is in your living room and about to become your best friend...<br><br>Kinectimals invites children, their parents and animal lovers of all ages to build lasting friendships with some of the world's most exotic creatures. Just like real pets, your Kinectimals will come running when they hear your voice, respond to commands like jump, roll-over and play dead, and purr with joy when you scratch them behind the ears.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Saber-Tooth Tiger (Plush)",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Purchase this cub to unlock it in the game."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Jaguar",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Purchase this cub to unlock it in the game."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"White Tiger",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Purchase this cub to unlock it in the game."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Asiatic Cheetah",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Purchase this cub to unlock it in the game."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"African Lion (Plush)",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Purchase this cub to unlock it in the game."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Golden Tabby Tiger",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Purchase this cub to unlock it in the game."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Iberian Lynx",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Purchase this cub to unlock it in the game."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Canadian Lynx",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Purchase this cub to unlock it in the game."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Bornean Clouded Leopard (Plush)",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Purchase this cub to unlock it in the game."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Asiatic Lion",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Purchase this cub to unlock it in the game."
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Kinectimals: Now with BEARS!",
				"releaseDate":"2011/10/11",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Explore a whole new island and mystery in the Kinectimals add-on Bear Island. Adopt a black bear, grizzly bear, cinnamon bear, panda bear or polar bear, and meet many more bears along your adventure! With your friendly cub and new guide Lina, you will embark on a journey across the mysterious island of Mira, solving Fiddler's Quest. Along the way, you and your cub will discover new ways to play together--juggling, climbing trees, fishing and much more!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F5PHRGnBM44"
			},
			{
				"type":"Kinectimals: Now with Bears! Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-kN6ngN87ck"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m9OVNwIqSEU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kinectimals/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kinectimals/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kinectimals"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1191,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft"],
			"synopsis":"With an all-new tracklist of kids' favorite songs, featuring brand new dances made with kids in mind, and exclusive kid-friendly features, children of all ages can Just Dance along with the rest of the family!<br><br>With Just Create mode, kids use Xbox Kinect to take the lead in their very own music video! They'll be able to create their own dance routines and challenge friends! Now you're the star!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SNoGz-ER0bU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nYsFpZl-w3U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uJXbno-QwVw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Just-Dance-Kids-2014/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Just Dance Wiki",
				"url":"http://justdance.wikia.com/wiki/Just_Dance_Kids_2014"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1192,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Virtual Air Guitar Company"],
			"synopsis":"Kung Fu High Impact is the first of its kind for Kinect for Xbox 360--a side-scrolling brawler that uses the peripheral's incredibly accurate body tracking technology to insert the real image of the player on screen. The gamer will be literally transported into the action, as he or she will be able to see real-life combat movements interacting with the enemies and objects on screen.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7a0HEy5-wcw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jzVJ_2yEWLQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y0CNnYjzHj4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/KungFu-High-Impact/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kung-fu-high-impact/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kung-fu-high-impact"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1193,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["N-Fusion Interactive", "Curious Pictures"],
			"synopsis":"Deepak Chopra, the internationally renowned author and expert on mind-body wellness, brings his extraordinary creativity, insight and philosophies to an entirely new milieu: video games. Deepak Chopra's Leela is an extraordinary journey into the self, blending ancient philosophies with advanced home-entertainment technology.<br><br>Breaking the boundaries of what has ever been created for video-game systems, Leela is not a game -- it is a one-of-a-kind experience that invokes whole-body movement with meditation and breathing techniques to relax, stretch and control both body and spirit. At its foundation is the concept of the Seven Chakras, spiritual energy centers inside every human being. When these ever-spinning Chakras are aligned, the result is greater well-being, opening new avenues of possibility and personal fulfillment. Seven individual stages of Leela focus on these Chakras -- each offering successively more challenging experiences. Each area uses a different section of the body, and as each section is mastered, players have a greater understanding of how to bring these energy centers into alignment. There is no traditional winning or losing in Leela, just as there really is no beginning and end -- Leela moves at an individual's pace, and its only aim is to instill an inner sense of harmony and accomplishment. Whether experienced for two minutes or two hours at a time, whether utilized once a week or three times a day, Leela is an utterly unique concept that offers an incomparable interactive experience.<br><br>Using Kinect for Xbox 360, Leela also incorporates \"Stillness Meditation\", an activity that -- for the first time ever -- utilizes Kinect technology to display a real-time graphical representation of breathing, offering gentle feedback and guidance for a number of deep-breathing exercises.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N9h_VTIqcbU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_x_foicedKk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Leela/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/deepak-chopras-leela"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1194,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cat Daddy Games"],
			"synopsis":"Three loud cheers are in order as 2K Play introduces the sport of Cheerleading to Kinect for Xbox 360. Cheer enthusiasts will learn to master moves like the High V and jumps such as the Toe Touch, resulting in a controller-free, full-body cheerleading experience. Whether cheering on the field of a varsity football game or dancing their hearts out in a national cheerleading competition, players will be challenged to keep the beat, break a sweat and start earning spirit stars!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eKrn0t0gunQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jRs9ftHEJaA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tb5E0EIweZ4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lets-Cheer/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lets-cheer/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1195,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Lightning Fish"],
			"synopsis":"Wrap yourself up in the rich soundtrack of Let's Dance: move your body to the rhythm and have fun with all the different choreographies available in the game. In this party game, you can turn your living room into TV a talent show! Choose from a wide variety of dance styles: pop, club, '80s disco, latin, urban, and more!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5OPEmBE2x_k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XogebIaGlj0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lets-Dance-with-Mel-B/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lets-dance-with-mel-b"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1196,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"He is the legendary King of Pop! In this game, players step into the shoes of Michael Jackson himself and re-live his most iconic performances through their own singing and dancing. The game includes the most famous tracks from Michael Jackson's extensive catalog such as Beat It and Billie Jean, as well as an array of his awe-inspiring dance moves for players to learn and emulate within the game. Additionally, fans can sing along and test their vocal skills while immersed in the performance.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yLazho_drwk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y_i-XCDBn7E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Michael-Jackson-the-Experience/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/michael-jackson-the-game/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/michael-jackson-the-experience"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1197,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Games"],
			"synopsis":"Take a competitive sports journey with one of the most celebrated athletes in history through Michael Phelps: Push the Limit, the first controller-free swimming experience to capture your true movements and translate them into accurate gameplay. The game utilizes Kinect for Xbox 360's unique capabilities to let players go beyond the pool in one of the most realistic and intense sports simulations ever created. The entirely new gameplay mechanic lets players accurately master the action of gold medal swim strokes and learn techniques that help Michael Phelps dominate his sport. With one-hundredth of a second often the difference between winning and losing, every stroke's importance is amplified and the room for error is razor thin.<br><br>In Career Mode, players compete in successive tournaments and travel to some of the most breathtaking locales the sport has seen. Race in progressively more challenging competitions, trekking from heated outdoor pools set against icy mountain ranges, to a Japanese dojo, to a huge, 80,000 seat outdoor arena as Phelps guides players along the way with tips and tricks of the trade. The path to glory culminates with the Annual Games tournament where players can find themselves up against the best swimmers in the world -- including Michael Phelps!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Whk9CrNcN68"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=13-u-6f1zUc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Michael-Phelps-Push-the-Limit/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/michael-phelps-push-the-limit/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/michael-phelps-push-the-limit"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1198,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SDP Games"],
			"synopsis":"Tackle unique challenges as you compete to win $1,000,000 in NBC s hit game show, Minute to Win It . With encouragement from All-American chef and host Guy Fieri, you will compete in series of simple, yet intimidating games that can lead you to a $1 million prize! The everyday household items used in each 60-second challenge may seem harmless, but it will take nerves of steel to conquer all 10 tasks. So be careful, because when that minute is up, so is your chance of winning.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QabKvdVZVZ0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wOJYgbY7wwY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Minute-To-Win-It/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1199,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Milan"],
			"synopsis":"MotionSports is a new sports title exclusive to Microsoft's Kinect that will bring players unparalleled immersion, as the movements they make in real-time are accurately represented by the on-screen athletes. Exciting sports challenges include skiing, horseback riding, hang gliding, football, soccer and boxing.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qPqxEpIMkOo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2nXQVcinjBw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MotionSports/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/motionsports"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":1200,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Milan"],
			"synopsis":"Make a name for yourself in the world of extreme sports! Try your hand at multiple crazy extreme sports and pose as a superstar phenomenon by challenging your friends in exciting competitions.<br><br>Motionsports Adrenaline will allow you, your friends and family to take part in extreme activities you would never dream of attempting in real life. From the peaks of the Himalayas to the waterfalls of the Amazon, this is the chance to release your inner daredevil. So one question remains: Will you take the challenge?",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Urban Jungle",
				"releaseDate":"2011/12/13",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"It's time to get your Adrenaline pumping even further with more tracks, challenges and outfits in this DLC pack - brought to you in partnership with Degree Men. Now you can put on a new wingsuit and weave at incredible speed through a metropolis filled with skyscrapers as if you were in blockbuster movie. Test your reactions along an intense South American urban mountain biking course, or take on the wildest rapids and waterfalls yet on a brand new whitewater kayak river challenge. All the courses are designed to test your reactions and co-ordination to the limit as you jump, duck, lean and paddle like crazy to get the best possible scores."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nYjfVdT4EkA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WAye8vw2NRc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MotionSports-Adrenaline/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/motionsports-adrenaline"
			}]
		}
	}]
}