{
	"catalog": [
	{
		"id":301,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Fun Labs"],
			"synopsis":"Cabela's Dangerous Hunts 2009 puts players in bone chilling, pressure-packed hunting situations as they seek out savage animals in the world's most dangerous locations.<br><br>Players will face raw danger as they encounter the fiercest animals on earth, including lions, grizzly bears, jaguars and more. Accurately modeled Cabela's equipment in the game means the firearms, tactics and gear are all realistic and precise - but this won't always help in the face of an unpredictable, open environment packed with avalanches, elephant stampedes, and piranha infested waters. If you do miss a shot and fail to stop a charging man-eating animal, you will be forced to fight it via a melee defense - but pay attention; it's likely another nearby animal will join the attack.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B-tgkCtfp0A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W_u4aKcczsU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cabelas-Dangerous-Hunts-2009/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cabelas-dangerous-hunts-09/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cabelas-dangerous-hunts-2009"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":302,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Traveller's Tales"],
			"synopsis":"From the creators of LEGO Star Wars, LEGO Batman: The Videogame brings the one-and-only Caped Crusader to life in a completely original storyline. Players will take control of the Dynamic Duo, Batman (Bruce Wayne) and Robin, as well as bonus hero Nightwing to fight Gotham City's most notorious criminals including The Joker, The Penguin, Catwoman, Scarecrow, and many more. Players can also explore their wicked side and fight their way through the game as the villains, experiencing the game from a completely different point of view with all-new criminal objectives.<br><br>With a collection of high-tech suits, gadgets and cutting-edge vehicles on hand, players are able to step into the unique LEGO Batman universe to bring super villains to justice - or, as the villains, to run amok in Gotham City.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x52K4e-LP_o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_lkIw8Z2c5s"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943952-lego-batman-the-videogame/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/LEGO-Batman/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lego-batman/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lego-batman-the-videogame"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Brickipedia",
				"url":"http://lego.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Batman:_The_Videogame"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Lego Batman Wiki",
				"url":"http://legobatman.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Batman_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":303,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Omega Force"],
			"synopsis":"Warriors Orochi is a crossover of two historical action epics, Dynasty Warriors and Samurai Warriors. In the game, Orochi the king of demons has merged together in time the Sengoku and Sangokushi periods in an attempt at world domination. The heroes of both Dynasty and Samurai Warriors must now fight together to defeat Orochi and his demon followers.<br><br>In addition to generals from both franchises, totalling over 70 playable characters in all, Warriors Orochi adds a new feature to gameplay: team battles with up to three team members. You can switch off between the three members as you take on the hundreds of enemies that line the fields and castles of the strange world created by the Orochi.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dCBKDrYSYjk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=adgAUdeNH4c"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/946499-warriors-orochi-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Warriors-Orochi-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/warriors-orochi-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/warriors-orochi-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Koei Wiki",
				"url":"http://koei.wikia.com/wiki/Warriors_Orochi_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":304,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Double Helix", "Konami"],
			"synopsis":"Silent Hill: Homecoming marks the sixth story in the Silent Hill mythos, and introduces a new protagonist to the mysterious town. The story follows Alex Shepherd, returning to his hometown of Shepherd's Glen to investigate the sudden disappearance of his brother and the strange occurrences taking place around town. Shepherd unravels a tale that takes him from his boyhood home to the fog-shrouded streets of Silent Hill, facing the darkest horrors of his soul to find his missing brother.<br><br>This game features all-new graphics that bring the fear and terror of Silent Hill alive like never before. Alex must survive the terrible denizens of Silent Hill using an all-new enhanced combat system that provides a wide array of attacks and counters. Along the way, Alex will encounter a variety of weapons to battle these horrific monsters and solve deadly puzzles, discovering the darkest secrets of Silent Hill. Silent Hill: Homecoming also features an all-new soundtrack by acclaimed series composer Akira Yamaoka.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5ViZHk0YOQk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YrLbG6jJRH4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942060-silent-hill-homecoming/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Silent-Hill-Homecoming/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/silent-hill-homecoming/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/silent-hill-homecoming"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Silent Hill Wiki",
				"url":"http://silenthill.wikia.com/wiki/Silent_Hill:_Homecoming"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":305,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Radical Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"In Crash Bandicoot: Mind over Mutant, a rejuvenated Neo Cortex is taking over the world one brain at a time! Cortex and N. Brio devise a new kind of evil; a text-messaging, do-anything device which controls both mutant and bandicoot minds. Armed with his quick-wits and lightening agility, Crash must free his friends, the titans and save the day!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FBLnhxStiOc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2UHI9h1Nxb4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Crash-Bandicoot-Mind-Over-Mutant/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/crash-bandicoot-mind-over-mutant/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/crash-mind-over-mutant"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Bandipedia - The Crash Bandicoot Wiki",
				"url":"http://crashbandicoot.wikia.com/wiki/Crash:_Mind_Over_Mutant"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":306,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Day 1 Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Fracture advances players to the year 2161, where ecological and seismological disasters have radically altered the planet's landscape, and a clash in ideologies places society on the threshold of war. Players set foot on the frontlines as Mason Briggs, a demolitions expert fighting for the Atlantic Alliance. Pitted against the genetically enhanced soldiers of the Pacifican army, players will experience a revolution in 22nd-century warfare.<br><br>In utilizing the core gameplay mechanic of Fracture, a destructive technology known as Terrain Deformation, players are equipped with an arsenal of futuristic weaponry to strategically reshape their surroundings on the fly. Every action they perform dynamically reshapes the earth in ways no videogame has ever seen. When Briggs throws a tectonic grenade on a level battlefield, the ground blasts upward to provide access to an otherwise unreachable area. Moving on, when he comes across what appears to be an impenetrable structure, Briggs utilizes the alt-fire functionality on his rocket launcher to create enormous craters to burrow underneath the wall. Surrounded on all sides by enemies, Briggs heaves a vortex grenade, creating a swirling tornado-like mass of boulder, dirt and debris to dispatch his foes. These are just a few samples of the possibilities for Terrain Deformation. Players not only change the battlefield - they change the face of the battle itself.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wN_lvdukB7M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7oQ9b7FGuJ8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939323-fracture/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fracture/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fracture/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fracture"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":307,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["ARC System Works"],
			"synopsis":"A 3D action spin-off in the Guilty Gear franchise in which humanity must battle the awesome power of biological weapons known as Gears. Guilty Gear 2: Overture features refined mechanics, multiplayer action, dual language capability, tactical melee action and more.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"New Master \"Raven\"",
				"releaseDate":"2008/10/15",
				"achievements":55,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Undying Disease, Raven, becomes available as a playable master. Please refer to the in-game TIPS or the official website, http://gg2nd.jp/, for controls."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"New Costume \"Ex. Sol\"",
				"releaseDate":"2008/10/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Sol Badguy's new costume! Note: No changes to his abilities."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"New Stage \"Holy Knight's Fortress\"",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/15",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Originally constructed as a base for the Sacred Order, the fortress saw more than its share of bloodshed and battle during the war with the Gears. Today, surrounded by the beauty of nature, the fortress will see a clash of swords to rival the battles of old!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MiJ0gZdovEM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zq-E36fPsTs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942201-guilty-gear-2-overture/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Guilty-Gear-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/guilty-gear-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/guilty-gear-2-overture"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Guilty Gear Wiki",
				"url":"http://guilty-gear.wikia.com/wiki/Guilty_Gear_2:_Overture"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":308,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts", "Kush Games"],
			"synopsis":"It's once again time to drive the lane with this 2008 edition of 2K Sports' b-ball game. NBA 2K9 is the premier basketball game for serious players, delivering a realistic, stylistic, and feature-rich simulation basketball experience. This year's edition features an advanced version of the revolutionary Shot Stick control system, allowing you to change your shots in mid-air. And with Association 2.0, you'll have access to all the latest rumors, trades, scores news stories and more. New features also include new mini-game drills , drastically improved HD visuals, a new broadcast team with Clark Kellogg, Cheryl Miller and Kevin Harlan, and more online features than ever before.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2SDX_DB9e-I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LoVHaAyBMGk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/946535-nba-2k9/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-2K9/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-2k9/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-2k9"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":309,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"NBA LIVE 09 is back, promising a fun, long-lasting and satisfying experience with new features of gameplay. New features like Pick and Roll Control, Defensive Lockdown Control, Signature Playcalling and Quickstrike Ankle-Breakers will make the NBA LIVE experience fun from beginning to end. For those in need of some extra coaching, NBA LIVE 09 takes you to training camp with the NBA Academy that gives you a chance to hone your skills.<br><br>NBA LIVE 09 has rewritten the rules and fundamentally shifted the way you look at sports simulation games. Dynamic DNA emulates - with absolute precision - an NBA player in every sense of the word and it does so dynamically. The game takes the statistical data of DynamicDNA and brings it to life. Play is now constantly evolving and authentically reflects what you see on the court in your virtual experience. Just like the real NBA game, players get injured, free agents sign late, great players go cold and no-names breakthrough. If you're a sports fan, this is a dream come true - NBA LIVE 09 is made fresh daily all season long.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IGd-3LznkYc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m2qp0wE8b6M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-LIVE-09/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-live-09/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-live-09"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":310,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Midway Games"],
			"synopsis":"As the sequel to the more than one million unit selling and award-winning football experience, Blitz: The League II, continues the franchise legacy as the ultimate alternative to the watered-down, licensed competition. In addition to an all-new story mode penned by Peter Egan (ESPN's Playmakers), Blitz: The League II features include: Precision-Aim Tackles, player-controlled touchdown celebrations, an enhanced on-the-field Clash Mode, online multiplayer capabilities, expanded rosters with all-new personalities, and the return of a cornerstone of the Blitz franchise ... Late Hits! Football legend Lawrence Taylor returns as the game's cover-athlete and star linebacker for the New York Nightmare, Quentin Sands, along with a star-studded supporting cast.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CWLGEkSWgps"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DlEZnIc87r0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Team Captain Movie 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d-uDHpaXf8k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Team Captain Movie 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UdkE5TXL2fU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Team Captain Movie 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zawsb3eWZKk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Team Captain Movie 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n-K28BvUaBw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Team Captain Movie 5",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y5FcLqPQP20"
			},
			{
				"type":"Team Captain Movie 6",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XhZZ_Pvg1hg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Team Captain Movie 7",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vaMzbYOcnHI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Blitz-The-League-II/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/blitz-the-league-ii/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/blitz-the-league-ii"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":311,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"Dance Dance Revolution celebrates its 10th anniversary! Dance Dance Revolution Universe 3 dances its way to you with an all new interface, fun new modes and settings for players of all skill levels, cool smash-hit songs, robust online and offline support and exciting new exclusives. In addition to one of the biggest soundtracks - more than 70 songs spanning from the '70s to some of today's hottest tracks - Dance Dance Revolution Universe 3 brings friends together from around the world via Xbox LIVE. Character customization features more than 400 options of clothing, faces, skin tones and hairstyles, allowing players to create the ultimate dancer.<br><br>This package also packs in a DDR dance mat for players to get their groove on with the game.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Voice Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/18",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Valencia's MC voice (Japanese). Play the game with her cute announcer voice"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Present song 01",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/30",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"A Dream / Big Idea"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Present song 02",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/30",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Koibana / Togo Project feat. *manna"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Download song Mega Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/01/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Pack containing the following songs:<br>- 39th St. Strut / oo39.com<br>- Dance Till The Sun Come Up / Big Idea<br>- HIT THE GROUND (Alexa Remix) / NAOKI<br>- Jewelya of De' Nile / Big Idea<br>- Lady Be Good To Me / In Geer<br>- Musk Up / The Blue Light Specialists<br>- oarfish / kors k<br>- Rhythm of My Heart / Master Source<br>- vertical / Ryu<br>- You're Such A Shredder / In Geer"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0-CMHMLY0NI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xKzEQdnQG2A"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/946372-dance-dance-revolution-universe-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dance-Dance-Revolution-Universe-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dance-dance-revolution-universe-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dance-dance-revolution-universe-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dance Dance Revolution Wiki",
				"url":"http://dancedancerevolutionddr.wikia.com/wiki/Category:DDR_Universe_3_Songs"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":312,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Redwood Shores Studio"],
			"synopsis":"Gamers step into a third-person sci-fi survival horror experience that promises to deliver the ultimate in psychological thrills and gruesome action. Set in the cold blackness of deep space, the atmosphere is soaked with a feeling of tension, dread and sheer terror. In Dead Space, players step into the role of engineer Isaac Clarke - an ordinary man on a seemingly routine mission to fix the communications systems aboard a deep space mining ship. It is not long before Isaac awakes to a living nightmare when he learns that the ship's crew has been ravaged by a vicious alien infestation. He must fight through the dead silence and darkness of deep space to stay alive.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Astronaut Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download the Astronaut Suit and Weapon Skin Pack, featuring an amazing 26th Century Astronaut Suit and new skins for the Plasma Cutter, Pulse Rifle, and Ripper!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Big Gun Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download the Steam Punk Force Gun, the ultimate in Necromorph-killing destruction."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Heavy Damage Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download the Heavy Damage Weapon pack featuring a cool new look and massive firepower for the Plasma Cutter, Contact Beam, Pulse Rifle, and Ripper."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Hot Rod Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download the Hot Rod Weapon Skin Pack, featuring awesome flame graphics for the Flamethrower and Pulse Rifle."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Military Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download the Military Weapon Pack for a new look and enhanced power for all 7 Dead Space weapons."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Pedestrian Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download the Pedestrian Weapon Skin Pack, featuring a fresh new look for the Contact Beam, Plasma Cutter, and Ripper."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Scorpion Suit",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download the Scorpion Suit now! Equip Isaac with this stunning Level 5 suit featuring enhanced armor and fully unlocked slots, in an awesome red Scorpion Skin."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Scorpion Weapon Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download the Scorpion Weapon Pack featuring a faster death-dealing Plasma Cutter, Line Gun, and Force Gun in awesome red skins."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Speed Kills Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download the Speed Kills Weapon Pack! Includes faster-firing Force Gun, Line Gun, and Plasma Cutter."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Tank Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download the Tank Pack featuring an upgraded Level 5 Suit and powered up Flamethrower, Force Gun, and Line Gun, all covered in Unitology script."
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Elite Weapon Skin Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download the exclusive Elite Weapon Skin Pack now, available only for the Xbox 360! Includes weapon skins in Xbox 360 colors for the Line Gun, Plasma Cutter, and Pulse Rifle."
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Elite Suit",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download the exclusive Elite Suit now, available only for the Xbox 360! Isaac Clarke becomes a juggernaut in this Level 5 suit featuring the Xbox 360 colors, upgraded toughness, and extra inventory slots."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aE2lPGsvjC4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8iqYgVuoTFA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943338-dead-space/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dead-Space/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dead-space/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dead-space"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dead Space Wiki",
				"url":"http://deadspace.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":313,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"Step onto the pitch and play professional football your way in FIFA 09. Powered by the third generation of the EA SPORTS football engine, FIFA 09 features more than 250 core gameplay additions and enhancements that deliver the most responsive, intelligent and realistic action ever for the series. Enjoy turning defenders with more controlled dribbling and ball control, snapping off precision shots with improved first-time shooting mechanics and firing beautifully timed passes with greater accuracy, placing the ball exactly where you want it. With new player momentum physics the speed and weight of the player determines everything from the distance of a slide tackle and the power of a header to the severity of player collisions and the height of a player's jump. Plus, players now behave according to their physical attributes with larger, stronger players dominating collisions, battles for control of the ball, and position in challenges for two player headers.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Ultimate Team",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/19",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Ultimate Team adds a brand new deep game mode to FIFA 09. Create your ultimate team by buying, trading and collecting the best players from around the world."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wrkGDjP1jB8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-3613xl7iFw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/947071-fifa-soccer-09/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/FIFA-09/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fifa-09/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fifa-soccer-09"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":314,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Secret Level"],
			"synopsis":"SEGA's fantasy adventure of blades and magic returns with this re-incarnation of the Golden Axe franchise. Golden Axe: Beast Rider delivers action-RPG thrills as a small band of Riders embark on an epic adventure to recruit allies, expose the enemy and prevent the annihilation of their breed. Delivering an intense and unique combat experience, players charge into battle on the backs of ferocious beasts or take their chances with the enemy while on foot. Fighting skill, wits and even magic are all called into action as players immerse themselves in the struggle to defeat an evil intent on enslaving the remains of civilization.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2Oir7u6qs94"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4FJB6897Iwc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/933095-golden-axe-beast-rider/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Golden-Axe-Beast-Rider/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/golden-axe-beast-riders/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/golden-axe-beast-rider"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":315,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Zoe Mode"],
			"synopsis":"Release your inner rockstar or allow your friends the privilege of picking up an axe or pounding the skins with you to 40 mind bending rock and roll tracks! Unleash your creative juices in the Jam Mode where you can create your own music in a state of the art multi-track studio! This is the musical revolution the world has been waiting for.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"She's the Bug",
				"releaseDate":"2008/10/24",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"\"She's the Bug\" is a FREE original funk rock track from the Rock Revolution Band within the Bemani Music Production team."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"NO PAIN, NO GAIN",
				"releaseDate":"2008/10/24",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"\"NO PAIN, NO GAIN\" is a FREE original rock track from the Rock Revolution Band within the Bemani Music Production team."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"MODEL DD 8",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"\"MODEL DD 8\" is an original instrumental metal track from Mutsuhiko Izumi of the Bemani Music Production team that features the guitar work of Marty Friedman."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Progressive Baby",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"\"Progressive Baby\" is an original instrumental progressive metal track by Daisuke Kurosawa of the Bemani Music Production team."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"My Only Shining Star",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"\"My Only Shining Star\" is a rock remake from Kuro of the Bemani dance classic written by NAOKI."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Death Real",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"\"Death Real\" is a metal original from Des-ROW of the Konami Bemani Music Production team."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"CHIMERA",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"\"CHIMERA\" is a power metal inspired original by Daisuke Kurosawa of the Bemani Music Production team."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=656yWb3hjc4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Chop Suey",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AqrCotG6E1M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rock-Revolution/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rock-revolution/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rock-revolution"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":316,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Volition"],
			"synopsis":"Saints Row 2 takes place a few years after the original. Several new upstart gangs have been able to sweep in and make their mark on Stilwater. At the same time, a multi-national conglomerate known as the Ultor Corporation has become a pivotal player in city politics, pumping millions of dollars into rebuilding the metropolis.<br><br>As leader of the Saints, you'll have to do whatever it takes to protect the members of your gang from new enemies, including the Ultor Corporation and rival gangs.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Ultor Exposed",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/23",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Disgruntled Ultor microbiologist Tera Patrick holds the key to the corporation's illicit research activities and revenue generating schemes. Help Tera dismantle the Ultor Corporation by exposing the megacorp's seedy operations to the citizens of Stilwater. Battle through three all new co-op enabled missions. Commandeer new air and ground vehicles including attack aircraft and luxury sports cars. Customize your character with new hairstyles, law enforcement uniforms, and all new clothes. Own the streets in new Strong Arm and Gangsta Brawl multiplayer maps. These are your Saints and this is your city like you've never seen it before... fully exposed!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Corporate Warfare",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/28",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"There is a civil war brewing within the Ultor Corporation. Dex, Ultor's newly appointed Head of Security, is running a black market nuclear weapons operation aided by Ultor management. Meanwhile, a defected Ultor executive offers the Saints a chance to bring the entire operation down. Take revenge in style with new transportation options for aircraft, exotic cars, and superbikes. Redefine your character with all new customization options including brand new outfits and facial bandanas to change your identity. Take the battle to the streets with brand new Strong Arm and Gangsta Brawl multiplayer maps or challenge your friends in an all new Co-Op competitive."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"The Unkut Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Pimp out your personality with over 60 brand new customization items including Unkut watches, necklaces, bracelets, T-shirts, tank tops, hoodies and camisoles. Change it up with a preppy polo, or dress it down with some jeans at Sloppy Seconds. Ink-up your character with 16 all new tattoo options."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DAxfRW5H4bQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_g7F7Pq-lh0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rEu6bqympEo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939458-saints-row-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Saints-Row-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rEu6bqympEo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/saints-row-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Saints Row Wiki",
				"url":"http://saintsrow.wikia.com/Saints_Row_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":317,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rockstar San Diego"],
			"synopsis":"The entire city of Los Angeles is your playground as you speed through the streets, parking lots, and back alleys in Midnight Club: Los Angeles, all on your way to becoming the most notable racer in the city. As a new arrival on the racing scene, you're going to need to earn REP for others to take you seriously, and earn the right to upgrade your ride or purchase an even better one. Reputation Points can be earned by completing any task or race in MCLA, regardless of what position you finish.<br><br>Midnight Club Los Angeles features over 40 vehicles from 4 different classes. Tuner, Luxury, Exotic and Muscle cars as well as Bikes will all be available to race throughout the game. All cars can be fully customized in one of two garages found in the game. Special Moves return from Midnight Club 3: Dub Edition - classics like Zone, Agro and Roar are joined by a newcomer, EMP. A wide variety of races can be begun just by flashing your headlamps at other racers, and there are also \"Freeway Racer\" challenges and Police Chases to test your skills on. Illegal street racing with no track, no load times, no rules: Welcome back to the Midnight Club.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"South Central Premium Upgrade",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/27",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"South Central Premium Upgrade is the total South Central experience for Midnight Club Los Angeles delivering 9 new vehicles, 26 new races, 12 new battle maps, 10 new delivery missions, over 100 new red light races, new vinyl packs, new parts, new music, and the free South Central Map Expansion which expands the massive city of Midnight Club: Los Angeles by one third, adding four neighborhoods that make up the iconic district of South Central. Features the following 9 vehicles: Luxury: 2008 Mercedes-Benz CLK63 AMG \"Black\" SUV: 2008 Range Rover Supercharged, 2008 Range Rover Sport Super Charged Lowrider: 1955 Chevy Bel Air, 1963 Buick Riviera, 1964 Chevy Impala, 1965 Chevy Malibu Muscle: 1970 Chevy Chevelle, 1966 Pontiac GTO."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"South Central Map Expansion",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/03",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Get tons more streets to race in with the free South Central Map Expansion which expands Midnight Club: Los Angeles by one third, adding four new neighborhoods to make up the iconic district of South Central. Download the South Central Map Expansion to race online with friends who have the South Central Premium Upgrade or for single-player offline cruising. The South Central Map Expansion features real world L.A. landmarks such as Exposition Park, the USC campus, Shrine Auditorium, Crenshaw Plaza, and the L.A. Memorial Coliseum."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"South Central Vehicle Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/16",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"South Central Vehicle Pack 1 adds some extra class to your garage with 3 new high-performance vehicles, the 2008 Mercedes-Benz CL 65 AMG, the 2008 Audi S5, and the 2009 Mitsubishi Eclipse GT."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"South Central Vehicle Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/23",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"South Central Vehicle Pack 2 brings power and status, featuring the 2008 Cadillac XLR V, the 2008 Lancer Evolution X, the 2007 Aston Martin DB9 and the free 2008 Ducati 1098 R."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Police Car Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/10/17",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Now you can dodge the cops by downloading the free Midnight Club Los Angeles Police Car Pack. Race in the Border, Highway or Squad Patrol cars (choose from the 1996 Chevrolet Impala or Dodge Charger SRT8) for the ability to evade the cops at red lights and race at high speeds - but don't trespass or the chase is on. Download the pack now, and get your cop cars from the vehicle showroom as they unlock."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lmgMYjLFPFs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KzvP7qwG8SI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=po0ec81P_ak"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G6x6OgYRoKo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mWzxGQwZTJQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939535-midnight-club-los-angeles/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Midnight-Club-Los-Angeles/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/midnight-club-los-angeles/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/midnight-club-los-angeles"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Midnight Club Wiki",
				"url":"http://midnightclub.wikia.com/wiki/Midnight_Club:_Los_Angeles"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":318,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Zoe Mode"],
			"synopsis":"Disney Sing It is a video-based karaoke game that features a mix of popular fan-faves and the hottest new Disney artists. The first game in this rockin' new franchise features songs and videos from Hollywood Records artists, Disney Channel Original Series and Disney Channel Original Movies. Players can belt out some of today's chart topping tunes and have a blast along with their friends and Disney stars!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OkpgJNrspjs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Breaking Free",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HhkGDfr1eC8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Miley Cyrus",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9NZR4IWZJzc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Disney-Sing-It/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/disney-sing-it/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/disney-sing-it"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":319,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Lionhead Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Set 500 years after the original game, Fable 2 offers even more choices and features, while building on the core gameplay theme of Fable where every choice continually defines who you become, allowing you to truly live the life you choose. Fable II expands upon the scope and depth of the original by adding incredible new features and creating a wider, more complex kingdom of limitless choices and consequences. Players will have the option to play as a man or woman, get married, have children, and live a life of their own design - all leading to different destinies.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Knothole Island",
				"releaseDate":"2009/01/13",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Discover new quests, locations, characters and more in the premium Knothole Island download. Meet Gordon the submariner in the Bowerstone docks, where you'll be showered with unique gifts to entice you to the mysterious island. There you will embark on new adventures, fight new creatures and find Albion's rarest weapons, clothes and potions. You will also be able to check your standing in over 50 new Leaderboards on Lionhead.com."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"See the Future",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/12",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Strange new quests, new dog breeds and a vision of your future await you in this premium download. Murgo, trader of highly unusual and magical items, has returned to Bowerstone, and he has brought with him objects that will transport you to worlds and quests no Hero has ever faced before. Bring colour back to the world, dress up in creature costumes, compete in a new combat arena and find out what awaits you in Albion's distant future."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v0OaBsWtwFc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ogm7d8Mx0Ic"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UTVzJZCVVV4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5pouqKKjh_M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vHUVDkvwAHU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/927246-fable-ii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fable-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fable-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fable-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Fable Wiki",
				"url":"http://fable.wikia.com/wiki/Fable_II"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":320,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"Caught between two rival factions in war-torn Africa, you are sent to take out \"The Jackal\", a mysterious character who has rekindled the conflict between the warlords, jeopardizing thousands of lives. In order to fulfill your mission you will have to play the factions against each other, identify and exploit their weaknesses, and neutralize their superior numbers and firepower with surprise, subversion, cunning and, of course, brute force.<br><br>Far Cry 2 immerses players in an entirely new kind of gaming experience, featuring a custom-made video game engine built from the ground up. Players discover a true open world gameplay set in Africa, brought to life by high-definition next-gen technology.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Fortune's Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/25",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Ramp up the terror with the Far Cry 2 Fortune's Pack. Loaded with 3 new weapons, 2 new vehicles and 4 new multiplayer maps:<br>- Silenced Shotgun: Power and stealth in one gun.<br>- Craftsman Shotgun: An ornamental shotgun with power and class to get people talking.<br>- Crossbow: Use explosive bolts to take out vehicles or start raging fires from a safe distance.<br>- ATV: Leave the roads and hit the fields with this All-terrain Vehicle.<br>- Utility Truck: Perfect for charging unsuspecting camps and taking out a couple of mercs.<br><br>Plus 4 new multiplayer maps. Get set to take out friends and enemies alike in these new environments: Last Resort, Cheap Labour, Lake Smear and Fort Fury. Let the mayhem begin..."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DMTDjKusVqY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xAmg61qzrcI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dVmvLxVSp_8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944400-far-cry-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Far-Cry-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/far-cry-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/far-cry-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Far Cry Wiki",
				"url":"http://farcry.wikia.com/wiki/Far_Cry_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":321,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Etranges Libellules"],
			"synopsis":"In the final chapter of the trilogy, players find Sypro teaming up with an unlikely ally - Cynder, his former enemy, to face his most challenging mission to date. As the Dark Master's evil envelopes the world like a plague, Spyro must fulfill his destiny and unlock the true power of the purple dragon within him to stop the Dark Master in his tracks.<br><br>The game introduces two never before seen elements into the Spyro universe: Spyro can now fly at any time and players can drop-in/drop-out with the new cooperative feature. The co-op feature allows players to have the option of completing the game as either Spyro or Cynder, giving them more freedom to explore Spyro's world in completely new ways.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CE65h78iBTg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qSLuD8c3JC8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945950-the-legend-of-spyro-dawn-of-the-dragon/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Legend-of-Spyro/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/legend-of-spyro-dawn-of-the-dragon/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-legend-of-spyro-dawn-of-the-dragon"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Spyro the Dragon Wiki",
				"url":"http://spyro.wikia.com/wiki/The_Legend_of_Spyro:_Dawn_of_the_Dragon"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":322,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Spark Unlimited"],
			"synopsis":"Legendary tells the story of Charles Deckard, an art thief who is duped into stealing Pandora's Box. When he opens the box, he releases hordes of beasts thought to be fictional - werewolves and gryphons and all means of beast and demon - into an unprepared modern world. A full scale war between man and myth begins, and it is quickly complicated by the actions of powerful secret societies. As the person responsible for releasing this terror, Deckard's unwittingly become the only person capable of containing it once more and saving civilization from being destroyed by the terrifying creatures of the box.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VQ9-Nn0DnVk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vjQ0gPChHI4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/941873-legendary/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Legendary/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/legendary/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/legendary"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":323,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Shaba Games", "Treyarch"],
			"synopsis":"Spider-Man: Web of Shadows immerse players in an all-new action-adventure saga that gives them unprecedented control, never before seen in a Spider-Man game. Armed throughout the battle and confronted by an unrecognizable New York City, players choose to play as a heroic web-slinger or a volatile, destructive anti-hero, fighting with or against a vast number of fan-favorite Marvel heroes and villains, switching instantly between sides, and deciding which missions to undertake to save mankind. An all-new combat system combines web slinging and customizable superpowers to give gamers the freedom to fight and explore in a free-roaming, open-ended environment. Battles blend Spider-Man's speed and agility with the landscape, challenging players to master fast moving acrobatic combat, powerful new web-slinging moves and destructive combo attacks, as they take the fight from the streets, up the sides of buildings and onto rooftops.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f_7uOrS_mvw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SzcXjF2vuHU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945883-spider-man-web-of-shadows/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Spider-Man-Web-of-Shadows/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/spider-man-web-of-shadows/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/spider-man-web-of-shadows"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Spider-Man Wiki",
				"url":"http://spiderman.wikia.com/wiki/Spider-Man:_Web_of_Shadows"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":324,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Electronic Arts"],
			"synopsis":"The Monopoly video games promise a fresh take on the timeless classic with accessible gameplay for players of all ages and skill levels. The all-new digital gaming edition brings a party twist and features 4-player simultaneous play, ensuring that everyone is engaged and allowing the whole family to get involved in the fun and play together. Faster gameplay eliminates downtime freeing up players to wheel and deal their way through some of the most recognizable cities and landmarks from around the world. Families can fill up their passports as they try to unlock new and never-before-seen game boards or challenge each other to fun interactive mini-games like breaking out of the jail cell and running away with all the loot. Play in offline single or multi-player mode and compete to own it all and win!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_g6zmxmXVcQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BpmlW7kD7YA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945916-monopoly/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Monopoly/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/monopoly/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/monopoly"
			},
			{
				"type":"Board Game Wiki",
				"site":"Monopoly Wiki",
				"url":"http://monopoly.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":325,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Neversoft Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Guitar Hero World Tour delivers more ways to play than ever before. Virtual musicians can live out their rock and roll fantasies by playing either a single instrument, or any combination of instruments, in addition to the full band experience.<br><br>In addition to all of the online gameplay modes from Guitar Hero III: Legends of Rock, Guitar Hero World Tour introduces Battle of the Bands mode which allows eight players to join online and challenge each other band-to-band to determine who is the best of the best. In the Band modes, up to four players can jam together, online or off, as they progress through the game, and in single-player Career Mode, players can jam on any of the instruments in branching venue progression enabling them to rock out in the order of their choice.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable tracks",
				"releaseDate":"2008/10/26",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"158 tracks available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jwl0qmmkTfQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ks3eEQQ2W0c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PS3ZGfp1qNE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944201-guitar-hero-world-tour/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Guitar-Hero-World-Tour/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/guitar-hero-world-tour/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/guitar-hero-world-tour"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wikihero",
				"url":"http://guitarhero.wikia.com/wiki/Guitar_Hero_World_Tour"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":326,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bethesda Game Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Vault 101 - Jewel of the Wastes. For 200 years, Vault 101 has faithfully served the surviving residents of Washington DC and its environs, now known as the Capital Wasteland. Though the global atomic war of 2077 left the US all but destroyed, the residents of Vault 101 enjoy a life free from the constant stress of the outside world. Giant Insects, Raiders, Slavers, and yes, even Super Mutants are all no match for superior Vault-Tec engineering. Yet one fateful morning, you awake to find that your father has defied the Overseer and left the comfort and security afforded by Vault 101 for reasons unknown. Leaving the only home you've ever known, you emerge from the Vault into the harsh Wasteland sun to search for your father, and the truth.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Operation: Anchorage",
				"releaseDate":"2009/01/27",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Enter the simulation pod and embark on one of the greatest military campaigns of the Fallout universe - the liberation of Anchorage, Alaska from its Chinese Communist invaders. Experience harrowing winter combat using Fallout 3's patented V.A.T.S. targeting system, and employ powerful new equipment like the Gauss Rifle, Chinese Stealth Armor, Winterized T-51b Power Armor, and more. Enlist today, soldier!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"The Pitt",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/29",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Pittsburgh was once the industrial center of the pre-war world. The city was spared the horrors of nuclear fire, only to have its people infected by a nightmare plague of disease, infection, and mutation. Travel to the ruins of this industrial city, now called The Pitt, and discover a secret that could send shockwaves through the entire Wasteland. Battle vicious mutated Trogs, employ deadly new weapons like the AutoAxe and Infiltrator silenced assault rifle, and decide the fate of the infected slaves and slavers that call this city home. Only you can find the cure - but will you have the guts to use it?"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Broken Steel",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/05",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"You may have dealt the Enclave a serious blow at Project Purity, but their forces are still out there, and still pose a grave threat to the people and security of the Capital Wasteland. In Broken Steel, you'll continue your current Fallout 3 character past the events of Project Purity, and work with the Brotherhood of Steel to eradicate the Enclave threat once and for all. You'll travel to new locations like the Olney Powerworks, wield destructive new weapons like the Tesla Cannon, fight powerful new creatures like the Super Mutant Overlord, marvel at the destructive power of Liberty Prime, earn new Perks like the devastating Nuclear Anomaly... and play Fallout 3 all the way to level 30!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Point Lookout",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/23",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Buy a ticket and hop onboard the Duchess Gambit, as Tobar the Ferryman takes you to the strange seaside town of Point Lookout. What secrets does the dilapidated boardwalk hold? Who lives in the sprawling mansion? Why is the Punga Fruit so important? And what horrors lie in the depths of the murky swamp? Point Lookout is the most open-ended DLC yet, and allows you to explore an entirely new and expansive gameplay area any way you'd like. A completely new questline allows you uncover the town's hidden secrets, and wield powerful new weapons like the Double-Barrel Shotgun against the swamp's dangerous, and deformed, denizens. So venture to Point Lookout, if you dare. Just pray it's not a one-way trip."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Mothership Zeta",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/03",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"A strange Alien signal is being broadcast throughout the Capital Wasteland, originating from a crashed UFO. Is it a distress call, or something far more sinister? That question is answered when you find yourself beamed aboard an enormous Alien spacecraft, with only one alternative - to fight your way to the bridge of the ship and secure your escape. Mothership Zeta takes Fallout 3 in an entirely new direction - outer space. Meet new characters and join with them in a desperate bid to escape the Aliens' clutches. To do so, you'll wield powerful new weapons, like the Alien Atomizer, Alien Disintegrator and Drone Cannon, and deck yourself out in brand new outfits, like the Gemini-Era Spacesuit and even Samurai Armor."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iYZpR51XgW0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Teaser Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zPt08UYmyMo"
			},
			{
				"type":"All DLC Trailers",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fPIHECWw9b4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OhJgIWca2rA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939933-fallout-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fallout-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fallout-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fallout-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Fallout Wiki",
				"url":"http://fallout.wikia.com/wiki/Fallout_3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":327,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Page 44 Studios"],
			"synopsis":"High School Musical 3: Senior Year Dance lets players experience the music, familiar locations and popular characters from all three movies, including the upcoming \"High School Musical 3: Senior Year.\"<br><br>Players take the role of Troy, Gabriella, Sharpay, Ryan, Chad or Taylor, or can customize their own Wildcat, using a variety of outfits, shoes and hairstyles. In addition, the game features various multiplayer modes, including competitive and cooperative play. In competitive mode, users can earn power-ups to affect other players' performances, while in cooperative mode players need to dance simultaneously and in sync to earn high scores. Fans can also follow along to choreography from the stars, and complete songs to earn points and unlock new songs, clothing and characters.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v-8L71pjepA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/High-School-Musical-3-Senior-Year-Dance/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/high-school-musical-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"High School Musical Wiki",
				"url":"http://high-school-musical.wikia.com/wiki/High_School_Musical_3:_Senior_Year"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":328,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Milestone"],
			"synopsis":"The official game of the 2008 season, MotoGP 08 features all the riders, bikes and tracks providing the definitive 2-wheeled racing experience. The development team's overriding aim was to deliver an unparalleled handling model that allows access points for gamers of all skill levels and just as importantly provide a challenge to meet each player's abilities.<br><br>MotoGP 08 puts the player at the center of the MotoGP experience by letting them join a team and compete alongside their sporting heroes in all three race classes - 125cc, 250cc and MotoGP. Good results in qualifying and racing earn points that can then be exchanged for bike upgrades to improve attributes such as straight line speed, braking and cornering.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sr9Uhc6HYJc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bd_LBWE0c_o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MotoGP-08/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MotoGP-08/walkthrough.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/motogp-08"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":329,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Screenlife", "Krome Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Scene It? Box Office Smash, the second entry in the revolutionary movie trivia game on Xbox 360, will ignite your game night with totally new questions, movie puzzles and more high-definition (HD) content from real movies including some of Hollywood's latest blockbusters. Trivia night goes global as players challenge each other online over Xbox LIVE, customize their own characters, and access extra questions and localized content from films around the world.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Award Winners",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/12",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"And the winner is... Scene It? Box Office Smash! - Award Winners Game Add-on! Load up on questions about award-winning movies, plus a new puzzle - Pop Quiz! Over 800 new questions added to your favorite puzzles like Movie Clips, Pixel Flix, Child's Play, and more."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BHrZpSdwCYA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DVZcqmV02UI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Scene-It-Box-Office-Smash/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/scene-it-box-office-smash/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/scene-it-box-office-smash"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":330,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Left Field Productions, Inc."],
			"synopsis":"SCORE International Baja 1000 recreates the unforgiving conditions and blistering speeds that make this event the most recognized and entertaining off-road racing event in the world.<br><br>Sporting over 90 vehicles across multiple classes in the real Baja 1000 - including trophy trucks, class I, motorcycles, ATVs and more - the game challenges players to not only be first across the finish line, but also keep their machine intact. Hyper-realistic dirt and damage modeling in the game means players need to be crazy enough to take chances, but not so reckless that their vehicle is destroyed before the race is over.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8pMrJfPT5es"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VfvFvkEpwZY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tm7X8sZqQ0E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/SCORE-International-Baja-1000/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/score-international-baja-1000/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/score-international-baja-1000"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":331,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"AC/DC LIVE: Rock Band features the master recordings from the best of the band's live performances. The live recording was specially remixed for Rock Band by Mike Fraser. The game features 18 tracks, with more than 99 minutes of game play for each instrument.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - T.N.T.",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kXF-y7qzPAU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Thunderstruck",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T0ytMHT7YEE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/ACDC-LIVE-Rock-Band/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rock-band-track-pack-acdc-live/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/acdc-live-rock-band-track-pack"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Rock Band Wiki",
				"url":"http://rockband.wikia.com/wiki/AC/DC"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":332,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Treyarch"],
			"synopsis":"James Bond is back to settle the score in Quantum of Solace: The Game. Introducing a more lethal and cunningly efficient Bond, the game blends intense first-person action with a unique third-person cover combat system that allows players to truly feel what it is like to be the ultimate secret agent as they use their stealth, precision shooting and lethal combat skills to progress through missions.<br><br>Seamlessly blending the heart-pounding action and excitement of the upcoming Quantum of Solace feature film with the Casino Royale movie, the title propels players into the cinematic experience of international espionage. Based on the renowned Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare game engine that has been specifically engineered to immerse players in the Bond universe, Quantum of Solace: The Game delivers superior high-definition graphics, reactive AI and visually stunning locations inspired by locales portrayed in the films.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Camille Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/30",
				"type":1
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JDOFEEiobCE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mAjNr3CSHAY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/946232-quantum-of-solace/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Quantum-of-Solace/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/quantum-of-solace/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/quantum-of-solace"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"007 Wiki",
				"url":"http://jamesbond.wikia.com/wiki/Quantum_of_Solace"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":333,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cauldron"],
			"synopsis":"In Civil War: Secret Missions, history buffs and first person action fans will get the chance to assume the role of Union and Confederate soldiers fighting behind enemy lines in famous Civil War battles. The player's goal is to disrupt the armies of both the North and South by any means necessary, including stopping enemy supply lines, stealing ironclad ships and sabotaging enemy strongholds. Engage in some of the Civil War's most famous battles, such as The Great Train Raid of 1861 and The Fall of Vicksburg as you utilize classic weapons of the era, including the pepperbox revolver and the coffee mill gun. All missions are based on the actions of famous partisans, scouts and rangers - fight as a member of Mosby's Rangers, Sheridan's Scouts and Grant's Secret Service and receive your mission commands from famous generals like Robert E. Lee, \"Stonewall\" Jackson, and Ulysses Grant.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FZvVuL9OmiY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/952381-the-history-channel-civil-war-secret-missions/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Civil-War-Secret-Missions/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/history-channel-civil-war-secret-missions/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-history-channel-civil-war---secret-missions"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":334,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Toys For Bob"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the feature film from DreamWorks Animation, the four famous zoo animals - Alex the Lion, Marty the Zebra, Melman the Giraffe and Gloria the Hippo - and their entire madcap Madagascar crew take players on a whole new action-packed journey to help save the African savannah. Assuming the roles of all their favorite characters, including those crafty penguins, players must work through 12 distinct levels featuring a variety of wild adventures and fun mini-games. In addition to the diverse single-player gameplay, the Madagascar: Escape 2 Africa Video Game delivers an enhanced multiplayer tournament mode allowing gamers to participate in outlandish competitions alongside or against friends and family.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WbuElXP7TLI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-p1IqfKTtpc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Madagascar-Escape-to-Africa/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/madagascar-escape-2-africa/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/madagascar-escape-2-africa"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Madagascar Wiki",
				"url":"http://madagascar.wikia.com/wiki/Madagascar_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":335,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cauldron"],
			"synopsis":"Secret Service allows players to assume the role of an elite agent, tasked with protecting America's top leadership. The game takes place on Inauguration Day in Washington D.C. An extremist assault has been launched against the capitol - security has been compromised and it is unclear who is friend or foe. There is no time for negotiation as you are thrust out of the shadows and into the line of fire in order to protect the nation's leaders. The tactical first person action takes place among famous landmarks and everywhere in between, including both Marine One and Air Force One.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3PRqQf-9-7A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AS9vAy55ZBA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Secret-Service/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/secret-service/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/secret-service"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":336,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Shanghai"],
			"synopsis":"From 2011 to 2014, the world enjoyed an unprecedented era of peace as enhanced defense technology eliminated the threat of nuclear war. It didn't last.<br><br>By 2020, constant depletion of resources has international tensions at a breaking point. One spark will ignite what no one thought could ever happen ... a third and final world war. World War III comes to life in Tom Clancy's EndWar.<br><br>In EndWar players represent one of three national armies (U.S. Russia or Europe) and participate in massive multiplayer battles. EndWar can be played almost entirely by voice command and also features a customizable army, as well as the ability to fight in various battlefields and cities around the world.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Escalation",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/11",
				"achievements":220,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Four new exclusive missions on all new battlefields playable in skirmish mode, three exclusive unit upgrades and an extra set of achievements or trophies to expand your experience with Tom Clancy's EndWar. The new missions include the Siege of the Kursk Firebase (Ukraine), the Assault on Devon beach (England), the Raid on Rota naval base (Spain) and the Conquest of Dorsey Knob (USA, West Virginia)."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Faction Elite Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/01/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Includes three new battalions (one per faction) and six new upgrades (two per faction). These new elite battalions include the legendary JSF 15th Special Operations, the Spetsnaz Alpha Brigade, and the Enforcer Corps Battlegroup. The \"Faction Elite Pack\" will also grant immediate access to six exclusive unit upgrades including Ceramic Armor for the Spetnaz Guard Brigade and Caseless Ammunition for The European Federation's Gunships to name a couple."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Veteran Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/26",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"2 exclusive missions on new battlefields playable in skirmish mode for battle-hardened commanders. New missions include the assault on Russia's Cosmodrome and the conquest of the Strategic Petroleum Reserve in Richton, Mississippi, U.S.A."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CyYNBYedzqw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dWoGR9a97S0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZKYx3HfrBdI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eNvTCoI3TT8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HLL9O-Jo7O4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OuF0WiJ2cLg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tom-Clancys-EndWar/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tom-clancy-endwar/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tom-clancys-endwar"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"EndWar Wiki",
				"url":"http://endwar.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":337,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Epic Games"],
			"synopsis":"The gears of war continue to turn as Marcus Fenix and his squad of Cogs go back into action in the sequel to Microsoft and developer Epic Games' blockbuster action title. Gears of War 2 continues the story of Marcus Fenix and Delta Squad, locked in an increasingly desperate battle against the nightmarish Locust Horde for the survival of humanity. The game promises to be an epic saga of survival, loss, and retribution. Just as Gears of War set the standard for high-definition visuals, Gears of War 2 raises the bar even further with the amazing technological advances of Unreal Engine 3, delivering a bigger, badder, and more intense experience as the story continues.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Combustible Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/15",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Explosive action takes center stage in these three new Gears 2 multiplayer maps: Flood, Gold Rush, and Fuel Station. Flood features a rising flow of Imulsion that drives the fight into close quarters. Infiltrate an Imulsion factory in Gold Rush, where multiple levels and volatile materials guarantee memorable encounters. Fuel Station delivers a dangerous battle around an abandoned refueling facility."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Flashback Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/01/07",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"As a special thanks to the fans, we've updated five popular maps from Gears of War: Gridlock, Subway, Canals, Mansion, and Tyro Station, and made them available to download. This map pack is also available for free with an Xbox LIVE redemption code included in new copies of Gears of War 2."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Snowblind Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/31",
				"achievements":190,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"This winter-themed pack brings you four Gears of War 2 maps sure to heat up your multiplayer and Horde action. Hunt your enemies down in the snowy day-lit heights or the dark tunnels of Under Hill. The massive industrial complex of Grind Yard gives numerous bunkers for cover, but watch out for snipers high in the flanking buildings. Beware the falling monuments in Courtyard, where wide-open spaces give you plenty of opportunities to gun down your enemies-unless they strike first. And due to fan demand, the popular Gears 1 map Fuel Depot makes its return."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Dark Corners Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/28",
				"achievements":325,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This downloadable content pack features 7 new Gears 2 multiplayer maps and a bonus deleted single-player chapter, \"Road to Ruin\", from the Gears of War 2 campaign. In \"Road to Ruin\", Marcus and Dom navigate the treacherous Locust highway, choosing stealth or blazing action to survive. For multiplayer fans, the 7 maps include a new War Machine, the much-requested Gears 1 map; Allfathers Garden, a heavy-weapons battle at a COG landmark; Highway, a fight deep in the Locust Hollow; Memorial, a battle at the Tomb of the Unknowns; Nowhere, a firefight in an old motel; Way Station, an unpredictable battlefield with parallel paths; and Sanctuary, a reimagined favorite from Gears for Windows."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer - Last Day",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FL_ZjJgbDmc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer - Rendezvous",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f3f4dhW9jFo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aVmnoBM4tCQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reveal Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fa1-91h8ELA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Campaign Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F22tMhXRmYc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YwirRvhVfx0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Horde Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YGjfQ9IP-Yg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938611-gears-of-war-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Gears-of-War-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/gears-of-war-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/gears-of-war-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Gearspedia",
				"url":"http://gearsofwar.wikia.com/wiki/Gears_of_War_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":338,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rare"],
			"synopsis":"Banjo-Kazooie: Nuts & Bolts embraces new and old fans alike, as the famous bear and bird duo return! High-definition graphics, user-created content and online gameplay are just three of the many advances people of all ages and skill levels will discover as they embark on their adventure.<br><br>The Lord of the Games (aka LOG) is tired of the petty squabbling between Banjo and the evil witch Gruntilda (aka Grunty), and has arranged a showdown to decide the rightful owner of Spiral Mountain. Claiming to have created every video game ever made, LOG has built the game worlds in which the contest's challenges take place. Banjo must complete LOG's challenges to win, while Grunty tries to stop him using every method her devious mind can muster. Throughout their adventure, players create their own abilities by building vehicles for Banjo to pilot over land, sea and air. Vehicle parts, which range from simple devices such as engines and wheels to more unusual equipment such as springs and egg guns, are earned and collected throughout the game. Players use their imagination to combine parts in any order to create whatever vehicle they choose.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"L.O.G.'s Lost Challenges",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/07",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Enjoying Banjo-Kazooie: Nuts & Bolts? With L.O.G.'s Lost Challenges you can tackle a whole world's worth of new Jiggy Games and a grab bag of bonus multiplayer scenarios. Ever wondered how the Test-O-Track would look as a fully fledged Game World stuffed full of characters and challenges? Here's your chance to live that crazy dream! Test drive new vehicles, win new Jiggies and unlock even more content (two words: Klungo's Arcade). Wide-ranging new multiplayer game types are also included for the benefit of players who would rather trash-talk real people than moles or aardvarks."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Reveal Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QLWLdO9GLWM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GRYYTzL8_q4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JHgDoVgaSuo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AUv6bNUcfKw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bCD9Zag94EM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935846-banjo-kazooie-nuts-and-bolts/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Banjo-Kazooie-Nuts-and-Bolts/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/banjo-kazooie-nuts-and-bolts/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/banjo-kazooie-nuts-bolts"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Banjo-Kazooie Wiki",
				"url":"http://banjokazooie.wikia.com/wiki/Banjo-Kazooie:_Nuts_%26_Bolts"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":339,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Avalanche Software"],
			"synopsis":"In Disney's Bolt, players take on the heroic personas of the TV star dog, Bolt, and his owner, Penny, from the high-action television series featured within the film. As Bolt, players can use his superpowers, including laser vision and his superbark, which sends out a sonic blast to devastate opponents, and as Penny, players utilize stealth, hacking skills and a wheelbar, inspired by her scooter seen in the movie, to outwit enemies.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RQ0tZuE3wLs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Disney-Bolt/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/disneys-bolt/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bolt"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":340,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Treyarch"],
			"synopsis":"Call of Duty: World at War throws out the rulebook of war to transform WWII combat through a new enemy, new tactics and an uncensored experience of the climatic battles that gripped a generation. As U.S. Marines and Russian soldiers, players will employ new features like cooperative gameplay, and weapons such as the flamethrower in the most chaotic and cinematically intense experience to date.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Map Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/17",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Call of Duty: World at War Map Pack 1 expands the addictive COD multiplayer experience with four new maps. Players fight through the burning streets of Berlin in \"Nightfire\" and take up battle positions in fortified Japanese bunkers in \"Knee Deep\". \"Station\" offers a bombed out underground train station, and the Nazi Zombies return in \"Verr&uuml;ckt\" (Zombie Asylum) featuring more weapons, new Perks-a-Cola machines and electroshock defenses."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Map Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/09",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Call of Duty: World at War Map Pack 2 continues to expand the addictive COD multiplayer experience with four new maps. Battle to control the river bridge in \"Banzai\" a bright jungle map featuring a waterfall and hidden caves. In \"Corrosion\" face down your enemy in a shattered train yard, and in \"Sub Pens\" wipe the monsoon rain from your eyes as you struggle over a bombed-out submarine base. The Zombies return in \"Shi No Numa\" (Zombie Swamp) featuring Perk machines, the deadly new Wunderwaffe DG-2, new Achievements and flaming Hell Hounds."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Map Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/06",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Call of Duty: World at War Map Pack 3 further expands the COD multiplayer experience with four new maps. Fight for ocean territory in \"Battery\" defend Russia's resources in \"Revolution\", and battle in the dense streets of \"Breach\". Zombies return in \"Der Riese\" (Zombie Factory), a Nazi research facility featuring a weapon upgrading Pack A Punch Machine, teleporters, and 10 Achievements."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y_Ip_SaJqpg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q6JcGw1OvBQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Map Pack 1 Trailer - Verruckt",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cvArR7CFXLs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Map Pack 2 Trailer - Shi No Numa",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JVavAfh-2sM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Map Pack 3 Trailer - Der Riese",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6uvNUDQEGSc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Campaign Gameplay - USA",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fJVqVsji41w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Campaign Gameplay - USSR",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gzVAmzSUDFk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QxbU97sreG0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Nazi Zombies Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WLkT7J8bJB8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944199-call-of-duty-world-at-war/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Call-of-Duty-World-at-War/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/call-of-duty-world-at-war/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/call-of-duty-world-at-war"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Call of Duty Wiki",
				"url":"http://callofduty.wikia.com/wiki/Call_of_Duty:_World_at_War"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":341,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Los Angeles"],
			"synopsis":"Return to the Red Alert continuity of the esteemed Command & Conquer RTS franchise in this full-fledged series sequel. Red Alert 3 breaks new ground in the RTS genre, featuring a fully co-operative campaign while bringing back the series' light-hearted style and classic, action-oriented gameplay.<br><br>In Red Alert 3, the desperate leadership of a doomed Soviet Union travels back in time to change history and restore the glory of Mother Russia. The time travel mission goes awry, creating an alternate timeline where technology has followed an entirely different evolution, a new superpower has been thrust on to the world stage, and World War III is raging. The Empire of the Rising Sun has risen in the East, making World War III a three-way struggle between the Soviets, the Allies, and the Empire with armies fielding wacky and wonderful weapons and technologies like Tesla coils, heavily armed War Blimps, teleportation, armored bears, intelligent dolphins, floating island fortresses, and transforming tanks.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Decimation Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/15",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The battle for global conquest rages on in this map pack featuring 6 new maps for Red Alert 3! Download this action packed add-on and annihilate your foes on these 2, 3, and 4 player skirmish maps for use in both online and offline play. Master your army and perfect your strategy on land, sea, and air as you wage war across Deep End, Pier Pressure, Repair Bay, Neon Crisis, Dreadnaught Alley, and Wrong Steppe."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=24ezB9sgY0s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SjALEbfKNIY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NEC9O65otkE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T4waUt-k05U"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944932-command-and-conquer-red-alert-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Command-and-Conquer-Red-Alert-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/comman-and-conquer-red-alert-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/command-conquer-red-alert-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Command & Conquer Wiki",
				"url":"http://cnc.wikia.com/wiki/Command_%26_Conquer:_Red_Alert_3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":342,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["iNiS"],
			"synopsis":"Lips, a music franchise exclusively from Xbox 360, is the only singing game that offers wireless motion-sensitive microphones and the ability to sing from your own music collection. Start channeling your favorite pop star, because it's you, your friends and, most important, your music that makes Lips the world's ultimate party experience. Offering interactive motion-sensitive microphones to make your party rock all night long, Lips encourages players to toss apprehensions out the window and join the party.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable tracks",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/11",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"397 tracks available for download at the marketplace"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Number One Hits",
				"releaseDate":"2009/10/20",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":6,
				"synopsis":"Grab your friends and family and warm up those vocal chords! \"Lips: Number One Hits\" sets the stage for the ultimate singing party with a new collection of global chart-topping songs to satisfy even the choosiest of performers. So regardless if your preferred stage is an amphitheatre or just your living room, everyone will love the latest from Xbox 360's exclusive singing franchise."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Canta en Espa&ntildeol",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/13",
				"type":6,
				"synopsis":"Only released in Spain, features songs in spanish."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Deutsche Partyknaller",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/13",
				"type":6,
				"synopsis":"Only released in Germany, features songs in german."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Party Classics",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/26",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":6,
				"synopsis":"\"Lips: Party Classics\" will feature 40 delightfully appealing songs on-disc from artists like the Spice Girls, KISS, Village People, Tiffany, Gloria Gaynor, The B-52's, Chumbawumba and more. Avatar integration, unlockable Avatar awards, gameplay challenges and now USB microphone support are just some of the features in \"Lips: Party Classics\" that will keep the singing party going all night."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"I Love the 80s",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/02",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":6,
				"synopsis":"\"Lips: I Love The 80s\", the latest title in the \"Lips\" franchise exclusive to Xbox 360 takes us back to a time when hair was big and shoulder pads were bigger! The game includes 40 of the most memorable tracks of the 80s including iconic hits like Spandau Ballet's Gold, Kim Carnes' Bette Davis Eyes, and the feel-good classic Walking On Sunshine by Katrina & The Waves."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H2-4ikGejHY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gy67b1MGqMA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TRDFEMhKMZ0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/950900-lips/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lips/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lips/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lips"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":343,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sand Grain Studios"],
			"synopsis":"The intensity of first-person-shooters and extreme sports collide in NPPL's Championship Paintball 2009. Feel the adrenaline of intense tournament and woodsball action like never before as you take your game to the next level with this release from the #1 publisher in paintball video games. With the most authentic and realistic paintball game to date, you'll feel like you're right in the action!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=39A0fyTy7js"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y8TjE3XK1ao"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NPPL-Championship-Paintball-2009/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nppl-championship-paintball-09/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nppl-championship-paintball-2009"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":344,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Yuke's Media Creations"],
			"synopsis":"The #1 fighting game franchise in the world upholds its commitment to providing gamers with the definitive simulation of live WWE programming. Featuring added depth and realism, along with a first-ever co-op story mode, WWE SmackDown vs. Raw 2009 enables players to come together and experience the virtual world of the WWE. On your own, you're great, but together, you're unstoppable.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Uxk5avKy-xk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LYsKrQNBuQE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945632-wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-2009/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/WWE-SmackDown-vs-RAW-2009/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-2009/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-2009"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":345,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["DICE"],
			"synopsis":"Mirror's Edge introduces players to Faith, a \"runner\" in a world where communication channels are highly monitored and the movement of human traffic is closely watched. When Faith's sister gets framed for a murder she did not commit, Faith finds herself on the edge of the city, on the wrong side of the law.<br><br>Mirror's Edge delivers players straight into the shoes of this modern day heroine as she traverses the vertigo-inducing cityscape, engaging in intense combat, fast-paced chases and challenging puzzles. With a never-before-seen sense of movement and perspective, players are drawn into Faith's world.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Pure Time Trials",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/19",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Mirror's Edge gameplay distilled down to its purest form and its purest vision in nine races across seven all-new and totally redesigned Time Trial maps. No cops, no guns, no city. Pure aesthetics, agility and flow that will challenge any Runner."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2N1TJP1cxmo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PEgOamzPm-k"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/941951-mirrors-edge-2008/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mirrors-Edge/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mirrors-edge/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mirrors-edge-2008"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Mirror's Edge Wiki",
				"url":"http://mirrorsedge.wikia.com/wiki/Mirror%27s_Edge_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":346,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Konami"],
			"synopsis":"The 2009 installment of the award-winning sports franchise brings a raft of extensive new additions that will further bridge the gap between PES and the real thing. The new game has undergone a stunning graphical update to ensure its players look and move even more like their real-life counterparts. Similarly, all-new options allow users to tailor the game to their own tastes, while new moves, innovative new control elements and key online elements will further the realism of the new game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F41vW23SKDU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kVjCm1Z46BQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X3mbNfW1xyQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4tVfQHJbVs8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/949452-pro-evolution-soccer-2009/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pro-Evolution-Soccer-2009/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pes-2009/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pro-evolution-soccer-2009"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":347,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Midway Amusement Games"],
			"synopsis":"When a cataclysmic force merges conquerors from two universes, conflict is inevitable. Kombat forces friends to fight, worlds to collide, and unlikely alliances to be forged. In order to save all they know, the heroes and villains of Mortal Kombat must wage war against the combined might of the DC Universe (DCU). How can either side prevail when rage blinds them to the dark threat poised to destroy them all?<br><br>For the first time ever Scorpion, Sub Zero and the warriors from Midway's billion-dollar fighting franchise face off against Batman, Superman and other iconic and powerful DC Super Heroes, featuring signature attacks for both sides and a unique and intertwining storyline, written as a collaboration between the Mortal Kombat creative team and top comic scribes Jimmy Palmiotti and Justin Gray. Choose your side and challenge your opponents with a new fighting system including Freefall Kombat and Klose Kombat along with dynamic multi-tiered environments. Plus, pick your favorite character from MK or DCU and pursue a fighting adventure in the new single player mode with an intertwined storyline and two unique perspectives.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QEoKLNYNC-g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=au789BgCiL0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943567-mortal-kombat-vs-dc-universe/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mortal-Kombat-vs-DC/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mortal-kombat-vs-dc-universe/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mortal-kombat-vs-dc-universe"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Mortal Kombat Wiki",
				"url":"http://mortalkombat.wikia.com/wiki/Mortal_Kombat_vs._DC_Universe"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":348,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"Enter a snowboarding world of total freedom. You can create your own experience in this game, and choose when, where, how and with whom you want to ride. Developed in close collaboration with Olympic Gold Medalist Shaun White - the most successful snowboarder in the history of the sport. Bomb down open-world mountain ranges in hot spots across the globe and seek out real-life friend in fully-integrated online runs.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Glamour Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/01/07",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get ready for new gear that's guaranteed to turn heads on the mountain! With new boards, jackets, pants and a bunch more, we will get you outfitted from head to toe in style with this first Shaun White Snowboarding gear pack."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"The Mile High Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/01/15",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Combine attitude with altitude in this pack, and get some new gear and a brand new mountain."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"The Freebie Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/01/15",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Here's an opportunity to grab some great new gear for guys and girls FOR FREE. With this pack you can dress up your character, and flex your style riding one of the boards from our contest winners. Who said nothing in life is free?"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lopJH-FbTXs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uHJlowvs_Fw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Shaun-White-Snowboarding/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/shaun-white-snowboarding/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/shaun-white-snowboarding"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":349,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Valve", "Certain Affinity"],
			"synopsis":"Setting out to do for co-op gaming what Counter-Strike did for team combat, Left 4 Dead is an ambitious survival horror game. Running on the Source engine, Left 4 Dead leaves four armed survivors of a world overrun with zombies, and they must fight their way out to escape the outbreak.<br><br>Designed for co-op play, the four players must work together to finish each stage of the game, lending each other artillery support, sharing ammo and rescuing each other when zombies are on top of them. In addition to the standard four players as humans, another four players can be amongst the masses of assaulting zombies, seeking to take down the other players. Zombie players might even find themselves become one of the four mutant \"boss\" zombies, who have unique powers that can be used to devastate, injure, tie up, mark and track, confuse, or even humiliate the gun-toting human survivors.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Survival Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/21",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Free pack that added the Survival game mode which requires players to see how long they can last against increasingly difficult waves of infected. Also included two complete campaigns for Versus Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Crash Course",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/29",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Left 4 Dead's Crash Course starts with our Survivors right after their rescue helicopter from the No Mercy campaign crash lands on the outskirts of town. This two chapter campaign includes Co-op, Survival and Versus action, and ten new achievements."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"The Sacrifice",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/05",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The Sacrifice adds a new campaign that links the end of the \"Blood Harvest\" campaign, with the original survivor's appearance in Left 4 Dead 2's \"The Passing\" DLC. It follows our Survivors to their ultimate test, who will sacrifice themselves so the others may live? The Sacrifice is fully playable in Campaign, Versus and Survival."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qvOGCZPDv7g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e_EqBfFdkEE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Versus Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=soiHpPEKclQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/937407-left-4-dead/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Left-4-Dead/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/left-4-dead/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/left-4-dead"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Left 4 Dead Wiki",
				"url":"http://left4dead.wikia.com/wiki/Left_4_Dead_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":350,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"NCAA Basketball 09's strategic gameplay features challenge gamers to replicate their school's style of play, set the tempo and win. Whether your school plays up tempo looking to push the ball in transition, runs a half-court offense that utilizes the clock and limits possessions or features a balanced attack that combines transition offense with set plays, NCAA Basketball 09 rewards the strategic gamer and emphasizes team specific styles of play. The game features Division I coaches in-game for the first time. Each coach will provide real time instruction and feedback, helping gamers control the tempo by executing their team's offense and defense to perfection.<br><br>This year on Xbox 360, NCAA Basketball 09 operates on a gameplay engine with over 1,000 new animation sequences that deliver a more responsive experience with improved ball physics and more intelligent AI. The animation system enables gamers to apply pressure defense with full-court presses and traps. Plus, improved AI and animations enable quicker players to get up and down the floor faster and make better decisions running the lanes and driving to the rim. Animations can be interrupted at any time, enabling you to read and respond to the action on the floor, just like real life.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I7XXSNo7YqE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=madcmDIg_pA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NCAA-Basketball-09/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ncaa-basketball-09/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ncaa-basketball-09"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":351,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Zoe Mode"],
			"synopsis":"Get ready for your close-up. You're in the Movies brings the cool factor to kitsch as you live out your dreams of becoming a scream queen, zombie or kung fu fighter. This game is the first and only game of its kind to literally transport players into a magical world of cinema mixed with the hilarious world of improvisation. Using the Xbox LIVE Vision camera, players' actions are captured and placed into short, riotous films. Performances never end up on the cutting-room floor, and are never the same.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ScYnLrpJmqQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mr5oTTg6IxI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Youre-in-the-Movies/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/youre-in-the-movies/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/youre-in-the-movies"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":352,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Games"],
			"synopsis":"Live out your dream as a singing sensation with Karaoke Revolution Presents: American Idol Encore 2! Play with friends and family online using the brand new co-op head-to-head mode, or compete in front of all three American Idol judges and sing your way to stardom. Tailor your game experience with all-new enhanced and customizable characters, features and downloadable songs. Are you ready to be the next American Idol?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MMtOq4lqAMM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TAPHHUfKTas"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Karaoke-Revolution-American-Idol-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/karaoke-revolution-american-idol-encore-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/karaoke-revolution-presents-american-idol-encore-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":353,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"Building on the success of Naruto: Rise of a Ninja, this new action adventure takes the story to a deeper level within the Naruto Universe. Now a respected ninja, Naruto evolves into a mature and strong hero. However, with his new status comes responsibility, and Naruto will soon find himself surrounded by conflict. Forced to relive bitter memories, Naruto's best friend Sasuke strikes out on a self-destructive quest for power. Now with the help of his friends, Naruto must confront Sasuke and save him before it's too late. Team up with multiple characters, explore open 3D environments and challenge some of the fiercest enemies from the Naruto Universe.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jbmN1FRiV88"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mK3O-az90B0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VcZHFRhtZJ0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OKC8bfP9N40"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/950874-naruto-the-broken-bond/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Naruto-The-Broken-Bond/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/naruto-broken-bond/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/naruto-the-broken-bond"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Narutopedia",
				"url":"http://naruto.wikia.com/wiki/Naruto:_The_Broken_Bond"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":354,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Black Box"],
			"synopsis":"EA's dominating racing series takes a left turn with this uniquely action-oriented entry in the franchise, where players use their driving skills honed in previous NFS games to control their vehicle in dangerous, high speeds encounters. The game features international movie star, Maggie Q, as the lead character in the big-budget live-action sequences that propel the story forward as players get behind the wheel. Undercover takes the franchise back to its roots and re-introduces break-neck cop chases, the world's hottest cars and spectacular highway battles.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Collector's Edition Upgrade",
				"releaseDate":"2008/11/17",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Take your experience to the next level with the Need for Speed Undercover Collector's Edition. This digital upgrade includes five brand new cars available for use in career mode (2006 Koeniggsigg CCX, 2006 Dodge Challenger Concept, 2007 Porsche Cayman S, 2007 BMW Z4 M, 2007 Mercedes SL 65 AMG) plus twelve new circuit, sprint and checkpoint track configurations. Also included are specially tuned versions of ten existing cars which are available in quick race & online modes, plus 35 exclusive vinyls for adding a unique visual style to any of your cars."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Challenge Series Expansion",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/27",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Think you've mastered the world of Undercover? Think again. This huge upgrade offers 60 new events, including two new game modes (highway wars and highway checkpoint) where you'll have the ability to earn up to three new cars as you race your way through hair-raising traffic. Best of all, this content is absolutely free!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Boss Car Bundle",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/27",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Blow away your competition with this explosive car pack, featuring eight unique boss cars available for use in any online race or offline career event. Race your way to the top of the leaderboards with each of these cars: Carmen's Shelby GT500, Chase's BMW M6, Chau Wu's Mercedes-Benz CLS 63 AMG, G-Mac's Lamborghini Gallardo LP560-4 , Hector's Nissan 370Z (Z34), Nickel's Dodge Viper SRT10, Rose's Porsche 911 GT2 and Zack's Volkswagen Scirocco."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mkHJzHIbQQg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gCkRSVChEfE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qAq4DEGwcVU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Need-for-Speed-Undercover/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/need-for-speed-undercover/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/need-for-speed-undercover"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Need for Speed Wiki",
				"url":"http://nfs.wikia.com/wiki/Need_for_Speed:_Undercover"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":355,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Liquid Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"As the King of Iolcus, Jason had everything - a prosperous kingdom, the respect of his peers and a beautiful fianc&eacute. But when she was assassinated on their wedding day, Jason vowed to take revenge on her killers - to do anything to restore her life and earn back the respect of his subjects. To accomplish this heroic feat, Jason must seek out the Golden Fleece and with the help of Greek mythology's greatest heroes, set sail on the most epic voyage of all.<br><br>An epic scale action-RPG, Rise of the Argonauts immerses gamers in a gladiatorial adventure set in wondrously imagined vision of ancient Greece. With deep exploration and epic quests, players live a life of brutal combat as they lead a team of iconic warriors - including Jason, Hercules and Atalanta- through a world ruled by mythological gods.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=orGI9EjBkm0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yWQPj1nowqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939162-rise-of-the-argonauts/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rise-of-the-Argonauts/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rise-of-the-argonauts/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rise-of-the-argonauts"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":356,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"Rock Band Track Pack Volume 2 is a standalone software product that allows owners of Rock Band Special Edition, Rock Bandor Rock Band 2 peripherals to keep the party going with more hit songs from the pantheon of rock music. The 20-song pack features an electrifying mix of classic hits and current favorites, including songs by Lynyrd Skynyrd, M&ouml;tley Cr&uuml;e, Red Hot Chili Peppers and Blondie.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TfqbV-KHAkk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TRXn8FQtXsM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rock-Band-Track-Pack-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rock-band-track-pack-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Rock Band Wiki",
				"url":"http://rockband.wikia.com/wiki/Rock_Band_Track_Pack_Vol._2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":357,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sonic Team"],
			"synopsis":"Everyone's favorite hedgehog breaks new ground yet maintains his roots in a game that combines amazing next gen capabilities with classic Sonic 2D gameplay! Developed by renowned studio Sonic Team, Sonic Unleashed utilizes the powerful \"Hedgehog Engine\" to mesh seamless 3D and classic 2D camera transitions, whilst delivering a rich and expansive world with multiple paths to choose from.<br><br>Having been broken apart by the evil Dr Eggman, it's down to Sonic to put the pieces of the world back together again by retrieving the power of the chaos emeralds. In doing so, Sonic will find himself in a race against time and faced with an unusual situation that will challenge him in ways never before seen. By completing a wide variety of action-packed stages, spanning the seven broken continents of the world, gamers will need to unleash Sonic's amazing abilities to save the world, and himself!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Chun-Nan Adventure Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/12",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Six new singleplayer missions for Sonic Unleashed set in the \"Chun-Nan\", a mountainous region best known for its dragon roads and majestic peaks. Four missions take place during the day as Sonic and two take place during the night as the Werehog. Half of the pack is remixed \"Hard Mode\" versions of existing levels."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Spagonia Adventure Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/26",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Six new singleplayer missions for Sonic Unleashed set in the \"Spagonia\", a beautiful area filled with cobble stoned streets, outdoor cafes, red-rooftops and old buildings rich with history. Four missions take place during the day as Sonic and two take place during the night as the Werehog. Half of the pack is remixed \"Hard Mode\" versions of existing levels."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Holoska Adventure Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/09",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Six new singleplayer missions for Sonic Unleashed set in the \"Holoska\", a northern land covered in snow and dotted with houses made of ice. Four missions take place during the day as Sonic and two take place during the night as the Werehog. Half of the pack is remixed \"Hard Mode\" versions of existing levels."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Mazuri Adventure Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/30",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Six new singleplayer missions for Sonic Unleashed set in the \"Mazuri\", an exotic town built on reddish-brown soil. Four missions take place during the day as Sonic and two take place during the night as the Werehog. Half of the pack is remixed \"Hard Mode\" versions of existing levels."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Apotos & Shamar Adventure Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/21",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Nine new singleplayer missions for Sonic Unleashed set in the \"Apotos\" and \"Shamar\" regions of the game, a quaint seaside town and ancient ruins in a desert oasis. Five missions take place during the day as Sonic and four take place during the night as the Werehog. Half of the pack is remixed \"Hard Mode\" versions of existing levels."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Empire City & Adabat Adventure Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/11",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Nine new singleplayer missions for Sonic Unleashed set in the \"Empire City\" and \"Adabat\" regions of the game, a high-rise metropolis and an exotic jungle strewn with ancient ruins. Five missions take place during the day as Sonic and four take place during the night as the Werehog. Half of the pack is remixed \"Hard Mode\" versions of existing levels."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j-ADCH064F4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WqnZ0R1Hu5Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945571-sonic-unleashed/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sonic-Unleashed/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sonic-unleashed/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sonic-unleashed"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sonic News Network",
				"url":"http://sonic.wikia.com/wiki/Sonic_Unleashed"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":358,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Crystal Dynamics"],
			"synopsis":"For generations, stories have been told of the fearsome weapon of Thor, the Norse god of thunder. Legend holds that Thor's hammer had the power to smash mountains into valleys and to destroy even the gods. For more than a thousand years it has existed only as a myth...until now.<br><br>In an ancient ruin on the floor of the Mediterranean Sea, Lara Croft uncovers proof of the Norse underworld and the mythical hammer. As she attempts to unravel the secrets behind these myths, Lara's perilous journey leads her toward a forgotten power that, if unleashed, could lay waste to all civilization.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Classic Costumes",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/29",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download Lara's iconic \"Classic\" and \"Legend\" outfits, for free!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Wetsuit Costume Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/01/06",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download two hot new wetsuits for Lara, totally free!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Beneath the Ashes",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/24",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"\"Beneath the Ashes\" is an all-new level that extends the Tomb Raider: Underworld experience. Lara Croft returns to the remains of Croft Manor in order to find a powerful artifact hidden in a mysterious centuries-old labyrinth deep beneath the estate. This download features a brand new action-packed adventure full of new challenges to overcome, an all new enemy and six new outfits!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Lara's Shadow",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/10",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Play Tomb Raider from a new perspective. Experience the world as the Doppelganger, a dark and deadly double of Lara with superhuman powers and instructions to end the Croft lineage once and for all. With the Doppelganger's unique Shadow Powers you can defeat enemies with brutal melee attacks. Use super-human agility to make it past challenges Lara could never pass. Fulfil this new mission and become the ultimate instrument of revenge."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Designer Costume Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download these two new costumes. Created by fashion designers, voted for and picked by the Tomb Raider fans."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aM1MqQua4hY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q-Jn3BFa5qU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8esvXB__kjU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943494-tomb-raider-underworld/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tomb-Raider-Underworld/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tomb-raider-underworld/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tomb-raider-underworld"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tomb Raider Wiki",
				"url":"http://www.tomb-raider.wikia.com/wiki/Tomb_Raider:_Underworld"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":359,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Square Enix"],
			"synopsis":"In ancient times, mysterious artifacts referred to as Remnants were discovered all over the world. People used these objects for their awesome powers - a choice that eventually began to cause a rift in the world's balance. Equality was replaced by those who ruled and those who were ruled over. War was inevitable. A thousand years later is when this story begins...<br><br>Rush lives with his sister Irina on secluded Eulam Island, far from the power struggles for Remnants that are occurring back on the mainland. However, this peaceful life is shattered when his sister is suddenly kidnapped by a mysterious group of soldiers right before his eyes. He immediately sets off after them, unaware of the evils of the outside world but determined to find his sister at any cost.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Key of Ancient Ruins",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/08",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Unlock the gates to the Ancient Ruins with this key, and discover what mysteries lie within its crumbling depths."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Challenge Pack 1: Purgatory's Sins",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/08",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Level up your game with this pack of ultra-challenging guild tasks. Adequate game progression is necessary."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"March to War Set",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/15",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Boost your tactical strength with this pack of three formations. Makes available the formations Goblet, Scatterswarm, and Catapult."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Challenge Pack 2: The Price of Lies",
				"releaseDate":"2008/12/29",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Up for a tougher challenge? Add this pack of the most difficult guild tasks yet. Adequate game progression is necessary."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UDpITm3y6zA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NET2fQcRxxM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JwNaFByOf54"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1eBeVq7eUcg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NKCpa7D98EA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939444-the-last-remnant/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Last-Remnant/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/last-remnant/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-last-remnant"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Last Remnant Wiki",
				"url":"http://lastremnant.wikia.com/wiki/The_Last_Remnant_Wiki_-_The_Last_Remnant_Guide"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":360,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sandblast"],
			"synopsis":"In Path of the Furon, the destructive alien Crypto is taking on the funkdafied times of the 1970s, adding a bit of disco destruction to the people of earth. Picking up where Destroy All Humans! Big Willy Unleashed leaves off, Crypto finds himself attacked by a mysterious new enemy that's threatens the entire Furon race. With a conspiracy quickly formed that threatens his way of life, Crypto embarks on a journey to gain enlightenment from an alien Kung Fu master, unlocking new powers that will let him save the Furons once again.<br><br>Path of the Furon expands on the open world format of the previous Destroy All Humans! titles - players will be able to decide what they want to obliterate and what they will spare, with five large open worlds on the ground and in the air (thanks to new augmentations to Crypto's UFO) to obliterate with new weapons and new alien powers.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TvyeHEGXcSA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3G9EYw4Wjck"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cr0095lOMeg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qBFZZ_lciaY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Destroy-All-Humans-Path-of-the-Furon/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/destroy-all-humans-path-of-furon/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/destroy-all-humans!-path-of-the-furon"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Destroy All Humans Wiki",
				"url":"http://destroyallhumans.wikia.com/wiki/Destroy_All_Humans!_Path_of_the_Furon"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":361,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"Escape to experience the new fantasy world of ancient Persia. Masterful storytelling and sprawling environments deliver a brand new adventure that re-opens the Prince of Persia saga. Now you have the freedom to determine how the game evolves in this non-linear adventure. Players will decide how they unfold the storyline by choosing their path in the open-ended world.<br><br>In this strange land, your rogue warrior must utilize all of his skills, along with a whole new combat system, to battle Ahriman's corrupted lieutenants to heal the land from the dark Corruption and restore the light. Also, history;s greatest ally is revealed in the form of Elika, a dynamic AI companion who joins the Prince in his fight to save the world. Gifted with magical powers, she interacts with the player in combat, acrobatics and puzzle-solving, enabling the Prince to reach new heights of deadly high-flying artistry through special duo acrobatic moves or devastating fighting combo attacks.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Epilogue",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/05",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"As the Prince and Elika, chased by unleashed Evil forces, enter the Underground Palace area and play a brand new region in the fantastic universe of Prince of Persia. With an all new powers, fighting skills, and bosses you're sure to enjoy hours of additional gameplay and continue the epic saga right from where you left off at the original Prince of Persia (2008)."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mg206YpaXlA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DdZT6HIwoU4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-4aqRiK1YsA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945943-prince-of-persia/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Prince-of-Persia/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/prince-of-persia-retail/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/prince-of-persia"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Prince of Persia Wiki",
				"url":"http://princeofpersia.wikia.com/wiki/Prince_of_Persia_(2008)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":362,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["49Games"],
			"synopsis":"Winter Sports 2: The Next Challenge is an arcade oriented 3D simulation of nine of the most popular winter sports. The player is placed at the center of high level sporting events broadcast live around the world. The excitement of this major international competition is portrayed authentically with commentators, TV cameras and immersive environments.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VmN8u09oJM8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xtiqUeEkL7w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WQ1ri-nNvho"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Winter-Sports-2-The-Next-Challenge/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rtl-winter-sports-2009-na/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/winter-sports-2-the-next-challenge"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":363,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Pandemic Studios"],
			"synopsis":"The Lord of the Rings: Conquest puts players into the thick of the tremendous battle over The One Ring, playing out battles from both sides of the confrontation! Conquest will let players take control of many of the characters and creatures from the series and pit them on any of the franchise's famous battlefields. From Cave-trolls to Oliphaunts to the Balrog and even Sauron, practically the entire universe will be available for battle with up to 150 characters on-screen at any one time. Up to 16 players will be able to clash online, with four players able to play cooperatively through the main campaign either online or via four-player split-screen. And with two distinct campaigns to play through, including an original take on what would happen if Sauron regained control of the One Ring, the game promises plenty of scenarios to wage battle through.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sPuM45X4k0E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MGaH_Xj2cO4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N6UFrHqPQj0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZM2uT5QTWek"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944924-the-lord-of-the-rings-conquest/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lord-of-the-Rings-Conquest/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lotr-conquest/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-lord-of-the-rings-conquest"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"One Wiki to Rule Them All",
				"url":"http://lotr.wikia.com/wiki/The_Lord_of_the_Rings:_Conquest"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":364,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bongfish GmbH"],
			"synopsis":"Developed in conjunction with world-renowned snowboarding movie creator Absinthe Films, Stoked captures the pioneering spirit of professional back country riders. Exhilarating snowboarding experiences are born from dynamic backcountry conditions. The riders who brave and master these conditions are the stuff of legend in Absinthe videos and on the pages of snowboarding magazines. The look and style of these riders are emulated across the world. In Stoked, it's your turn to become a legendary rider and wow the world on the Xbox Live online entertainment network by becoming an absolute snowboarding phenomenon.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iHHkC4AqW78"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1krQWkuSVjk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XA65X0LasnQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Stoked/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/stoked/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/stoked"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":365,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Black Box"],
			"synopsis":"Skate 2 brings gamers to New San Vanelona, a city that's been rebuilt after an unspeakable disaster five years ago. Equipped with double the bag of tricks, players are tasked to rebuild their career and revive the skate scene. Now with the ability to get off-board and move objects around, gamers can create their own epic spots and challenges which can then be uploaded, shared and experienced by others around the world.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Rob Dyrdrek's Fantasy Plaza Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/19",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Skate the inspiration for the new show Rob Dyrdek's Fantasy Factory, including the surrounding area located in downtown LA."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"San Van Classic Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/26",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Enjoy 3 remastered areas of the original skate game. It includes the community center, the parkade and the elementary school. Use all the new abilities of Skate 2 in your favorite Skate 1 places."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Throwback Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Unlock the retro gear and celebrate the past with some short shorts, knee high socks, tie dyed shirts and crazy sunglasses. While you're at it, play some air guitar and throw out the peace signs with our classic gestures."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Maloof Money Cup Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/09",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Hit the course of one of skateboarding's biggest contests, then battle some of skating's heaviest hitters for some serious Maloof loot."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6wrmaSFkICA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G5I1t_KAKmM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HvOj7gx_iTQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944909-skate-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Skate-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/skate-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/skate-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":366,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blue Castle Games"],
			"synopsis":"MLB Front Office Manager lets gamers do everything a real-life baseball GM can do to develop a team from Spring Training through a full MLB season, into the playoffs and the World Series. Using Major League teams and players, gamers will create their own fictional baseball universe and build their reputation into elite status. Gamers can replace aging veterans with rookies, scout the Minor Leagues, make blockbuster trades, and even participate in bidding wars for posted players from Japan as they make their way to the Hall of Fame.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zqlAHzu91VA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2 (Dev Diaries)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YVBuQsCpsmE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kBVsJ1eu41E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MLB-Front-Office-Manager/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mlb-front-office-manager/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mlb-front-office-manager"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":367,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bandai Namco Games"],
			"synopsis":"Follow Afro Samurai as he fights to become the number one warrior, a title currently held by Justice, the man who killed Afro's father when he was a child. The game follows the plot of the original series with added material and background for fans and new comers alike.<br><br>Blood is beautiful in this hip hop infused action adventure as Samuel L. Jackson reprises his role as Afro and Ninja Ninja. A striking art style gives Afro Samurai a truly unique look and feel across beautifully animated open environments as he wages war against his adversaries to become number one. Using an innovative gameplay system, enemy AI is affected by the beat of the musical score produced by RZA of Wu-Tang Clan fame. These dynamic battles ensure stylized encounters throughout the game that affect the overall tone of gameplay. Slice and dismember opponents as Afro acrobatically leaps from one location to the next, interacting with anything and everything in the environment to help him on his journey.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jYvXnsqe9Fc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nh5OpRwrIYs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/940049-afro-samurai/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Afro-Samurai/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/afro-samurai/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/afro-samurai"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":368,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Monolith Productions"],
			"synopsis":"A routine assignment to locate the president of Armacham Technology Corporation in connection with an unfolding hostage crisis turns into a desperate battle for survival after an explosion decimates the city and unleashes Alma Wade, the terrifying supernatural menace at the center of Armacham's highly classified Project Origin. As Alma's power swells out of control, special forces Sgt. Michael Becket and his squad must battle through an apocalyptic landscape of shattered buildings and buckled streets in search of clues for how to destroy her. The more Becket learns about Armacham's secret experiments and reckless agenda, the more he begins to suspect that he's somehow linked to the crisis and may be the only one capable of averting total disaster.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Toy Soldiers Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/16",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Experience FEAR 2 multiplayer from a new perspective. Players are only inches tall as they battle inside a pinball machine, a hospital lab room, and a playground sandbox. FullTilt: Battle inside a retro 1970's era pinball machine, \"Snake Fist\" style! Flippers, targets, spinners and pop-bumpers provide cover for the fast paced action. Multi-level playfield and authentic sounds set the mood for destruction! Cockroach: A blood drenched hospital room filled with heart pounding action. Climb up electrical cords, laboratory equipment and pill bottles in a tightly connected environment. Recess: Wage mayhem from the top of a giant sandcastle to the cockpit of a toy bulldozer! Go commando and blend in with plastic army men!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Armored Front Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/15",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Continue the mechanized mayhem in this new map pack! Experience two new battlegrounds for F.E.A.R. 2's \"Armored Front\" multiplayer mode. Conductor: Push your way out of a train yard into the vast and open-ended junction station built around a turntable. EPAs will battle their way through the ground floor as infantry can choose to either support from below, or scale the heights of the station and engage in long-range combat. Decoy: Put your skill to the test in this full-scale training ground for Replica soldiers! Once a controlled arena for combat exercises, now it is a full-blown assault for control between Replica and ATC. Watch out for ambushes, and don't let the pop-up target dummies fool you!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Reborn",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/03",
				"achievements":230,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Experience four brand new single-player levels in this additional DLC campaign for F.E.A.R. 2! Coinciding with the events seen in the full game, you will experience the chaos of Alma's aftermath from an entirely new point of view: that of Replica Soldier 813. Your mission begins with an orbital Powered Armor drop to reinforce your fellow Replica squad... But not everything is as it seems. Supernatural events run wild in the apocalyptic remains of Auburn. Another voice is beckoning you; contradicting orders from Replica command. Find out the answer to this, and many new questions, in the DLC campaign F.E.A.R. 2: Reborn!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kBTnDwW3i48"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lGq30NVc-SE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932146-fear-2-project-origin/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/FEAR-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/project-origin/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fear-2-project-origin"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"F.E.A.R. Wiki",
				"url":"http://fear.wikia.com/wiki/F.E.A.R._2:_Project_Origin"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":369,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tamsoft"],
			"synopsis":"Evil crawls the night, and only a super-hot vixen in a string bikini and a cowboy hat can slaughter the undead to save us all! Take on the role of Aya or her little sister Saki, both of whom will need to put their legendary samurai skills to the test in order to battle legions of zombies terrorizing their city. Armed with only their swords and their beauty, these deadly sisters will stop at nothing to rid their home of the zombie threat. Every person they meet and enemy they battle gets them closer to understanding who or what is behind this zombie outbreak and putting an end to it. Babes, bikinis, zombies and swords ... who could ask for more!",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Anna: Extra Costume Data [SPECIAL]",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A new costume for Anna, giving her a black dress, silver tiara and sunglasses, really bringing out her sex appeal. Can be used during the game as a new costume for Anna. Can also be viewed in View Mode. (This costume does not alter Anna's abilities)."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Himiko: Extra Character Data",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Allows Himiko, a new enemy character, to be used during the main game. Also allows her to be viewed in View Mode. Experience the violence of Himiko and her own twist on Aya's double sword style. She can also earn experience and level up in the same way as other characters."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Misery: Extra Character Data",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Allows Misery, a new enemy character, to be used during the main game. Also allows her to be viewed in View Mode. Experience the violence of Misery and her unique range of attacks. She can also earn experience and level up in the same way as other characters."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Anna: Extra Costume Data [LEGACY]",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A new costume for Anna. Designed in a military style. Can be used during the game as a new costume for Anna. Can also be viewed in View Mode. (This costume does not alter Anna's abilities)."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Saki: Extra Costume Data [SPECIAL]",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A new costume for Saki from her personal wardrobe. A checked mini-skirt, sweater and red ribbon brings out Saki's cuter side. Can be used during the game as a new costume for Saki. Can also be viewed in View Mode. (This costume does not alter Saki's abilities, aside from making her even cuter)."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Aya: Extra Costume Data [SPECIAL]",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A new costume for Aya from her personal wardrobe. Offers taunting glimpses of her front and back. Can be used during the game as a new costume for Aya. Can also be viewed in View Mode. (This costume does not alter Aya's abilities, aside from making her even sexier)."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Reiko: Extra Character Data",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Allows you to experience the sword and gun combo of Reiko in battle. She can also earn experience and level up in the same way as other characters."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Aya: Extra Costume Data [LEGACY]",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A nostalgic look for Aya, this is a flashy renewal of her original Onechanbara costume. Can be used during the game as a new costume for Aya. Can also be viewed in View Mode. (This costume does not alter Aya's abilities)."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Saki: Extra Costume Data [LEGACY]",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A nostalgic look for Saki, this is a flashy renewal of her original Onechanbara costume. Can be used during the game as a new costume for Saki. Can also be viewed in View Mode. (This costume does not alter Saki's abilities)."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D-dW9SOfebM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jAzUeGvJoUc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/929267-onechanbara-bikini-samurai-squad/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Onechanbara/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/onechanbara-bikini-samurai-squad/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/onechanbara-bikini-samurai-squad"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Onechanbara Wiki",
				"url":"http://onechanbara.wikia.com/wiki/OneChanbara_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":370,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gaijin Entertainment", "TopWare Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"X-Blades a third-person hack-and-slash action title featuring an enchanting heroine that destroys anything in her path using guns, blades, magic, and a healthy dose of stylish flair. Players assume the role of Ayumi, a stunningly seductive yet tenacious heroine who battles enemies with her pistol blades, acrobatic ability, and magic spells. The story unfolds revealing demonic powers and spectacular landscapes, all ripe for exploration and battles. X-Blades features a special combination of cinematic style, stunning animation, and relentless, high speed gameplay.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Sky Levels",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/27",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Sky Levels adds three levels that were not originally included in the Xbox 360 version."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8sTskYekYWU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m1xsyxhrmK4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945132-x-blades/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/XBlades/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/x-blades/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/x-blades"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":371,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Zoe Mode"],
			"synopsis":"Disney Sing It: High School Musical 3: Senior Year is a karaoke-based video game that allows players to perform 10 memorable songs from the film High School Musical 3: Senior Year as well as selected songs from the first two High School Musical movies. Players can perform with their friends or sing solo with the stars. Players can also select any song and difficulty level in single or multiplayer mode, which allows for teams up to 8 players.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z6fKbKW0vXc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4s1ckVN_wUg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sing-It-High-School-Musical-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/disney-sing-it-high-school-musical-3-senior-year/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":372,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SimBin Development Team"],
			"synopsis":"Race Pro recreates a breathtaking reality giving gamers the ultimate racing simulation experience - with precision physics and handling, racers will feel every bend and burst of acceleration along with every emotion from pre-race tension in the pit lanes to the exhilaration of capturing the checker flag. Race Pro provides unrivalled realism and deep immersion into the racing world through ultra realistic car models and official FIA championships and tracks. Putting players in the driving seats of their simulated racing careers, racers will have the opportunity to work their way up the leader boards through intense training and winning key races. Race Pro has something for everyone, allowing players of all levels to pick up and play, while offering challenging tracks and advanced modes for the more experienced players.<br><br>Race Pro offers a wealth of cars ranging from 200 to over 1000 horse power, as well as a host of championships including WTCC (World Touring Car Championship), Formula 3000 and Formula BMW. GT cars from manufacturers including Aston Martin and Saleen take their place on the grid as well as production cars such as the Audi R8 and Dodge Viper SRT10. In addition, RACE Pro is exclusively bringing all the WTCC cars from manufacturers Alfa Romeo, BMW, Chevrolet and Seat to Xbox 360 for the very first time. For a blast of accessible fun, the Mini Cooper Challenge invites players of all abilities to take the wheel.<br><br>Gamers and racing fans alike will experience the thrill of racing these powerful cars on 13 real life tracks covering all continents, of which Macau, Porto and Pau are exclusive to RACE Pro, and US tracks Laguna Seca and Road America are brand new to SimBin fans.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Race Pro Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/28",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"8 cars (40 skins) / 3 tracks: '08 Dodge Challenger SRT8 Production '08 Dodge Challenger SRT8 Race '08 Dodge Charger SRT8 Super Bee Production '08 Dodge Charger SRT8 Super Bee Race '09 Cadillac CTS-V Production '09 Cadillac CTS-V Race '09 Chevrolet Camaro Production '09 Chevrolet Camaro Race Road America Imola (Italy)."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Race Pro Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/28",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"8 cars (52 skins) / 2 Tracks / WTCC 08 season Lada 110 WTCC Honda Accord Euro R Volvo C30 BMW E90 Chevrolet Lacetti Seat Leon TDI Seat Leon TFSI Formula Master Estoril (Portugal) Okayama (Japan)."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Race Pro Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/28",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"9 cars (49 skins) / 4 tracks Pagani Zonda R Volvo Amazon '71 BMW 2002 '68 Mini Cooper S Volvo P1800 Opel Commodore GS3000 '73 BMW 3.0 CSL '74 Chevrolet Corvette '70 Chevrolet Camaro Spa Mid Ohio."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1UvjIb6mwcQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vBlRtTHfYt8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vk1z6TAkiM0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Race-Pro/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/race-pro/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/race-pro"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":373,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Capcom", "Dimps"],
			"synopsis":"The long-awaited fourth entry in the Street Fighter series. Street Fighter IV features a mix of returning favorites such as Ryu, Ken, Chun-Li and Guile along with new characters created for this game, such as Crimson Viper, Abel, El Fuerte, and Rufus. Characters and environments are rendered in stylized 3D, while the game is played in the classic Street Fighter 2D perspective with additional 3D camera flourishes. Six-button controls for the game return, with a host of new special moves and features integrated into the input system. Mixing classic genre-defining game mechanics the franchise is known and loved for with all-new, never-before-seen gameplay systems, Street Fighter IV brings a brand new fighting game to fans the world over.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Power Up Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/01",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Add the exciting new Championship Mode and Replay download functionality to Street Fighter IV."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Complete Alternate Costume Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This pack contains alternate costumes for all 25 characters."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2uOt-XmNrQw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=61PxEDKlEMo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943712-street-fighter-iv/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Street-Fighter-4/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/street-fighter-iv/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/street-fighter-iv"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Street Fighter Wiki",
				"url":"http://streetfighter.wikia.com/wiki/Street_Fighter_IV"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Shoryuken",
				"url":"http://wiki.shoryuken.com/Street_fighter_4"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":374,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tri-Ace"],
			"synopsis":"In the aftermath of World War III, Earth has been ravaged and the population decimated by a deteriorating environment. The countries that survived have joined together to form the Greater Unified Nations and turned their eyes skyward. Edge Maverick and his childhood friend Reimi Saionji are chosen as pioneer members of the Space Reconnaissance Force, created to seek out new worlds beyond the stars. And so, Edge and his crew aboard the Calnus begin their voyage in search of a new haven for humanity ... and a second chance.<br><br>With Star Ocean: The Last Hope, celebrated development studio tri-Ace delivers the fourth entry in its futuristic space opera RPG series. Exhilarating combat expands upon the franchise's famous real-time battle system, introducing amazing graphics and next-gen visual effects.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h3S9wTwBBSQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9ywY4S5Q0MM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=umBTbhk_wLk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/946860-star-ocean-the-last-hope/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Star-Ocean-the-Last-Hope/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/star-ocean-the-last-hope/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/star-ocean-the-last-hope"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Star Ocean Wiki",
				"url":"http://starocean.wikia.com/wiki/Star_Ocean:_The_Last_Hope"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":375,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Swordfish Studios"],
			"synopsis":"In the sequel to 50 Cent: Bulletproof, players again become one of the world's biggest hip-hop stars in an all out battle to protect 50 Cent's assets and to collect payment from a crooked overlord. The game features 50 Cent in a multi-player online drop-in and drop-out co-op world that allows him to call on his G-Unit pals to watch his back in intense gameplay action.<br><br>50 Cent: Blood on the Sand features interactive counter-kills that let the player take control of the finishing moves. And for the first time in a game, 50 Cent finds himself behind the wheel and flight stick in a variety of driving missions and aerial combat challenges. It also comes packed with more exclusive unreleased music from 50 Cent and G-Unit, that provides a new arsenal of beats to listen to as the player battles to regain control of 50's possession's.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rOsVkiHiAPE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1utqEK9Rcos"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yqTSE_idPog"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/50-Cent-Blood-on-the-Sand/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/50-cent-blood-on-the-sand/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/50-cent-blood-on-the-sand"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":376,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rebellion"],
			"synopsis":"War is hell, and the ShellShock franchise delivers gamers to the deepest circles of this hell with the series' second brutal and twisted psychological first person shooter experience.<br><br>At the height of the Vietnam War, a covert ops cargo plane carrying a top-secret consignment known only as 'Whiteknight' is lost over the deepest, uncharted jungles. Special Ops soldiers are immediately dispatched to the scene to retrieve the top secret shipment and one-by-one they disappear without a trace ... until one month later, one of them suddenly walks out of the jungle. Crazed and deranged, something in the jungle had ripped out his humanity, poisoning his soul. Something in the darkness had driven him mad ... and followed him out. Taking the first-person war game and turning it on its head, Shellshock 2: Blood Trails places you in a war where fear takes on a whole new meaning.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=etoiFyApwaY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E11MdYEqWoE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Shellshock-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/shellshock-2-blood-trails/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/shellshock-2-blood-trails"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":377,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Vicious Cycle"],
			"synopsis":"In Eat Lead: The Return of Matt Hazard, videogame action hero Matt Hazard gets his chance to prove once and for all that he is the king of shooters when the new owner of mega game publisher, Marathon Megasoft, gives Matt his comeback role starring in a new title for next-gen consoles that pits him against all of his memorable foes from videogames past. In the world of Eat Lead, however, everything stops being a game and becomes reality when it is clear that someone is using the new game to bring about Matt's death once and for all. With only the mysterious QA to help him, Matt must fight against a legion of Marathon Megasoft catalogue of videogame characters to keep it from being Game Over forever.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5guCRWEhG-g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5s2SuakAc4s"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/954401-eat-lead-the-return-of-matt-hazard/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Eat-Lead/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/eat-lead-the-return-of-matt-hazard/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/eat-lead-the-return-of-matt-hazard"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":378,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ensemble Studios", "Bungie Software"],
			"synopsis":"A strategy game based on the Halo universe, Halo Wars immerses you in an early period of the storied Halo universe, allowing you to experience events leading up to the first Halo title. With the guidance of Serina, a spirited artificial intelligence (A.I.) persona, direct legions of UNSC soldiers, Warthogs, Scorpions, and more, each group having its own strengths and uses in battle. Adventurous commanders can also call upon ancient Forerunner technology, if they are fortunate enough to find it hidden throughout the battlefield.<br><br>In campaign mode, command the armies of the UNSC warship Spirit of Fire, with familiar and new UNSC units in its initial encounters against the Covenant, an alien coalition threatening to obliterate mankind. Covenant forces are also waiting for you to lead them into battle in multiplayer skirmishes via the New Xbox Experience. Call upon an arsenal of new and familiar Covenant units such as Grunts, Elites, Ghosts, and even Scarabs to defeat foes on the battlefield.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Strategic Options",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/19",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"This add-on brings new multiplayer rulesets to Halo Wars. The new rulesets are: Keepaway - capture the flag style game; Tug of War - who can field and maintain the strongest army; Reinforcements - adapt your tactics as you are granted waves of troops."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Historic Battle",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/21",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"This pack adds four new maps to Halo Wars' multiplayer mode that highlight key turning points in the epic war between the UNSC and Covenant forces. These maps are as follows: Blood River - battle a single opponent over a treacherous natural chokepoint; Barrens - engage your enemy in the midst of the Flood; Memorial Basin - two vs. two team play in one of the bloodiest battles in Halo history; and Glacial Ravine - three vs. three action as you fight to control a narrow corridor flanked by energy walls."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wg1kB2VmPE4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G5y61mxFBDE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DceRcyVRYSE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935835-halo-wars/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Halo-Wars/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/halo-wars/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/halo-wars"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Halo Nation",
				"url":"http://halo.wikia.com/wiki/Halo_Wars"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Halopedia",
				"url":"http://www.halopedia.org/Halo_Wars"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":379,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"Major League Baseball 2K9 offers fans improved two-step Precision Pitching controls, deeper Swing Stick batting and quick fielding responses for even greater control of the game. The improved batting controls provide the ability to influence hits with timing and aim, improved hit distribution and variety to deliver more hit types including spray shots, pulls, line drives and long bombs. With more than six years of scouting reports infused into the action on the field, Inside Edge produces remarkably accurate player tendencies to ensure players react to in-game situations as they would in real life. Major League Baseball 2K9 also features new commentary, as Gary Thorne provides the play-by-play calls alongside color analyst Steve Phillips giving a new perspective and more depth for a true-to-life, insightful broadcast. In addition, Living Rosters has been added this season to provide fresh and active roster updates that guarantee every game is current and automatically updated behind the scenes, so players are never late on a trade and always have the hottest players in their starting lineup.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"All Trailers",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p3AFXWBxmVk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xqdr4PnvczI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MLB-2K9/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/major-league-baseball-2k9/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/major-league-baseball-2k9"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":380,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Romania"],
			"synopsis":"Set in conceived version of the future inspired by the best-selling Tom Clancy videogame franchises, this flight combat action game imagines a world where a private military force has cumulated such power that it attacks the USA. Thrust into the cockpits of incredibly powerful and technologically advanced jet fighters, gamers will benefit from hi-tech piloting assistance, providing comfort, security and enhanced perception. As players gain skills and confidence, they will be able to shed the assistance. But before choosing performance over security, they'll have to weigh the risks carefully.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Air Supremacy",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/11",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Secure a powerful fleet of 16 mainstay and prototype aircraft and fight for supremacy in online and single player modes. This download combines three packages: the US Eagles pack, the European Assault pack, and the Russian Falcons pack. Rafale M (Dassault); Saab 37 Viggen (SAAB); Mirage 2000N (Dassault); Mirage 4000 (Dassault); FB-22 (Lockheed); F-4 Phantom II (Boeing); RF-15 Peak Eagle (Boeing); A-12 Avenger II (Boeing); F-111F Aardvark (Lockheed); SR-71 (Lockheed); Mig-31 Foxhound (MIG); Mig-1.42 (MFI); Mig-23 Flogger (YF-113) (Mig); Su-39 (Sukhoi); F18 HARV (Boeing); Razorback (End War plane)"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9lIAQ8t4KLw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bw8-HaIv6sA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943417-tom-clancys-hawx/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tom-Clancys-HAWX/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tom-clancys-hawx/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tom-clancys-hawx"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"H.A.W.X Wiki",
				"url":"http://hawx.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":381,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Electronic Arts"],
			"synopsis":"The console version of Trivial Pursuit brings the party to the living room TV allowing players to customize the experience with several ways to play. Players can connect with friends in classic trivial pursuit mode, hone their knowledge with the single player mode, and gather their buddies and bet on their brains with the high stakes mode where every answer counts.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Movie Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/10",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"For the Movie Buff in everyone! Premiering now, hundreds of new questions for Trivial Pursuit featuring all your favourite films. Download the free movie question pack and you can choose ingame to play movie questions exclusively, or mix them in with the rest of the questions."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"TV Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/07",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"For the TV fanatic in everyone! Our new season of hundreds of fresh questions featuring all your favourite TV shows."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Sports Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/10/29",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"For Sports fans everywhere! Trivial Pursuit enters a new league with hundreds of new questions from the world of Sports."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1BqadI7atrY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wqdgOk7D8pw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/955051-trivial-pursuit/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Trivial-Pursuit/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/trivial-pursuit/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/trivial-pursuit"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":382,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Capcom"],
			"synopsis":"Produced by series veteran Jun Takeuchi, this next-generation follow-up to the terrifying series introduces the theme of escape as its core survival instinct. As Chris Redfield (former S.T.A.R.S. member and now part of the BSAA unit), your life is in danger as you strive to complete your most dangerous mission yet in a sweltering desert colony where a new breed of evil has been unleashed. Swarms of marauding evil beings will charge at you when your pulse is racing at a heart-shattering pace. Environments will play a bigger factor than ever here, using the power of next-gen systems to create a world where terror might lurk in any alcove or shadow. Powerful lighting effects overwhelm the player with mirage movement and blinding brilliance, and even in the light of day, there is no safe haven in this Resident Evil.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Versus Mode",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/07",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"VERSUS is a new mode available for Resident Evil 5. Take control of Chris, Sheva and other RE5 favorites in online battles of up to 4 players! Compete for points by defeating Majini in SLAYERS or take down other players in SURVIVORS. Fight alone or in a team for a total of 4 exciting variations!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Extra Figures",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/15",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Unlock items in Extra Figures. You will be able to add figures like Barry and Rebecca to your collection, all for the affordable price of a free download!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Costume Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This costume pack is compatible with the original game. Show off Chris' muscled physique with his Warrior outfit, and add a bit of elfin fantasy to Sheva with Fairy Tale. These costumes can also be used in The Mercenaries Reunion in addition to the main story."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Lost in Nightmares",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/17",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This is the first installment of new content for Resident Evil 5. During the main story of Resident Evil 5, Chris Redfield alludes to a mission where he lost his partner Jill during a conversation with Sheva. Now you can find out what happened during that mission at Spencer's estate. This package also allows you to unlock two new characters in the all-new The Mercenaries Reunion. Play as one of the unsung heroes of the original Resident Evil, Barry Burton, or step into the designer-made high heels of one of Resident Evil's newest villains, Excella Gionne."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Desperate Escape",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/03",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"This is the second installment of new content for Resident Evil 5. After Jill Valentine is rescued by Chris Redfield, he leaves her to finish his mission. Find out how she made it out on her own, and what role Josh Stone played in her escape. This package also allows you to unlock two new characters in the all-new The Mercenaries Reunion. Play as one of the stars of Resident Evil 0, Rebecca Chambers, or take on the role of Delta Team's commander, Josh Stone."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Costume Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This costume pack is compatible with the original game. Play with Chris' completely new take on tactical field armor with Heavy Metal, and give Sheva the sleek elegance of a power suit with Business. These costumes can also be used in The Mercenaries Reunion in addition to the main story."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xxJbz_3PKQo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GOgzJdm3eJc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/929197-resident-evil-5/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Resident-Evil-5/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/resident-evil-5/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/resident-evil-5"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Resident Evil Wiki",
				"url":"http://residentevil.wikia.com/Resident_Evil_5"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":383,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["ColdWood Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Live for Adrenaline! The sound of the snow and ice scraping across the skis, the arctic wind biting your cheeks, and the only thing louder than the roar of the crowd is the roar of your engine. This is the pulse-pounding world of snowmobile racing, and it's always intense. The follow-up to Ski-Doo Snow-Cross Racing, Ski-Doo Snowmobile Challenge has more sleds, more races, and more action. Play in online matches and compete against up to 11 opponents in any game mode, including the new Stunt Challenge!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5dPDzsebNa8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5-0jHFzWvhY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ski-Doo-Snowmobile-Challenge/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ski-doo-snowmobile-challenge/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ski-doo-snowmobile-challenge"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":384,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Creative Assembly"],
			"synopsis":"Experience the heat of the battlefield by leading your troops from the front line, instead of the traditional way of controlling the units from a detached view point. Stormrise also allows units to be commanded in the air, across rooftops, on the earth's surface and even underground, this unique idea of \"verticality\" introduces multiple layers of gameplay that must be mastered for strategic advantage. The experience is heightened by a simple yet effective control system tailored specifically for consoles, which allows easy unit selection, rapid navigation and precise deployment.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=30FVg5NoF2U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kzcx5sLZO14"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_4AGdMu4c4k"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/950804-stormrise/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Stormrise/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/stormrise/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/stormrise"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":385,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["GRIN"],
			"synopsis":"Based on Universal Pictures' action-thriller Wanted, this game promises to deliver the same fantastic visual style, in-your-face attitude and edge-of-your-seat action as the blockbuster motion picture. The game continues the story of hero Wesley Gibson, picking up the action where the film leaves off and creating an entirely new chapter exploring both Wesley's journey to becoming an unmatched &uuml;berassassin and the epic fiction of \"The Fraternity\".<br><br>Featuring intense third-person action, the Wanted video game will take combat to the next level with iconic moves - such as \"Curving Bullets\" and \"Assassin Time\" - drawn directly from the film, as well as an innovative, multi-layered cover mechanic.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=awbBDIzWsKo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oHcDQKKMDkE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/951188-wanted-weapons-of-fate/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wanted-Weapons-of-Fate/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wanted-weapons-of-fate/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wanted-weapons-of-fate"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wanted Wiki",
				"url":"http://wanted.wikia.com/wiki/Wanted_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":386,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Midway Games", "Tigon"],
			"synopsis":"Combining spectacular Hollywood-style stunts with a gripping storyline, Wheelman provides an adrenaline-fueled, cinematic thrill ride guaranteed to leave you breathless. Vin Diesel stars as an undercover agent and highly skilled driver who must infiltrate the Barcelona underworld to gather intelligence surrounding a covert heist. Posing as a driver-for-hire, he ends up caught in a crossfire of corruption and chaos while trying to stay one step ahead of local law enforcement and rival gangs.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Wheelman Free Street Showdown Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/30",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Have you got what it takes to be the first across the finish line? This FREE Street Showdown pack features a unique race that puts you head-to head against 5 other opponents. Will you put your foot down and head for the line using pure speed, or will you use all of your skills in vehicle melee and projectile attacks to eliminate your opponents in a no-holds-barred, all out assault?"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Wheelman Premium Street Showdown Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/30",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Have you got what it takes to be the first across the finish line? The Premium Street Showdown pack features 5 unique races that put you head-to head against 5 other opponents. Will you put your foot down and head for the line using pure speed, or will you use all of your skills in vehicle melee and projectile attacks to eliminate your opponents in a no-holds-barred, all out assault?"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7bRXfevskvg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RWXzWIXMFYk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xPYlwrOwHjY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=21W42urjvqQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/932152-wheelman/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wheelman/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wheelman/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wheelman"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":387,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["THQ"],
			"synopsis":"WWE Legends of WrestleMania embraces the leading sports entertainment organization's rich history to relive, rewrite or redefine the definitive elements of WWE from the Eighties and Nineties. Players will experience the entertaining lives of 40 larger-than-life Legends and have control over Legendary Managers, each of whom will play crucial roles in match outcomes. The game's new grapple-based fighting system captures the high-energy action and drama seen in vintage WWE matches, while a historically accurate representation of past WWE telecasts will set the stage, including dynamic visual treatments, signature ring entrances, renowned commentators and notable venues. WWE Legends of WrestleMania also includes a WrestleMania Tour Mode that allows players to participate in key matches from multiple WrestleMania events, a Create-A-Legend system to develop the Legends of tomorrow, as well as online functionality for players to compete on the biggest stages in WWE history.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H3bTwKPGMtc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xDZOgHR0pi4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/946180-legends-of-wrestlemania/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/WWE-Legends-of-WrestleMania/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wwe-legends-of-wrestlemania/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/legends-of-wrestlemania"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":388,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Beenox"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the 3D animated picture by DreamWorks Studios, the Monsters vs. Aliens videogame puts the fate of the planet in players' hands as they lead a dynamic team of five misfit monsters on a mission to save the world ... as only they can. The game allows fans to experience the movie's action and humor while playing as The Missing Link, the macho half-ape, half-fish; the gelatinous, indestructible and always hungry B.O.B.; and Ginormica, the 49-foot-11-inch tall woman and Insectosaurus, the 350-foot tall grub. Players utilize each character's distinct strengths, sizes and abilities to battle giant alien robots that are wreaking havoc on earth. Friends or family members can join in the excitement at anytime as the world's most brilliant scientist, Dr. Cockroach, Ph.D., in the unique co-op multiplayer mode.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BUADxp5eqaY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Monsters-vs-Aliens/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/monsters-vs-aliens/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/monsters-vs-aliens"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Monsters vs Aliens Wiki",
				"url":"http://monstersvsaliens.wikia.com/wiki/Monsters_Vs._Aliens_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":389,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Neversoft Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"\"Ride the Lightning\" with musical icons Metallica and over 20 other rocking acts in an all new Guitar Hero experience - Guitar Hero: Metallica. Enter the world of Lars Ulrich, James Hetfield, Kirk Hammett and Robert Trujillo and experience the intensity and skill of one of the greatest bands of all time. Shred on guitar, rip on drums and wail on the mic to a set list featuring over 45 explosive hits from Metallica's illustrious career and a wide variety of other legendary artists personally selected by the band, such as Alice In Chains, Foo Fighters and Queen. Fans will be able to rock as Metallica while performing in venues reminiscent of the band's epic album covers, themes from their music and real world locales.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Death Magnetic",
				"releaseDate":"2008/09/12",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Metallica's most recent album available for play in Guitar Hero: Metallica."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xm9p0GyRxgo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jUAb263vQZM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Battery",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Rt7F-FFUzuk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - For Whom The Bell Tolls",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zfqXwCa0aYc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/946755-guitar-hero-metallica/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Guitar-Hero-Metallica/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/guitar-hero-metallica/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/guitar-hero-metallica"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wikihero",
				"url":"http://guitarhero.wikia.com/wiki/Guitar_Hero:_Metallica"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":390,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Team17 Software"],
			"synopsis":"The Leisure Suit Larry Box Office Bust video game gives gamers an all-access pass to the glitz, glamour and gorgeous women of Tinseltown. The original Larry is now a movie mogul, but he's got a problem ... the studio across the road always seem to know what he's making: there must be a mole in the studio! Uncle Larry turns to you, his nephew, Larry Lovage - to solve the mystery - after all, no one would suspect a guy working in the mail room right? You must uncover the identity of the mole ... the very existence of the studio depends upon it! What could possibly go wrong?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hGgP7qWpUNk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ruf2TVzvwUM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944568-leisure-suit-larry-box-office-bust/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Leisure-Suit-Larry/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/leisure-suit-larry-box-office-bust/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/leisure-suit-larry-box-office-bust"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Leisure Suit Larry Omnipedia",
				"url":"http://leisuresuitlarry.wikia.com/wiki/Leisure_Suit_Larry_Omnipedia"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":391,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Starbreeze AB"],
			"synopsis":"This game in the Chronicles of Riddick franchise puts players into the role of enigmatic anti-hero Riddick. A hi-def re-imagining of the blockbuster 2004 game, The Chronicles of Riddick: Assault on Dark Athena follows up the story from the original game title as Riddick must now flee the Dark Athena, following his harrowing escape from the notorious Butcher Bay prison. During the adventure, Richard B. Riddick must escape the predatory Merc-ship Dark Athena using stealth and action to overcome its merciless crew and challenge the nefarious Captain Revas.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"'Escape From Butcher Bay' Commentary Mode",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/21",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Exclusive in-game Commentary Mode for the 2004 classic 'Chronicles of Riddick: Escape from Butcher Bay' presented by the award winning developer Starbreeze! Re-live the original EFBB campaign with hints and tips from the senior designers and programmers who worked on the game. When you play a Commentary Mode EFBB level, there will be symbols that you can select to hear behind the scenes stories from the developers about the making of the game. Fans of the original version will be excited to learn new revelations about the game that they never knew. Gamers who have never had the opportunity to play the original will gain new insight on a cult classic. The Comm. Mode features four and a half hours of exclusive content from Starbreeze."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Premium MP Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/21",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Unleash Riddick's fury across this blood-soaked multiplayer pack, including a brand new \"Munity\" Butcher Bay Riot map, available now for download. Maps in the pack: \"Munity\" for Butcher Bay Riot, \"Sneerock\" for Deathmatch, \"Tracker Star\" for Cupture the Flag, \"Viper Run\" for Butcher Bay Riot and \"The Tangle\" for Pitch Black."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EwQBCWw4y-U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kTZTrWaLemg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wWl3hbDO8VU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939612-the-chronicles-of-riddick-assault-on-dark-athena/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Assault-on-Dark-Athena/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-chronicles-of-riddick-assault-on-dark-athena/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-chronicles-of-riddick-assault-on-dark-athena"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Riddick Wiki",
				"url":"http://riddick.wikia.com/wiki/Assault_on_Dark_Athena"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":392,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Redwood Shores Studio"],
			"synopsis":"The Godfather II game goes beyond the film's story by setting players in the world of organized crime in 1960's Florida, Cuba and New York.<br><br>After being promoted by Michael Corleone to Don of New York, players expand to new cities, as they build up their families through extorting businesses, monopolizing illegal crime rings and defeating new families in an effort to become the most powerful mob family in America. To help players manage their empire, The Godfather II introduces \"The Don's View\" - an innovative strategy meta-game that allows players to oversee the entire world as they grow the family business. Using the Don's View, players will be able to build, defend and expand their crime rings, while keeping an eye on the movements and plans of the rival families. Players will also learn to master the business of organized crime by building a family of Made Men, hiring crew, handing out orders, and promoting their best men up the ranks.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Level 4 Firearms",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"These five firearms are exactly what a Don needs to put his family on top! Each weapon can be equipped by you and your family. This collection includes the Modern Dillinger, the .700 Magnum Impact, the Herzstopper, the MG-S1 Sniper Wolfe, and the Street Sweeper. Equips once New York is unlocked."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Pentangeli Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/23",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"This pack includes the Cuba and Junkyard multiplayer maps. The Cuba map is outdoors and suited for large battles, featuring lots of cover and strategic chokepoints for your team to defend and take over. The Junkyard features structures with several tiers to explore and defend. Use elevation to your advantage to get a drop on the competition."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Jack of All Trades",
				"releaseDate":"2009/04/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Jimmy Lira: The ONLY recruit who can ultimately be upgraded to have every specialty in the game! Jimmy Lira starts with the arsonist, engineer, medic, and safecracker specialties, and comes equipped with a level 2 machine gun: the MP38. He appears in the NY Don's office when NY is first unlocked, and in your NY safehouse at all times after that."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J7UCwTS699A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dCKYiYOOZvg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/948959-the-godfather-ii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Godfather-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-godfather-ii/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-godfather-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Godfather Wiki",
				"url":"http://godfather.wikia.com/wiki/The_Godfather_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":393,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["N-Space"],
			"synopsis":"Step into the secret dual life of Miley Stewart and Hannah Montana in Hannah Montana The Movie videogame. Journey beyond the movie and for the first time ever perform as Hannah Montana or Miley Stewart! Explore Miley's hometown of Crowley Corners as she rediscovers the world she left behind.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lHrjRIGGE38"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Hannah-Montana/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hannah-montana-the-movie/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/hannah-montana-the-movie"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Hannah Montana Wiki",
				"url":"http://hannahmontana.wikia.com/wiki/Hannah_Montana"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":394,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FromSoftware"],
			"synopsis":"High atop the towering skyscrapers of modern-day Tokyo, Ken Ogawa and his team of skilled ninjas are deployed to destroy the infected monster horde and stem the spreading disease as humanity hangs in the balance. Matters quickly take a turn for the worse as Ogawa and his team are betrayed from within their own ranks. After narrowly escaping death, Ogawa is left to fight the daunting battle alone while also attempting to understand the motivations behind his father's betrayal.<br><br>Armed with an extensive arsenal of specialized ninja weapons, tools and skills including the powerful forces of Ninja Vision and Todom&eacute Attack, players must fight insurmountable odds, and once again bring peace and order to Tokyo.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Bonus Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/05",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Your Style, Your Way. You can choose from 11 outfits and 9 emblems to enjoy your unique Ninja experience."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EawBtc6HxRo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a1j3LFa5Yfc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/952858-ninja-blade/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ninja-Blade/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ninja-blade/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ninja-blade"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":395,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Omega Force"],
			"synopsis":"Dynasty Warriors: Gundam 2 combines the devastating power of the Mobile Suit, the rich legacy of the Gundam universe and the furious Tactical Action game play of the Dynasty Warriors series. The game will thrust players into incredible battles against legions of enemy Mobile Suits on distant planetary surfaces and in the far reaches of outer space. For the first time, Dynasty Warriors: Gundam 2 will let players engage in melee battles against colossal enemies such as the Psycho Gundam. The massive Psycho Gundam can quickly reconfigure their bodies into titanic mobile fortresses which can move with remarkable speed. However, highly-trained pilots can utilize their own Mobile Suit's speed, agility, and of course firepower to defeat these deadly juggernauts.<br><br>Dynasty Warriors: Gundam 2 will also include new stories featuring mecha from the latest Gundam anime, plus mecha from Char's Counter Attack and more. With mecha parts collected throughout the course of the game, players will be able to adapt a Mobile Suit which can be piloted into combat.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Additional Mission 01",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/14",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"\"The Lost 1\" Face off against waves of giant Mobile Armor on the surface!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Additional Mission 02",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/14",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"\"The Lost 2\" Face off against waves of giant Mobile Armor in space!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Additional Mission 03",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/14",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"\"True Dynasty Warriors Gundam! Space Edition!\" Of course, by brand new, we mean the same mission, but now in space!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Additional Mission 04",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/28",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"\"War!?\" Amidst the chaos that engulfs the battlefield, it is up to you put an end to the madness..."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Additional Mission 05",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/28",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"\"Holy cow! Look at all this sweet junk! 1\" This mission will give you the opportunity to collect those hard to find parts for rare mobile suits."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Additional Mission 06",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/28",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"\"Holy cow! Look at all this sweet junk! 2\" This mission will give you the opportunity to collect those hard to find parts for rare mobile suits."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Additional Mission 07",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/11",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"\"Focus!\" A mission like you've never experienced before... Where you destroy wave after wave of enemies!"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Additional Mission 08",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/11",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"\"Decisions... decisions...\" It is up to you to tip the balance of power and decide who will be glorified the victor and who will be forever shamed!"
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Additional Mission 09",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/11",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"\"True Dynasty Warriors Gundam II! Surface Edition!\" The ultimate battle has begun yet again!"
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Additional Mission 10",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/11",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"\"True Dynasty Warriors Gundam II! Space Edition!\" The ultimate battle has begun yet again!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fQOiUDtv6RM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_0OaxSu2aQI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/952638-dynasty-warriors-gundam-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dynasty-Warriors-Gundam-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dynasty-warriors-gundam-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dynasty-warriors-gundam-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Koei Wiki",
				"url":"http://koei.wikia.com/wiki/Dynasty_Warriors:_Gundam_2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Gundam Wiki",
				"url":"http://gundam.wikia.com/wiki/Dynasty_Warriors_Gundam_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":396,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Replay Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Inspired by the fascinating story and unbreakable spirit of British secret agent Violette Szabo, players take control of Violette Summer, a beautiful spy deep behind enemy lines during World War II. Intense stealth-action gameplay with a startling real-time lighting system and surreal visuals combine to produce an incredible gaming experience. Through third-person gameplay, sneak up on enemies and pull the pins from their belted grenades. Infiltrate a Gestapo prison and slip cyanide to your own men before the Germans make them talk. Slink through the shadows to finish off your unsuspecting enemies with a single, silent move. Through Violette's fever dreams, experience what she experienced. Walk where she walked. And kill those she killed.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=feJxKQJ3Is8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CxdYn_ljcKE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942963-velvet-assassin/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Velvet-Assassin/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/velvet-assassin/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/velvet-assassin"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":397,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Raven Software"],
			"synopsis":"X-Men Origins: Wolverine is an action-adventure featuring a true-to-character Wolverine gameplay experience that takes gamers through and beyond the movie's storyline. Set in a variety of vivid real-world locales, the title challenges players to hone their animal instinct as they uncover hidden dangers, hunt and destroy enemies, and take on seemingly insurmountable situations while discovering the truth about Wolverine's tragic past. With razor-sharp adamantium claws unsheathed, the future X-Man enacts lightning-quick combat, evasive maneuvers, in-depth combo attacks, and an array of brutal finishing moves. Wolverine doesn't just deliver massive damage, either - he also takes it, thanks to his mutant regenerative power that heals him in real time right before the player's eyes.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Weapon X Arena",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/04",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"1 complete level, 4 intense simulators, limitless user-created scenarios - a combat utopia. In the Dismemberment Room, select body parts on a holographic soldier and watch them get severed with spectacular results. In the Environmental Kill Room, creatively skewer enemies on objects found in jungles, labs and a ruined temple. In the Ladder Challenge Room, beam in stages of increasingly difficult enemies to test Wolverine's strength. In the Custom Combat Arena, face off against any combo of enemies from the story. Endless permutations of exciting gameplay await."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g5i0ct8IML8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gcUvgrh9Uus"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/953919-x-men-origins-wolverine/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/X-Men-Origins-Wolverine/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/x-men-origins-wolverine/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/x-men-origins-wolverine"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":398,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Pipeworks Software"],
			"synopsis":"In Night at the Museum: Battle of the Smithsonian, players assume the role of Ben Stiller's character, Larry Daley, former night guard of New York's Museum of Natural History. Larry must rescue Jedediah and his other friends from Akhmenrah's brother who captured them while stealing a powerful Magic Tablet that can raise the Army of Horus to take over the world. Daley is well aware of the havoc that history's most notorious figures can wreak when the sun goes down and the museum exhibits come alive. He races to DC to help his friends in the Smithsonian.<br><br>Using Larry's trusty key chain and flashlight, players must solve puzzles and adventure through 14 levels including the Federal Archives, the National Air and Space Museum and the Lincoln Memorial. Gamers can travel in style on the back of a T-Rex skeleton, within the Lunar Lander and in the cockpit of Amelia Earhart's Pitcairn Autogyro. Along the way, players must find pieces of the Magic Tablet and collect other items to unlock mini-games, new areas and bonus content from the Smithsonian including trivia questions, in-game audio tours and factoids.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FPXTO2D9reQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5VKewVj8I50"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Night-at-the-Museum/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/night-at-the-museum-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/night-at-the-museum-battle-of-the-smithsonian"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":399,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gulti"],
			"synopsis":"A compilation of games in the Raiden Fighters franchise. All three arcade classics have been faithfully recreated in this ultimate collection. A new Training mode lets you modify every aspect your ships and wingmen, skip to any level, or play in slow-motion. Comprehensive screen and control settings let you play each game full-screen as a side-scroller, or even vertically on a rotated 4:3 display! Play 2-player co-op games offline, or play Arcade Mode as a lone-wolf, posting high-scores and gameclips to Xbox Live.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FR23flVwGe0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hu44Jw8V5d4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944128-raiden-fighters-aces/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Raiden/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/raiden-fighter-aces-us/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/raiden-fighters-aces"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":400,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eidos Studios"],
			"synopsis":"The second of Eidos' action/simulation game series, Battlestations: Pacific delivers intense, action-packed combat and strategic warfare at an extraordinary scale and features two distinctly different single player campaigns. The game features a massive U.S. and Japanese single player campaign that offers a unique blend of action and strategy. Players must plan their moves carefully on huge open-world arenas and fight in the air, above sea and underwater to relive some of the most hard-fought battles in WWII history. With the newly added Japanese faction, players will also gain insight into what could have been, should Japan have gained the upper hand against the United States. Battlestations: Pacific also features five new innovative multiplayer modes to strategically plan and battle against friends with all new maps and units.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Volcano Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/06/11",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Download 2 new maps for Battlestations: Pacific playable in both Skirmish and Multiplayer modes! The Volcano Map can be played in Island Capture, Competitive and Duel modes. The Choke Point Map can be played in Siege, Escort and Duel modes. Battle for supremacy in these all-new and unique environments."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Mustang Unit Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download brand new units for Battlestations: Pacific with the Mustang Unit Pack. Take to the skies with the legendary P-51 Mustang and the G5N Liz long range bomber or take command of the Alaska Class cruiser, Montana Class battleship, Kuma Torpedo cruiser and the Super Yamato Class battleship. Decorate the side of your planes with 9 new US pin-up girl nose arts and 9 all-new Japanese nose arts!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Carrier Battles Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/23",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Take your skills to the next level of combat with the Battlestations: Pacific Carrier Battles Map Pack. Download four brand new maps playable across all 5 multiplayer modes. Take part in a Clash of Carriers at Midway, do battle at dawn in the mist of the Philippine Islands, experience the fury of kamikaze attacks in the rocky islands of the Leyte Gulf and take control of your forces amongst the mountain peaks and glacial waters of the icy Aleutian Islands."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZOq3BrDNT28"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v0IP-kkLsBw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YSowvVPQyJM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Battlestations-Pacific/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/battlestations-pacific/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/battlestations-pacific"
			}]
		}
	}]
}