{
	"catalog": [
	{
		"id":401,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ascaron Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"T Energy has been flowing through Ancaria since time itself. This mysterious power forms the beginning of all life, is the source of all magic and the origin of all thought. For an era, it was the angelic Seraphim who watched over the T Energy and therefore over the fate of the entire world. They passed their knowledge on to the High Elves, so that they could benefit from T Energy. But the High Elves let the power over T Energy tear their society apart, and war and strife broke out. Worse than that, the T Energy itself went out of control, turning negative and creating destructive evil in the land.<br><br>The nobility as well as the clerical caste of the High Elves struggled to seize power over the high-elvish imperium, so that they alone might hold the T Power in their rule. The land once more faced with war; a war that was much larger, and more far reaching consequences than all previous wars and battles. Two thousand years before Shaddar the cry for heroes arises to avert this war and to regain control over the T Energy. Will those heroes prevent the world lapsing into final chaos, or will they instead deepen it with their actions?",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Carrier Imp",
				"releaseDate":"2009/05/29",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Carrier Imp is a pet that provides additional inventory storage when needed."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pY2GhYXEnYE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Blind Guardian Concert Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uS3_ss8E650"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FyIvARweN7c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jRpQiHQdJ5I"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938603-sacred-2-fallen-angel/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sacred-2-Fallen-Angel/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sacred-2-fallen-angel/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sacred-2-fallen-angel"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sacred Wiki",
				"url":"http://www.sacredwiki.org/index.php/Sacred_2:Fallen_Angel"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":402,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["GRIN"],
			"synopsis":"One of Capcom's all-time great franchises returns with this re-envisioned modern version of Bionic Commando. Continuing the story 10 years later (with slight modifications to character names in the re-envisioned story), gamers are once again playing the role of Nathan Spencer (aka \"Rad\" Spencer), a highly decorated government operative that distinguished himself in battle against a group known as the Imperials. However, Spencer finds himself betrayed by his commander known as Super Joe (who Commando fans should easily recognize). With his bionic arm removed and Spencer imprisoned for crimes he didn't commit, the warrior is sentenced to death. However, on the day that he's going to be executed, an experimental weapon is detonated in Ascension City by a terrorist group called Bio-Rain. With the city in ruins and the terrorists in control of tons of weapons, Joe has no choice but to offer Spencer a deal: if he will take on and defeat the terrorists, Joe will clear his name. Gaining a new bionic arm, Spencer leaps into action.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-1iin6J_cC4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7C9_we55J_4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-VbBHSwl8rA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=asAViGs4JPk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943680-bionic-commando/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bionic-Commando/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bionic-commando/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bionic-commando"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":403,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"Rock Band Track Pack: Classic Rock is a standalone software product that allows owners of Rock Band and Rock Band 2 to keep the party going with more hit songs from the pantheon of rock music. In addition, Rock Band Track Pack: Classic Rock, like all Rock Band software, is compatible with all Rock Band instrument controllers and other current music-based video game peripherals. The 20-song pack features an outstanding mix of Rock Band fans' favorite classic rock hits including songs by mega artists The Who, Rush, Boston and Police.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rbzaXuX-224"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rock-Band-Classic-Rock/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rock-band-track-pack-classic-rock/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rock-band-track-pack-classic-rock"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Rock Band Wiki",
				"url":"http://rockband.wikia.com/wiki/Rock_Band_Track_Pack:_Classic_Rock"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":404,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["GRIN", "Halcyon Co."],
			"synopsis":"Terminator Salvation: The Future Begins focuses on the exploits of now 30-year-old John Connor in a world on the road to the extinction of humanity. The game offers players the chance to assume the role of John, battling for survival against the far superior forces of Skynet. Played in a third-person action game, Terminator Salvation features concentrated armed combat against all of the Skynet enemies from the film as well as new enemies specifically designed for the game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=To7tNEuJx9w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SUyuDOnBknw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gpZcn8eI-mY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944033-terminator-salvation/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Terminator-Salvation/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/terminator-salvation/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/terminator-salvation"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Terminator Wiki",
				"url":"http://terminator.wikia.com/wiki/Terminator_Salvation_(video_game)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":405,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Yuke's Media Creations"],
			"synopsis":"UFC 2009 Undisputed is an explosive fighting game detailing the action, intensity and attitude of the Ultimate Fighting Championship (UFC). Featuring an authentic and comprehensive UFC atmosphere, including an extensive roster of the best mixed martial arts fighters in the world, players will push the envelope with a powerful new game engine and put their best fighting disciplines to the test in the world famous Octagon.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"TUF DLC",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/10",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Ryan Bader and Efrain Escudero"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hdyOVHnFjzc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TYRyQ6EZEb8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/949120-ufc-undisputed-2009/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/UFC-Undisputed-2009/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ufc-2009-undisputed/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ufc-undisputed-2009"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":406,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blue Omega Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Evolving the shooter genre with its unique and exhilarating combination of fluid action and combat, Damnation features huge, open environments, frenetic combat, daredevil acrobatics and high-octane vehicle-based stunts. Presenting players with an intense test of reflexes, quick thinking and rapid-fire conflict, Damnation will feature vast, breathtaking landscapes, each covering miles of distance and thousands of vertical feet. Billed as a 'shooter gone vertical,' and visually inspired by iconic elements of American history, these massive streaming landscapes will form the battlegrounds for a post-industrial conflict between humanity and an unstoppable arms dealer hell-bent on total world domination. Players will be able to choose their own paths and navigate the world by performing daredevil feats on the edge of human ability. However players aren't the only ones with mind-blowing acrobatic skills; intelligent enemies will give chase and engage players in frantic gun fights and attacks that can come from any direction - in Damnation's world there's no safe place to hide. In addition to the single player experience, Damnation comes complete with a unique set of multiplayer options that take full advantage of the game's expansive levels.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JJBU7ocsVJE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mp8fFBOMCgc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945215-damnation/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Damnation/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/damnation/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/damnation"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":407,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Spiders", "Frogwares"],
			"synopsis":"The year is 1888, and the setting is London's Whitechapel area, where a horrible series of crimes has taken place in this East End district. The bodies of several women who have suffered horrible mutilations have been found. The police have been having a hard time finding a serious lead as the murders continue, creating paranoia and terror in the streets. Sherlock Holmes sets out to find clues in the dark, gloomy streets of Whitechapel, following a macabre trail of the one that the press calls Jack the Ripper. During this terrifying adventure, Sherlock will attempt to shed some light on the mystery that shrouds the identity and motive of the one who hides behind this terrifying nickname.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CAXVan-8-qk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_nFr2KiWA9U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vR4Ow9YIvKk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sherlock-Holmes-vs-Jack-the-Ripper/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sherlock-holmes-vs-jack-the-ripper/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sherlock-holmes-vs-jack-the-ripper"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Baker Street",
				"url":"http://bakerstreet.wikia.com/wiki/Sherlock_Holmes_versus_Jack_the_Ripper"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":408,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["THQ"],
			"synopsis":"The Up video game takes players on an exotic adventure with Carl Fredricksen and his young sidekick, Wilderness Explorer Russell, as they set off on a wild journey through the undiscovered jungles of South America. Players are able to experience all four main characters from the movie - Carl, Russell, Dug the lovable dog or Kevin the prehistoric bird - while playing as a single-player or with a friend cooperatively throughout the entire game. Players can encounter exciting, new environments as they navigate through treacherous jungle terrains, battle dangerous creatures and trek the slippery slopes of the Amazonian Tepuis. In addition, the game also features multi-player game modes, including an epic level that allows up to four players to compete in aerial combat.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rTdS0OX_lUk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/959270-up/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/UP/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/disney-pixar-up/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/up"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":409,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Asobo Studio"],
			"synopsis":"Fuel will present players with an astonishing no-boundaries playfield that's over 5,000 square miles (14,000+ square km) in size. Creating the ultimate competitive go-anywhere racing experience, the game has players competing across wildly different terrain and executing spectacular death-defying stunts as they race dozens of varied two and four-wheeled rides and explore this epic world on an unprecedented scale.<br><br>Fuel is set in an alternate present in which whole swathes of the globe have been ravaged by the effects of climate change brought on by decades of environmental abuse. Here oil prices have rocketed and yet a new breed of racing junkie takes to the wastelands, pitting their grungy home-tuned vehicles against each other in an all-new extreme sport as they compete to win fuel supplies. To triumph means travelling the wastelands to challenge the best; from the tsunami-wrecked pacific coast through the Nevada wastelands, including the Grand Canyon, up treacherous snow-capped mountains, thick forests, arid deserts, abandoned lakeside resorts and much more.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lIHF7eqrptk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P85HCuPc5fg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZJeJP2NkLAA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=anWDwL_jODk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/952474-fuel/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fuel/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fuel/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fuel"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Fuel Wiki",
				"url":"http://fuel.wikia.com/wiki/FUEL_GAME_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":410,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Volition"],
			"synopsis":"Red Faction: Guerrilla is a 3rd person, open-world action shooter set on Mars, 50 years after the events of the original Red Faction. Players take the role of an insurgent fighter with the newly re-established Red Faction movement as they battle for liberation from the oppressive Earth Defense Force. Throughout their fight for freedom, players carve their own path, wreaking havoc across the vast, open-world environment of Mars, from the desolate mining outpost of Parker to the gleaming EDF capital city of Eos.<br><br>Utilizing improvised weapons, explosives and re-purposed mining equipment and vehicles, Red Faction: Guerrilla allows players to tear through fully destructible environments in an unforgiving Martian landscape swarming with EDF forces, Red Faction resistance fighters, and the downtrodden settlers caught in the cross-fire. Red Faction: Guerrilla also features a robust multiplayer component, including several modes focused on destruction-based gameplay.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Demons of the Badlands",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/13",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Break free and experience the all new single player game in this prequel chapter of the Red Faction universe. Mariner Valley, the once peaceful home of the Marauder people, has been torched and defiled by the EDF. The Marauders demand vengeance and Samanya leads the revolt. Set several years before the arrival of Alec Mason on Mars, take control of Samanya to explore the Mariner Valley outside of Tharsis. Exact your revenge with 7 all new weapons including the Spiker machine gun and Marauder Missilepod, and 3 new vehicles including the Punisher walker. Perfect your guerrilla tactics with 11 new actions including raids and demolitions. Show off your skills with 10 new unlockable achievements. Take control and lead the Marauder revolution."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Multiplayer Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/17",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Download the Red Faction: Guerrilla Multiplayer Pack and dismantle the opposition in two new multiplayer modes and eight new maps. In Bagman, players scores points by securing the \"bag\" and taking out their opponents. Increase the carnage in Team Bagman, where the same rules apply, but players are forced to utilize teamwork and guerrilla tactics to eliminate the opposition. Experience a constant sense of vertigo in the new map Puncture, or smash your way through Remnant where the density of destruction is higher than any other multiplayer level."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Smasher Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/10/01",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Strategic destruction takes center stage in this Red Faction: Guerrilla Smasher Pack that adds a new Wrecking Crew mode along with eight new Wrecking Crew maps. This new mode focuses on using walker vehicles to inflict as much destruction as possible before handing off the controller to the next player. Jump behind the controls of an armored Walker and demolish large towers and structures in the new map Repercussion, then sit back and witness the devastating glory as the enemy stronghold crumbles in cascading destruction."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9Ndb3g3n52Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hrl0FdQXbqY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EE5ecIpTEb4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_mOKqrYrokY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944786-red-faction-guerrilla/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Red-Faction-Guerrilla/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/red-faction-guerrilla/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/red-faction-guerrilla"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Red Faction Wiki",
				"url":"http://redfaction.wikia.com/wiki/Red_Faction:_Guerrilla"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":411,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sumo Digital"],
			"synopsis":"Virtua Tennis 2009 allows you to take on the world's top tennis players. Take on the likes of Rafael Nadal and Roger Federer or play as Maria Sharapova against Venus Williams to recreate some classic court battles. Joining this impressive roster of tennis stars are Andy Murray and ladies French Open champion Ana Ivanovic. In addition to the traditional singles, doubles and mixed doubles matches, Virtua Tennis 2009 also has the official Davis Cup license, giving players the coveted opportunity to lead their country to glory.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8tOvsIuA9yM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3PyMQ14j0pg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZQzyvg0E6Bg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/957950-virtua-tennis-2009/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Virtua-Tennis-2009/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/virtua-tennis-2009/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/virtua-tennis-2009"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":412,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"Feel the drama of tournament golf with Tiger Woods PGA Tour 10! Test your stick skills as you play in front of huge galleries and hear the roar of the crowd at every hole. For the first time in franchise history, take on one of the toughest tests in golf - the U.S. Open at Bethpage Black. Fight a multitude of tough courses, real-time weather conditions, the challenge of online tournaments, and more - Tiger Woods PGA Tour 10 provides an inside-the-ropes experience like never before.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tj03hKxik-4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U7P9BvPkXYI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tiger-Woods-PGA-TOUR-10/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tiger-woods-pga-tour-10/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tiger-woods-pga-tour-10"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":413,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Radical Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"In Prototype, players take control of Alex Mercer - a dark, genetically mutated shape-shifter with no memory of his past, hell-bent on solving the mystery of his existence as he tears through a densely populated New York City moving with Parkour-style fluidity and consuming anything that gets in his way.<br><br>'Deceive or Destroy' gameplay allows gamers the choice to either blend in with the population and covertly progress through the story, or fully unleash Alex's powers, and move through New York City like a walking slaughterhouse, taking control of military vehicles, and causing destruction at every turn.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RahEtkVxAPA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gQoMELyEYFQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JvsUkUaJjYs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UCua_TkPI0I"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942351-prototype/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Prototype/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/prototype/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/prototype"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Prototype Wiki",
				"url":"http://prototype.wikia.com/wiki/Prototype_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":414,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Omega Force"],
			"synopsis":"Dynasty Warriors 6 Empires is game that brings together the best aspects of the action and strategy genres. In this latest edition, players can experience Ancient China's greatest and most glorious war as an all-powerful lord or as an officer.<br><br>As a lord, gamers must think strategically. By deciding when to attack, when to resist invasion, or when to initiate policies, a lord can expand their power and influence. An easy-to-learn \"card collecting\" system lets players enact policies that will increase their empire's strength, improve the abilities of their forces, and more. The cards that a player receives will depend on the attributes of the officers and their army.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Queen Armor Set (women)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Kempo Armor Set (men)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Royal Armor Set (men)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Artemis Armor Set (women)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Additional Music Set 1",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/09",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Add these additional \"Dynasty Warriors\" music tracks to the game's BGM Select screen."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Shaman Armor Set (women)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Lion Armor Set (men)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Paladin Armor Set (women)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Desert Armor Set (men)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/16",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Additional Music Set 2",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/23",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Add these additional \"Dynasty Warriors\" music tracks to the game's BGM Select screen."
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Valkyrie Armor Set (women)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Eclectic Armor Set (men)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"Norse Armor Set (men)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"Priestess Armor Set (women)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":15,
				"name":"Additional Music Set 3",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/06",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Add these additional \"Dynasty Warriors\" music tracks to the game's BGM Select screen."
			},
			{
				"id":16,
				"name":"Mystic Armor Set (men)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":17,
				"name":"Wa Armor Set (women)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":18,
				"name":"Arabian Armor Set (women)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			},
			{
				"id":19,
				"name":"Shinobi Armor Set (men)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/13",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get this new set of attire to customize your character's appearance in Edit Mode."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lEVrzPmq2f4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AXcLFEO-FAs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/954492-dynasty-warriors-6-empires/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dynasty-Warriors-6-Empires/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dynasty-warriors-6-empires/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dynasty-warriors-6-empires"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Koei Wiki",
				"url":"http://koei.wikia.com/wiki/Dynasty_Warriors_6:_Empires"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":415,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Terminal Reality"],
			"synopsis":"The real Ghostbusters return in this videogame sequel to the Ghostbusters movies. Stars Harold Ramis, Dan Aykroyd, Ernie Hudson and Bill Murray reunite to reprise their roles as Spengler, Stantz, Zeddmore and Venkman. Supporting the ghost busting crew are the talents of Annie Potts, Brian Doyle Murray and William Atherton.<br><br>With Manhattain newly overrun by ghosts and other supernatural creatures, it's up to you to take on the role of a new recruit joining the original, famous Ghostbusters team. Equipped with a variety of unique weapons and gadgets, you will hunt, fight and capture a wide range of uncanny phantasms and demons in an all-new, funny and frightening battle to save New York City from its latest paranormal plague.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MNf7gh9Tt2c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bkUMacaIWcg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=quunRdq7s9k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xGgHJdz8WT8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944011-ghostbusters-the-video-game/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ghostbusters/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ghostbusters-the-video-game/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ghostbusters-the-video-game"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Ghostbusters Wiki",
				"url":"http://ghostbusters.wikia.com/wiki/Ghostbusters_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":416,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Beenox"],
			"synopsis":"Turn down the lights, crank up the amps and prepare to command center stage as some of the most famous AND infamous tracks from Guitar Hero, Guitar Hero II, Guitar Hero Encore: Rocks the 80s and Guitar Hero III: Legends of Rock step into the spotlight in the most epic, full band jam session to-date - Guitar Hero Greatest Hits. The #1 best-selling video game franchise of 2008 presents the best of the best to music video game aficionados so they can join together with guitar, bass, drums and vocals and rock to master tracks of their favorite Guitar Hero music.<br><br>Featuring 48 master recordings, Guitar Hero Greatest Hits delivers exciting online and offline gameplay modes including Band Career and 8-player \"Battle of the Bands\", which allows two full bands to compete head-to-head online. In Guitar Hero Greatest Hits players' rock n' roll fantasies turn to realities as they create their rocker, compose their music and share it with the world through the innovative Music Studio, GHTunesSM and robust Rock Star Creator gameplay modes first introduced in Guitar Hero World Tour.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bQAi4l_hsSo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2p7PV0OuqaA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958079-guitar-hero-smash-hits/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Guitar-Hero-Smash-Hits/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/guitar-hero-smash-hits/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/guitar-hero-smash-hits"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wikihero",
				"url":"http://guitarhero.wikia.com/wiki/Guitar_Hero:_Smash_Hits"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":417,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Triumph Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Overlord II is the sequel to the hit warped fantasy action adventure that had players being delightfully despotic. In Overlord II, a new Overlord and a more powerful army of Minions take on an entire empire in a truly epic adventure, inspired by the rise of the Roman Empire. As the Glorious Empire conquers kingdoms and destroys any sign of magic it finds, it's time to go Minion Maximus and send in the horde.<br><br>The Minions return smarter, deadlier (and funnier) and are ready to fight in large scale battles that will see their wild pack mentality squaring up to the organised legions of the Glorious Empire. As ever, they'll do anything and everything the Overlord commands of them, especially now that they can run ravage and wreck buildings and scenery. They've also learn to ride: In Overlord II, Minions will be able to mount up and ride wolves and other magical creatures around the landscape and take them into battle, making our band of merry fighters faster and fiercer than ever before.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Battle Rock Nemesis",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/29",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Bring the Battle Rock to the Netherworld with this content add-on for Overlord II. Once the Minions have finished constructing the Battle Rock you'll be able to take part in a number of challenging combat rounds against new opponents. Battle your way to the top to win exciting new rewards for the Overlord and his Minions. Once you've installed the Battle Rock head over to the Netherworld to activate it. Sit on the throne and look for new audience events to choose from. You'll have to progress part way into the game before the first Battle Rock practice rounds become available."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tgwql7jpVoo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=28OozEGW8TE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WaevnkKd4X0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bO_B2XaWUes"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/952370-overlord-ii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Overlord-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/overlord-ii/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/overlord-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Overlord Wiki",
				"url":"http://overlord.wikia.com/wiki/Overlord_II"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":418,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Luxoflux Corp."],
			"synopsis":"The Transformers: Revenge of the Fallen video game lets gamers step into the shoes of the Autobots or Decepticons, select any available mission and pick from the largest, most diverse range of playable Transformers - each with their own distinct abilities and weaponry. Set in unique environments across the globe such as Cairo and Shanghai, the game allows players to instantly switch between vehicle and robot modes as they drive, fly, fight and blast their way through intense, pressure-packed levels. After engaging in single player action, players will be able to go online and battle friends in all-new multiplayer modes.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Character and Map Pack Plus",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/27",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Transformers: Revenge of the Fallen gets BIGGER with new characters, maps, achievements and Expert mode. Enter battle in single player and multiplayer with 11 new characters from the movie & Generation One series. Three new multiplayer maps take the online battle to new locations. Expert mode makes the single player campaigns more challenging for experienced users - including new leaderboards."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kMPZvwyg1mY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BcJNqXMBEUI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LWua79SAy4k"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/957956-transformers-revenge-of-the-fallen/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Transformers-Revenge-of-the-Fallen/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/transformers-revenge-of-the-fallen/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/transformers-revenge-of-the-fallen"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Transformers Wiki",
				"url":"http://transformers.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":419,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Front Wing"],
			"synopsis":"Time Leap takes the romance dating game a leap forward by animating the characters in real time throughout the game. Using the full power of the Xbox360 consoles, the romance game flows out smoothly like an anime, complete with a star studded cast of voice actors and actresses behind it.<br><br>You are living with a group of girls in a shrine on a secluded island, one of them is Ayumi the popular upperclassman whom everybody looks up to and there is Yuu, the cute girl you love like a little sister. One day, a younger version of Ayumi appears in front of the group due to a time leap and it is your job and desire to get a long with her.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zk7v1WFTpJU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rM_gt7nXBIM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/950324-time-leap/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Time-Leap/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/time-leap/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":420,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["ARC System Works"],
			"synopsis":"A 2D one-on-one fighting game by ARC System Works (the makers of Guilty Gear.) Produced by Guilty Gear producer Toshimichi Mori, the game features an all-original cast (including many weapon fighters) and uses a four-button control scheme (weak, medium and strong attacks plus an EX button which makes your character perform unique special attacks.) The fighting system is based around players being able to continue combos when opponents are in a down state. On the defensive side, you'll have a number of ways of getting back up when downed, so you don't get pummeled by combo attacks.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Additional character colors (All Types)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This package includes 4 additional colors for all 12 characters."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"All additional character colors 2!",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This package includes 4 additional colors based on the flags of various European countries for all 12 characters."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"All additional character colors 3!",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This package includes 4 more colors for all 12 characters."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o-gJv16az48"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uDA_vslBUcE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958721-blazblue-calamity-trigger/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/BlazBlue-Calamity-Trigger/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/blazblue/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/blazblue-calamity-trigger"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"BlazBlue Wiki",
				"url":"http://blazblue.wikia.com/wiki/BlazBlue:_Calamity_Trigger"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":421,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Techland"],
			"synopsis":"Call of Juarez: Bound in Blood transports players from a ravaged Civil War-era Georgia to the Aztec ruins of Mexico. In the wildest West ever depicted, players can embody both McCall brothers in an intense Wild West storyline full of greed, lust and lawlessness that takes place during a legendary period of American history.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Old West Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/06",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Relive even more legendary Wild West shootouts with four additional multiplayer maps."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ikqg99Q4FAw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PnW0n7m6QCM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=in1h_Sehiu8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=84Pdh_NiRGY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/955868-call-of-juarez-bound-in-blood/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Call-of-Juarez-Bound-in-Blood/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/call-of-juarez-bound-in-blood/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/call-of-juarez-bound-in-blood"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Call of Juarez Wiki",
				"url":"http://callofjuarez.wikia.com/wiki/Call_of_Juarez:_Bound_in_Blood"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":422,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"EA returns to the ring with this fourth entry in the boxing franchise. Featuring a re-written gameplay engine, Fight Night Round 4 adds a variety of fighting styles and boxer differentiation to authentically emulate the greatest fighters of all time. Pressure your opponent with the brawling inside style of young Mike Tyson, bobbing and weaving to set up powerful hooks and uppercuts. Capitalize on Muhammad Ali's reach, hand speed and fleetness of foot to bewilder your opponent with lightning fast jabs and straights from the outside. For the first time in history, Fight Night Round 4 gives you the opportunity to pit these legendary heavyweights against one another and name a true champ.<br><br>No fight will be the same with an all-new physics-based animation system that recreates the full spectrum of true-to-life punch impacts, giving boxers a devastating arsenal of punches, blocks and ring movement. The new physics system allows for missed punches, glancing punches, knockout blows and for the first time ever, rough and tumble inside fighting. Fatigue, adrenaline, footwork and timing all come into play as you hammer away at your opponents.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable Content 1",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/04",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"This downloadable content features Sponsored Tournaments, Additional Training Gym, New Gameplay Sliders, and additional apparel."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Boxing Gear Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/08/27",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This downloadable content features new boxing trunks, boots and gloves."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Olympic Sugar Ray Leonard",
				"releaseDate":"2009/10/20",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download the Olympic version of Sugar Ray Leonard for FREE."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Evander Holyfield",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download boxing heavy weight legend Evander Holyfield. Few in boxing history \"brought it\" like the Real Deal did. He is a multiple world champion in multiple divisions. Available for use offline and over Xbox LIVE."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Old School Rules",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/21",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Fight like the champions of the past by downloading the Old School Rules game mode. Available for use Offline and over Xbox LIVE, Old School Rules simulates the common rules of boxing prior to the establishment of the Marquis of Queensbury Rules. 1-2 Players Offline and over Xbox LIVE Leaderboards Fight can only be won by KO No Ref stoppages for Cuts or Swelling Round stoppages after knockdowns only."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Bernard Hopkins",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/21",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download boxing legend Bernard Hopkins. Known as the Executioner he holds the longest successful title defense streak in boxing history. Seemingly ageless Bernard can mix it up or outbox you ... he is the complete package. Available for use offline and over Xbox LIVE."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Sonny Liston",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/28",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Download boxing legend Sonny Liston. This former heavy weight champion of the world was one of the most powerful punchers in the history of the sport. Available for use offline and over Xbox LIVE."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Ring Rivalries",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/28",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Relive some of the best fights in boxing history by downloading the Ring Rivalries game mode. Included are over 20 classic match-ups each with unique boxer ratings reflecting the boxer's status at the time of the fight. Change history or recreate it... it's up to you in Ring Rivalries."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Free Gear",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Free Gear Pack gives you immediate access to over a dozen different & new accessories, including new gloves, boots, and trunks."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hjs7H_dCb4o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iRUXxki6wdU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/946195-fight-night-round-4/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fight-Night-Round-4/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fight-night-round-4/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fight-night-round-4"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":423,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Bright Light"],
			"synopsis":"In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, Voldemort is tightening his grip on both the Muggle and wizarding worlds and Hogwarts is no longer the safe haven it once was. Harry suspects that dangers may even lie within the castle, but Dumbledore is more intent upon preparing him for the final battle that he knows is fast approaching. Together they work to find the key to unlock Voldemort's defenses and, to this end, Dumbledore recruits his old friend and colleague, the well-connected and unsuspecting bon vivant Professor Horace Slughorn, whom he believes holds crucial information. Meanwhile, the students are under attack from a very different adversary as teenage hormones rage across the ramparts. Harry finds himself more and more drawn to Ginny, but so is Dean Thomas. And Lavender Brown has decided that Ron is the one for her, only she hadn't counted on Romilda Vane's chocolates! And then there's Hermione, simmering with jealously but determined not to show her feelings. As romance blossoms, one student remains aloof. He is determined to make his mark, albeit a dark one. Love is in the air, but tragedy lies ahead and Hogwarts may never be the same again.<br><br>In the game, players will return to Hogwarts to help Harry survive a fraught sixth year. They will also have a chance to engage in exciting wizard duels, mix and brew magical ingredients in Potions class and take to the air to lead the Gryffindor Quidditch team to victory. Players may even get sidetracked by Ron's romantic entanglements as they journey towards a dramatic climax and discover the identity of the Half-Blood Prince.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7M46Qg_Y5Mg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=odl7OfUv6oI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945904-harry-potter-and-the-half-blood-prince/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Harry-Potter-and-the-Half-Blood-Prince/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/harry-potter-and-the-half-blood-prince/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/harry-potter-and-the-half-blood-prince"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Harry Potter Wiki",
				"url":"http://harrypotter.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":424,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eurocom"],
			"synopsis":"The Ice Age: Dawn of the Dinosaurs video game reunites fans with Scrat, Sid, Manny and Diego in an all-new quest based on the upcoming film from Twentieth Century Fox. As the unlikely herd travels across the tundra and beyond, they stumble upon another world - a lush Dinosaur World teeming with jungles, mysterious plants, fierce dinosaurs, wild new adventures and several new friends. Taking on the role of more than six playable characters, including everyone's favorite Ice Age friends and newly introduced characters, players master their unique skills and abilities across more than 15 action-packed levels.<br><br>In addition to the expanded features of the single-player gameplay, for the first time in an Ice Age game, players can team up with friends and family in eight competitive multiplayer mini-games.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8x3YOraM8Gs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ige-Age-Dawn-of-the-Dinosaurs/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ice-age-dawn-of-the-dinosaurs/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ice-age-dawn-of-the-dinosaurs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Ice Age Wiki",
				"url":"http://iceage.wikia.com/wiki/Ice_Age_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":425,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Metropolis Software House"],
			"synopsis":"Infernal: Hell's Vengeance calls on players to assume the role of Ryan Lennox, an unlikely hero who has turned into a ghost and feeds himself on defeated souls after being recruited by hell to fight Etherlight - heaven's own secret agency. Etherlight has eliminated most of hell's earthly agents and is planning its final blow against its arch-rival by sending Lennox back to the bowels of hell.<br><br>Armed with a vast arsenal of weapons and supernatural powers, players are left to take on Etherlight single-handedly. The captivating plot sends players from ancient monastery catacombs and secret mountain hideouts to sprawling harbor docks and oil refineries, before finally facing the ultimate showdown!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C9uMY7efVDk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DYwyyWcbSZk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/959302-infernal-hells-vengeance/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Infernal-Hells-Vengeance/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/infernal/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/infernal-hells-vengeance"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":426,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blue Castle Games"],
			"synopsis":"Known for its over-the-top style of gameplay, The BIGS 2 focuses on the \"big\" fast-paced moments in Major League Baseball with new opportunities to go up against MLB legends, more mini-games like Home Run Pinball, and a variety of other thrilling new features.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Max TeamBuilder Slots",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"This download contains 120 slots to download teams for use in Play Now or Dynasty Mode. This will not add to any slots previously unlocked only give you a maximum of 120 teams."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"5 Star Defensive Back",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"This download will give you the ability to start your college career in Road to Glory as a 5 star Cornerback, Strong Safety, or Free Safety."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Recruiting Reports",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"The Recruiting Reports will bring the information from the previous week. Knowing which recruits your opponent is targeting and how much time they are spending with each recruit can help you make informed decisions while spending your Recruiting Time. This will affect every team you control in Dynasty Mode and Online Dynasty Mode."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7OJUWXCEYBc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LH4Iil971sE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958531-the-bigs-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-BIGS-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-bigs-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-bigs-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":427,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"With all 120 Football Bowl Subdivision schools represented in the game, NCAA Football 10 offers fans an exciting way to experience the thrill of authentic college football year-round. NCAA Football 10 brings the college football atmosphere to life with enhanced stadiums packed with school colors, cheerleaders and mascots. Enjoy the sights of game day with new field goal nets, flags waving in the wind and camera flashes exploding during pivotal moments.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fgQies1yHEk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_PogrE9Vj3g"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958704-ncaa-football-10/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NCAA-Football-10/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ncaa-football-10/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ncaa-football-10"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":428,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eurocom"],
			"synopsis":"The G-Force, a group of highly-trained covert guinea pig spy agents, is the only team that can save the world from an evil billionaire and his army of robot appliances. Based on the 2009 Walt Disney Pictures and Jerry Bruckheimer Films movie, G-Force is an action-packed platformer that puts you in control of Darwin, the G-Force team leader, and his housefly surveillance sidekick Mooch. Use awesome high-tech gadgets and stealth strategy as you team up with the other G-Force agents to complete your exciting mission.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=huFg13akxp4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958998-g-force/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/GForce/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/g-force/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/g-force"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":429,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"Rock Band Country Track Pack is a standalone software product that allows owners of Rock Band andRock Band 2 to keep the party going with 21 songs from an outstanding mix of country artists, including Kenny Chesney, Alan Jackson, Shania Twain, Rascal Flatts and the legendary Kenny Rogers. Many of the tracks will be exclusive to the Rock Band Country Track Pack disc for a limited time before joining the Rock Band Music Store as downloadable content.<br><br>In addition, Rock Band Country Track Pack, like all Rock Band software, is compatible with all Rock Band instrument controllers, as well as most Guitar Hero and other current third party video game instrument controllers. Fans who buy the Rock Band Country Track Pack for Xbox 360 can play directly from the disc or download the songs onto their consoles' hard drives through a free offer with Xbox Live. Once downloaded, the songs will automatically appear in the player's custom Rock Band library and can be integrated into setlists and played in all game modes.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V1CIkS6v3jo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rock-Band-Country-Pack/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rock-band-track-pack-country/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rock-band-country-track-pack"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Rock Band Wiki",
				"url":"http://rockband.wikia.com/wiki/Rock_Band_Country_Track_Pack"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":430,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SNK Playmore"],
			"synopsis":"In celebration of its landmark 15th Anniversary, The King of Fighters XII - one of the last great arcade 3-on-3 fighter games - is about to get even greater. For the first time in its history, this ultimate fighting game has undergone a complete graphical overhaul. KOFXII features 22 gorgeous hand-drawn 2D characters from SNK's arcade history. All sprites used over the past 14 years have been dropped and replaced with new 2D high-definition, high-resolution sprites on detailed backgrounds. KOFXII aims to knock players out with new gameplay elements including critical counter attacks, Sousai (deadlock) counters and guard attacks, and the introduction of new online elements.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"BGM \"Hard Rock\" Arrangements",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/26",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"BGM Arrangement Packs for The King of Fighters XII now available! 10 tracks of the game's BGM will be arranged in Hard Rock style. To change BGM, set the sound arrangement to \"Hard Rock\" in \"SOUND OPTION\"."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"BGM \"Classic\" Arrangements",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/26",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"BGM Pack for The King of Fighters XII now available! 10 tracks of the game's BGM will be changed to Classic KOF Music. To change BGM, set the sound arrangement to \"Another\" in \"SOUND OPTION\"."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"BGM \"Dance\" Arrangements",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/26",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"BGM Arrangement Packs for The King of Fighters XII now available! 10 tracks of the game's BGM will be arranged in Dance style. To change BGM, set the sound arrangement to \"Dance\" in \"SOUND OPTION\"."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"BGM \"Jazz\" Arrangements",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/26",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"BGM Arrangement Packs for The King of Fighters XII now available! 10 tracks of the game's BGM will be arranged in Jazz style. To change BGM, set the sound arrangement to \"Jazz\" in \"SOUND OPTION\"."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sYaMX-8_Gyk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1WVfLsK8f9Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mHsaLa6ELRs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958497-the-king-of-fighters-xii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/King-of-Fighters-XII/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/king-of-fighters-12/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-king-of-fighters-xii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"SNK Wiki",
				"url":"http://snk.wikia.com/wiki/The_King_of_Fighters_XII"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":431,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Collision Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Set in a fantastic world based upon the mythology of Native America, Brave: A Warrior's Tale plays as a series of flashbacks in which a now elderly Brave describes the events of his life. Between the warrior's tales of his youth, the player takes control of Courage, a young boy who takes lessons from his elder's experiences to stop the current threat to their village. The game provides players expansive exploration and in-game interactivity on their quest to defeat the sources of evil, continuously offering a significant challenge to players as they advance through a world of untamed wilderness. Brave is able to transform into various animals, track prey, and battle enemies that stand in his way with bows and arrows, tomahawks and a variety of ancient powers.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A0iuhSGzKfQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7HxMYBmV3zI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Brave-Warriors-Tale/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/brave-a-warriors-tale/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/brave-a-warriors-tale"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":432,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Double Helix"],
			"synopsis":"As COBRA unleashes its deadliest plot yet, the G.I. JOE Team is counting on you and your hand-picked team of heroes to lead the counterattack. Every mission is critical and so is every G.I. Joe character. Picking up where the live action film leaves off, G.I. Joe The Rise of Cobra is an accessible third person action-arcade shooter that allows players to recreate and relive the greatest moments from the film, cartoon series and action toy line.<br><br>Choose from 16 playable characters (four of which are unlockable COBRA characters) - each with a unique set of abilities and weapons. Then gear up with the latest in high-tech gadgets (like the film-inspired Accelerator Suit) and high-powered vehicles and take your forces across 20 levels to face the worst threats in Cobra Commander's arsenal. Adding to the adrenaline rush will be an intense single-screen co-op mode allowing two players to easily unite as a team in a classic struggle between good and evil as they work together to defeat the powers of the COBRA organization.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x0mZStfjkko"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v2EoP391GBM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958043-gi-joe-the-rise-of-cobra/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/GI-JOE-Rise-of-the-Cobra/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/gi-joe/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/gi-joe-the-rise-of-cobra"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Joepedia",
				"url":"http://gijoe.wikia.com/wiki/Joepedia_-_The_G.I._Joe_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":433,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"Experience first-hand what it's like to \"Fight for Every Yard\" in Madden NFL 10. With the all-new Pro-Tak animation technology, players have more control over the outcome of each play. Whether driving a receiver towards the first down, or battling for a fumble at the bottom of a pile, the play won't end until the whistle blows. Add to that the most immersive broadcast presentation and online innovation to date, and Madden NFL 10 captures the authenticity and emotion of the NFL like never before.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"AFL Legacy Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/24",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Relive the glory of the '60s with this add-on. Play as one of the 8 original teams in the American Football League. This DLC also adds retro presentation, jerseys, equipment, etc."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Madden Ultimate Team",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/07",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Madden Ultimate Team brings a level of strategy to the Madden NFL franchise like never before. Create the definitive NFL team by collecting virtual cards that include nine types of cards ranging from NFL superstars, head coaches, stadiums and much more. You are responsible for selecting everything from the team playbook to the uniforms. Create your team by buying card packs, acquiring cards through the auction block and collecting the best players from around the league, including rare, legendary players. The perfect mode for card collectors and fantasy football gurus, Madden Ultimate Team provides a unique football experience, giving you total control over building a single team in the quest to be crowned the ultimate Madden team."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nfRWrwA9XbY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z8FKtE8CPfA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958702-madden-nfl-10/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Madden-NFL-10/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/madden-nfl-10/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/madden-nfl-10"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":434,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["MachineGames"],
			"synopsis":"Set within a near-fictional, historical WWII setting, players take on the role of the heroic OSA agent BJ Blazkowicz as they are thrust into the unknown and unexpected to battle against combat troops, otherworldly forces, and the dark science created by a supernatural Nazi force hell-bent on world domination. Wolfenstein offers players an action-packed experience as they investigate the powers of a dark parallel dimension, join with resistance forces, and employ an arsenal of conventional and otherworldly weapons in attempts to annihilate the Nazi war machine. Ensuring a deep variety of action, Wolfenstein provides gamers with an assortment of interlinked missions that drive an intense, story-driven combat experience; while the Wolfenstein multiplayer experience continues the world-renowned tradition of class-based team objective gameplay with a full arsenal of conventional and supernatural weapons for addictive online warfare.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ujycthb4B8E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mk9pMyrDOWA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u-x9N-U5054"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930281-wolfenstein/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Wolfenstein/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wolfenstein/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wolfenstein"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wolfenstein Wiki",
				"url":"http://wolfenstein.wikia.com/wiki/Wolfenstein"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":435,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rocksteady Studios"],
			"synopsis":"In Batman: Arkham Asylum the player assumes the role of Batman as he delivers The Joker to Arkham Asylum. There, the imprisoned super-villains have set a trap and an immersive combat gaming experience unfolds. With an original script penned by Emmy Award-winning Batman writer Paul Dini, the game brings the universe of DC Comics' detective to life!<br><br>Batman: Arkham Asylum exposes players to a unique, dark and atmospheric adventure that takes them to the depths of Arkham Asylum - Gotham's psychiatric hospital for the criminally insane. Gamers will move in the shadows, instigate fear amongst their enemies and confront The Joker and Gotham City's most notorious villains who have taken over the asylum. Using a wide range of Batman's gadgets and abilities, players will become the invisible predator and attempt to foil The Joker's demented scheme.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Crime Alley Challenge Map",
				"releaseDate":"2010/05/11",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Experience the unique FreeFlow combat system in this all new Combat Challenge Map, set in the iconic Gotham location of Crime Alley. You will face 4 consecutive waves of The Joker's henchmen armed with a range of weapons. Batman: Arkham Asylum exposes players to a unique, dark and atmospheric adventure that takes them to the depths of Arkham Asylum -Gotham's psychiatric hospital for the criminally insane."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Dem Bones Challenge Map",
				"releaseDate":"2010/05/11",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Enter this villain's nightmarish world and experience a unique combat challenge that will test you to the very limits. Batman: Arkham Asylum exposes players to a unique, dark and atmospheric adventure that takes them to the depths of Arkham Asylum -Gotham's psychiatric hospital for the criminally insane."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Insane Night Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/24",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Download this Challenge Map Pack and test your combat and Invisible Predator skills in 2 new locations, the Admin Secure Records Facility and the Arkham Prison Watchtowers."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r9fSkcAYyZ8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=02utCE9AQB4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uPnTSvX86Dw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DT98swC0Q-c"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/952337-batman-arkham-asylum/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Batman-Arkham-Asylum/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/batman-arkham-asylum/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/batman-arkham-asylum"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Batman Wiki",
				"url":"http://batman.wikia.com/wiki/Batman:_Arkham_Asylum"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":436,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Atomic Motion"],
			"synopsis":"Raven Squad puts players in control of two groups of mercenary squads who crash land behind enemy lines in the Amazonian jungles. It will require tactical planning and a liberal amount of brute force to escape to safety. Each of the eight squad members possesses distinctive skills and weaponry that the player will have to use wisely to progress through the game's story driven objectives. Raven Squad sets itself apart by allowing players to switch freely between real-time strategy and first-person shooter gameplay. Only by mastering both of these modes of play, and becoming adept at switching between the two, will players make it out of the jungle alive.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bXMZ3FXq_fE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2p66pbfvO8A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G4ial2bZu0E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Raven-Squad/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/raven-squad/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/raven-squad-operation-hidden-dagger"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":437,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Neversoft Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Featuring the best variety and biggest rock stars of today combined with classic rock anthems, Guitar Hero 5 cranks it up again for videogame rockers. For the first time ever, players can customize the make-up of their band by rocking with any combination of instruments in-game: whether it be two guitars and two drums, or three guitars and a microphone, any combination is possible, allowing players to experience music their own way. Brand new, innovative, easy-to-use gameplay modes like Party Play and RockFest put fun, competition and control at center stage as fans tailor the Guitar Hero experience to match their personal style and interests.<br><br>For extended hours of entertainment, downloadable content from Guitar Hero World Tour will be compatible with the game and will automatically be updated to include all of the upgrades and enhancements of Guitar Hero 5.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable tracks",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/01",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"More than 100 tracks available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VERjrXefCF0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r6TjqMuuqQw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Smells Like Teen Spirit",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bm2XfzICd78"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - We are the champions",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9MRvFzsdqmQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9MRvFzsdqmQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960093-guitar-hero-5/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Guitar-Hero-5/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/guitar-hero-5/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/guitar-hero-5"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wikihero",
				"url":"http://guitarhero.wikia.com/wiki/Guitar_Hero_5"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":438,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["TimeGate"],
			"synopsis":"Section 8 is a large-scale, futuristic first person shooter that brings strategy and tactics to the first-person shooter genre in a game where players can modify the battlefield on the fly.<br><br>The game's name refers to the super elite squad of powered armor infantry that serve as the focus of the single-player content. The squad's nickname is because of its penchant for taking on suicide missions that no one else will tackle.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Seek and Destroy Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/19",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":1
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8Zxi0PqkbJE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6dQyRYx1_yU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZntKOFniCjY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/941830-section-8/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Section-8/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/section-8/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/section-8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Section 8 Wiki",
				"url":"http://section8.wikia.com/wiki/Section_8_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":439,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Codemasters"],
			"synopsis":"Following on the success of the original Dirt as well as a decade of videogame development in partnership with the late Colin McRae, DiRT 2 explores various disciplines of off-road racing. Dirt 2 features a roster of contemporary off-road events, taking players to the most diverse and challenging real-world environments. This World Tour has players competing in aggressive multi-car and intense solo races at extraordinary new locations, from canyon racing and jungle trails to city stadium-based events.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QVqkPxykqpA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JVZ04fYgmNU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n5tl-KrbMWg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/955086-dirt-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/DiRT-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/colin-mcrae-dirt-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dirt-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Colin McRae DiRT Wiki",
				"url":"http://dirt.wikia.com/wiki/Colin_McRae_DiRT_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":440,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["8monkey Labs"],
			"synopsis":"In Darkest of Days, players travel back and forth through the annals time to relive some mankind's most dire hours, when human society was at its lowest points. By fighting through terrible events such as The Battle of Antietam, the bloodiest conflict of the Civil War, and the volcanic eruption in Pompeii in the year 79, the player attempts to save certain key individuals who were never meant to become involved in these truly monstrous events and thereby change human history for the better.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7_X4rbtP7qk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aZbzikj42iw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sc5PCj_8NFA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/961398-darkest-of-days/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Darkest-Of-Days/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/darkest-of-days/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/darkest-of-days"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":441,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gaijin Entertainment", "1C Company"],
			"synopsis":"IL-2: Sturmovik: Birds of Prey brings the hit flight game IL2-Sturmovik to console owners for the first time, with all new graphics, missions, physics and planes. The game includes large-scale aerial combat and ground based military operations from World War II. Players will participate in some of the war's most famous battles piloting fighters, battle planes and heavy bombers across a range of thrilling missions.<br><br>There are five areas of war to engage in - The Battle of Britain, Stalingrad, Berlin, Sicily and Korsun' representing the main airborne battles of World War II in Europe. As well as advanced environmental visuals enriching the game play, IL-2 also boasts an all new damage effects engine. Players can see real time damage to the aircraft such as holes in the wings and trail lines during dog fights. Hundreds of airplanes will take part in air battle in IL-2: Sturmovik: Birds of Prey and the unique environmental engine produces highly detailed, realistic landscapes that allows players to see breathtaking ground support actions. The difficulty levels will range from arcade to simulation.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Mission Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/10/06",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Soar over Europe in the legendary fighter-bomber - Republic P-47D Thunderbolt! Defend the besieged Belgian town of Bastogne, trash enemy tank columns and dogfight against a new Luftwaffe fighter - Ta 152 H-1 in the skies above Berlin. This download pack adds a new chapter of Single Missions, as well as two planes; P-47D, Ta 152 H-1."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8N9_C--zqZI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=75f1W63R3v0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iqSU-KDEtlQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/IL-2-Sturmovik-Birds-of-Prey/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/IL-2-Sturmovik-Birds-of-Prey/walkthrough.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/il-2-sturmovik-birds-of-prey"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":442,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Io-Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"Prepare yourself for a Ninja adventure like you have never seen before! Join Hiro, the smallest hero on the biggest adventure, as he embarks on an epic and electrifying quest to restore harmony to a world on the brink of chaos. Use your skills and mighty Ninja training to battle a magical army of evil Samurai. Harness the power of your Kuji magic and utilise the special skills of your Mini Ninja friends as you travel through a perilous world to reach the final confrontation with the Evil Samurai Warlord in his Fortress of Doom.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tQtT8njV2RQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M3Za8chLCGY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PcHDyz1lFzc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JrhSeLsOK3o"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/956191-mini-ninjas/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mini-Ninjas/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mini-ninjas/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mini-ninjas"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":443,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Moss Ltd."],
			"synopsis":"Continue the fight with the fourth edition in the shooter series. Raiden IV utilizes the power of the Xbox 360 to deliver Raiden graphics, gameplay and style like never before. The screen will be filled with countless sorties that you must shoot, evade and destroy, utilizing amazing new weaponry, along with fan favorites. Fight your way through countless enemy squadrons using four devastating weapons types.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Additional ship #1: Raiden MK-II",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/07",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A legendary fighter returns! From the 1990 \"Raiden\" series, this fighter has been added to the game. Defeat the enemy with the powerful weapon!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Additional ship #2: Fairy",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/07",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"That mysterious character that appeared in the series in the shadows is a surprise participant in Raiden! A fairy is added to the game."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R5YxiqptSoU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bpq2eDaiKkI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Raiden-IV/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/raiden-iv"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":444,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"The Beatles: Rock Band allows fans to pick up the guitar, bass, mic or drums and experience The Beatles extraordinary catalogue of music through gameplay that takes players on a journey through the legacy and evolution of the band's legendary career.<br><br>The Beatles: Rock Band offers the introduction of three-part vocal harmonies to game play, allowing gamers to revel in the unparalleled vocal stylings of the Fab Four. Beatles fans will also be thrilled to hear previously unreleased authentic voice recordings from John, Paul, George and Ringo chatting between takes during studio sessions recorded at Abbey Road more than four decades ago.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"All You Need Is Love",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/09",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Build your The Beatles: Rock Band library by purchasing this song game track: \"All You Need Is Love\""
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Abbey Road (Album)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/10/20",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Abbey Road. This includes 9 tracks: all of the songs from The Beatles' 1969 album Abbey Road, except \"Come Together\", \"Something\", \"Octopus' Garden\", \"I Want You (She's So Heavy)\", \"Here Comes the Sun\" and \"The End\" found on The Beatles: Rock Band game disc."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band (Album)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/17",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band. This includes 8 tracks: all of the songs from the The Beatles' 1967 album Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band, except \"Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band/With A Little Help From My Friends\", \"Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds\", \"Getting Better\" and \"Good Morning Good Mornin\" found on The Beatles: Rock Band game disc."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Rubber Soul (Album)",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/15",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Rubber Soul. This includes 11 tracks: all of the songs from the The Beatles' 1965 album Rubber Soul, except \"Drive My Car\", \"I'm Looking Through You\" and \"If I Needed Someone\" found on The Beatles: Rock Band game disc."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bpBDOolcs9g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bpBDOolcs9g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Yellow Submarine",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A5k4lZWAd8Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/954874-the-beatles-rock-band/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Beatles-Rock-Band/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-beatles/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-beatles-rock-band"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Rock Band Wiki",
				"url":"http://rockband.wikia.com/wiki/The_Beatles:_Rock_Band"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":445,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Activision"],
			"synopsis":"Cabela's Outdoor Adventures features North America's top outdoor destinations, over 50 hunting and fishing adventures and intensive use of gear and tactics, such as animal calls and stealth skills. Emphasis is placed on moments that are instinctively associated with hunting and fishing, like stalking the animals, squeezing the trigger, hooking a fish or snap-shooting a flushed bird, all while respecting real life hunting rules and regulations. Players can also upgrade their hunting gear with authentically branded real life equipment.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Uf4VBJReV1I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lV8E4dSEg2g"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/search/index.html?game=Cabela%27s+Outdoor+Adventures"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cabelas-Outdoor-Adventures-2010/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cabelas-outdoor-adventure-2010/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cabelas-outdoor-adventures-2009"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":446,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Transmission Games"],
			"synopsis":"The sequel to the mighty World War II flight combat game Heroes of the Pacific, Heroes over Europe takes aspiring combat pilots into the bullet-ridden heart of major World War II European air battles in glorious, dogfight-friendly high definition. Heroes over Europe follows the Allied campaign from the attacks on London to the destruction of Berlin, with players under orders to strap themselves into the authentically rendered cockpits of the campaign's iconic aircraft. Their mission: to survive the most intense dogfights ever seen in a flight combat game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jrmk8WqK4mg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=74vXUGbAAUU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Heroes-Over-Europe/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cabelas-outdoor-adventure-2010/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/heroes-over-europe"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":447,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Vicarious Visions"],
			"synopsis":"The greatest Super Hero action/RPG of all time is back with the world's largest army of heroes and villains in Marvel: Ultimate Alliance 2, the highly anticipated sequel to 2006's award-winning Marvel: Ultimate Alliance.<br><br>Incorporating elements of the acclaimed Marvel Civil War storyline, players must choose their side and team up to battle or interact with returning favorites and all-new characters, including Spider-Man, Wolverine, Hulk, Iron Man, Deadpool, Venom, Green Goblin, Iron Fist and Captain America, whose powers can be combined to unleash astonishing new attacks. Marvel: Ultimate Alliance 2 engages players in co-operative multiplayer through graphically rich and destructive real-world environments, and allows players to strengthen their ultimate Super Hero dream teams by teaming up to unleash astonishing fusions of super-powers.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Juggernaut Playable Character",
				"releaseDate":"2009/09/14",
				"type":2
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Character & Sim Mission Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/05",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=85y9xNlMiKc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7wweortLxUE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jUAECUM2RPc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/951211-marvel-ultimate-alliance-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Marvel-Ultimate-Alliance-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/marvel-ultimate-alliance-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/marvel-ultimate-alliance-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Marvel Ultimate Alliance Wiki",
				"url":"http://mua.wikia.com/wiki/Marvel:_Ultimate_Alliance_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":448,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Slightly Mad Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Shift into high gear! Designed to deliver a true driver's experience that reflects contemporary motorsports, Need for Speed Shift is built by racers for racers. Need for Speed Shift delivers an authentic and immersive driving experience, replicating the true feeling of racing high-end performance cars like never before. Players are thrust into the heart of the action with immersive and exciting features including a stunningly realistic first-person cockpit view camera and an all-new crash mechanic, providing an unrivaled sensation of the speed and feeling of racing a car on the extreme edge of control.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Team Racing",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/08",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"In Need For Speed Shift Team Racing players must prove they can be a team player as well as a great driver to keep their opponents off the podium. Teams of up to six players compete together against the best teams from around the world to prove they are the best. Team racing wouldn't be complete without some fan favourite cars to race in, so five new cars make their Need For Speed Shift debut. Please note - the five new cars are available immediately for use online and in quick race, and from tier two in the career."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Ferrari Racing Series",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/16",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Need For Speed Shift Ferrari Racing Series sees the long awaited return of the legendary Ferrari marque into a Need For Speed game. Some of the most celebrated Ferrari's of all time make an appearance, including the FXX, F50, F430 GTC and California. Players will be able to participate in new events designed exclusively for the Ferraris to participate in including hot laps, eliminators, endurance races and a world tour. Completing the perfect Ferrari package are an additional 125 gamerpoints as a reward for undertaking various exciting challenges."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Exotic Racing Series",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/18",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The Need For Speed Shift Exotic Racing Series brings together seven sensational racing machines including the McLaren MP4-12C, GUMPERT apollo and the Mercedes-Benz SLR McLaren Stirling Moss for a host of challenging events set on four beautiful new Riviera circuits."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dxkqsHf3rGk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VfXOAc9xSy8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O_Iq-Xgr7lI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/957702-need-for-speed-shift/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Need-for-Speed-SHIFT/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/need-for-speed-shift/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/need-for-speed-shift"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Need for Speed Wiki",
				"url":"http://nfs.wikia.com/wiki/Need_for_Speed:_Shift"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":449,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"The hopes of a franchise and its fans rest on your shoulders as you skate onto the ice to a deafening roar from towel-waving fans in an arena alive with the dreams of thousands. Here's your chance to prove you are tough enough to battle the most skilled and determined athletes in the world in pursuit of the ultimate prize - the Stanley Cup Championship. Prove your resolve, inspire your teammates and write your own history with NHL 10 from EA SPORTS.<br><br>NHL 10 features more than 200 gameplay refinements that replicate the skill and finesse of hockey, spectacular new ways to score, and improved goaltender intelligence. Winning one-on-one battles for possession of the puck along the boards is now a test of will and skill. Utilizing an all-new board physics engine, players can use their body to shield the puck on the boards and kick-pass it to teammates. Watch bigger, stronger players pin opponents to the boards while fanatical fans bang the glass, just like real life. Grab and tug an opponent's jersey to land the punch that ignites the fans and sparks your team to victory. Prove you are tough enough to quiet the crowd, silence the opposition and survive a playoff run to lift the Stanley Cup!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n09EMvrC1qc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dMk8XAR5D0o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NHL-10/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nhl-10/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nhl-10"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":450,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"2K Sports brings the fun back to hockey video games with an intuitive control scheme and hard-hitting action in NHL 2K10. True hockey fans will respect the attention to detail, while the pick-up-and-shoot controls allow anyone to play.<br><br>Improved controls deliver better puck handling, new defensive moves like stick lifts, plus stumble shots so you can always get the puck on net. Improved A.I., meanwhile, makes gameplay more authentic in the offensive and defensive zones. More accurate player looks and styles, brighter arenas and realistic pre-game introductions. And with 2K Sports' online gameplay, gamers can play in leagues and tournaments with players across the globe.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cZmADKbTIB4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DKXpIQfrC3I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NHL-2K10/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nhl-2k10/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nhl-2k10"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":451,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Loose Cannon Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Harness the power of a raging tornado and battle the forces of evil in an effort to save to world! Sinister forces have deceived you to believe that your destructive behavior will save an epic hero. In reality, you're working for evil. Take control of a dynamic tornado as you tear through open environments chewing up the landscape and spitting out everything in your path. The more you destroy, the bigger you grow as you work against time based, collection and point challenges in the search for hidden elements and enemies from another world. Watch the debris fly as you leave a trail of destruction, as you battle bosses and defeat the forces of evil. The world is your playground, tear it up!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vN9SG9mjTAQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I9RbqKQHEck"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tornado-Outbreak/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tornado-outbreak/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tornado-outbreak"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":452,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["A2M"],
			"synopsis":"Beautiful, graceful, brutal, and deadly ... Rubi is a problem fixer. She fixes problems. She's good at it. But when she agrees to fix a wealthy man's problem by finding and bringing back his wayward son, she thinks it's all going to be cut and dry. She thought wrong. The job wasn't so simple. And the man who hired her isn't who he appears to be. Now Rubi's on the run, needing to find the man who left her for dead, leaving a massive body count in her wake.<br><br>Double-crosses. Enemies. Allies. Guns. Swords. Drugs. Old books. In an adventure that spans three continents, two warring factions, and one very pissed off problem fixer, Wet is a sexy, super-stylish action game that will keep the adrenaline pumping. Rubi is focused. Rubi is determined. Rubi is a problem fixer. Rubi is Wet.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZvqnRUm1yMQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2eWMYei-5Sg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qn9nXH3ezWo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942900-wet/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/WET/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wet/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wet"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":453,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FarSight Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Williams Pinball Classics features stunningly accurate recreations of some of the most popular Williams tables of all time. Every texture, every flashing light and every sound effect has been lovingly recreated in order to deliver the most accurate simulation of the classic pastime. From the surreal thrills of Funhouse, to the intergalactic delights of Pin Bot, you'll be whizzed straight back to another time when life was far simpler.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bQ0MTfZd98w"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958022-pinball-hall-of-fame-the-williams-collection/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pinball-Hall-of-Fame/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pinball-hall-of-fame/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pinball-hall-of-fame-the-williams-collection"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":454,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Shanghai"],
			"synopsis":"Have you ever fought with food? Then join the most hilarious food fight ever with Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs videogame! Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs is the video game based on the CG family movie. Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs videogame offers kids and parents an entertaining experience that they can share together while reliving their favorite moments from the film.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JUoM_RxNDFc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/959216-cloudy-with-a-chance-of-meatballs/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cloudy-With-a-Chance-of-Meatballs/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cloudy-with-a-chance-of-meatballs/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cloudy-with-a-chance-of-meatballs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs Wiki",
				"url":"http://cloudywithachanceofmeatballs.wikia.com/wiki/Cloudy_with_a_Chance_of_Meatballs_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":455,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Nerjyzed Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"The Doug Williams Edition is a first-of-its-kind game that immerses players in the rich culture, history and pageantry of football game day on Historically Black College and University (HBCU) campuses. The game fuses realistic, bone-jarring football action created using the Unreal 3.0 engine with two unique new rhythm games - the interactive Halftime Show and Drum Line Challenge. In addition, a wealth of historical data has been integrated in the Legacy Museum and dozens of licensed tracks performed by college football's most entertaining marching bands are included in the game's Jukebox.<br><br>BCFx - The Doug Williams Edition features teams from 36 HBCU schools - including each campus' beautifully rendered stadium brimming with game day atmosphere - and offers players multiple modes of gridiron action. The Road to the Championship lets gamers pick a school and navigate a grueling schedule on their way to the BCFx Black College Football National Championship while The Classics Mode takes players through a season of legendary HBCU rivalries. In addition, quick play is offered for single and multi-player fun and Practice Mode is where players hone their skills.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oEDIxMJ2Lc8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u3yF-g-YjaY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Black-College-Football-Experience-Doug-Williams-Edition/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/black-college-football-xperience/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/black-college-football-experience-the-doug-williams-edition"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":456,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cauldron"],
			"synopsis":"In Cabela's Big Game Hunter 2010, players must combine precision, guts, and technology to earn a place among world's most respected hunters. Seek \"Super Hunter\" status and join the ranks of hunting's best of the best - a club where it takes much more than tall tales to gain respect. Players must prove their fearlessness and ability by successfully bagging the largest trophies in the world's most rugged regions. The most prized animals can only be reached by climbing cliffs, crossing raging rivers, and facing countless more perilous situations. Added elements for Cabela's Big Game Hunter 2010 also include rewards for successfully using cover to progress through missions and a VITALS system which helps players visualize the perfect shot.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0RFY2iKf68M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JB2IzC5y9uI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cabelas-Big-Game-Hunter-2010/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cabelas-big-game-hunter-2010/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cabelas-big-game-hunter-2010"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":457,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bungie Software"],
			"synopsis":"Halo 3: ODST's tale focuses on the legendary ODSTs or \"Orbital Drop Shock Troopers\" as they drop into the ruined city of New Mombasa, looking for clues behind the Covenant's catastrophic attack on the city.<br><br>The new campaign chapter predates the events that unfold in \"Halo 3\" and gives players a new perspective through the eyes of a new hero in the \"Halo\" universe. New multiplayer maps ensure that the award-winning Xbox LIVE experience of \"Halo 3\" continues to thrive.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Live Action Trailer - We Are ODST",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8wKbM_8kWUo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rQUZWx7o17k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iHk6znWyHPw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Firefight Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=clPN7bZkIZA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Campaign Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HTLsyNcPgsA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Firefight Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i1rO7ToDsEI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/954261-halo-3-odst/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Halo-3-ODST/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/halo-3-odst/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/halo-3-odst"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Halo Nation",
				"url":"http://halo.wikia.com/wiki/Halo_3:_ODST"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Halopedia",
				"url":"http://www.halopedia.org/Halo_3_odst"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":458,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Piranha Games"],
			"synopsis":"The Strike literally puts the fishing rod in players' hands as they head out to their favorite hot spots, including several popular lakes in North America. By combining high-quality, advanced gameplay with an innovative, motion-sensing fishing pole controller, The Strike is quite the catch for gamers and outdoor enthusiasts alike.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sMVZ8pMyj9o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j6LCrceeqVw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/961213-bass-pro-shops-the-strike/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Strike/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bass-pro-shops-the-strike/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bass-pro-shops-the-strike"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":459,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Brain in a Jar"],
			"synopsis":"You are the engineer of your racing destiny during the birth of modern racing. Reign supreme by pushing the boundaries of safety, reflexes and strategy in your experimental vehicle as you race against the biggest names in racing, and up to 32 of your friends, at the Indianapolis 500, Milwaukee Mile, Trenton, Riverside, Hanford and Langhorne Speedway.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KXSLB_e_KTg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=erroS06vD_Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Indy-500-Evolution/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/indianapolis-500-evolution"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":460,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts", "Kush Games"],
			"synopsis":"NBA 2K10 raises the bar again with revised gameplay components, enhanced graphics, even more realistic Signature Style animations, all-new presentation elements and competitive online play - this season you won't just play the NBA, you'll take over!<br><br>With brand new offensive controls that enhance dribbling and post game handling, you can pull off ankle breaking Iso-Motion moves and dominate like Kobe from the perimeter to the paint. Round up your friends and build the ultimate squad, using either your created players from My Player mode or an actual NBA team, then go online and battle other Crews for bragging rights and progression points as you try to climb your way to the top of the Crew leaderboard rankings. And with NBA Today integration, all the real world matchups, news and stats are automatically streamed right into your game providing dynamic commentary and presentation elements based upon what is happening in the real NBA.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Rp-sywkyUOc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EUkKP_Wpiw4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gGREtVlDzhU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g8-saLVUUL4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-2K10/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-2k10/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-2k10"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":461,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"Featuring several innovations to the core gameplay experience and online game modes, NBA Live 10 is bringing a renewed focus to the long-running EA Sports basketball franchise. The groundbreaking Dynamic DNA service, driven by Synergy Sports Technology, will make a return in NBA Live 10, with significant improvements that will allow players to connect their game to the NBA season like never before.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9T2bLCu1aK0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WVF9iB82lU4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hJm-lauNQUo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QfnMjOFFbhA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NBA-LIVE-10/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nba-live-10/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nba-live-10"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":462,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Codemasters"],
			"synopsis":"Building on the original game's heritage, Operation Flashpoint 2 aims to deliver the most realistic modelling of conflict scenarios in a new contemporary theatre of war. By offering a multitude of military disciplines, gameplay delivers warfare more realistic and intense then ever before, while an extensive multiplayer component creates battles on an incredible scale. The game challenges a new generation of players to survive the chaos and rapidly evolving situations of military combat in a new and contemporary warzone.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Skirmish Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/03/28",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Download the essential 'Skirmish' pack to extend the unique Operation Flashpoint experience with 4 new multiplayer maps and 4 new Fire Team Engagement (FTE) missions featuring solo and 4 player co-operative play.  Hunt down SAM Launchers hidden in the sprawling complex of 'Lumberyard' or assault dug in PLA forces in 'White Fang', two tense new 'Infiltration' maps. 'Annihilation' maps pitch armour and infantry against each other in rolling battles across a valley in 'Stomping Grounds' and in 'Force Dispersal' military bases separated by a strategic hill become a close-quarters killing ground. FTE mission 'All Round Defence' places you in control of air support to repel relentless waves of PLA and 'Uphill Struggle' tasks you to capture a bunker under fire from hillside reinforcements."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Overwatch Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/21",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Get some with the 'Overwatch' DLC pack for Operation Flashpoint: Dragon Rising, featuring new multiplayer modes and Fire Team Engagements. In Blindside, the PLA must complete objectives in the shortest time possible while the USMC defends in tense, tactical engagements. Meanwhile Supremacy tasks opposing forces to occupy strategically vital positions featuring force multipliers like gun emplacements and air strikes. These multiplayer modes are complimented by two exhilarating new FTEs. In Friendly Skies, PLA anti-aircraft artillery prevents US airborne reinforcements inserting into the combat zone. In Hostile Takeover, intel reveals enemy movement in the village of Armudan, a perfect base for launching attacks deep into enemy territory."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZqzZjVRqgGA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mv9XUsG8zy0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5HAmnz1W4LU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TWSTO82Oopc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7KQNKxpJEdg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Operation-Flashpoint-Dragon-Rising/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/operation-flashpoint-dragon-rising/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/operation-flashpoint-dragon-rising"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":463,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Zombie Studios"],
			"synopsis":"The story centers on Detective David Tapp who awakens in a decrepit, abandoned asylum. He has been captured by his longtime nemesis, Jigsaw. Obsessed with catching this serial killer, Tapp's mission has consumed him and ruined his family, resulting in divorce, mental imbalance, and abandonment. Worse yet, this frantic hunt destroyed Tapp's career while he watched his long-time friend and partner get killed by one of Jigsaw's traps. Now Jigsaw has the upper hand and has captured the detective. Tapp must play a deadly game-the likes of which he has been investigating for years-to escape, and in order to do so he must survive the lethal traps and puzzles that Jigsaw has put in place for him and others. But each victim has a dark connection to Tapp. Will Tapp save them? Can he survive his obsession to find the Jigsaw killer?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vpcORzvt2z0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NONH9mlBHw4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944706-saw/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Saw/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/saw/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/saw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Saw Wiki",
				"url":"http://sawfilms.wikia.com/wiki/Main_Page"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":464,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Krome Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Fans of the popular Star Wars: The Clone Wars TV series can continue the battle for galactic peace in this videogame that puts players right in the middle of the Clone Wars. Take up arms on behalf of the noble Galactic Republic, pursuing the mysterious bounty hunter Cad Bane and combating the all-new Skakoan super villain Kul Teska.<br><br>Players fight as both Jedi Knights and Clone Troopers through over 30 unique missions, all created incorporating the same ground-breaking, stunning visual style from the TV series. Featuring a brand-new storyline, players will get the chance to take part in the key events that lead directly into the second season of the TV show. Jedi characters can slice and dice their way through countless enemies, commandeer droids and show off their combat prowess on foot and in a variety of vehicles. Clone Troopers fire things up with a heavy weapons armament that includes rocket launchers, thermal detonators and even jet packs in levels built specifically to take run-and-gun gameplay to exciting levels.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SZdkN7_oqKE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960114-star-wars-the-clone-wars-republic-heroes/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Star-Wars-the-Clone-Wars-Republic-Heroes/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/star-wars-the-clone-wars-republic-heroes/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/star-wars-the-clone-wars-republic-heroes"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Clone Wars Wiki",
				"url":"http://clonewars.wikia.com/wiki/Star_Wars:_The_Clone_Wars:_Republic_Heroes"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wookieepedia",
				"url":"http://starwars.wikia.com/wiki/Star_Wars:_The_Clone_Wars:_Republic_Heroes"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":465,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Double Fine Productions"],
			"synopsis":"The latest creation from gaming icon Tim Schafer and the award-winning team at Double Fine, Br&uuml;tal Legend is a 3rd person Action/Adventure game starring Jack Black in the role of roadie Eddie Riggs, who sets on an epic quest to build an army of rockers with only a broad axe, a big block V8 and his faithful guitar in hand. Eddie Riggs has been drawn back through time to a mythical world dripped in Rock and Roll folklore; where great Metal titans once ruled and power chords rang from the countryside for all to hear. When an oppressed people request Eddie's knowledge of modern warfare, he pulls from his own experience in the only occupation he's ever had, a roadie for a Heavy Metal band. From this springs the most hellacious army man has ever seen, and thus brings this ancient world into the Age of Metal.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Tears of the Hextadon",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/03",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Br&uuml;tal Legend Tears of the Hextadon Map Pack expands the addictive Br&uuml;tal Legend Xbox LIVE experience with two new maps. In \"Circle of Tears\", vile waters have carved a rough-hewn circular battlefield into a forsaken land that players must circumvent to destroy their opponent. In \"Death's Fjord\", players find themselves on an icy mountain pass. A dense cluster of fans lie below, waiting to be harvested by those brave enough to capture them without cover from enemy attack. Bonus: includes a free axe, the Blade of Ormag&ouml;den."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Hammer of Infinite Fate",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/17",
				"achievements":90,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Br&uuml;tal Legend Hammer of Infinite Fate Map Pack adds four new maps to Br&uuml;tal Legend's multiplayer mayhem. \"Coiled Remains\" is located deep within the heart of Tainted Coil territory, forcing armies to fight in a desecrated Titan temple. \"Altar of Blood\" separates opponents by a dangerous arena that can be activated to fill with drowning blood. \"The Amplified Cliffs\" pits players against each other in a desolate wasteland of amps and lava. \"Crucible of the Titans\" plunges players deep underground to fight in the company of the Metal Gods as they dangerously forge the Br&uuml;tal landscape."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zxnho1yTjRo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3pxEH-v7E5U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CLW2Z0ijIP0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HHQoQ1npNBs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943672-brutal-legend/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Brutal-Legend/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/brutal-legend/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/brutal-legend"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Brutal Legend Wiki",
				"url":"http://brutallegend.wikia.com/wiki/Br%C3%BCtal_Legend_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":466,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Incinerator Games"],
			"synopsis":"In Cars Race-O-Rama, players will join Lightning McQueen and Chick Hicks in Radiator Springs as they prepare their academy of student racers to compete in the Race-O-Rama Exhibition. Players will encounter 12 new playable characters making their video game debut. A new and improved Lightning McQueen will come fully equipped with special racing kits, allowing him to better maneuver brand new, action-packed tracks that will take players to metro city streets, the Baja desert and sandy beaches. In addition, players are now able to modify Lightning McQueen's wheels, rims, hood, side skirt, rear bumper, spoiler and paint with special customization features, giving Lightning a personalized style and look that has never been seen before. As players compete in this high-speed, racing adventure game, they will be able to utilize Lightning McQueen's newly designed drifting abilities and perform \"Kachow\" poses for enthusiastic reporters and fans encountered throughout the game.<br><br>Cars Race-O-Rama will also feature multiplayer mini-games based on Disney/Pixar's \"Cars Toons\", a series of animated shorts from the Disney Channel.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=16nb72Q3v_0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uXBC_webb6o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cars-RaceORama/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cars-race-o-rama/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cars-race-o-rama"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Cars Wiki",
				"url":"http://pixarcars.wikia.com/wiki/Cars_Race-O-Rama"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"World of Cars Wiki",
				"url":"http://worldofcarsdrivein.wikia.com/wiki/Cars:_Race-O-Rama"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":467,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Softmax"],
			"synopsis":"The shadow of civil war looms over the kingdom of Lanzheim and Juto, a boy with no recollection of his past may be the key to ending the cycle of bloodshed. Magnacarta 2 delivers a unique role-playing experience that combines real-time action, timing-based attacks, over-drive combinations and the strategic use of skills, magical power and critical attacks on a journey to discover one's true destiny in the midst of tragedy and war.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Bonus Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/10/13",
				"achievements":240,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The MagnaCarta 2 Bonus Pack features a number of premium items for Magnacarta 2. 3 Bonus Cutscenes: Catch a glimpse of Magnacarta 2 characters when they are not busy fighting the forces of evil in these 3 candid and comical cutscenes. 12 Weapons: Acquire powerful weapons for each of the 6 main characters in Magnacarta 2. Each character will receive two weapons, one for each of their two fighting styles."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0T6W4foLRvE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PSckTbW36Jk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fssHc7wL_XU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_VFHP5ovbmM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/930253-magna-carta-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Magnacarta-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/magna-carta-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/magna-carta-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":468,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"Rock Band Track Pack: Metal is a standalone software product that allows owners of Rock Band and Rock Band 2 to keep on rocking with more hit songs from the pantheon of rock music. In addition, Rock Band Track Pack: Metal, like all Rock Band software, is compatible with all Rock Band instrument controllers and other current music-based video game peripherals.<br><br>Summoning power from the metal gods on high, the Rock Band team has assembled 20 on-disc tracks exploding with bone-crushing, ear-lashing, face-melting metal including anvil-heavy cuts from Godsmack, Children of Bodom, Evile, Judas Priest, Bullet For My Valentine and more! Six of the on disc tracks are brand new to the Rock Band platform via this package. (Fans who buy the Rock Band Metal Track Pack can play directly from the disc or download the songs onto their consoles' hard drives through a free online offer - once downloaded, the songs will automatically appear in the player's custom Rock Band library and can be integrated into setlists and played in all game modes of various Rock Band editions.)",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3wiY_rMrpjs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rock-Band-Metal-Pack/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rock-band-track-pack-metal/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Rock Band Wiki",
				"url":"http://rockband.wikia.com/wiki/Rock_Band_Metal_Track_Pack"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":469,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Griptonite Games"],
			"synopsis":"Where the Wild Things Are is a fun-filled adventure that takes players on a journey through the mysterious island of the Wild Things. Players assume the role of Max, \"King of All Wild Things\", as they team up with the fearsome but loveable creatures. While journeying across their island, players learn amazing new skills and abilities. Solve action puzzles, overcome challenging obstacles, and play through a unique story narrative to uncover the mystery behind the hostile island and save the Wild Things before it's too late!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UnBmC3OaolQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0lkr5dilew8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960686-where-the-wild-things-are/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Where-the-Wild-Things-Are/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/where-the-wild-things-are/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/where-the-wild-things-are"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":470,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Humongous", "FarSight Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Backyard Football '10, features co-op play for exciting 2 vs 2 action and is packed with a roster full of NFL superstars featured as animated middle-schoolers in the game. The game featuring top NFL players as kids and combines realistic NFL plays and strategies with wild arcade style power moves and comical scenarios so gamers of all ages can learn the fundamentals of football while having fun. Multiple levels make it easy enough for beginners, yet challenging enough for even die-hard football fans.<br><br>In addition to co-op, 2 vs. 2 multi-player action, Backyard Football '10 features unlockables bonuses, insane power ups, custom teams and characters, multiple play modes (single player, season play, tournament and all-pro) as well as a hall of fame.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w6nw3zvvXrM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RD98J1s2hF0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Backyard-Football-10/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/backyard-football-2010/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/backyard-football-10"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":471,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Now Production"],
			"synopsis":"Bakugan tells the story of Dan and his friends as they battle their Bakugan Brawlers to save the planet of Vestroia and, ultimately, Earth from destruction.<br><br>Everything a Bakugan enthusiast and gamer would love is here - intense battles, the ability to create your own Brawler, cartoon quality graphics and multiplayer combat.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HRNsTV5FRoY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iyxOyXmhyAA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6KHVoeEmR6g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xnsKWnKlNQY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/959714-bakugan-battle-brawlers/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bakugan/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bakugan-battle-brawlers/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bakugan-battle-brawlers"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Bakugan Wiki",
				"url":"http://bakugan.wikia.com/wiki/Bakugan_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":472,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gearbox Software"],
			"synopsis":"A sci-fi action RPG from acclaimed developer Gearbox, Borderlands combines the best in first-person action with player customization and vehicular combat for incredible layers of gameplay depth. The game features a groundbreaking content generation system allowing for near-endless variety in missions, environments, enemies, weapons, item drops and character customization. Borderlands allows for multiple players to share the same game experience simultaneously online in co-op gameplay. Players can freely join or leave each other's games at anytime, or choose to play in the full single-player mode. The game also boasts lifelike character animations, impressive real-time physics, and customizable vehicles.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Zombie Island of Dr. Ned",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/24",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The Zombie Island of Dr. Ned is an add-on pack for Borderlands with new enemy types, new missions, and new... surprises. The Jakobs Corporation would like to invite you to experience the splendor of a corporate owned small town known as Jakobs Cove. Any rumors you may have heard about the \"undead\" walking our streets are completely preposterous and we officially deny them all. If those rumors turn out to be true simply purchase a firearm from the conveniently located Jakobs Brand Vending Machines and aim for the head. Also, would you mind saving our employees? (Non-union only please)."		
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Mad Moxxi's Underdome Riot",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/29",
				"achievements":125,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Mad Moxxi's Underdome Riot is an add-on pack for Borderlands that includes a new cooperative arena game mode and a stash to store your gear. Are you god's gift to gun fights? Think you're the best? Wanna prove it? Then help us celebrate the grand opening of Marcus Bank (a subsidiary of Marcus Corp) by killing hundreds and hundreds of people in Mad Moxxi's Underdome Riot, the only competitive arena around where your next of kin can be assured that you're coming back famous... or not at all. (All proceeds are kept by us)."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"The Secret Armory of General Knoxx",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/23",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Borderlands goes to ELEVEN! You may have seen some games raise their level cap by 5, or maybe even 10, but with The Crimson Lance Assassination Squads wreaking havoc and Crawmerax the Invincible being all invulnerable and stuff we knew you'd need more than just 10. And that's why Borderlands goes to ELEVEN! The Secret Armory of General Knoxx is an add-on pack for Borderlands that adds new guns, new Class Mods, new vehicles, new missions, new enemy types, and increases the level cap to 61. In other words... best add-on ever. Of all time. Forever. The End. ELEVEN!"			
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Claptrap's New Robot Revolution",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/28",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"To combat second hand sales of used munitions among greedy, haggling treasure hunters on Pandora, the Hyperion Corporation have decided to activate the Interplanetary Ninja Assassin Claptrap. Instead, it has organized all of the claptraps into a revolution, and they've been assimilating all life on Pandora and converting them into claptraps. With our heroes caught in the middle, they must stop the Interplanetary Ninja Assassin Claptrap in order to release his control over all of Pandora's claptraps and collect their reward, of course."			
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v3ZWbpce_Os"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ly06B4j6KXA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Claptrap Web Series",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EmJEewnLRq8"
			},
			{
				"type":"The Zombie Island of Dr. Ned Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bu5TNw4O1bg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Mad Moxxi's Underdome Riot Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8b6i_I0x8pQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"The Secret Armory of General Knoxx Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xgVMhJI1zDU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Claptrap's New Robot Revolution Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xv92B2fPba4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lop16KBnDaA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=paldxVNu5jU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942810-borderlands/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Borderlands/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/borderlands/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/borderlands"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Borderlands Wiki",
				"url":"http://borderlands.wikia.com/wiki/Borderlands_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":473,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"FIFA Soccer 10 features core gameplay refinements based on responsiveness and intelligence, plus a completely overhauled Manager Mode that includes more than 50 major improvements. These enhancements and more deliver a high standard of authenticity, as FIFA Soccer 10 continues to set the benchmark in both innovations and gameplay as the most complete simulation of soccer.<br><br>Features include the 360 degrees dribbling system, which provides finer dribbling control, more than 50 major improvements to Manager Mode, more accurate passing and and authentic shooting, improved trapping intelligence, advanced positioning, and much more.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Ultimate Team",
				"releaseDate":"2009/02/25",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"FIFA 10 Ultimate Team offers fans a strategic new game mode and way of playing FIFA 10.<br><br>Build your Ultimate Team of the best football stars from around the world, manage multiple squads simultaneously, and take them into competition against other gamers in dynamically updated online and offline tournaments and competitions. Build your ultimate football team and play your way to football supremacy."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/results?search_query=FIFA+10+trailer"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RSSpmMU0M98"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MzJTIoMcpqg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/FIFA-10/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fifa-10/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fifa-soccer-10"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":474,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Codemasters"],
			"synopsis":"LMA Manager kicks off the new 2006/2007 season in massively expanded editions, with teams from over 50 countries to manage or pick transfers from. Every piece of information is no more than a couple of button-presses away in this management sim. LMA Manager 2007 utilises a new game and database engine to handle more teams, a Transfer Market system with greater depth for more complex contract negotiations, and a detailed 3D match section that brings the reality and pressures of match day alive. The game's enhanced visual engine will make full use of next-generation rendering systems, adding normal mapping, parallax mapping, and realistic lighting effects for even more detail that really brings match day home.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Stats Update",
				"releaseDate":"2006/09/21",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Update your game with the latest real-world player transfers and manager changes."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cpgMj_ejKuA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B5H_f-mwdfk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/LMA-Manager-2007/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lma-manager-2007/guide/"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":475,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Acquire"],
			"synopsis":"The consequences of your actions will determine your fate. Choose to fight along side good or evil during the tumultuous time of the Sengoku Era and carve your name into history. Take the role of a samurai and choose your own path, blazing a trail of honor, loyalty and respect, or one of villainy, corruption, murder and greed. Become a hero or become infamous, the choice is yours.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Head and Apparel Items",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Customize your avatar with a 'Western Samurai' visage or choose from 10 different outfits, including traditional samurai armor to unique, one-of-a-kind pieces like the Ghillie and Carbboard suits!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=htgA69_-9n8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0JmjAlQ8S9s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EQBnjSb_AQc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f5IuNndgRoc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/955514-way-of-the-samurai-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Way-of-the-Samurai-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/way-of-the-samurai-3-us/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/way-of-the-samurai-3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":476,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Yuke's Media Creations"],
			"synopsis":"Get ready the get the smack laid down on you once again with the '010 version of WWE SmackDown vs. Raw 2010. Stepping back into the virtual ring, players will experience unparalleled creation tools, a robust Superstar roster, key franchise improvements and even a few surprises in WWE SmackDown vs. Raw 2010.<br><br>The franchise's renowned customization interface delivers a new look, improved graphical quality and a host of new parts in Create-A-Superstar Mode, allowing players to create Superstars who are comparable in quality with their WWE counterparts. Take creation one step further with a new Paint Tool to detail created Superstars with original tattoos, logos and other unique designs. And for the first time in franchise history, create alternate ring gear for Superstars by customizing the colors of shirts, logos, face paint, elbow pads, boots and much more. Save the alternate looks for use throughout the game and online to show off the Superstars in grand fashion. Share created content with the WWE Universe by uploading created Superstars, entrances, finishing moves, highlight reels, created storylines and more. Utilize the keyword search engine to view created content from around the world and download for use both offline and online.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Stone Cold Steve Austin",
				"releaseDate":"2009/10/20",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Download this pack and play as WWE Legend, Stone Cold Steve Austin."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7uj_kK1Yttw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IJRpvSntvXA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960291-wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-2010/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/WWE-SmackDown-vs-RAW-2010/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-2010/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-2010"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":477,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sidhe"],
			"synopsis":"Jump behind the wheel and drive yourself wild as you play as Alex, Marty, Gloria, Melman, King Julien or those crafty penguins! You can power-up and perform zany jumps, outlandish flips, and radical rolls on amazing tracks from the world of Madagascar, including the New York City Zoo, the plane crash site, the volcano, plus many more.<br><br>Keep an edge on your wild competitors with cool pickups, such as power boosts, obstacles, and projectiles. DreamWorks' Madagascar Kartz features split-screen head-to-head multiplayer action, allowing up to four players to go bananas and race locally against one another in Championship, Quick Race and Time Trial modes.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NiD8TrpXR_0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QCjB9WZ9h_8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Madagascar-Kartz/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mad-karts-of-madagascar/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dreamworks-madagascar-kartz"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Madagascar Wiki",
				"url":"http://madagascar.wikia.com/wiki/Madagascar_Kartz"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":478,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Heavy Iron Studios"],
			"synopsis":"In SpongeBob's Truth or Square, players must journey through memorable SpongeBob locations to find the missing Krabby Patty formula in time for the Krusty Krab's Eleventy Seventh Anniversary. From the Jellyfish Fields to downtown Bikini Bottom, players run, jump, spin and hammer their way through 10 challenging levels. Each level takes players back to one of SpongeBob's happy moments from the show, such as when he becomes a fry cook, gets into the Salty Spittoon or meets Sandy for the first time.<br><br>Equipped with special morphing abilities, players can transform SpongeBob into bizarre objects, such as the Spatula Slam, Propeller Spin and Sledgehammer Smash, to help him conquer treacherous obstacles and legions of Plankton's robots. Players are also be able to soak up water, hose down enemies, and jump into a bubble gum fling as they navigate their way through an obstacle course of traps. In two-player co-op mode, friends are able to join in on the action and control Plankton to help SpongeBob solve puzzles, unlock new pathways and defeat super-powered creatures.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3_XL9my38Ss"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2IW4ntG-xxU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Spongebob-Truth-or-Square/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/spongebob-truth-or-square/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/spongebobs-truth-or-square"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Spongebob Wiki",
				"url":"http://spongebob.wikia.com/wiki/Truth_or_Square"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":479,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Imaginengine"],
			"synopsis":"Find out if you are Smarter Than A 5th Grader! Face Jeff Foxworthy's jokes as you try to answer more than 5,000 Game Time questions. Become a whiz kid in over 25 categories. Play like the show or try your hand in brand new Game Time modes including Three & Out and Schoolroom Showdown. Try your hand at Extra Credit mini games to boost your GPA. And if you think you're the smartest in the room, play against your friends and family in four-player challenges.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2kPNwCym3-o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Are-You-Smarter-than-a-5th-Grader-Game-Time/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/are-you-smarter-than-a-5th-grader-game-time/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/are-you-smarter-than-a-5th-grader-game-time"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":480,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Papaya Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Ben 10: Alien Force: Vilgax Attacks, players take control of Ben and the popular alien forms: Echo Echo, Goop, Brainstorm, ChromaStone, Big Chill, Humungousaur, Spidermonkey, Swampfire, Jet Ray, and Cannonbolt to manipulate fire, harness electricity, freeze enemies and more.<br><br>Gamers journey to exciting alien home planets on Ben's first intergalactic adventure as they travel in an upgradeable spacecraft and blast through asteroid fields and enemy ships. Offering a solid blend of combat, puzzle solving and platform gameplay, Ben 10: Alien Force: Vilgax Attacks provides hours of gameplay for players of all skill levels.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=biqP2P4BnjA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Laey7FWBDso"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ben-10-Vilgax-Attacks/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ben-10-alien-force-vilgax-attacks/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ben-10-alien-force-vilgax-attacks"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Ben 10 Planet",
				"url":"http://ben10.wikia.com/wiki/Ben_10_Alien_Force:_Vilgax_Attacks"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":481,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Telltale Games"],
			"synopsis":"In CSI: Crime Scene Investigation: Deadly Intent, players help solve Las Vegas' most gruesome crimes with the brand new characters and cast from the latest season of CSI: Crime Scene Investigation.<br><br>Explore crime scenes, dissect a victim's body, or follow the twists and turns of the story. CSI: Deadly Intent is an all-new immersive experience thanks to intriguing cases written with CSI show writers, a new rendering engine allowing for more realistic graphics, improved lighting effects, and enhanced character acting and lip sync with the voices of the actors from the show.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U96qhgFzEGs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nd00W1aBnRg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/961517-csi-crime-scene-investigation-deadly-intent/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/CSI-Deadly-Intent/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/csi-deadly-intent/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/csi-crime-scene-investigation-deadly-intent"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":482,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["FreeStyleGames"],
			"synopsis":"Introducing players to an all-new innovative turntable controller, DJ Hero transforms players into DJs who rule the club scene by creating original mixes of popular songs and music from the world's most exciting artists and DJs. This game features an amazing variety of music across genres. Using its authentic turntable controller, you spin and scratch more than 100 songs into unique mixes and become the life of the party.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Extended Mix Pack 01",
				"releaseDate":"2009/10/29",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Extended Mix Pack 01 contains two playable mixes: \"All Of Me\" by 50 Cent featuring Mary J. Blige vs \"Radio Ga Ga\" by Queen and \"DARE\" by Gorillaz vs \"Can't Truss It\" by Public Enemy."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Domination Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/29",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Darude - Sandstorm Vs Josh Wink - Higher State of Consciousness Danny Byrd - Red Mist VIP (Beat Juggle) Wolfgang Gartner - Wolfgang's Fifth Symphony (Beat Juggle)."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"David Guetta Mix Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/24",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"\"When Love Takes Over\" featuring Kelly Rowland \"Sexy Chick\" featuring Akon \"On The Dance Floor\" featuring will.i.am and apl.de.ap."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"The JAY-Z vs. Eminem Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/18",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"\"Shake That\" by Eminem Mixed With \"Show Me What You Got\" by JAY-Z, \"Without Me\" by Eminem Mixed With \"Encore\" by JAY-Z \"Can I Get A...\" by JAY-Z Mixed With \"Lose Yourself\" by Eminem."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Dance Party Mix Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/29",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"Lady Gaga's \"Poker Face\" mixed with \"Girls On Film\" by Duran Duran, Pussycat Dolls' \"Buttons\" beat juggle, Rihanna's \"S.O.S.\" beat juggle."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JkqKYvHxYKc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OoaNGBnPevM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Daft Punk Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P9S_1_6BzeY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PHzjZNC1IYg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/DJ-Hero/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dj-hero/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dj-hero"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"DJ Hero Wiki",
				"url":"http://djhero.wikia.com/wiki/DJ_Hero"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":483,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Playlogic"],
			"synopsis":"A sick & twisted fighting game featuring many of your favorite fairy tale characters from childhood now acting like the crazy maniacs your deviant adult mind could only imagine them to be! Players choose one favorite fairytale character with whom they will try and save a fantasy world from certain doom. Luckily many different weapons lay around in this fairytale world, which players can use to shoot and carve up enemies... and this is where the fun begins! Cute fairytale characters will fight each other until nothing else remains than a big puddle of blood!<br><br>Foes are sliced and diced in real-time, thanks to Playlogic's in-house \"Dynamic Slicing\" technology. Instead of using preset animations, players have the ability to slice up an enemy in any way they like by using the analog stick. Apart from this \"cutting\" edge technology, the game will also use the tested powers of the Unreal 3 engine.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=glG8N4MinwM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yJ1qbEnhp4c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Fairytale-Fights/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fairytale-fights/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fairytale-fights"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":484,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Turn 10 Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Forza Motorsport 3 unites the racing game genre, making it possible for everyone to experience the thrill of the world's most exotic and exquisite cars. Live the most realistic racing experience ever as you take the wheel of more than 400 of the most-beloved cars on over 100 renowned real-world tracks and exotic road courses from around the globe. With breathtaking high-definition graphics and the most advanced vehicle performance modeling in a video game, Forza Motorsport 3 includes a host of driving assists and adjustable skill levels to make the game a gripping pick-up-and-play experience for audiences of all ages and skill levels.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Legends Car & Track Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/10/27",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"10 Cars, '65 Alfa Romeo Giulia Sprint GTA, '64 Aston Martin DB5 Vantage, '81 BMW M1, '60 Chevrolet Corvette, '69 Dodge Charger, '57 Ferrari 250 Testa Rossa, '80 Fiat 131 Abarth, '67 Lamborghini Miura P400, '71 Nissan Skyline 2000 GT-R and '65 Shelby Cobra Daytona Coupe. Two Tracks, Benchmark High Speed Ring and Sidewinder Proving Grounds."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Hyundai Genesis Coupe Car Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/17",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Rhys Millen Racing Hyundai Genesis Coupe, HKS Hyundai Genesis Coupe, Forza Motorsport 3 Genesis Coupe."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Hot Holidays Car Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/08",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"2010 Ferrari 458 Italia, 2010 Audi S4, 2010 Mercedes SLR Stirling Moss, 2010 Lamborghini Murcielago LP 670-4 SV, 2009 Audi #2 Audi Sport Team Joest R15 TDI , 2010 Jaguar XFR, 2009 #007 Aston Martin Racing LOLA, 2010 Porsche Panamera Turbo, 2009 Ferrari 599XX, 2010 Nissan GT-R SpecV (R35)"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"AutoWeek Car Show Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/12",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Car Pack 02. Collect, race, and customize new cars. This pack contains ten cars: 2010 Aston Martin One-77, 2010 Chevrolet Corvette Grand Sport, 2010 Ford Shelby GT500, 2010 Porsche Boxster S, 2010 Pagani Zonda R, 2009 Audi R8 LMS Show Car, 2010 BMW Motorsport M6 Coupe, 2009 Audi RS 6, 2009 Lotus 2-Eleven, 2010 Saleen S5S Raptor. In-game credits required to purchase these cars in Season Play."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Nurburgring GP Track Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/09",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Download and race on the N&uuml;rburgring Grand Prix Circuit environment. This track pack brings a modern touch to the 'Ring: run either the Full or Short loops, famous for hosting the ADAC 1000km N&uuml;rburgring endurance race."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Jalopnik Car Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/09",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Car Pack 03. Collect, race, and customize new cars. This pack contains ten cars: 2008 Mazda Furai, 2010 Jaguar #33 Jaguar RSR XKR GT, 2009 Ford #40 Robertson Racing Ford GT Mk7, 2010 Aston Martin V12 Vantage, 2010 Porsche 911 Sport Classic, 1992 Bugatti EB110 SS, 2011 BMW Motorsport Z4 sDrive35is, 2010 Audi TT RS Coupe, 2010 Aston Martin Rapide, 2010 Honda Mugen Civic Type-R 3D. In-game credits required to purchase these cars in Season Play."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Road & Track Car Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/13",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"10 Cars from Road & Track: 2010 SEAT Leon Cupra R, 2010 Mazda MX-5 Superlight, 2010 Bentley Continental Supersports, 2010 Mini Coupe Concept, 2010 Mercedes-Benz E63 AMG, 2009 Holden HSV w427, 2010 Ford Taurus SHO, 2010 Renault Megane RS 250, and 2010 Vauxhall Insignia VXR"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Summer Velocity Car Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/08",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"2010 Lotus Evora Type 124, 2010 Ford Fusion Sport, 2009 Chrysler Jeep Grand Cherokee SRT8, 2010 Subaru Legacy B4 2.5GT, 2010 Bertone Mantide, 2010 Mazda Mazdaspeed 3, 2010 Morgan Aero SuperSports, 2010 Peugeot RCZ, 2010 Mercedes-Benz SLK 55 AMG, 2010 BMW Motorsport X6 M"
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"World Class Car Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/13",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"2011 McLaren MP4-12C, 2010 Mercedes-Benz C63 AMG, 2010 Mercedes-Benz CL 65 AMG, 2011 Cadillac CTS-V Coupe, 2010 Fiat Punto Evo SPORT, 2010 Kia Forte Koup, 2011 Citroen DS3, 2011 Mazda 2, 2010 Acura TSX, 2010 Mitsubishi Colt Ralliart"
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Community Choice Classics Car Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/14",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Car Pack 08. Collect, race and customise new cars. This pack contains ten cars: 1957 Ferrari California, 1982 DeLorean DMC-12, 1973 BMW Motorsport 2002 Turbo, 1990 Mercedes 190E 2.5-16 Evolution II, 1987 Ford Sierra Cosworth RS500, 1971 De Tomaso Pantera, 1971 AMC Javelin-AMX, 1983 Volvo 242 Turbo Evolution, 1978 Saab 99 Turbo, 1970 Chevrolet El Camino SS-454. In-game credits required to purchase these cars in Season Play."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3JaF3HZBwBA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ncJQwOaYlQg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5cVsdMMDsW4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lWdvAz2juRk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jme7oKv_MQg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/948030-forza-motorsport-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Forza-Motorsport-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/forza-motorsport-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/forza-motorsport-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Forza Motorsport Wiki",
				"url":"http://forzamotorsport.wikia.com/wiki/Forza_Motorsport_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":485,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Namco"],
			"synopsis":"Tekken 6 sees the return of many familiar faces as well as new characters to create the largest line-up the series has ever seen. Adding to the already rich gaming experience, a deeper character customization feature will only further enhance the incredible fighting intensity as players knuckle up against each others. Players can also take the battle online for classic match-ups and to compete for world domination.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cS0O-o9qY9I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UXSeYmB8BWU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Story Mode Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2GSf1ijucvc"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/954474-tekken-6/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tekken-6/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tekken-6/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tekken-6"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tekken Wiki",
				"url":"http://tekken.wikia.com/wiki/Tekken_6"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":486,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Vicarious Visions"],
			"synopsis":"Brought to you by the makers of Guitar Hero, one of the best-selling video game franchises of all time, Band Hero features the hottest chart-topping hits from everyone's favorite bands including No Doubt, Nelly Furtado, Lily Allen, The All-American Rejects and Jackson 5. Headlined by some of the leading names in music as in-game artists and playable characters, including singer, songwriter and guitarist Taylor Swift and Maroon 5 frontman Adam Levine, Band Hero is the ultimate party game where friends and family can choose to join the band or \"take five\" at any time without interrupting the performance, in Party Play mode. Band Hero allows fans to create the band of their dreams, using any combination of vocals and guitar or drum controllers, providing budding pop stars the chance to customize how they interact with and experience their favorite music.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable tracks",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/13",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"More than 100 from the Guitar Hero series tracks available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VI20gNiB7gc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0S3aJ_limXI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960601-band-hero/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Band-Hero/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/band-hero/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/band-hero"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wikihero",
				"url":"http://guitarhero.wikia.com/wiki/Band_Hero"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":487,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["BioWare"],
			"synopsis":"Dragon Age: Origins is the spiritual successor to BioWare's critically acclaimed Baldur's Gate, featuring deep character customization and role-playing, morally challenging decisions, tactical party-based combat, and a wealth of gritty, mature sub-plots. It is a dark, heroic fantasy game that combines original storytelling techniques with classic role-playing challenges.<br><br>In Dragon Age, your choices change the world and affect the people around you. Certain situations, storylines, and conversation options will change drastically depending on your origin and your motivations. You choose your origin, and from that starting point, your story begins. You play through your character's early days, defining his or her background and motivation and begin to learn more about the world of Ferelden from your own distinct perspective. Your choice of origin defines how you will view the world and how it views you. Choose a sneaky, disrespected commoner and you will play a story that focuses around subtle skills and careful wordplay. Choose a noble origin and the world will be much more positive and helpful, but those jealous of your status will not be afraid to take what you have, violently if necessary.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Stone Prisoner",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/03",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Crafted by the ancient dwarves as their first line of defense against the darkspawn, the dread sentinels known as golems dwindled in number after the art of their creation was lost. Shale, one of the few golems remaining, was found in the Deep Roads, reactivated and brought to the surface, and may prove to be the Grey Wardens' most effective weapon against the onslaught of the Blight. Includes: (1) Shale, a unique and powerful golem, as a recruitable party member who is fully integrated into the main Dragon Age: Origins campaign. (2) Brand new plots and adventure areas. (3) Fantastic new items."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Warden's Keep",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/03",
				"achievements":50,
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Two centuries ago, the Grey Wardens were expelled from Ferelden amidst a storm of blood and betrayal. Their fortress remains at remote Soldier's Peak, overgrown and reportedly haunted. Now comes a chance to unearth this lost chapter of Grey Warden history, to unravel the mystery behind its fall, and finally reclaim it for the order! To begin the journey to Soldier's Peak, return to your party camp from the world map and seek out a merchant named Levi Dryden. Includes: (1) A fun dungeon-delving adventure; (2) A set of ancient Grey Warden armor, complete with heraldry; (3) A chance to gain two of six mysterious new abilities. (4) A new base complete with merchants and a party chest to store your hard-earned loot."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Blood Dragon Armor",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"A set of unique armor also available in Mass Effect 2."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Return to Ostagar",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/29",
				"achievements":25,
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"The battle of Ostagar laid waste to your order and claimed the lives of many great men and women, including the brash King Cailan and your mentor, Duncan. Now, there are rumors that a fellow survivor of the battle has escaped from captivity and is seeking the Grey Wardens' help. The time has come to make your return to Ostagar and exact revenge upon the darkspawn. Includes: (1) A return to the battlefields of Ostagar, now thick with darkspawn encamped amidst the snow. (2) An opportunity to regain the lost arms and armor of a king. (3) A second chance to add Dog to your party. To find the survivor: (1) Play through Dragon Age: Origins until after the village of Lothering. (2) Travel to Bann Loren's Lands along the Bannorn's northwest border."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Awakening",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/16",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The archdemon lies dead - and yet in coastal Amaranthine, strange darkspawn still plague the land. As the newly appointed commander of the Grey Wardens, you must rebuild your shattered stronghold, recruit new Wardens to the cause, and defeat this terrifying menace. Includes: (1) A brand new campaign. (2) Five new party members - plus the return of an old favorite. (3) Six new specializations. (4) Nearly 70 new player abilities. To begin this epic adventure: From the main menu, select New Game, then either import your character from Dragon Age: Origins or create a new, high-level hero!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Darkspawn Chronicles",
				"releaseDate":"2010/05/18",
				"achievements":75,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Play as the darkspawn! The city of Denerim, jewel of Ferelden, girds itself for war. As a hurlock vanguard, you alone hold the power to make thralls of your fellow darkspawn and drive them into the heat of battle. Heed the archdemon's call-Denerim must burn! Includes: (1) A standalone adventure in which you command genlocks, hurlocks, shrieks, and even the mighty ogres. (2) A look at an alternate history: what if your character had died in the Joining ceremony, and the Wardens marched under Alistair's command instead? To begin this dark new tale: From the main menu, select New Game, then select The Darkspawn Chronicles."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Leliana's Song",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/06",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"A standalone adventure in which you play as Leliana during the mission - and betrayal - that changed her forever. It is years before the Blight, and Leliana is a young bard whose curiosities run more to passion than to the Chant of Light. Her mentor, Marjolaine, is determined to inflict the Orlesian game of intrigue on Ferelden. It is a time of adventure and excitement. And it cannot last. From the main menu, select New Game, then select Leliana's Song."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Golems of Amgarrak",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/10",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The dwarves' lost thaigs, forgotten for a thousand years, are finally within reach. Among them is Amgarrak, once home to scholars intent on rediscovering Caridin's art of golemcraft. But an expedition to the ruins has gone missing. Only you can uncover the gruesome fate that befell them. From the main menu, select New Game. Then, either import your character from Origins or Awakening or create a new, high-level hero!"
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Witch Hunt",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/07",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"A final confrontation with Morrigan! \"Never follow me\". With these words, Morrigan vanished into the shadows. Her plans and her whereabouts have remained a mystery... until now. But whether you seek answers, revenge, or reconciliation with your lost love, you may find more than you bargained for. From the main menu, select New Game. Then, either import your character from Origins, Awakening, or the Golems of Amgarrak, or create a new, high-level hero!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j5St9phiHHE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NKeEsG6mmHg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J6AuI_gpBbo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jJyZgArGbkk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fReq-56xLyM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/950918-dragon-age-origins/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dragon-Age-Origins/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dragon-age-origins/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dragon-age-origins"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dragon Age Wiki",
				"url":"http://dragonage.wikia.com/wiki/Dragon_Age:_Origins"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":488,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cauldron"],
			"synopsis":"Jurassic: the Hunted is an epic shooter set on a dark, mysterious island lost in time. Players assume the role of weapons and survival expert Craig Dylan, who has been hired to protect a research team studying the strange temporal energy of the island. Protection quickly becomes a fight for survival as Dylan is pulled back in time through the Bermuda Triangle and finds himself facing the most terrifying creatures in the history of the planet.<br><br>Combat encounters include arena style fights, fortification sieges, survival modes and unforgettable boss battles. Adrenaline bursts give you an edge - this cinematic gameplay feature allows the player to visualize and then target an opponent's weak points in slow motion. Jurassic the Hunted promises hours of dino-survivalist entertainment at its finest.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wG2wDli02ys"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hh1GipMBqmE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Jurassic-The-Hunted/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/jurassic-the-hunted/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/jurassic-the-hunted"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":489,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["TT Games", "Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"LEGO Rock Band is a unique family-friendly music experience which will allow families, tweens and teens to experience a wild journey to rock stardom where they can, build a band and rock the universe. The game combines the multiplayer music experience of Rock Band with the fun, customization and humor of the LEGO videogame franchise packed with brilliant chart-topping songs and classic favorites suitable for younger audiences.<br><br>Players will become rockers as they embark on a journey to stardom that the whole family can enjoy as they work their way through local venues, stadiums and fantasy locations on Earth and beyond that mimic the imaginative settings that the LEGO world offers. Also continuing the LEGO \"build-and-play\" gaming experience, players will be able to create their own LEGO Rock Band style as they customize their minifigure avatars, band and entourage, including roadies, managers and crew. LEGO Rock Band supports Rock Band instruments, as well as other music game controllers.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable tracks",
				"releaseDate":"2009/11/03",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"More than 500 tracks available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jd5fzsn70LI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J-xwjPuaCEQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C94uPWpqrdc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tzNq4bRS41Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qMEGhixAMY8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/959647-lego-rock-band/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/LEGO-Rock-Band/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lego-rock-band/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lego-rock-band"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Rock Band Wiki",
				"url":"http://rockband.wikia.com/wiki/Lego_Rock_Band_Setlist"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Brickipedia",
				"url":"http://lego.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Rock_Band"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":490,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Winning Eleven Productions"],
			"synopsis":"In Pro Evolution Soccer 2010 you'll find yourself on the largest stage in digital soccer: The Champions League. Imagine you're in a 1-1 tie in stoppage time against Manchester United. You've broken their defense and are sprinting full throttle into a man to man match of wits and reflexes with Edwin van der Sar ... Do you have what it takes to punch it in for the win?<br><br>The 2010 benefits from the most exhaustive raft of new features in the series' history, with every aspect of the game adjusted with key improvements. The Tokyo-based development team has collated feedback on the series' strengths and weaknesses via fan forums, both ardent and casual PES players and press comment, and has incorporated a wide range of requests in the game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OTL4ShdzuRE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MUT4sts3qJw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pro-Evolution-Soccer-2010/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pes-2010/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pro-evolution-soccer-2010"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":491,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Infinity Ward"],
			"synopsis":"Return to today's war front with the second chapter in the Modern Warfare series. Modern Warfare 2 continues the gripping and heart-racing action as players face off against a new threat dedicated to bringing the world to the brink of collapse. Playing as as Sgt. Gary \"Roach\" Sanderson, your international squad of elite soldiers battle through harrowing combat scenarios that range from snowy mountaintops in Siberia to the crowded streets of Rio de Janiero, Brazil and beyond, facing a terrorist force hellbent on redefining the boundary lines of today's modern warfare. Players can face the threat alone or with other players in cooperative SpecOps mode. For even more intense combat, take up arms against online foes in enhanced deathmatch warfare on a host of Modern Warfare 2 maps.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Stimulus Package",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/30",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Stimulus Package delivers 5 additional action-packed multiplayer maps featuring a variety of locations: \"Bailout\", a multi-level apartment complex; \"Storm\", an open industrial park littered with heavy machinery; \"Salvage\" a snowy junkyard fortified by stacked debris and crushed cars. Two legendary fan-favorites from Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare return, including \"Crash\", a war-torn urban environment; and \"Overgrown\", which features a massive dry creek bed."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Resurgence Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/03",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Resurgence Pack delivers five epic multiplayer maps: \"Carnival\", an abandoned amusement park with a variety of unique vantage points; \"Fuel\", a massive oil refinery with extremely long sightlines; \"Trailer Park\", a maze-like mobile estate surrounded by war-torn debris. Two legendary maps from Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare return more detailed than ever, including \"Strike\", a large urban center in the desert; and \"Vacant\", a fast-paced Russian office complex with few places to take cover."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XWIJTydRLt8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CbOWr1boplE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Campaign Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tco1i_ibOuQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Campaign Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hysduyu4JHs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L-VfGyvgZgo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Spec-Ops Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vuZRMpgpjfw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/951944-call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Modern-Warfare-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/call-of-duty-modern-warfare-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Call of Duty Wiki",
				"url":"http://callofduty.wikia.com/wiki/Call_of_Duty:_Modern_Warfare_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":492,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Activision"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the popular trading card game and animated television series, Chaotic combines action, role playing and turn-based strategy gameplay elements for an epic adventure in Perim, the stunning Chaotic world. Players adventure through vibrant, fully-realized 3D environments and interact with various characters from the best-selling trading card game and hit animated series. Players will build and manage their own army of Chaotic creatures while fighting enemies, collecting battlegear and unlocking new mugic (magic) spells and attacks. The Chaotic videogame features dramatic tactical battles, a variety of captivating gameplay modes, as well as powerful upgrades and valuable unlockables.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lizVoB5C3IM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HeJZNFHGS8Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Chaotic-Shadow-Warriors/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/chaotic-shadow-warriors/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/chaotic-shadow-warriors"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":493,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Spike"],
			"synopsis":"Featuring stunning HD graphics and audio, destructible environments and enhanced character features, Dragon Ball: Raging Blast takes players far beyond the realms of the original anime series. Interactive and destructible environments bring a new layer of intensity to the battle stages featured in Dragon Ball: Raging Blast. Smash opponents into rocks to increase their damage count and gain the upper hand in battles. Featuring the series' trademark combat style, the game hosts a variety of the most popular characters taken from the series, all of which have enhanced features such as facial expressions for a deeper level of immersion into the Dragon Ball universe.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Warriors on Earth Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The \"Dragon Ball: Raging Blast\" Character Pack #1 is now available! The first release is the \"Warriors on Earth Pack\"! This pack contains Krillin, Yamcha, Tien and Chiaotzu! These familiar warriors with unbelievable powers enter the battle and add intensity to the gameplay! Experience the ultimate battle with these warriors with exceptional abilities!!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Alien Warriors Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/17",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The \"Dragon Ball: Raging Blast\" Character Pack #2 is now available! The second release is the \"Alien Warriors Pack\"! This pack contains Vegeta (Scouter), Raditz, Nappa, Zarbon and Dodoria!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Ginyu Force Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/31",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The \"Dragon Ball: Raging Blast\" Character Pack #3 is now available! The third release is the \"Ginyu Force Pack\"! This pack contains Captain Ginyu, Recoome, Burter, Jeice and Guldo! The members of the Ginyu Force enter the battlefield! Goku fought them on Planet Namek in the past, but in this pack, they are more unique and stronger than ever! Strategic battling as a team is now required in order to outdo the rival fighters!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Androids Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/14",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The \"Dragon Ball: Raging Blast\" Character Pack #4 is now available! The fourth release is the \"Androids Pack\"! This pack contains Android #16, Android #17, Android #18, Android #19 and Dr. Gero! The Red Ribbon Army's deadly weapons have now been upgraded! The fortified androids' destructive powers are simply beyond your imagination! Their only mission is to destroy Goku..."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Warriors of Justice Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The \"Dragon Ball: Raging Blast\" Character Pack #5 is now available! The fifth release is the \"Warriors of Justice Pack\"! This pack contains Kid Gohan, Gohan, Kid Trunks, Goten and Videl! They fight in the name of justice! The power of justice will conquer all!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Revived Warriors Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/11",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The \"Dragon Ball: Raging Blast\" Character Pack #6 is now available! The sixth release is the \"Revived Warriors Pack\"! This pack contains Majin Buu, Kid Buu, Broly, Super Gogeta and Super Saiyan 3 Broly! The warriors among all warriors are now resurrected as downloadable characters! Make your own Dragon Ball battle history by fully controlling these fierce fighters!"
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Saiyans Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The \"Dragon Ball: Raging Blast\" Character Pack #7 is now available! The seventh release is the \"Saiyans Pack\"! This pack contains very popular Saiyan fighters: Majin Vegeta, Trunks (Fighting Teen), Vegito, Bardock and Super Saiyan 3 Vegeta! The Saiyans of all Saiyans now enter the Raging Blast battles! Who will be the last fighter standing...?"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Ultimate Warriors Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/11",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The \"Dragon Ball: Raging Blast\" Character Pack #8 is now available! The eighth release is the \"Ultimate Warriors Pack 1\"! This pack contains the fighters with ultimate abilities: Goku, Teen Gohan, Piccolo, Bardock and Super Gogeta! These fighters are already strong, but they now go beyond your imagination! See their true powers for yourself!"
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Ultimate Warriors Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The \"Dragon Ball: Raging Blast\" Character Pack #9 is now available! The ninth release is the \"Ultimate Warriors Pack 2\"! This pack contains Majin Vegeta, Frieza, Android #17, Android #18 and Cell! The ultimate fighters with exceptional abilities join the Raging Blast battles! Can you control their incomparable powers?!"
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Ultimate Warriors Pack 3",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The \"Dragon Ball: Raging Blast\" Character Pack #10 is now available! The tenth release is the \"Ultimate Warriors Pack 3\"! This pack contains Vegeta (Scouter), Vegeta, Trunks (Sword), Vegito and Super Saiyan 3 Vegeta! The long-awaited warriors finally enter the arena! Prevail against the life-and-death battles and become the strongest warrior in the universe!"
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Ultimate Warriors Pack 4",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/22",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The \"Dragon Ball: Raging Blast\" Character Pack #11 is now available! The eleventh release is the \"Ultimate Warriors Pack 4\"! This pack contains the earth-rending fighters: Majin Buu, Super Buu, Kid Buu, Broly and Super Saiyan 3 Broly! All the ultimate warriors are now itching to face each other and the battles now reach the climax! Your legend as the world's greatest warrior begins today!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9MxsiXVigjg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NICu0F4A5iY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960318-dragon-ball-raging-blast/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dragon-Ball-Raging-Blast/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dragon-ball-raging-blast/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dragon-ball-raging-blast"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dragon Ball Wiki",
				"url":"http://dragonball.wikia.com/wiki/Dragon_Ball:_Raging_Blast"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":494,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"Delve deeper into the secret society of assassins with the sequel to the blockbuster action-adventure game. Assassin's Creed 2 is an epic story of family, vengeance and conspiracy set in the pristine, yet brutal, backdrop of a Renaissance Italy. Ezio befriends Leonardo da Vinci, takes on Florence's most powerful families and ventures throughout the canals of Venice where he learns to become a master assassin. This game retains the core gameplay experience that made the first opus a resounding success and features new experiences that will surprise and challenge players.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Sequence 12: Battle of Forli",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/18",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Join Machiavelli and Caterina Sforza to defend Forli from the Orsi Brothers. Accomplish a daring rescue and prevent the Piece of Eden from falling into the hands of the Templars. Uncover new depths to the historical conspiracy by gaining access to six challenging new memories. Pilot Leonardo's flying machine across Romagna."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Sequence 13: Bonfire of the Vanities",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/28",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Work with Machiavelli to free the city of Florence from the grip of the mad monk Savonarola by targeting influential citizens under his control. Battle, sneak and freerun your way through twelve challenging new memories. Discover a new district of Florence, and utilize Ezio's new move, the sprint jump."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mVWhWsgHzKM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BI-OKx4GB5Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R20-MOOZPpY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PYyJWBxLfEU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Florence",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6EQcfB00fbY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Venice",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V0lhn9wustg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Assassin's Creed Lineage (Prequel of the game)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vcE8xJkK6t4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/956858-assassins-creed-ii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Assassins-Creed-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/assassins-creed-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/assassins-creed-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Assassin's Creed Wiki",
				"url":"http://assassinscreed.wikia.com/wiki/Assassin's_Creed_II"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":495,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Valve"],
			"synopsis":"Down in the bayou of Louisiana, all hell has broken loose in this second entry of the multiplayer zombie-fest. Players assume the role of four new survivors, each with their own personality and new dialog. The game leads them through the southeastern region of the US - from Savannah, Georgia through the bayou country, and climaxing in New Orleans' French Quarter.<br><br>This co-operative action horror FPS takes you and your friends through the cities, swamps and cemeteries of the Deep South, from Savannah to New Orleans across five expansive campaigns. You'll play as one of four new survivors armed with a wide and devastating array of classic and upgraded weapons. In addition to firearms, you'll also get a chance to take out some aggression on infected with a variety of carnage-creating melee weapons, from chainsaws to axes and even the deadly frying pan. You'll be putting these weapons to the test against (or playing as in Versus) three horrific and formidable new Special Infected. You'll also encounter five new \"uncommon\" common infected, including the terrifying Mudmen.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Passing",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/22",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Left 4 Dead 2's \"The Passing\" brings the original Left 4 Dead Survivors down south for a meeting with the L4D2 cast, while delivering new single-player, multiplayer and co-operative gameplay."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"The Sacrifice",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/05",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Left 4 Dead 2's \"The Sacrifice\" introduces the Left 4 Dead 1 cast into L4D2 in two action packed campaigns. This content contains English dialog with localized closed captions."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Cold Stream",
				"releaseDate":"2012/08/03",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Left 4 Dead 2's \"Cold Stream\" features the community made and tested \"Cold Stream\" campaign and four classic Left 4 Dead campaigns. This content contains English dialog with localized closed captions."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y0sJ5s7fUMQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9XIle_kLHKU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R8UE0rB1ZPI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Versus Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b2EXbk1_S2c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Scavenge Mode Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LfOLxtQs-4o"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960511-left-4-dead-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Left-4-Dead-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/left-4-dead-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/assassins-creed-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Left 4 Dead Wiki",
				"url":"http://left4dead.wikia.com/wiki/Left_4_Dead_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":496,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Traveller's Tales"],
			"synopsis":"LEGO Indiana Jones 2: The Adventure Continues combines the fun and creative construction of LEGO bricks with the wits, daring and non-stop action of one of cinema's most beloved adventure heroes. With a unique, tongue-in-cheek take on all the Indiana Jones films - including for the first time ever Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull - LEGO Indiana Jones 2 follows Dr. Jones' escapades from the jungles of South America to the Peruvian Ruins and beyond. Fans can experience the most authentic LEGO experience yet by designing and building their own levels brick by brick, and by fusing their levels with the ones in the game to create a custom experience. In LEGO Indiana Jones 2, everyone can build, battle and brawl their way through their favorite cinematic moments - or create their own.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KuSwjQem9-0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1ny3Rc1Bsrk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ulPHttYNyKs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cQvQVp7lZ44"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960444-lego-indiana-jones-2-the-adventure-continues/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/LEGO-Indiana-Jones-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lego-indiana-jones-2-the-adventure-continues/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/assassins-creed-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Brickipedia",
				"url":"http://lego.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Indiana_Jones_2:_The_Adventure_Continues"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Lego Indiana Jones Wiki",
				"url":"http://legoindianajones.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Indiana_Jones_2:_The_Adventure_Continues"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Indiana Jones Wiki",
				"url":"http://indianajones.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Indiana_Jones_2:_The_Adventure_Continues"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":497,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Pyro Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the sci-fi adventure CG family movie from Handmade Films International, which focus on an alien invasion of a different kind: the human kind! Astronot Chuck Baker has landed on a planet that has always feared alien invasion, and now a few youngsters must strive to help this \"spaceman\" get off their planet before the populace goes crazy!<br><br>In Planet 51 players will test their skills in out of this world action-filled adventures. They'll race, chase and evade enemies in an incredible array of hover vehicles and play as key characters from the movie as well as complete numerous story-based missions.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4X82FKP3ers"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4XaN1INd_7g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Planet-51/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/planet-51/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/assassins-creed-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Planet 51 Wiki",
				"url":"http://planet51.wikia.com/wiki/Planet_51_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":498,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Robomodo"],
			"synopsis":"Tony Hawk: Ride features a wireless skateboard controller designed in conjunction with the game to offer a dynamic gaming experience built from the ground up. Using a combination of accelerometers and motion sensors, the intuitive controller allows players to physically control the action by performing various movements and gestures on the board that directly translate into amazing tricks in the game. Without complex button combinations or analog sticks, gamers of all skill levels can literally step on the board and play!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GSopU76e3Us"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QDChr6rOBRI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JGc_wt_nbiQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0iztW6CageU"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960208-tony-hawk-ride/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tony-Hawk-Ride/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tony-hawk-ride/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/assassins-creed-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tony Hawk's Games Wiki",
				"url":"http://tonyhawkgames.wikia.com/wiki/Tony_Hawk:_Ride"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":499,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"NCAA Basketball 10 unearths the core of college basketball - excitement, emotion, intensity, and tradition. A laser focus on improving and refining core gameplay has resulted in the most fluid college basketball game to date.<br><br>College basketball is known for its strategic and calculated nature. NCAA Basketball 10 lets you use the unique styles and strategic motion offenses of every NCAA team to reach your full potential on the court. Force your opponent to play on your terms and let your team's strengths shine.<br><br>For the first time, watch your Maui Invitational or March Madness final broadcast with full CBS or ESPN integration, hear the shots being called by real CBS SPORTS and ESPN NCAA Basketball announcers, and witness the spirited crowds roar and mascots dance as you take home the win.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G8tCLrhMvug"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CfJ-u85CJWg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NCAA-Basketball-10/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ncaa-basketball-10/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/assassins-creed-ii"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":500,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blitz Games"],
			"synopsis":"Grab the mic and sing your heart out with the brand new Karaoke Revolution! Get the party started with friends or compete to win your chance at stardom. Includes 50 new songs, 16 new venues and online modes. Tailor your gameplay experience with all-new enhanced and customizable characters, a custom venue creator and downloadable songs and accessories. Can you handle the spotlight?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X1681XxV7Qw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wXbcyeKyEdU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ju3ytPcaIQc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Karaoke-Revolution/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/assassins-creed-ii"
			}]
		}
	}]
}