{
	"catalog": [
	{
		"id":501,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"James Cameron's Avatar: The Game is the official videogame based on the highly anticipated film James Cameron's Avatar. The videogame will take you deep into the heart of Pandora, an alien planet that is beyond imagination. Gamers will encounter the Na'vi, Pandora's indigenous people and discover other life forms the likes of which have never been seen in the world of video games before. When conflict erupts between the RDA Corporation, a space-faring consortium in search of valuable resources, and the Na'vi, gamers will find themselves thrust into a fight for the heart of a planet and the fate of a civilization.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eyCzeXYID7Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xw5lV0KgW20"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7I78EXQtN8g"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/956854-james-camerons-avatar-the-game/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/James-Camerons-Avatar/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/james-camerons-avatar/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/assassins-creed-ii"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":502,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rainbow Studios"],
			"synopsis":"MX vs. ATV Reflex marks the highly anticipated return of the best-selling off-road racing franchise and features the all-new Rhythm Racing 2.0 physics engine, Rider Reflex control system and real-time terrain deformation. The Rider Reflex control system provides unparalleled precision and fluidity by separating machine steering from body positioning, which allows the independently controlled rider to shift his weight, perform death-defying stunts and avoid potentially devastating wrecks. Unprecedented terrain deformation creates ever-changing courses as off-road vehicles carve lines and deep ruts that have a real-time impact on gameplay and remain persistent through the full length of each race.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RN69i4gN4vk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1mmWJmEdRMc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X13qRj44GQI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960123-mx-vs-atv-reflex/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MX-vs-ATV-Reflex/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mx-vs-atv-reflex/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/assassins-creed-ii"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":503,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rebellion"],
			"synopsis":"Rogue Warrior is a story-driven shooter that provides team-based tactical combat set in massive, contiguous levels using Unreal 3 streaming technology. Central to the game's single and multiplayer experience is the idea of a freeform battlefield, where players are given the freedom to choose how to complete a given objective.<br><br>You play Dick Marcinko, leader of an elite SEAL unit trapped behind enemy lines in North Korea as a war breaks out between North and South Korea. Greatly outnumbered and with no support and limited resupply, you must try to lead your team back into South Korea without alerting the North Korean army of your presence. Your journey will take you through a variety of never-before-seen environments inside of North Korea, including submarine pens, shipbreaker yards, prison camps, and more.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=STNiws4H6Go"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VbvKqIY7HuA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935989-rogue-warrior/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rogue-Warrior/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rogue-warrior/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/assassins-creed-ii"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":504,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Pandemic Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Experience the ultimate open-world action/adventure as The Saboteur. Fight, climb, and race your way through a uniquely stylized version of Nazi-occupied France, and hunt down your sworn enemies who have taken everything from you. Enter the seedy underground world of a saboteur living in 1940s Paris, where the women are sexy, the missions are epic, and the revenge is satisfying.<br><br>Play as Sean Devlin, a street-tough Irish racing mechanic seeking personal redemption in the first open-world action game set in Nazi-occupied Europe. Now, it's time for payback - with the help of the French Resistance, British intelligence, an arsenal of weaponry, and your own street smarts and brawn, you must exact revenge on those who aimed to destroy your life. Motivated by retribution and armed with tactics of sabotage, blow up zeppelins, derail trains, implode bridges, destroy armored tanks, and level enemy facilities in the name of vengeance.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Midnight Show",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/08",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Adds adult content that includes a V.I.P. room, hiding spots and nudity to the game."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l2gClnlzo4o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XhTizv7XYeU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=54WM3vdUgWA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/938953-the-saboteur/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/The-Saboteur/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/the-saboteur/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/the-saboteur"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"The Saboteur Wiki",
				"url":"http://thesaboteur.wikia.com/wiki/The_Saboteur_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":505,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Artificial Mind & Movement"],
			"synopsis":"Scene It? Bright Lights! Big Screen! offers a wide variety of media-rich trivia that provides movie fans and social gamers with a lively, competitive group gaming experience. Trivia content in the game includes recent hit movies as well as fan favorite Hollywood hits from four decades of films. Single-player mode challenges player speed and entertainment trivia know-how, while multi-player mode creates a challenging social gameplay experience.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UD1mK1XRsnc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tLjFtvqyKyw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Scene-It-Bright-Lights-Big-Screen/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/scene-it-bright-lights-big-screen/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/scene-it-bright-lights!-big-screen!"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":506,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Underground Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Guitar Hero Van Halen brings to life the flamboyance, virtuosity and unadulterated fun that has made Van Halen one of the most successful and popular rock and roll acts of any era. Along with 19 larger than life musical artists, including Queens of the Stone Age, Weezer, The Offspring, Blink-182 and Queen, guitar legend Eddie Van Halen, famous frontman David Lee Roth, dynamic drummer Alex Van Halen and skilled songwriter and bassist, Wolfgang Van Halen, give fans the chance to own the stage and put on show-stopping performances in the coolest, all-new venues from around the world. With over 25 of Van Halen's greatest hits from \"Jump\" to \"Panama\", the set list crafted for Guitar Hero Van Halen is the perfect combination of high-energy rock that will appeal to a wide range of fans.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hHUUUTGy240"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Panama",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IsBJYwhyicE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay - Dance the night away",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a9VDMmkhQ8g"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Guitar-Hero-Van-Halen/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/guitar-hero-van-halen/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/guitar-hero-van-halen"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wikihero",
				"url":"http://guitarhero.wikia.com/wiki/Guitar_Hero:_Van_Halen"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":507,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Platinum Games"],
			"synopsis":"Bayonetta is a stylish and cinematic action game, directed by Hideki Kamiya.<br><br>A witch with powers beyond the comprehension of mere mortals, Bayonetta faces-off against countless angelic enemies, many reaching epic proportions, in a game of 100 percent pure, unadulterated all-out action. Outlandish finishing moves are performed with balletic grace as Bayonetta flows from one fight to another. With magnificent over-the-top action taking place in stages that are a veritable theme park of exciting attractions, Bayonetta pushes the limits of the action genre, bringing to life its fast-paced, dynamic climax combat.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1L8-KZhW04s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TAqtig_EI-c"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OWolGErlxlU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZDtRb-iDAAw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/946346-bayonetta/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Bayonetta/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bayonetta/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bayonetta"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Bayonetta Wiki",
				"url":"http://bayonetta.wikia.com/wiki/Bayonetta_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":508,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Vigil Games"],
			"synopsis":"Penned by legendary comic book artist Joe Madureira (X-Men, Battle Chasers, The Ultimates), Darksiders: Wrath of War is set in a Post-Apocalyptic demon-ravaged world where evil forces have prematurely brought about the end of the time. Originally sent to oversee the destruction of Earth, the Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse have been betrayed by their master, stripped of their powers and cast down to Earth. Players take on the role of WAR - the first of the Four Horsemen - as he embarks on a brutal quest of vengeance and revenge against the forces that betrayed him with the help of his phantom steed RUIN. Darksiders: Wrath of War features open-world exploration, a deep combat system and a huge arsenal of modern and mythical weapons.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9VMxP_GstP8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NzI0O4-kOSk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B4JPTHf975A"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xKIahqn6WYw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942006-darksiders/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Darksiders/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/darksiders-wrath-of-war/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/darksiders"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Darksiders Wiki",
				"url":"http://darksiders.wikia.com/wiki/Darksiders_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":509,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Larian Studios"],
			"synopsis":"In Divinity II: Ego Draconis, players find themselves once again in Rivellon, a timeless world full of awe and magic, shattered and frightened by the apocalyptic wars of the past. No one knows why so many people had to give their lives. Everything seems to be over, but the peace was deceptive, for the demon has returned and the horror once again runs its course.<br><br>Players begin as a Dragon Slayer, hunters whom travel the countryside determined to rid their lands of Dragons. As the story of Divinity 2 - Ego Draconis unfolds, the player will discover new abilities and possibilities as they evolve into a legendary Dragon Lord. In addition, the player character's abilities can be steadily improved over the course of the game and specialized in specific areas. The world of Divinity II: Ego Draconis is filled with humans and fantasy creatures, each having special combat abilities. Players will need to use every skill, potion and hidden trick to their strategic advantage to reclaim the lands of Rivellon.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YWKkkNkE8fo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UEf8FxYvFTQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8QpuXJvlEjM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/977060-divinity-ii-ego-draconis/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Divinity-2-Ego-Draconis/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/divinity-2-ego-draconis/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/divinity-ii-ego-draconis"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Divinity Wiki",
				"url":"http://divinity.wikia.com/wiki/Divinity_II:_Ego_Draconis"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":510,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"The wild boys of the SSC face hell again in this sequel to the hit third-person teamwork-based shooter. Army of Two: The 40th Day reunites Salem and Rios as they're forced to survive in a city under siege. The sequel includes more co-op moves for players to use at any time, which will allow for completely different strategies and options in battle, adding up to a bigger, more organic and immersive co-op experience.<br><br>The story of The 40th Day places Salem and Rios in the middle of Shanghai, China, as a disaster of epic proportions strikes the city. While they happen to be in the wrong place at the wrong time, they are the right men to react to the chaos. As they fight their way through ruined districts of the city, they discover more and more catastrophes are being orchestrated to devastate Shanghai piece by piece. It's up two Salem and Rios to uncover the secret of the 40th Day and survive the chaos.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Chapters of Deceit",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/18",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Get ready for more action-packed co-op in two brand new campaign maps, \"Collateral\" and \"Assassination\"."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sZPSM7l9RKk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ki1A5GoqRS4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VjNYwu_bUIk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958804-army-of-two-the-40th-day/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Army-of-Two-the-40th-Day/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/army-of-two-the-40th-day/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/army-of-two-the-40th-day"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Army of Two Wiki",
				"url":"http://armyoftwo.wikia.com/wiki/Army_of_Two:_The_40th_Day"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":511,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eurocom"],
			"synopsis":"Vancouver 2010 is an authentic simulation of a host of events from the Vancouver 2010 Olympic Winter Games, focusing on the adrenalin rush that comes from the extreme speed of winter sports. Including an all new challenge mode, the game allows players to immerse themselves in the world's greatest sporting event like never before.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YUb-ctlljhI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q_IJc_CeMfI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gPajsNzRUH4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Vancouver-2010/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/vancouver-2010/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/vancouver-2010---the-official-video-game-of-the-olympic-winter-games"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":512,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Airtight Games"],
			"synopsis":"Dark Void delivers a ground breaking combination of fast paced vertical combat mixed with mid-air and on-foot action.<br><br>Something is consuming our universe, a vast and ancient force almost beyond our comprehension. Millions of years ago, the minions of that power found their way to the 3rd planet of an unremarkable yellow star. Ours. The race they created came to call their masters \"The Watchers\". For millennia we knew them as gods and served their dark purposes, but a few humans developed extraordinary powers. They were known as the Adepts and they rose up, banishing The Watchers into a parallel universe, where they've manipulated and schemed from afar. Until now.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Survivor Missions",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/10",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"Fight off waves of Watchers in this \"arcade-esque\" add-on."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EzPwCz1nbE8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UuEZ-Bw3xtQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943726-dark-void/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dark-Void/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dark-void/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dark-void"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":513,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cyanide"],
			"synopsis":"A brutal team sport unfolding in a parallel fantasy world based on Warhammer and American football, Blood Bowl invites gamers to form a team of players from races including: Orcs, Elves, Humans, Dwarfs and many other fantasy creatures, and launch themselves into battle in the bloodiest of arenas. This strategy sports game combines a fine balance of tactics and bone crunching action.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Dark Elves",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/30",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Dark Elves take to the pitch! The dreadful Dark Elves encompass the best traits of the best teams in the whole Blood Bowl world, in one perfect package... or so their arrogant coaches would have you believe! This new team enters the Blood Bowl arena with their own Star Player, cheerleaders, and players combining Wood Elf agility with a more obvious brutality. A real treat to play and to watch!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t3xsSN7UEFI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9mF2s9NuFq0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Blood-Bowl/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/blood-bowl/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/blood-bowl"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":514,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["BioWare"],
			"synopsis":"Once again stepping into the role of the heroic Commander Shepard, gamers command their crew on a suicide mission in space. Players must assemble their squad from amongst the galaxy's most powerful mystics, geniuses, and convicts and lead them on a suicide mission to discover why humans are vanishing from the galaxy. The success of the mission hinges on the squad recruited and their loyalty to the mission. Shepard's future depends on it.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Cerberus Network",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/26",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Original copies of Mass Effect 2 contain a redemption code to obtain Cerberus Network activation. Connect now and receive bonus downloadable content. Access henchmen, missions, and news via direct feed in-game."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Zaeed - The Price of Revenge",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Shepard's shadowy backers buy the loyalty of Zaeed Massani, the galaxy's most feared bounty hunter and mercenary soldier. This DLC adds a new henchman (Zaeed Massani), new weapons research, and new achievements. This DLC is free through the Cerberus Network."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Normandy Crash Site",
				"releaseDate":"2010/01/28",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Shepard discovers the location of the Normandy Crash Site, emotionally charged and reflective moment for Shepard as he/she is on a mission salvage and recovery. This DLC is free through the Cerberus Network."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Firewalker",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/23",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The Firewalker downloadable content pack features 5 missions centered around the Hammerhead hovercraft. This DLC is free through the Cerberus Network."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Alternate Appearance Pack 1 (Garrus, Thane, Jack)",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/23",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Jack straps on a black biker vest, low-slung jeans, and steel-toe boots made for starting riots. Garrus suits up in new military-grade, blue-lit armor equipped with a dual-input communication headset. Thane slips into blood-red reflective shades and a new uniform for blending into the urban shadows."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Kasumi's Stolen Memory",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/06",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Cerberus has procured the service of Kasumi Goto, the galaxy's most enigmatic master thief. In return for her help, Kasumi has asked Shepard's help on a dangerous heist to infiltrate the vault of a deadly master criminal named Donovan Hock. Gain Kasumi's loyalty on the planet Bekenstein, where Hock is throwing a party for the galaxy's richest and most deranged criminal minds to recover data of great importance to Kasumi... and to the galaxy at large. New squad member, weapon, research, and achievement."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Equalizer Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/05/04",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Cerberus doesn't just need a hero - they need a one-man army. That's why The Equalizer Pack adds the Capacitor Helmet, Archon Visor, and Inferno Armor to Shepard's armor locker. The Capacitor Helmet stores power for kinetic barriers, allowing Shepard's shields to recharge faster. The Archon Visor manages omni-tools and biotic amps, reducing the recharge time of Shepard's powers. The powered Inferno Armor speeds up Shepard's movements and increases his tech and biotic power damage. Stress analysis software even gives him an edge in negotiations outside of combat."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Overlord",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/15",
				"achievements":25,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Keep a powerful hybrid VI intelligence - and the geth it has unleashed upon a planet - from wreaking havoc across the galaxy! \"Overlord\" includes 5 new levels, exciting ground combat and Hammerhead missions, and all-new achievements!"
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Aegis Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/06",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Aegis Pack adds the M-29 Incisor sniper rifle and the Kestrel armor to Shepard's armor locker. The Incisor sniper rifle is a burst-fire weapon that excels in destroying enemy shields. The Kestrel armor comes in five pieces: The Kestrel Helmet adds weapon damage, shield strength, and headshot damage. The Kestrel Torso Sheath adds melee and weapon damage and shield strength. Kestrel Arm Sheathing adds melee and weapon damage and shield strength. Kestrel Shoulder Pieces adds shields and melee damage. The Kestrel hip-mounted Power Pack ups shields and heavy weapon ammo capacity."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"FirePower Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/03",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Firepower Pack adds three new weapons to Shepard's armor locker: When a \"heavy\" pistol won't do the job, the Phalanx brings the bang! It hits like a hand cannon and features an integral laser sight for a whole new aiming experience! Ever wanted a sniper rifle without the scope or an assault rifle without the recoil? The Mattock heavy rifle is a hybrid of the two, a semi-auto beast usable by any class with an assault rifle skill! The Geth Plasma Shotgun is a three-barreled monster that creates plasma the right way - on impact! Charge it up for even greater damage, or blast away rapid-fire at longer ranges than normal shotguns!"
			},
			{
				"id":11,
				"name":"Lair of the Shadow Broker",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/07",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Liara T'Soni is tracking down the mysterious Shadow Broker, and no one is safe. She'll do anything to recover the man the Broker kidnapped... and the Shadow Broker's agents will do anything to stop her. Team up with Liara and chase clues from the luxurious heights of Illium to the Shadow Broker's own secret lair. Adds the Shadow Broker intel center, new research, and five new achievements - and the chance to continue a relationship with Liara."
			},
			{
				"id":12,
				"name":"Alternate Appearance Pack 2 (Miranda, Grunt, Tali)",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Alternate Appearance Pack 2 gives new outfits to Miranda, Grunt, and Tali. How do you make Grunt feel at home? You can start by encasing him in 100 kilos of bullet-resistant plating! This krogan-built ensemble sends a message, but just what it says, we can't repeat in polite company. Tali's envirosuit gets an upgrade, armoring her delicate torso and projecting a heads-up-display on the inside of her visor. Being hermetically sealed from all contamination has never looked so good! Miranda shows her colors with the \"do not touch\" palette of Cerberus armor. Say goodbye to catsuits and hello to composite ceramics in bad-girl black! Alternate Appearance Pack 2 - Because it's time to put the \"war\" back in \"wardrobe\"."
			},
			{
				"id":13,
				"name":"Arrival",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/29",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"A deep cover operative has gone missing in Batarian space, days after reporting conclusive evidence of an imminent Reaper invasion. Shepard must travel to the edge of the galaxy, rescue the Alliance agent, and discover the truth behind the Arrival. Uncover new research and three new achievements in this spectacular new mission for Mass Effect 2!"
			},
			{
				"id":14,
				"name":"Mass Effect: Genesis",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/17",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"This digital comic back-story was created by BioWare and Dark Horse comics. The 15 minute interactive experience allows you to make the key choices of Mass Effect 1. This retelling will also let you have those choices reflected during Mass Effect 2."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bIG2dWLHaYU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lBRo7JWy744"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y2O-0-fQOOs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5vKECDzAC_M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Mass Effect 1 Recap in 10 minutes",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gvuwY50ngR0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/944907-mass-effect-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mass-Effect-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mass-effect-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mass-effect-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Mass Effect Wiki",
				"url":"http://masseffect.wikia.com/wiki/Mass_Effect_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":515,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["2K Marin", "Digital Extremes"],
			"synopsis":"Set during the fall of Rapture, players assume the role of a Plasmid test subject for Sinclair Solutions, a premier provider of Plasmids and Tonics in the underwater city of Rapture that was first explored in the original BioShock. Players will need to use all the elements of the BioShock toolset to survive as the full depth of the BioShock experience is refined and transformed into a unique multiplayer experience that can only be found in Rapture.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Zigo & Blanche",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/09",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Enroll in Sinclair Solution's Consumer Rewards Program with two new characters for the BioShock 2 Multiplayer experience: Mlle Blanche de Glace, the internationally acclaimed actress, or Zigo D'Acosta, one of Rapture's great sailors. Get out there and start earning those rewards!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Sinclair Solutions Test Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/11",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Opportunity Awaits! Expand your BioShock 2 multiplayer experience with a rank increase to 50 with Rank Rewards including a 3rd set of weapons upgrades. Plus, enjoy 20 new Trials, 2 new playable characters and 5 new Masks. Yes! We'd thought you'd like the sound of that!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Kill 'em Kindly",
				"releaseDate":"2010/05/10",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"What's your golf handicap? Take this chance to turn your handicap into your enemy's with this fresh melee mode where every blunt object is a golf club. No putting."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Rapture Metro",
				"releaseDate":"2010/05/11",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"As one of our valued Sinclair Solutions testers, we specially invite you to enjoy the pleasure of Rebirth! But only if you are truly dedicated and fully ranked up. However all testers are eligible for the 6 new maps in Rapture Metro."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Protector Trials",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/03",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"You receive the call: Tenenbaum desperately needs you to steal as much ADAM as possible, to help thwart Sofia Lamb's insane plan. Enter the Protector Trials: frantic combat challenges designed to push your mastery of weapons and Plasmids to the limit. The goal in each Trial is simple: get your Little Sister to an ADAM-rich corpse and keep her safe while she gathers precious ADAM. Opposition mounts as your Little Sister nears her goal - will you survive the onslaught? Each Trial features three unique weapon and Plasmid load-outs, keeping the challenge fresh, as well as a fourth bonus load-out the player receives when all previous load-outs are completed."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Minerva's Den",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/31",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Minerva's Den offers a brand-new, self-contained BioShock story, presenting a side of Rapture you've never seen before. Seek out the tools you'll need to unlock new goals and spaces in the order you choose. Face Rapture's full range of opposition as you increase in power-a new challenge is always right around the corner. Expand your combat abilities with the experimental Ion Laser and chaotic Gravity Well Plasmid, unique to Minerva's Den. Face off against the new Lancer Big Daddy, the most advanced Protector that Rapture ever produced. Explore every shadowy corner of Minerva's Den, unraveling the mysterious past of The Thinker's inventor, and the dark secrets hidden within the unfeeling, omniscient machine he created."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Cinematic Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q8lngIFXRi4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j9btcfmntC8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=85KluhX53J4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945380-bioshock-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/BioShock-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bioshock-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bioshock-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Bioshock Wiki",
				"url":"http://bioshock.wikia.com/wiki/BioShock_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":516,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visceral Games"],
			"synopsis":"In Dante's Inferno, players assume the role of Dante as he travels on an epic descent through Dante Alighieri's nine circles of Hell - limbo, lust, gluttony, greed, anger, heresy, violence, fraud and treachery. Players assume the role of Dante, who descends into Hell after returning home to find his beloved Beatrice murdered, with Lucifer seducing her soul into the underworld. His mission is to save Beatrice, but he soon realizes he is also in Hell to face his own demons and ultimately to redeem himself.<br><br>To take down the demons of Hell, Dante is outfitted with two primary weapons: the Scythe he takes from Death and the Holy Cross given to him by Beatrice, which has spiritual powers that will help Dante collect souls and spells from the creatures he defeats on his journey. The game also features a deep upgrade system so gamers can customize their abilities to their specific gameplay style. Each circle showcases its own distinct look, with demons, monsters, damned and geography that are crafted straight from the poem's vivid descriptions.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Florentine Dante Costume",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Dress Dante as the famous Italian poet of the Middle Ages, Dante Alighieri. Part one of his poem The Divine Comedy serves as the backdrop for EA's action-adventure epic Dante's Inferno."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Animated Film Dante Costume",
				"releaseDate":"2010/02/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Dress Dante as one of the heroes from Starz Media's animated feature film based on Dante's Inferno video game."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Dark Forest",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/04",
				"achievements":40,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Includes a prologue level before the opening of Dante's Inferno where Dante meets Virgil. Also includes additional costume \"Disco Inferno\" and two new enemies \"Forest Siren\" and \"Death Knight\""
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Relics Triple Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/18",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This pack contains three relics: 'Paolo's Heart' for turning souls into mana, 'Wing of Furie' to increase the hit counter on your scythe, and 'Brain of Ruggieri' to allow you to dodge-roll from any special combo."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Godlike Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/01",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This pack includes the 'Heavens Embrace' holy magic ability as well as the 'Serpent of Thieves' relic that unlocks a special scythe move."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Devil Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/15",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This pack includes the 'Putrid Voice' magic ability as well as the 'Panderer's Lash' relic that augments this unholy power."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Trials of St. Lucia",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/29",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Play solo or online co-op with St. Lucia (a new playable character!) or Dante to defeat combat Trials for medals and leaderboard scores. Create NEW custom battles that you can share online with the Editor!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9rbeAGdYk_0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WdBE8UIz1BA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SdqY2a9iRXw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P4MBKoFgWbs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/955367-dantes-inferno/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dantes-Inferno/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dantes-inferno/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dantes-inferno"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Infernopedia",
				"url":"http://dantesinferno.wikia.com/wiki/Dante%27s_Inferno_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":517,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rebellion"],
			"synopsis":"Developed at Rebellion by the team responsible for the original 1999 PC classic, the all-new Aliens vs. Predator allows players to take the role of three infamous species: Colonial Marines, Predators and Aliens. The game features a unique three-way online multiplayer experience, allowing gamers to battle for survival and the right to be crowned the deadliest species in the galaxy. Each race will also have its own distinct action-packed single-player campaign mode, with a storyline that cleverly interweaves with the other two species' paths.<br><br>Set on planet BG-386; a human colonist mining group discovers an ancient pyramid containing a dark and horrible secret. Across the galaxy, a race of warriors is alerted to the discovery of their pyramid and a hunting party is dispatched to ensure that it remains sealed at all costs. Deep inside the ruined pyramid meanwhile, nature's deadliest species awakes from centuries of hibernation intent on finding new prey.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Swarm Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/03/19",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Swarm Map Pack consists of four new multiplayer maps."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Bughunt Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/09",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Bughunt Map Pack consists of four new maps: Crashsite, Furious, Tempest, Monument."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ej2ve-1MZew"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vHppPp0Nj_U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Alien Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VoQJImOEBLg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Predator Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BTUkuF87XoM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Marine Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nkgk4P3WG_Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Alien Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DAQ0Fyu_X6Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Predator Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ovtNccLzexk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Marine Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j41nCTuZpdo"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958076-aliens-vs-predator/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Aliens-vs-Predator/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/aliens-v-predator/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/aliens-vs-predator"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Xenopedia",
				"url":"http://avp.wikia.com/wiki/Aliens_vs._Predator_(2010_video_game)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":518,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Omega Force"],
			"synopsis":"Dynasty Warriors: Strikeforce is a game unlike any other in the franchise. Until now, the quintessential Dynasty Warriors experience pitted a lone warrior against thousands of enemies. For the first time in a Dynasty Warriors game, up to four friends can join together to form a \"Strikeforce\". Working as a team, players can plan coordinated assaults to conquer massive armed fortresses and colossal beasts.<br><br>While immense castles, towers and ships serve as the settings for these legendary quests, the lighting-fast action will go where it has never gone before- the skies above. Gifted with new supernatural abilities characters can streak across the skies and battle enemies at high-altitude. With both single-player and multi-player quests, new \"air\" fighting techniques, radical character customization, new challenges to conquer, and downloadable content, Dynasty Warriors: Strikeforce will forever change the way gamers experience the Dynasty Warriors universe.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0uSp-gR_B64"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HtUpGDVhU5g"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/974379-dynasty-warriors-strikeforce/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dynasty-Warriors-Strikeforce/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dynasty-warriors-strikeforce/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dynasty-warriors-strikeforce"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Koei Wiki",
				"url":"http://koei.wikia.com/wiki/Dynasty_Warriors:_Strikeforce"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":519,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Haemimont Games AD"],
			"synopsis":"Tropico 3 goes back to the roots of the hit strategy series closely following the original Tropico story-line. The time is yesterday and the Cold War is in full swing. Through means devious and dubious you have seized power in the Caribbean island country of Tropico, where you now rule as the all-powerful \"El Presidente\". You decide whether you want to use your army to secure your power base in the best traditions of corrupt, unscrupulous tyrants everywhere or lead your people to prosperity in your role as generous elder statesman.<br><br>No matter whether you turn Tropico into a vacation paradise, a police state or a modern industrial nation - you will always have to defend your actions before your people! Wander through Tropico as El Presidente in order to intimidate political opponents, hold populist speeches or just to enjoy your country's own Caribbean flair. Don't forget to keep a sharp eye on the dangers and side-effects of your absolute power! Danger lurks on every corner, be it militant revolutionaries bent on installing a communist junta, or the machinations of the superpowers USA and the Soviet Union, both of whom would like to see a more amenable ruler in strategically important Tropico!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bUYOOJtvfXg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=voEkMtqKCLk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/961100-tropico-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tropico-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tropico-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tropico-3"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Tropico Wiki",
				"url":"http://tropico.wikia.com/wiki/Tropico_3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":520,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Access Games"],
			"synopsis":"A horror title by Marvelous Entertainment, this game begins when the body of a young girl named Anna Graham is found one particularly rainy morning in the woods outside the town of Rainy Woods. This sends the town into panic. Has the legendary Raincoat Killer returned? To investigate, the FBI has sent agent David Young Henning to the town to investigate. He's not alone, though, as three peacekeepers from the town support David as he attempts to solve the case. David can also turn to Jeter for advice. Only problem is, Jeter is a person who exists only in David's mind...<br><br>Taking control of David (and his split-personality character Jeter), you find yourself placed in a recreation of a classic American west town, right down to stoplights and paved roads. The game takes place in a eight kilometer squared sandbox world that features weather and time-based changes. You're free to move through the town as you see fit. In addition to walking, you also have access to a car. As you investigate the case, you'll learn that there's something not exactly human behind it all. David is thankfully skilled with the weapons. You'll end up using guns and swords as you face off against creatures who stalk the night.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iGTEkSLH7J4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_wpSP3Jlos"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0mbpuO7YxwM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lVFpvMgH2a4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KESRUWoscxI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943397-deadly-premonition/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Deadly-Premonition/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/deadly-premonition/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/deadly-premonition"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Deadly Premonition Wiki",
				"url":"http://deadlypremonition.wikia.com/wiki/Deadly_Premonition_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":521,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Piranha Bytes", "Pluto 13"],
			"synopsis":"This epic role playing game is set in a medieval world on a volcanic Mediterranean island, The \"Risen\" story unfolds over four chapters and will offer multiple ways to develop the story by his own actions and decisions. An innovative and intuitive user control interface will support both casual and hardcore gamers. With full world streaming support, the player will have a seamless experience while playing in a fully simulated game world with authentic characters.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9IFsIXGi9i4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AW91HxzE4FE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XUG9c9o8MN8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/959034-risen/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Risen/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/risen/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/risen"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Risen Wiki",
				"url":"http://risen.wikia.com/wiki/Risen"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":522,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Sumo Digital"],
			"synopsis":"Get ready for the ultimate racing showdown with Sonic and his SEGA friends! Sonic & SEGA All-Stars Racing is a fast and furious battle to the finish line. In a frantic battle to the checkered flag, Sonic & SEGA All-Stars Racing sees Sonic and friends speed around tracks set in medieval castle ramparts, lush rain forests and bustling cities, all taken from the visually rich and varied universes of Sonic and SEGA. Fan favorites such as Dr. Eggman, Tails, AiAi, Amigo and many more will join Sonic in their custom built vehicles, revving their engines and jostling to stay ahead of the pack. Each character will race around the track in cars, planes, motorbikes, and in AiAi's case - a banana mobile! Secret short cuts, swift handling and avoiding strategically placed obstacles are certainly the best way to get to the top of the podium.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Ryo Hazuki - Forklift Truck",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/01",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Rev your engine, jostle to stay ahead of the pack and drive as Ryo Hazuki from Shenmue in his signature forklift truck."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Metal Sonic & Death Egg Zone",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/08",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Get your telescopic limbs, jet engine and Black Shield forcefield ready and race as new character Metal Sonic with this exclusive download! Also speed around new track the Death Egg, a huge orbital fortress created by Dr. Eggman, containing some of his most diabolical creations. Take care not to fall off the edge in the frantic battle for cosmic first place!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=umWR5kCvWPc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XLTUX6Pjg48"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960424-sonic-and-sega-all-stars-racing-with-banjo-kazooie/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sonic-and-Sega-All-Stars-Racing/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sonic-and-sega-all-stars-racing/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sonic-sega-all-stars-racing-with-banjo-kazooie"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sonic News Network",
				"url":"http://sonic.wikia.com/wiki/Sonic_%26_Sega_All-Stars_Racing"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":523,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["DICE"],
			"synopsis":"In Battlefield: Bad Company 2, the Bad Company crew again find themselves in the heart of the action, where they must use every weapon and vehicle at their disposal to survive. The action unfolds with unprecedented intensity, introducing a level of fervor to vehicular warfare never before experienced in a modern warfare action game.<br><br>The 'B' company fight their way through snowy mountaintops, dense jungles and dusty villages. With a heavy arsenal of deadly weapons and a slew of vehicles to aid them, the crew set off on their mission and they are ready to blow up, shoot down, blast through, wipe out and utterly destroy anything that gets in their way. Total destruction is the name of the game - either online or offline, enemies will soon learn there is nowhere to hide.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Onslaught Mode",
				"releaseDate":"2010/05/18",
				"achievements":120,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Expanding the Battlefield: Bad Company 2 online multiplayer experience, Onslaught Mode delivers the first online co-op Battlefield action to Xbox 360! Up to 4 players can team up and put their squad skills to the test across 4 enhanced multiplayer maps, fighting against enemy land, sea, and air forces such as the new Mark V SPECACT boat. Work together to secure and hold a series of capture points in the quickest time possible and compare your stats on the Onslaught Leaderboards against your friends and other players across the community. With 4 different levels of difficulty, including Hardcore, Onslaught is the ideal battle ground for Battlefield: Bad Company 2 players, whether new or seasoned veterans, to perfect their squad play skills!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"SPECACT Assault Upgrade",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/09",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This unique uniform and a camouflaged M16A2 gives players a different visual look on the battlefield in multiplayer matches. The pack also includes 3 new awards and one Achievement."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"SPECACT Engineer Upgrade",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/09",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This unique uniform and a camouflaged UMP-45 gives players a different visual look on the battlefield in multiplayer matches. The pack also includes 3 new awards and one Achievement."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"SPECACT Medic Upgrade",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/09",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This unique uniform and a camouflaged MG3 gives players a different visual look on the battlefield in multiplayer matches. The pack also includes 3 new awards and one Achievement."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"SPECACT Recon Upgrade",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/09",
				"achievements":15,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This unique uniform and a camouflaged M95 gives players a different visual look on the battlefield in multiplayer matches. The pack also includes 3 new awards and one Achievement."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Vietnam",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/22",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Get ready for a whole new war, as DICE's massively popular online shooter Battlefield: Bad Company 2 makes the journey back to the 60's and the infamous Vietnam war. At the heart of this expansion lie four distinct, brand-new multiplayer maps based on the Vietnam War. Each map brings a new gameplay experience and fresh visuals, with characteristics such as foxholes, tunnels and dense jungles from where the enemy can launch surprise attacks. 15 weapons and 6 vehicles from the Vietnam War era are available from the moment you go online."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DLYdoodBh5w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KnQc9PjpZsk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Single-Player Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gApu9Xa3dgw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2WOO97Lc6pI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UMwkAUMRdDQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Single-Player Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wV0egoKW00o"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/957916-battlefield-bad-company-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Battlefield-Bad-Company-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/battlefield-bad-company-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/battlefield-bad-company-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Battlefield Wiki",
				"url":"http://battlefield.wikia.com/wiki/Battlefield:_Bad_Company_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":524,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Visual Concepts"],
			"synopsis":"Celebrating the milestone 10th anniversary of 2K Sports Major League Baseball, this 2K10 edition of the game features Evan Longoria of the Tampa Bay Rays, a 2009 American League Gold Glove and Silver Slugger Award recipient, as the cover athlete. Based on each pitcher's mechanics and official scouting reports, Total Control Pitching lets you put the ball exactly where you want it - provided you keep a close eye on your pitch count. And with Total Control Hitting you can time your swing to hit for power, put the ball in play or take a defensive cut. Batter's Eye uses a hitter's real-life eye rating to help you identify Fastballs, Breaking Balls and Off Speed pitches before they get to the plate.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XCZHhW3rjts"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LWcAk3e-p_s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0n52xIJafNc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MLB-2K10/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/major-league-baseball-2k10/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/major-league-baseball-2k10"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":525,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Namco"],
			"synopsis":"At a time when football fever rise, Bandai Namco delivers to everyone with confidence it's ultimate \"Japan representative Soccer game\". Playing this, taste the same feeling with the Japanese representative, let's cheer Japan representative!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nK2tLC8Mw-k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Love-Football/achievements.htm"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":526,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Square Enix"],
			"synopsis":"In Final Fantasy XIII, players will embark on a journey through the cityworld of Cocoon and the outerworld of Pulse, encountering and fighting alongside a diverse group of allies. Execute powerful attacks with weapons and magic, and summon the enigmatic Eidolons with an evolved Active Time Battle system. Experience seamless transitions between real-time gameplay and in-game cinematics. Do you have the courage to face your destiny?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Debut Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B7uwtFpC4iI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eJPbozRomX4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hDjkGUM7skk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d5dGi0a0_Z4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J9cQZ9A1VkI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dGPtevO43yQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/950899-final-fantasy-xiii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Final-Fantasy-XIII/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/final-fantasy-xiii/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/final-fantasy-xiii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Final Fantasy Wiki",
				"url":"http://finalfantasy.wikia.com/wiki/Final_Fantasy_XIII"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":527,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tri-Ace"],
			"synopsis":"Resonance of Fate (End of Eternity in Japan) redefines the RPG genre with a unique storyline, highly stylized graphics, and an emphasis on realistic gunplay and engrossing action. Players will be immersed in a gritty, highly mechanized world unlike any other. With Hollywood-style action sequences, customizable weapons, and memorable characters, Resonance of Fate takes players far beyond the boundaries of the typical RPG.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d326pL1MM-s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zWqhRgMhoPg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JJD9sxnR-No"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/959318-resonance-of-fate/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Resonance-of-Fate/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/resonance-of-fate/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/resonance-of-fate"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":528,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["4A Games"],
			"synopsis":"An action-oriented combination of horror, survival, RPG, and shooting, all based on a story by Russian author Dmitriy Glukhovskiy.<br><br>The whole world lies in ruins. Humanity is almost annihilated. Due to the high-level of radiation cities became unsuitable for living. Humans have yielded the supremacy on Earth to a new species. Creatures mutated by radiation are more adapted to the changed world. There are only clusters of humans left on the planet ... At least, that's what the ten thousand survivors camped out in the various sections of the Moscow metro must believe, since they have no evidence that they are not the last ones alive. And now, even this way of life is being threatened by the evolved evil from outside. As Artem, you set out from the first invaded colony, fighting through a society of divided by desperate politics, ideologies and economies to warn the rest and reach the Polis stronghold before everything is destroyed.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Ranger Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/03",
				"achievements":240,
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Return to the Moscow Metro and face the ultimate survival challenge with the Ranger Pack. This downloadable content adds new weapons, new achievements and the deadly 'Ranger Mode' game rules. In standard Ranger Mode, ammo is dramatically reduced and all weapons cause more damage. Your foes are deadlier than ever - but so are you! 'Ranger Hardcore' adds an additional challenge as the HUD is totally removed, creating the most immersive Metro 2033 experience yet. Rise to the challenge with two new weapons - the Heavy Automatic Shotgun, and the Volt Driver, Miller's signature gun."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xc2hhef-Nzo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P6pAvMqQm3k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hDb13umf_SE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/935091-metro-2033/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Metro-2033/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/metro-2033/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/metro-2033"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Metro Wiki",
				"url":"http://metrovideogame.wikia.com/wiki/Metro_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":529,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Monumental Games"],
			"synopsis":"As the most comprehensive MotoGP game to date, MotoGP 09/10 will not only deliver all the bikes, riders and tracks from the 2009 championship, but brand new gameplay modes that offer rewards to the rider for their riding style. Furthermore, players will have the ability to update the game with accurate real-time content from the 2010 championship at no extra cost. MotoGP 09/10 will see the introduction of a fully realized Career Mode where players take part in the ultimate MotoGP world championship, competing in actual races and managing all aspects of their team. Gamers will hire engineers, team managers and press officers, all of which have a real impact on their career as a racing pro.<br><br>Complementing Career Mode, MotoGP09/10 features three additional gameplay modes to deliver the richest MotoGP experience ever. Arcade Mode is not limited to simply crossing the finish line, but adds a variety of challenges where players can earn and steal points from their opponents, encouraging a risk element for those who feel that simply leading the pack isn't enough.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=62H1G8bysBc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U1aDccYPR_4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MotoGP-09-10/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/motogp-09-10/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/motogp-0910"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":530,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Gas Powered Games"],
			"synopsis":"Experience brutal battles on a massive scale! In Supreme Commander 2, players will wage war by creating enormous customizable armies and experimental war machines that can change the balance of power at any given moment. Take the role of one of the three enigmatic commanders, each representing a unique faction with a rich story that brings a new level of emotional connection to the RTS genre, or fight the battle online. Where do your loyalties lie?",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Infinite War Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/28",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Epic Map Pack includes new multiplayer and skirmish maps: Tourneydome - When commanders enter, only one leaves, a four player map. Way Station Zeta, a ramp and platform-heavy map for four players; Rigs, a naval map with small land areas for four players; Etched Desert, a four-player desert map with plenty of area to explore and hide; Desolatia, a snow-covered two-player island map; Seraphim Isles, a four-player naval and land map with multiple islands; Igneous, a rocky naval and land map for four; and QAI Labs, a four-player land and air map."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YQMEOBM9fBQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s4V1JkP3C7Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FrfPvyPfm38"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960638-supreme-commander-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Supreme-Commander-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/supreme-commander-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/supreme-commander-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Supreme commander Wiki",
				"url":"http://supcom2.wikia.com/wiki/Supreme_Commander_2_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":531,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Activision"],
			"synopsis":"How to Train Your Dragon is a third-person action-adventure where the gamer plays as a Viking hero that must embark upon an epic quest to become the ultimate dragon trainer.<br><br>In this larger-than-life adventure, players will train dragons, explore environments and battle in prestigious dragon tournaments as they battle for Viking victory. Plus, gamers can become the Dragon hero of their living room as they square-off with friends and family in endless head-to-head multi-player combat.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8Jg7W1pvzAY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/How-to-Train-Your-Dragon/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/how-to-train-your-dragon/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/how-to-train-your-dragon"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"How to Train Your Dragon Wiki",
				"url":"http://howtotrainyourdragon.wikia.com/wiki/How_to_Train_Your_Dragon_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":532,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Avalanche Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Rico returns to action in the sequel to Avalanche Studios' gargantuan action game. Just Cause 2 stars Rico Rodriquez, back to wreak havoc once again, this time with a new destination - the huge playground of the South East Asian islands of Panau. The sequel features more stunts, vehicles and weapons than ever before and an incredible overhauled grappling hook system. Panau itself is an incredibly detailed and vast 1000 sq km game world of different climates and ultra-realistic weather effects. Leap from your plane and skydive from 10,000 feet down into a tropical jungle, tear across an arid desert in a dune buggy or climb your way up a snowy mountain in a 4x4. The vast open-ended, unique gameplay is back, allowing you full freedom once again to free roam and explore the massive world of Panau and tackle your assignments however you want.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Chevalier Ice Breaker",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Bring on the chaos in Panau with a pimped-up Ice Cream Van. Featuring a sturdy front ram, side skirts and greater top speed, you have the perfect tool for causing some serious fender-benders. This extreme makeover also includes a jingle to match."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Monster Truck",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/15",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The usefulness of an oversized monster truck when destabilizing small countries is clearly evident."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Black Market Aerial Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/29",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"With the Black Market Aerial Pack you get these cool items: - F-33 DragonFly Jet Fighter: With quad-mounted miniguns and double missile launchers, this agile bird is the definite ruler of the skies, and packs a serious punch to land based targets as well. - Dual Parachute Thrusters: Take to the air for longer! The Dual Parachute Thrusters when mounted to the parachute rig provides bursts of forward momentum to extend airtime. - Multi-lock Missile Launcher: This highly sophisticated weapon of destruction allows you to lock up to four targets and unleash a barrage of homing missiles to take care of all your troubles."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Black Market 'Boom' Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/05/25",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"With the Black Market 'Boom' Pack you get these cool items: - Quad Rocket Launcher: Combine a rocket launcher with a shotgun and you've got yourself the powerful Quad Rocket Launcher - expect some collateral damage! - Cluster Bomb Launcher: A natural progression of the grenade launcher, the Cluster Bomb Launcher is a small-scale weapon of mass destruction for personal use. - Air Propulsion Gun: Courtesy of the Agency Propulsion Labs, this gun was originally designed as a jet engine but was soon repurposed for the weapons division where the Air Propulsion Gun was born."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Tuk Tuk Boom Boom",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/22",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Try out a true weapon of mass destruction in the new and improved Tuk Tuk. No longer the runt of the litter, this particular Tuk Tuk features a ridiculously oversized mounted weapon on the roof. Just the thing you need to wreak havoc in paradise!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Chevalier Classic",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/22",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"No agent should be without a hot set of wheels and with an increased top speed and superior handling, you can arrive at your destination in style or make a guaranteed quick getaway. "
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Rico's Signature Gun",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/22",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Customised by the Agency and adapted for Rico's shooting style, this deadly accurate and powerful pistol packs a punch with precision, power and flair"
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Bull's Eye Assault Rifle",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/22",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"More powerful than the standard assault rifle, this lightweight and lethal automatic rifle features increased accuracy in close combat and a higher magnification scope."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Agency Hovercraft",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/24",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The ultimate in amphibious transport, the Agency Hovercraft is the most flexible form of transport in the game. Steered by a thrust-based engine for smooth and agile movement, the vehicle is as comfortable on land as off. Equipped with a turret-mounted grenade launcher, you're guaranteed to blow your opposition out of the water."
			},
			{
				"id":10,
				"name":"Chaos Parachute",
				"releaseDate":"2010/16/11",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Featuring a skull motif, make an entrance no one will forget... should you leave anyone alive to remember."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5kjs-SC70Wg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oTXqYg_S4Ps"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J3WzQLY9j_Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k_C6TjwxbGI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/943500-just-cause-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Just-Cause-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/just-cause-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/just-cause-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Just Cause Wiki",
				"url":"http://justcause.wikia.com/wiki/Just_Cause_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":533,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["ZootFly"],
			"synopsis":"Prison Break: The Conspiracy is a tense action title based on the hit television show. The protagonist of the \"Prison Break\" game is Company agent Tom Paxton. He is sent to the Fox River State Penitentiary to find out why Michael Scofield (the hero of the TV series), a man without a previous criminal record, became a bank robber. The storyline runs parallel to the first season of \"Prison Break\": Paxton encounters several characters from the series and experiences key events from his own perspective. With a gripping storyline paralleling Season 1 of the critically-acclaimed FOX TV series, Prison Break: the Conspiracy will take you inside the Prison Break world like never before.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0nhZOvOn404"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uqdZa97CE6A"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/952385-prison-break-the-conspiracy/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Prison-Break/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/prison-break-the-conspiracy/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/prison-break-the-conspiracy"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Prison Break Wiki",
				"url":"http://prisonbreak.wikia.com/wiki/Prison_Break_-_The_Conspiracy_(Game)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":534,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SNK Playmore"],
			"synopsis":"Samurai Shodown Sen follows a young European girl named Suzu, rescued from a sinking ship off Japan's coast, adopted by the Amori Clan and raised as Princess Suzu. A decade later she saves Takechiyo, a self-proclaimed master of martial arts, after his ship sinks and he ends up washed on the beach; soon after this chance meeting, the tables turn when Princess Suzu mysteriously disappears and Takechiyo pledges to find his missing rescuer.<br><br>Staying close to its roots, alongside Princess Suzu, Takechiyo and a host of new characters, a plethora of old favorites from the series have been faithfully incorporated, including Haohmaru, Galford, Hanzo Hattori, Nakoruru and Ukyo Tachibana- taking the warriors to over 20 in total. Players can become any one of these unique fighters via the Xbox LIVE online entertainment network, to battle friends to see who can reach the top of a worldwide online ranking system.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-CCJ6GzFI_0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lBj5xiizQfM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l0RcsahawRI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960636-samurai-shodown-sen/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Samurai-Shodown-Sen/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/samurai-shodown-sen/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/samurai-shodown-sen"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"SNK Wiki",
				"url":"http://snk.wikia.com/wiki/Samurai_Shodown_Sen"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":535,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"The adventures of Sam Fisher continue in the fifth entry of the stealth-based series. In this game, all of the rules have changed, as the storyline takes a dramatic turn that will reinvent the Splinter Cell franchise forever. Fisher can no longer rely on his trusted bag of tools and iconic goggles.An investigation into his daughter's death unwittingly leads former agent Sam Fisher to discover he's been betrayed by his prior agency, the Third Echelon. Now a renegade, Fisher finds himself in a race against time to thwart a deadly terrorist plot that threatens millions.<br><br>Uniting revolutionary gameplay enhancements with a high-octane, no-holds-barred storyline, Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell Conviction arms you to the teeth with all the high-tech weaponry and lethal skills of an elite operative and invites you to enter a dangerous world where justice means making your own rules.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Deniable Ops: Insurgency",
				"releaseDate":"2010/05/27",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The critically acclaimed multiplayer mode is back and takes aim at Xbox LIVE with 4 new Deniable Ops maps."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TszuTgFx93U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i6E2D11n-qQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Single-Player Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fBsRx-RYPTk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Co-Op Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=otYuucnFVAg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/939336-tom-clancys-splinter-cell-conviction/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tom-Clancys-Splinter-Cell-Conviction/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tom-clancys-splinter-cell-conviction/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tom-clancys-splinter-cell-conviction"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Splinter Cell Wiki",
				"url":"http://splintercell.wikia.com/wiki/Tom_Clancy's_Splinter_Cell:_Conviction"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":536,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"2010 FIFA World Cup South Africa will feature all the emotion and passion of the fiercest national rivalries battling on the world's biggest stage, with all 199 national teams that took part in qualification, all 10 official stadiums to be used in South Africa and stadiums from each qualifying region. Gamers will be able to play as their home nation from qualification right through to a virtual reproduction of the FIFA World Cup Final and feel what it is like to score the goal that lifts a nation. Everything fans love about the World Cup will come to life in spectacular detail, including confetti rain, streamers, & fireworks-just like the official tournament.<br><br>For the first time ever in a videogame compete in a full and authentic online World Cup tournament. Carry the hopes and dreams of a nation into battle against fans from rival countries, from the group stage through the knockout rounds to the chance to be crowned 2010 FIFA World Cup South Africa champion. For fans of nations that failed to qualify for South Africa this is the chance to replay and re-write history. Plus, gameplay innovations capture the journey from qualification to the final tournament with home and away strategies for every nation, situational tactics in-game, and altitude effects that fatigue players faster and even impact the flight of the ball.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bjy71sJJrBY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gpTC2Mu0Sss"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/2010-FIFA-World-Cup/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/2010-fifa-world-cup/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/2010-fifa-world-cup-south-africa"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":537,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Volatile Games"],
			"synopsis":"Returning to Grant City, a boom town gone bust that is falling to the worst excesses of crime, greed and corruption; Dead to Rights: Retribution follows vice cop Jack Slate as he fights to expose shadowy figures that will stop at nothing to exert their deadly influence over the crumbling metropolis. Dead to Rights: Retribution will form an original story portraying key events that shape and define Jack Slate's character including how he and Shadow first come together as partners against those who would bring the once great city to its knees.<br><br>Introducing an innovative hybrid combat system, Dead to Rights: Retribution puts the full combat potential of a highly trained, highly agitated law-enforcement officer into players' hands. Use your sidearm to pick off enemies from a distance, take cover and blind-fire with the game's new ranged combat mechanics, or push the issue by taking human shields, stealing weapons with special disarm moves or dishing out Jack's own brutal brand of justice with deadly takedown moves. Jack is equally lethal in close-quarters combat, offering players branching melee combos, counterattacks and disarms as they take the fight to the criminal element of Grant City. Jack will encounter a variety of ruthless gangs in the filthy slums and menacing alleys of Grant City, each with their own unique abilities and fighting style that will test his resolve to crush their murderous stranglehold.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"GAC Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/02",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"\"GAC Pack\" features four new modes of play, including the all new Assault on the 87th Precinct and Riot Control Mode. In Assault on the 87the Precinct, take control of 3 different type of GAC soldiers in their efforts to liberate Grant City's 87th Precinct. In Riot Control Mode, fend off waives of GAC assault forces as Jack and Shadow while playing for style and speed to achieve a maximum score. Also in the GAC Pack, new skins for Jack and Shadow, Action Mode which turns rounds into explosive rounds, Noir Mode allowing for replay of the game with authentic Noir Visuals, Achievements and Leaderboard support."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pZXx4X6NFrw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T-NpNiopACs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z8o2GYmvIek"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9wK94G_9ChE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958250-dead-to-rights-retribution/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dead-to-Rights-Retribution/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dead-to-rights-retribution/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dead-to-rights-retribution"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":538,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["SEGA Studio USA"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the sequel to the blockbuster movie, Iron Man 2 features a refined game engine to give players an entirely new and enhanced gameplay experience. The game allows players to truly feel the power of Iron Man with new destructible environments, epic enemies, and innovative hand-to-hand combat moves. This brand-new tale takes gamers deeper into the world of Iron Man, adding to the excitement of the Marvel Studios film.<br><br>Iron Man 2 offers fans a chance to play against epic enemies not found in the film of the same name, such as the unforgettable Crimson Dynamo. In the game's original story, Tony Stark has gifted the world with new technology in order to make it a better place. His philanthropic nature isn't enough to keep evil at bay, however, as Iron Man's enemies have crafted their own devious designs based on the technology. Ultimately, Iron Man will face epic battles against huge enemies, as the fate of the world is left in his powerful hands.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B2sNGmd68zY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yRdkF6Ms3bY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/957906-iron-man-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Iron-Man-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/iron-man-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/iron-man-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Iron Man Wiki",
				"url":"http://ironman.wikia.com/wiki/Iron_Man_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":539,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cavia"],
			"synopsis":"Nothing is as it seems in this action adventure game, set in a crumbling world plagued by disease and dark, unrecognizable creatures. Players assume the role of the unyielding protagonist, Nier, resolute in his quest to discover a cure for his daughter, who is infected with the Black Scrawl virus. With powerful allies and a mysterious book, Nier encounters things that will confound even the mightiest of warriors.<br><br>Created by Cavia and Square Enix, Nier blends both innovative and traditional RPG gameplay mechanics with an intense, bloody combat system to create an action-packed single-player experience where players explore and discover a future lost to a shadowy past. Armed with a powerful set of magical abilities as well as mighty swords and armor, players will do battle alongside a set of formidable allies against waves of dark enemies and giant bosses to discover the truth about the disease, his daughter... and himself.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The World of Recycled Vessel",
				"releaseDate":"2010/05/11",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The diary of Nier's wife opens a gate to a strange world where an unnamed warrior battles powerful Shades. Engage in 15 nightmarish battles to unlock bonus costumes, weapons, and a special quest."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y2nPvrOZVGc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CsWZ27odqRQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kUY7Sw_8Uyw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x6OXbqTbtHs"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960450-nier/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Nier/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nier/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nier"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Nier Wiki",
				"url":"http://nier.wikia.com/wiki/NIER_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":540,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Capcom"],
			"synopsis":"An expansion on the blockbuster fourth official iteration of the fighting game series, Super Street Fighter IV features the full roster of 25 characters from Street Fighter IV such as Ryu, Ken, Crimson Viper, Abel, El Fuerte, and Rufus, while adding several characters new to the world of Street Fighter IV. Added to the roster are classic combatants from previous Street Fighter games like T. Hawk as well as all-new characters such as the mysterious and deadly female fighter, Juri.<br><br>Super Street Fighter IV also adds new Ultra Combos and advancements to the online matchmaking and online gameplay services with numerous additional features. Once again, characters and environments are rendered in stylized 3D, while the game is played in the classic Street Fighter 2D perspective with additional 3D camera flourishes for that next-gen fighting experience. Super Street Fighter IV takes many of the groundbreaking features introduced in Street Fighter IV and refines everything to deliver the ultimate vision of Street Fighter to fans the world over.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Super Complete Alternate Costume Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/27",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Pack of alternate costumes for Super Street Fighter IV! Outfit every character in the game with brand new threads! Only available for use with Super Street Fighter IV."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Ultra Complete Alternate Costume Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Ultra-powered pack of alternate costumes for Super Street Fighter IV! Every character's Ultra Alternate Costume is included in this pack! Show everyone who is the strongest fighter in the world! This downloadable content does not include any Super Alternate Costumes, and is only compatible with Super Street Fighter IV."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Arcade Edition",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/07",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Adding new characters, an all new balancing update as well as an enhanced Replay Channel, Super Street Fighter IV Arcade Edition delivers the definitive version of Street Fighter.<br><br>Super Street Fighter IV Arcade Edition features a roster of 39 characters such as Ryu, Chun-li, Juri, El Fuerte, and Rufus, while adding 4 new characters to the roster including classic combatants from previous Street Fighter games like Yun and Yang as well as the all-new Oni."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Ultra Street Fighter IV",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/07",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The Street Fighter IV tournament evolves to a whole new level with Ultra Street Fighter IV! Continuing the tradition of excellence the series is known for, five new characters (Decapre, Elena, Hugo, Poison, and Rolento) and six new stages have been added for even more fighting mayhem, with rebalanced gameplay and original modes topping off this ultimate offering."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R8SD_M_ccac"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TCxQQiYjfcA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Arcade Edition Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E_RUWj4vUG0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Ultra Street Fighter IV Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d__QncYv3VU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XrpxpTiJltM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Arcade Edition Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-15Kn4u9iMY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Ultra Street Fighter IV Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YFBuFKXJI1k"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/975211-super-street-fighter-iv/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Super-Street-Fighter-4/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/super-street-fighter-iv/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/super-street-fighter-iv"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Street Fighter Wiki",
				"url":"http://streetfighter.wikia.com/wiki/Super_Street_Fighter_IV"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Shoryuken",
				"url":"http://wiki.shoryuken.com/Super_Street_Fighter_IV"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":541,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Capcom"],
			"synopsis":"Lost Planet: Colonies provides explosive action for both online and offline players. Gamers who missed the original Lost Planet will have the opportunity to experience the epic gameplay that made the original a global hit with the added bonus of fresh new content and cross platform multi-play.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZPDPP9odYqo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cUifM1GoR2o"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats (Original)",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/931114-lost-planet-extreme-condition/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lost-Planet-Colonies/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lost-planet-colonies/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lost-planet-extreme-condition-colonies-edition"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Lost Planet Wiki",
				"url":"http://lostplanet.wikia.com/wiki/Lost_Planet:_Extreme_Condition_Colonies_Edition"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":542,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Montreal"],
			"synopsis":"Visiting his brother's kingdom following his adventure in Azad, the Prince finds the royal palace under siege from a mighty army bent on its destruction. When the decision is made to use the ancient power of the Sand in a desperate gamble to save the kingdom from total annihilation, the Prince will embark on an epic adventure in which he will learn to bear the mantle of true leadership, and discover that great power often comes with a great cost.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dJ8hccoZ6hQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T2WbkJqqXbc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tU9bQ-7U3Xw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jLcQzhlxkrE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/980490-prince-of-persia-the-forgotten-sands/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Prince-of-Persia-the-Forgotten-Sands/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/prince-of-persia-the-forgotten-sands/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/prince-of-persia-the-forgotten-sands"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Prince of Persia Wiki",
				"url":"http://princeofpersia.wikia.com/wiki/Prince_of_Persia:_The_Forgotten_Sands"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":543,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Black Box"],
			"synopsis":"In SKATE 3, teammates can complete challenges together while advancing each other's careers. From rewarding epic bails and fails with a beefed up Hall of Meat mode to honing your craft with the all-new skate school, players of all skill levels have multiple ways to kill it in the game. The game also includes Create feature suite, an innovative toolset that empowers gamers to truly express their skate style by creating their own graphics, videos, and skate parks.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Skate Share Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/05/14",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Skate Share enables the ability for you to share your own skate creations (videos, photos, parks) as well as access Skate.Reel footage and custom Skate.Parks created by the Skate community. Don't miss out on being a part of the most creative game community out there!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Maloof Money Cup 2010 NYC Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/12",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Compete in one of skateboarding's biggest annual contests. For the first time ever, the Maloof Money Cup travels east to New York where you'll skate the course and battle with some of skating's heaviest hitters in fierce competition for the ultimate purse."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Black Box Distribution Skate Park",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/22",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Hone your skills and rip like the pros of Zero, Mystery, and Fallen by skating their private training facility, a park with a little something for every skater."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Danny's Hawaiian Dream",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/06",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Danny Way has been living the dream for years, now you can skate his Hawaiian dream...an enormous skater's paradise loaded with everything from original street terrain to flowing skateparks and Danny's signature Mega-madness. Drop in for a Hawaiian blast."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Skate.Create Upgrade Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/17",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"If you're looking to change up your look and spice up your skate.parks, then the Skate.Create Upgrade Pack has got you covered. With new gear to wear, objects to shred and new lots to build on, this pack takes creativity to a whole new level of fun. "
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"San Van Party Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/21",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The party is on! Revisit some old San Van favorites along with a massive new park and get your creative Zen flowing with a new Skate.Park lot. Party Play is back so get ready for some head to head skating in Spot Battle, 1-UP, SKATE and HOM!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=esyRn-gTB3o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wCaWYweXpyA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x0sIm45e_30"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Skate-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/skate-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/skate-3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":544,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Remedy"],
			"synopsis":"Fill the shoes of one Alan Wake, a man who makes his living from the terror of others as a best-selling suspense novelist. Trapped in the deceptively peaceful Washington town of Bright Falls, where he came to escape the trauma of losing his fianc&eacute;e, Alan must piece together a mystery to prevent himself from being trapped inside a nightmarish world forever.<br><br>An intense psychological thriller from Remedy, the creators of Max Payne, Alan Wake looks to raise the bar for future games, creating a true cinematic experience. Explore an expansive world filled with missions, unique puzzles, intense combat, and horrifying enemies. Dig into a twisting and multi-layered story filled with suspense, engaging characters, and shocking revelations.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Signal",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/27",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"In this first downloadable content pack we find Wake facing a threat unlike anything he's ever encountered before -- and yet one he's intimately familiar with. In order to make sense of it all, he must follow the Signal."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"The Writer",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/12",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"The second downloadable content pack, \"The Writer\", finds Wake in strange circumstances; now fully aware of the thing that opposes him, he must survive one increasingly nightmarish situation after another."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F0MsWKJVQ84"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sSB4QcQMm6E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aMVrTiN9dgM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JalnwYBLlUo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Bright Falls (Prequel to the game)",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=boyGPvfA5B4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/928006-alan-wake/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Alan-Wake/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/alan-wake/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/alan-wake"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Alan Wake Wiki",
				"url":"http://alanwake.wikia.com/wiki/Alan_Wake_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":545,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Panic Button"],
			"synopsis":"Attack of the Movies 3D transports players to six fantastic movie-themed worlds where they will battle large alien space cruisers, shoot underwater monsters, join the resistance against the machines and more.<br><br>Packaged with four pairs of 3D glasses to support four-player multiplayer action, and featuring classic enemies culled from the annals of film history, this inspired 3D shooter jumps right out of your television and into your living room",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_LxEZ5H8wtA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hNjKqAkDbQs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/AttackOfTheMovies3D/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/attack-of-the-movies-3d/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/attack-of-the-movies-3d"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":546,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Capcom"],
			"synopsis":"A decade has passed since the events of Lost Planet, and the face of E.D.N. III has changed dramatically. Terraforming efforts have been successful and the ice has begun to melt, giving way to lush tropical jungles and harsh unforgiving deserts. Players will enter this new environment and follow the exploits of their own customized snow pirate on their quest to seize control of the changing planet.<br><br>Players control their heroes across 6 interconnected episodes, creating a truly unique interactive experience that changes depending upon the actions of the players involved. With this concept, players will have the opportunity to engage in the story in a much more dynamic way as plot threads evolve from different players' perspectives. Beyond the deep single player mode, Lost Planet 2 is loaded with extensive multiplayer modes. The intense and action packed campaign mode comes with the ability to form teams of up to 4 players online to clear mission objectives with friends.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Map Pack #1",
				"releaseDate":"2010/05/11",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Download two new battlegrounds in this Map Pack for Lost Planet 2. In \"Helix\", fight in a multilayered NEVEC ocean research facility at the bottom of the ocean. \"Back to the Island\" brings the new weapons and abilities of LP2 back to Island 902, a remake of the classic map from the original Lost Planet."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Map Pack #2",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/04",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Explore two extra battlefields in this Map Pack for Lost Planet 2. \"Dockyard Battle\" takes the fight to the overland battleship construction site seen in Episode 4 of the Campaign mode, while \"Frozen Wasteland\" is a remake that returns you to the frozen tundra of the original game's fan-favorite map."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Rush Arena",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/27",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Run the gauntlet against the biggest beasts of E.D.N. III in Rush Arena, a new mode for Lost Planet 2! Form a team of up to 4 players in this special mode that pits you against all the bosses that appear in the game - from the salamander-like Gordiant and the mysterious Akrid X, right up to the final boss. Compete with other players from around the world on the Leaderboards to post the best completion time in this classic Capcom mode!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=391jmN38GCU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EGwq1HVYoQc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XSTQ5O70neM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SQgfztbfSK8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8nYeuz-_F6I"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958322-lost-planet-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Lost-Planet-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lost-planet-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lost-planet-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Lost Planet Wiki",
				"url":"http://lostplanet.wikia.com/wiki/Lost_Planet_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":547,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Rockstar San Diego"],
			"synopsis":"Red Dead Redemption is a Western epic, set at the turn of the 20th century when the lawless and chaotic badlands began to give way to the expanding reach of government and the spread of the Industrial Age. A follow up to the 2004 hit Red Dead Revolver, this game tells the story of former outlaw John Marston, taking players on a great adventure across the American frontier.<br><br>Red Dead Redemption features an open-world environment for players to explore, including frontier towns, rolling prairies teaming with wildlife, and perilous mountain passes - each packed with an endless flow of varied distractions. Along the way, players will experience the heat of gunfights and battles, meet a host of unique characters, struggle against the harshness of one of the world's last remaining wildernesses, and ultimately pick their own precarious path through an epic story about the death of the Wild West and the gunslingers that inhabited it.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Outlaws To the End",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/22",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Outlaws To The End Co-Op Mission Pack lets up to four players join forces and take on the Dying West together. Missions include raiding gold mines, clearing the outlaw-infested town of Tumbleweed with cannons and Gatling guns, battling rebel insurgents across the river banks, and more in 6 new co-op missions. With new achievements and Challenges, this extensive co-op pack brings hours of gunslinging action to your Red Dead Redemption experience."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Legends and Killers",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/10",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The massive, action-packed world of Red Dead Redemption gets bloodier with the epic new multiplayer content of the Legends and Killers Pack. Battle it out in nine new map areas, unlock new challenges and achievements, and hone your combat skills with the deadly Tomahawk. Then play as classic characters from Red Dead Revolver -- Red Harlow, Annie Stoakes, Jack Swift, Buffalo Soldier, Shadow Wolf, Pig Josh, Ugly Chris, and Mr. Kelly."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Liars and Cheats",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/24",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The world of Red Dead Redemption multiplayer expands again with the new Liars and Cheats Pack. Challenge friends to horse races, try your luck with multiplayer Poker or Liar's Dice or hold your ground in the new Stronghold competitive mode. Reduce your enemies to dust with the Explosive Rifle. Play as legendary heroes and villains from the single-player story as you take on several new Gang Hideouts and Hunting Grounds in Free Roam."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Hunting and Trading Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/12",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Hunting and Trading Outfits Pack features two new outfits with challenges to unlock in Red Dead Redemption single player. Buy guns and ammo at half the cost with the Savvy Merchant Outfit. Collect double the amount of skins and hides from hunting with the Expert Hunter Outfit."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Undead Nightmare",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/26",
				"achievements":200,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Unleashed upon the world of Red Dead Redemption. The Undead Nightmare Pack features an entirely new single-player campaign that follows John Marston as he tries to find a cure for the highly-infectious undead plague spreading across the frontier. In addition to this epic single-player adventure, the Undead Nightmare Pack also features a brand new multiplayer mode in addition to new gameplay mechanics, weapons, undead animals and mythical creatures."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Deadly Assassin Outfit",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/12",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"John Marston's Deadly Assassin outfit causes your Dead Eye meter to regenerate at twice the speed. With more Dead Eye, you have more time to place each shot with total accuracy, making you the deadliest gunslinger in any fight."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Golden Guns Weapon Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/12",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Available for use in the Red Dead Redemption Single Player story, the player who wields the Golden Guns receives more Fame for each kill. The more Fame you get, the more in-game side missions become available. So there will be more opportunities to duel, more kidnapped townsfolk to rescue and you can bribe lawmen for less."
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"War Horse",
				"releaseDate":"2011/04/12",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"There are countless horses to be found in the massive world of Red Dead Redemption, but none is stronger, faster or tougher than the War Horse. Whether storming gang hideouts, exploring the wilderness for hidden treasure, or outrunning the law, the War Horse gives gunslingers an advantage in nearly every situation."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Myths and Mavericks",
				"releaseDate":"2011/09/13",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Myths and Mavericks Bonus Pack offers another expansion to the world of Red Dead Redemption multiplayer. Battle your enemies in 11 new map areas including the snowy mountains of Cochinay, the army stronghold of El Presidio and the mining camp in Gaptooth Breach. Play as additional multiplayer characters from the single-player story: Landon Ricketts, Drew MacFarlane, Uncle, Javier Escuella, Captain Vincente De Santa, Deputy Eli, Deputy Jonah and Nastas."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Debut Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aOpKJ6hjPIM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Launch Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3gBctl1h_2o"
			},
			{
				"type":"All Trailers Part 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kJG76lUbZm4"
			},
			{
				"type":"All Trailers Part 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4S_5NgmYBbY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Undead Nightmare Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Di2eOr-kqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DJJh9vrznU4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=arbLWiF1Bf0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Undead Nightmare Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aMDTwPv_W6c"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/957922-red-dead-redemption/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Red-Dead-Redemption/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/red-dead-redemption/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/red-dead-redemption"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Red Dead Wiki",
				"url":"http://reddead.wikia.com/wiki/Red_Dead_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":548,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["XPEC"],
			"synopsis":"Longing for the days when he felt like a real ogre, Shrek is duped into signing a pact with the smooth-talking dealmaker, Rumpelstiltskin. Shrek suddenly finds himself in a twisted, alternate version of Far Far Away, where ogres are hunted, Rumpelstiltskin is king, and Shrek and Fiona have never met. Now, it's up to Shrek to undo all he's done in the hopes of saving his friends, restoring his world, and reclaiming his one True Love.<br><br>There's tons of living room fun to be had in the Shrek Forever After video game, which turns Shrek into a social and team experience that the whole family can enjoy. Players can join in on the action at any time in the co-operative multiplayer mode to form a team of up to four players. Together, teams can navigate through Shrek's two realities while solving mind-bending puzzles, and fending off Rumplestiltskin's army of baddies. Shrek, Fiona, Puss In Boots, and Donkey, all have their own unique game skills that will come in handy to progress through the game. A single-player experience is also offered, which allows the player to switch between the four characters as needed at any time.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YXlhlUVyym8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fqnaat1N2LQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Shrek-Forever-After/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/shrek-forever-after/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dreamworks-shrek-forever-after"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":549,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Black Rock Studio"],
			"synopsis":"Split/Second, an intense action racing game set within the world of a hyper-competitive reality television show. Competitors vie to be the first across the finish line in a made-for-TV city built for destruction, with the ultimate goal of becoming the season champion. Competitors in Split/Second don't just collide with other vehicles to knock them from the track -- they can also trigger explosive events that drastically alter the dynamics of the race. Players must use strategy and pinpoint timing to derail opponents, tactically alter the track or create entirely new routes. ",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"\"High Octane\" Supercar Vehicle Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/31",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Download the new \"High Octane\" Supercar Pack and enhance your supercar selection with 3 new vehicles as well as a new livery for the upgraded Ryback Cyclone! These are some of the fastest supercars available giving you real speed on the track against your toughest opponents offline and online. Activate your downloadable content on the Press START screen."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"\"The Elite\" Vehicle Livery Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/31",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Download the \"The Elite\" Vehicle Livery Pack and access new liveries for the Elite vehicles of Brawn, Vixen and Raptor. This pack's high-octane new liveries will really make these turbo-powered Elite vehicles stand out from the rest of the crowd like never before! Activate your downloadable content on the Press START screen."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Ryback Cyclone Special Edition",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/31",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Download this special edition vehicle now based on the original classic Ryback Cyclone to look slick on the race track and increase your car collection."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Survival At The Rock Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/05",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Download the Survival At The Rock Pack featuring a brand new Minepit Park Quarry environment as well as a new Survival game mode. This circuit provides a visually stunning new environment to really test your \"defensive\" driving skills. Download the pack today!"
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Deadline Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/20",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Download the \"Deadline\" pack featuring 3 brand new cars and the Ryback Coyote Special. Also included is the brand new single player \"Deadline\" mode. Dodge the Power Plays and drift through pickups to set the fastest time!"
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Onslaught Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/02",
				"type":3,
				"synopsis":"Download the \"Onslaught\" pack featuring the brand new Quarry race track, full of exclusive new Power Plays. Also, 8 players can battle it out in the new Onslaught mode, which brings the Split/Second attack chopper to multiplayer for the first time!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WpnUzI04_1s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C1Vkc86jI80"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l1IdWmjPOE8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XAkvXvsuuVI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958271-split-second/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/SplitSecond/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/split-second/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/splitsecond"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":550,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["HB Studios", "Humongous"],
			"synopsis":"As the snow melts and the temperatures rise, one thing is sure to pop into the minds of boys everywhere: baseball season! Backyard Sports: Sandlot Sluggers allows players to join their favorite neighborhood friends and play ball in fun and exciting arcade style sports action. Sandlot Sluggers is a completely new take on a longtime favorite franchise with all-new features, updated graphics, enhanced gameplay, and extensive options that will keep players and gamers alike enthusiastically entertained.<br><br>Backyard Sports: Sandlot Sluggers offers hours of entertainment with laugh out loud comedic commentary and exaggerated animations for a one-of-a-kind gaming experience. The game is packed with loads of surprises and stars a neighborhood full of fun and diverse kids -- both fan favorite characters and new friends.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MdMxdz94uZc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gbGpijpJtxc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sandlot-Sluggers/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/backyard-sports-sandlot-sluggers/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/backyard-sports-sandlot-sluggers"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":551,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bizarre Creations"],
			"synopsis":"Made by the masters behind Project Gotham Racing and Metropolis Street Racer, Blur is a racing project by Bizarre Creations that aims to take arcade-style action and realistic driving physics to a whole new level. The game drops players into heart-pumping, electrified racing action with 20 cars on a track all targeting the finish line and battling each other as they trade paint and collect intense power-ups, including the ability to blast other cars out of the way with huge bursts of energy, boost their speed, and more.<br><br>While controlling photo-realistic cars, gamers can use offensive and defensive attacks as they battle for the lead and careen through real-world track locations ranging from L.A. and San Francisco to the streets of Hackney, UK and the treacherous roads of Barcelona.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vYNVrTgGYNw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SunVAais0Y4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Upot7mCGYQ8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Spot",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jPqRue51GZ8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wqOZ-PuvLi0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/959893-blur/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Blur/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/blur/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/blur"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":552,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Yuke's Media Creations"],
			"synopsis":"So... you want to be a fighter? UFC Undisputed 2010 delivers the action, intensity and prestige of the Ultimate Fighting Championship. Step into the Octagon to experience the most advanced and commanding virtual MMA action with more than 100 of the best UFC fighters in the world. Experience intelligent and intuitive combat, increased fighter customization, robust career progression, challenging new gameplay modes and explosive online offerings. UFC Undisputed 2010 embodies the ultimate essence and supremacy of a UFC fighter. Ready to be one?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6gAKJmKtO9k"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e9IS6H28N50"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-2YdhU1DWYA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/981302-ufc-undisputed-2010/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/UFC-Undisputed-2010/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ufc-2010-undisputed/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ufc-undisputed-2010"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":553,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Obsidian Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Loyalty carries a price and no one knows this more than agent Michael Thorton. A talented young agent cast out by his government, Thorton is the only one with the information needed to stop an impending international catastrophe. To do so means he must cut himself off from the very people he is sworn to protect. As players determine how to accomplish different objectives, the decisions made and actions taken in each mission will ultimately transform the type of secret agent Michael Thorton will become. Every choice the player makes as Michael Thorton will carry consequences for his future and the fate of the world.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lEMruKVTP6o"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bAoL4TI_i24"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gQ58AqfgENY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 4",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EmXrbo3sRrM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e6PrzYIMjYM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945401-alpha-protocol/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Alpha-Protocol/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/alpha-protocol/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/alpha-protocol"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Alpha Protocol Wiki",
				"url":"http://alphaprotocol.wikia.com/wiki/Alpha_Protocol_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":554,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Natural Motion"],
			"synopsis":"Backbreaker breaks the mold of traditional football video games with realistic, physics-based motion AI, crisp high-definition graphics and a camera angle that follows the perspective of the player. At its core, Backbreaker is full-on 11-versus-11 competitive play, and also includes online multiplayer and split-screen multiplayer modes. In addition, the game features total team customization including a fully featured logo editor.<br><br>The game welcomes newcomers to the genre with its intuitive pick-up-and-play Arcade Mode control scheme, while seasoned players can go head-to-head in the game's demanding Pro Mode that turns off AI and visual assists. Backbreaker also boasts online play for networked action as well as local split-screen modes customized specifically for this game's unique take on the gridiron fight.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gaPI4FwNNXQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=udmgf8sI5GA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZVqaJYiYZSM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Backbreaker/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/backbreaker/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/backbreaker"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":555,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["XS Games"],
			"synopsis":"The Hunt drops players into the wilderness of North America's most famous hunting locations where players will be able to stalk and hunt their prey using a variety of different firearms-bolt-action rifles, shotguns, pistols, bows, and knives. To help them in their hunt they will use Bass Pro Shops gear and equipment like calls, scents, stands and a uniquely designed GPS to guide the player to the action. The Hunt features three game modes: Quick Hunt, Career Mode, and the Bass Pro Shops Continental Classic Hunting Championship as well as four mini-games (Target Range shooting, ATV Racing, Blind Fire, and Coyote Cruise).",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8f-NBtS1V84"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lK3Dsf7C_YQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kZF632siwIA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kCtjt9sl_bg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/BPS-The-Hunt/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/bass-pro-shops-the-hunt/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/bass-pro-shops-the-hunt"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":556,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Vancouver"],
			"synopsis":"Pure Futbol is a unique vision of soccer video games, emphasizing the intense, physical and spectacular aspects of the sport. The over-the-shoulder camera and visceral audio dynamically react to the context of the match, placing the gamer in the heart of the five-a-side soccer action, as opposed to the feeling of watching a TV broadcast.<br><br>Pure Futbol will include 230 elite soccer players, 17 international teams, and 17 legendary players. Gamers will have the opportunity to create their own customized athlete who can progress through the campaign mode to ultimately test themselves against the world's best players in the final tournament. Up to four people can play multiplayer locally and 1vs1 matches are supported online, along with the inclusion of leaderboards that allow players to match up to one another and celebrate the pure competitive nature of soccer.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cB0sQ8InvAU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4eIgSEUfjc4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PKFnJTxh_JI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Pure-Football/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/pure-futbol/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/pure-futbol"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":557,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Red Entertainment", "Idea Factory"],
			"synopsis":"At the dawn of time, a terrible war raged between the forces of good and evil, ending in the destruction of the world of Agarest. After their victory, the Gods of Light unified the decaying bodies of the Gods of Darkness and created a new world. Now, the forces of darkness are awakening once again...<br><br>Choose the path of Darkness or Light through a truly epic story, spanning multiple generations. Battle hundreds of different creatures using an array of character abilities, in a compelling and innovative turn-based combat system. Build your ultimate army of warriors and master Extra Skills, Special Arts and Over Kills to defeat colossal enemies! Unite with your chosen heroine and use the \"Soul Breed\" system to shape the fate of the next generation of heroes.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bgOOPUj0lwo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HPNWxxANo8U"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e6Fx2TRp6m0"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/952954-record-of-agarest-war/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Record-of-Agarest-War/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/record-of-agarest-war/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/record-of-agarest-war"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Record of Agarest Wiki",
				"url":"http://agarest.wikia.com/wiki/Agarest_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":558,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Harmonix"],
			"synopsis":"Featuring the likenesses of Green Day members Billie Joe Armstrong, Mike Dirnt and Tr&eacute; Cool, Green Day: Rock Band covers everything from the band's earliest punk hits to the epic scope of their latest albums, giving players the unique chance to experience the music of this pioneering band in a whole new environment featuring select venues and art specific to the band's history.<br><br>Green Day: Rock Band lets players perform vocals, guitar, bass and drums, as well as featuring special three-part vocal harmonies not only with the on-disc setlist but also when importing Green Day DLC tracks from the Rock Band Music Library of downloadable content. As they progress through the game, players gain access into the band's media vault, where they can unlock collectible images, and rare and unreleased video footage of the band.<br><br>This Plus version of Green Day: Rock Band packs in extra value for Green Day fans. In addition to the full game, this includes an \"export disc\" to pull all of the songs and Green Day character avatars into your Rock Band DLC library. Also featured is a coupon to download six Green Day DLC tracks (21 Guns, Know Your Enemy, East Jesus Nowhere, Viva la Gloria!, Last of the American Girls & Christian's Inferno.)",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"21 Guns",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/07",
				"type":9
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Know Your Enemy",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/07",
				"type":9
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"East Jesus Nowhere",
				"releaseDate":"2009/07/07",
				"type":9
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Viva la Gloria!",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/15",
				"type":9
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Last of the American Girls",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/15",
				"type":9
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Christian's Inferno",
				"releaseDate":"2009/12/15",
				"type":9
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N43SZIbcfvc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SLA9JRSIRZY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Green-Day-Rock-Band/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/green-day-rock-band/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/green-day-rock-band"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Rock Band Wiki",
				"url":"http://rockband.wikia.com/wiki/Green_Day:_Rock_Band"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":559,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"The biggest name in the sport returns for the 2011 edition of the blockbuster golfing franchise. Gamers will select a team and square off to try and bring home The Ryder Cup for their squad. Not only will players have the ability to participate in team play but they will now be able to take a team online. This mode will allow up to 24 players to compete head-to-head as members of team. Team members can also talk strategy with their teammates over Xbox Live.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable courses",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/08",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"New courses available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=snGK56QmzWE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VfY74H86pxU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tiger-Woods-PGA-TOUR-11/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/tiger-woods-pga-tour-11/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tiger-woods-pga-tour-11"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":560,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["505 Games"],
			"synopsis":"Getting underway from New York harbor, Naval Assault: The Killing Tide tells the story of the Allied submariner effort against Axis forces across the key naval warzones of World War II. Players will captain an arsenal of faithfully recreated U.S. Naval submarines against enemy warship assaults both above and below the water's surface. In Naval Assault: The Killing Tide, players will need a healthy dose of stealth and cunning as well as sharp-shooting deck gun and torpedo skills to successfully destroy the enemy fleets in the 30 missions throughout the game.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-D0oruy_OK8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MoT3etjbGd0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Naval-Assault-the-Killing-Tide/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/naval-assault-the-killing-tide/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/naval-assault-the-killing-tide"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":561,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Avalanche Productions"],
			"synopsis":"Embracing the adored and inspired fun of the Toy Story franchise, Toy Story 3: The Video Game features a story mode that follows the Toy Story 3 film adventures in which Buzz, Woody and friends grapple with their uncertain future as Andy prepares to depart for college. Dive into to all new heroic adventures in Story Mode or let your imagination run wild in the exiting new open world of Toy Box Mode!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wGuFgOfRGeo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0VT4JzCFhK4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/945065-disney-pixar-toy-story-3/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Toy-Story-3/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/toy-story-3/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/disneypixar-toy-story-3"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":562,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["505 Games"],
			"synopsis":"Featuring a true-to-life, first-person perspective, in Field & Stream: Total Outdoorsman Challenge, players explore authentic environments, listen for animal calls, check the ground for tracks and sign, and use 'Scent Vision' to spot and track prey. As their hunting skills progress, players can close in on targets by utilizing special scents and decoys, and by setting up permanent hideouts and vantage points. To further challenge players, and add even more authenticity to the hunt, each mission must be completed while respecting local rules and regulations.<br><br>More than 30 big game, small game, predator and game bird species roam each of the multiple environments, which feature exciting wildlife activity and varying weather conditions in both day and night cycles. Gamers can play in serious and casual modes, starting with Practice Mode, where they learn to aim at targets and train with skeet shooting. Free Hunt Mode allows players to hunt any animal without restrictions, regulations or licenses. Players can also experience the thrill of the hunt in Ultimate Hunt Mode-the most challenging, rigorous experience in the game-which requires players to use traditional tracking and stalking techniques to hunt prize catches and brave the wilderness.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lPWN-YTtoUw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Field-and-Stream/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/field-stream-total-outdoorsman-challenge"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":563,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["High Moon Studios "],
			"synopsis":"Transformers: War for Cybertron challenges players to become the ultimate weapon as a Transformers character in the final, epic war that will determine the survival of their entire race. Armed with a diverse arsenal of lethal, high-tech weaponry and the ability to instantly convert from robot to vehicle at any time, players will engage in heart-pounding battles on land and in the air in this gripping, 3rd person action shooter set in the Transformers' war-ravaged homeland.<br><br>Complete with several multiplayer modes, Transformers: War for Cybertron allows gamers to play through story missions with their friends in drop in/drop out online co-op, and also create their own Transformers character for competitive head-to-head multiplayer modes, choosing among four distinct character classes, personalizing its look and selecting from a huge variety of weapons, skills and abilities.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Map and Character Pack #1",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/27",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"New Multiplayer maps are HAVOC and FORTRESS. New Escalation maps are DISTRICT and FORSAKEN. Also access 5 new chassis for multiplayer including SCATTERSHOT, ONSLAUGHT, DEMOLISHOR, SHOCKWAVE and JAZZ."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Map and Character Pack #2",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/07",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"New multiplayer maps include HORIZON, SECTOR and METROPOLIS. New Escalation maps include STATIC and PULSE. Also, the 2 new characters available in Multiplayer are ZETA PRIME and DEAD END."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WtvLeWR8bgs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d4hqgnXHIw8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/981363-transformers-war-for-cybertron/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Transformers-War-for-Cybertron/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/transformers-war-for-cybertron/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/transformers-war-for-cybertron"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Transformers Wiki",
				"url":"http://tfwiki.net/wiki/Transformers:_War_for_Cybertron_(360/PS3/PC)"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":564,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Cave"],
			"synopsis":"Gothic horror and shoot-em-up action collide in Deathsmiles! Face wave upon wave of monstrous creatures intent on your destruction as you turn your skills to the defense of the besieged world of Gilverado. If your trigger finger's itchy, Deathsmiles is the only way to scratch it.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TcChaLM-QPs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=shAm2oeWOjs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-GT6BeURYpA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Deathsmiles/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/death-smiles-na/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/deathsmiles"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":565,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Traveller's Tales"],
			"synopsis":"LEGO Harry Potter: Years 1-4 combines two of the most beloved franchises to deliver a magical, fun-filled adventure. Based on Harry's first four books and films -- Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone, Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban, and Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire -- fans can experience Harry's first four years at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry in a new an exciting way. Players will build the adventure from Privet Drive to the Triwizard Tournament in an interactive journey that takes them through some of the most detailed and expansive environments ever created for a LEGO game. Featuring potion-making, spell-casting, puzzle-solving, and more, players of all ages can relive the adventures like never before with the humor and creative customization that is unique to LEGO videogames.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UbhlMgnE5bM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=033fPhmTTJk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960495-lego-harry-potter-years-1-4/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/LEGO-Harry-Potter/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/lego-harry-potter-years-1-4/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/lego-harry-potter-years-1-4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Harry Potter Wiki",
				"url":"http://harrypotter.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Harry_Potter:_Years_1-4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Brickipedia",
				"url":"http://lego.wikia.com/wiki/LEGO_Harry_Potter:_Years_1-4"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":566,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Feel Plus", "Q Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Set on a ravaged world, N3II: Ninety-Nine Nights invites the player to take on all comers in a series of spectacular battles. Players can enjoy the story from five different perspectives - including humans, elves and goblins - and are pitted against wave after wave of adversaries in the ultimate 'last man standing' free-for-all. Each of the species is given a specific back story which unfolds as the game progresses, while the various races also bring unique skills and abilities to the battle field.<br><br>N3II: Ninety-Nine Nights also has a two-player co-op online mode, wherein players team up against the oncoming hordes, working together to expand their combo range to take out more enemy assailants at once. This two-player mode features online ranking boards detailing the most effective pairings across the globe.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Rolland pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/12",
				"type":2
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Map pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/22",
				"type":4
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Equipment pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/02",
				"type":2
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_wgynxNUE-Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KWd6nL8-KJQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iCDO0PBjq8Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/954476-n3ii-ninety-nine-nights/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Ninety-Nine-Nights-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ninety-nine-nights-ii/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/n3ii-ninety-nine-nights"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":567,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["A2M"],
			"synopsis":"In Naughty Bear, players take on the role of Naughty Bear, a bear driven to seek vengeance after the other bears don't invite him to the big birthday party. Scorned for the last time, Naughty Bear becomes hell bent on manipulating and terrorizing the blissful bears inhabiting the Island of Perfection.<br><br>As Naughty Bear, players will wreak havoc on every stuffing-filled foe that crosses their path. Featuring an array of weapons, objects and scare tactics, gamers strive to earn Naughty Points as they inflict physical and psychological harm on Naughty Bear's enemies. This all-new scare-based points system means players will win the most rewards for being deviant and maniacal. The variety allows for a completely new experience every time players pick up a controller and the ill-fated bears become more difficult to harass and terrorize as the game progresses.<br><br>Naughty Bear features more than 30 levels to unlock, with unique characteristics and weaponry encountered at every stage. Gamers can search the game world and collect all the hidden party items locked away by the other bears.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Episode 8",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/10",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"When Naughty Bear receives an invitation from the other bears to appear as guest of honour at a magnificent Cake Tasting Party, Naughty thinks it is finally a chance to make friends with the other bears. Will Naughty Bear finally make friends with the residents on Perfection Island - or is this much more likely a devious plot to trap him?"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Episode 9: The Treasure of Bear Beard",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/04",
				"achievements":100,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Episode 9: \"Treasure of Bear Beard\" is a completely new episode to add to Naughty Bear. In this episode, Pirates led by the infamous Bear Beard come to the Island to dig up a fantastic treasure said to be hidden right in the middle of the island. Naughty Bear can't let those annoying invaders dig in his backyard, can he!? Along with the new story, get four new pirate costumes to wear. Arm yourself with the powerful Cutlass, a brand new weapon that comes with its unique Ultra-Kill. In addition, complete the four challenges for a total of 20 new Naughty Cups to unlock and 5 new leaderboards to dominate!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Episode 10: The Vampiricorn",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/07",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"In \"Naughty Bear Episode 10: The Vampiricorn\" Stardust summons a vampire hoard to the island, lead by the legendary and terrifying Vampiricorn who is determined to hunt Naughty Bear down and suck his fluff. Fright your way through a bearifying new story, disguise yourself with new costumes and bring death to the undead with the terrifyingly new Vicious Vampire Claw! Four brand new modes also included!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gQWAxgPR0yU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l6AxuaL0XRA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/981294-naughty-bear/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Naughty-Bear/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/naughty-bear/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/naughty-bear"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Naughtypedia",
				"url":"http://naughtybear.wikia.com/wiki/Naughty_Bear_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":568,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Raven Software"],
			"synopsis":"In Singularity, you fight your way through an ever-shifting environment haunted with time ravaged creatures, while sudden time waves hurl you back and forth between 1950 and the present day. Use your wits and the perfect weapon -- the Time Manipulation Device -- to unravel the conspiracy on the remote island of Katorga-12. Armed with powerful, advanced weaponry and this experimental Time Manipulation Device, fight enemies from the past, the present, and abominations caught somewhere in between.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vkk4jK_qVkI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_qCRFcTxckA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6Y2mDE-VtU4"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/956437-singularity/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Singularity/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/singularity/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/singularity"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Singularity Wiki",
				"url":"http://singularity.wikia.com/wiki/Singularity_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":569,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["CI Games"],
			"synopsis":"Based on the covert, shadowy world of the military sniper, Sniper: Ghost Warrior throws players into the chaos of a military coup, as they aid the rebels in restoring the rightful government to the embattled country of Isla Trueno.<br><br>When the democratic government of Isla Trueno is overthrown, an aggressive and hostile military command rises to power. A highly trained special ops unit is sent in to help the rebels accomplish objectives that only a sniper can handle. In addition to intense sniper missions, players will also take part in a variety of assault scenarios where their prowess with weapons will be a huge help to the undermanned rebels.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/14",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Sniper: Ghost Warrior Map Pack further expands multiplayer experience with 5 new maps. Battle to control ruined oil-rigs or lie in wait to capture one of mystic stone towers. This Map Pack brings new sniping spots and chance to eliminate enemies from even longer distance. Sniper: Ghost Warrior Map Pack includes new maps for deathmatch, team deathmatch and VIP modes featuring a variety of new locations!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Second Strike",
				"releaseDate":"2011/08/30",
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Sniper Ghost Warrior Second Strike Pack includes an additional single player campaign called \"Unfinished Business\" with refined AI and new challenging levels. It also introduces a new multiplayer mode (\"Capture the Flag\") and three additional weapons: the M200 and L96 sniper rifles and the Desert Eagle high caliber pistol. To put your skills to the ultimate test we also included the Challenge map."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D63T-XK58v8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C4URFHKeKvU"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hylV64BJFJM"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/991134-sniper-ghost-warrior/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Sniper-Ghost-Warrior/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/sniper-ghost-warrior/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/sniper-ghost-warrior"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Sniper: Ghost Warrior Wiki",
				"url":"http://sniperghostwarrior.wikia.com/wiki/Sniper:_Ghost_Warrior_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":570,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ruffian Games"],
			"synopsis":"In the vertical, free-form world of Pacific City, tensions are high and escalating exponentially between the Agency and its opposing factions, the Cell and the Freaks. Returning to Pacific City as an advanced Agent, you'll be judge, jury and executioner as you reclaim the city and eliminate all threats, either solo or with friends on Xbox LIVE.<br><br>Building upon the groundbreaking success of its predecessor, Crackdown 2 will elevate the open-world genre to unprecedented levels with the ultimate cooperative and competitive multiplayer experiences. Friends around the world will be able to sweep the streets of crime and lawlessness with the complete freedom to explore, destroy and restore justice to Pacific City - by any means necessary.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Premium Deluge Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/31",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Premium Deluge Pack features the complete Deluge co-op arcade mode where you defend the city zones against ever growing waves of Pacific City bad guys. Try it alone or with up to four players on Xbox LIVE for ever more demanding battles.  In addition, the premium pack includes new achievements, avatar awards, and the sixteen-player Capture the Orb mode with 6 arenas."
			},
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Premium Toy Box Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/31",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Expand Crackdown 2 with the Toy Box Pack! It's bursting at the seams with extra toys and treasures, including an expanded Keys to the City mode, the ATV Assault Vehicle, the Squad Chopper, Suit Thrusters, new Agent armor colors, and a Vehicle Tag game, just to name a few. The Toy Box Pack is packed so full it would take a Level 5 Agent to hold it closed!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tnnhj0rBZIg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bYR45iqOufw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hp4h0B7TS08"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960509-crackdown-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Crackdown-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/crackdown-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/crackdown-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Crackdown Wiki",
				"url":"http://crackdown.wikia.com/wiki/Crackdown_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":571,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Now Production"],
			"synopsis":"Compete in one of the biggest baseball competitions in Little League World Series 2010. Little League World Series has everything to offer a baseball player from easy to play mechanics, next generation graphics, new teams and talents, skill challenges and earning achievements to trophies you can win. Online functionality offers the ability to upload records and leaderboards. Don't miss the chance to become the next Little League World Series Champion!",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xV-S3Yvu5EE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YM2AjkfKadI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Little-League-World-Series-2010/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/little-league-world-series-2010/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/little-league-world-series-baseball-2010"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":572,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"NCAA Football provides the ultimate experience for the true football fan, delivering the excitement and pageantry that can only be found in college football. NCAA Football 11 will give players 120 ways to win with real college offenses that, for the first time ever, reflect the authentic style of every NCAA FBS school. NCAA Football 11 recreates the intensity of college football Saturdays, achieving all-new levels of quality in core gameplay for the award-winning franchise.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8K5ovMEPMTY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hYM77FtOtk4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jdWSVGI22qI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VPGCASCalGs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jxmWlhBAT20"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/988956-ncaa-football-11/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NCAA-Football-11/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ncaa-football-11/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ncaa-football-11"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":573,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["ARC System Works"],
			"synopsis":"BlazBlue: Continuum Shift inherits all the key features of its predecessor while adding a few twists of its own. Tsubaki, Micro-12 and Hazama will join the ranks of the veterans, who will be reborn with additional moves to their arsenal. With additional modes like Beginner Mode and Tutorial Mode, even fighting game beginners can pull off combos like the pros and dive right into the action.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Additional System Voice Type-K",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/01",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"This DLC will add the option to switch the announcer's voice of the game to that of Jin Kisaragi. There are two versions included in this package."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Additional System Voice Type-C",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/08",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"This DLC will add the option to switch the announcer's voice of the game to that of Taokaka. There are two versions included in this package."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Additional Character Colors #1",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/08",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The first batch of additional colors. Includes Ragna, Jin, Noel, Rachel, Taokaka, Tager, Litchi, Arakune, Bang, Carl, Hakumen, Lambda, Tsubaki, Hazama, and Mu's colors. Each character will receive four additional colors."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Additional Character Colors #2",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/15",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The second batch of additional colors. Includes Ragna, Jin, Noel, Rachel, Taokaka, Rager, Litchi, Arakune, Bang, Carl, Hakumen, Lambda, Tsubaki, Hazama, and Mu's colors. Each character will receive four additional colors."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Additional System Voice Type-M",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/15",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"This DLC will add the option to switch the announcer's voice of the game to that of Sawashiro Miyuki. There are two versions included in this package."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Additional Character Colors #3",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/22",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The third batch of additional colors. Includes Ragna, Jin, Noel, Rachel, Taokaka, Rager, Litchi, Arakune, Bang, Carl, Hakumen, Lambda, Tsubaki, Hazama, and Mu's colors. Each character will receive four additional colors."
			},
			{
				"id":7,
				"name":"Additional Playable Character \"Makoto Nanaya\"",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/03",
				"achievements":80,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"You can now use the new character, Makoto. This DLC package comes with the Unlimited version and all 12 additional colors. "
			},
			{
				"id":8,
				"name":"Additional Playable Character \"Valkenhayn R. Hellsing\"",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/10",
				"achievements":85,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"You can now use the new character, Valkenhayn. This DLC package comes with the Unlimited version and all 12 additional colors."
			},
			{
				"id":9,
				"name":"Additional Playable Character \"Platinum the Trinity\"",
				"releaseDate":"2011/05/10",
				"achievements":85,
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"You can now use the new character, Platinum. This DLC package comes with the Unlimited version and all 12 additional colors."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BQh1EW3-tAI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MH7ciVrJMGs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zh8GJq9oOkg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/988982-blazblue-continuum-shift/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/BlazBlue-CS/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/blazblue-continuum-shift-jp/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/blazblue-continuum-shift"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Blazblue Wiki",
				"url":"http://blazblue.wikia.com/wiki/BlazBlue:_Continuum_Shift"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":574,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ascaron Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"In DarkStar One - Broken Alliance, players will explore the vast reaches of space, encountering, battling and trading with six mysterious alien races in a quest to unravel the mysterious death of the protagonist's father.<br><br>Players can create their own career paths - be it brigand, mercenary, privateer, merchant or whatever mix they please - while buying (or capturing) alien technology to customize their highly adaptable ship, the DarkStar One, with hundreds of possible combinations of weapons, shields, armor and components. Full 1080p HD graphics and an intuitive, streamlined user interface bring this immersive space combat experience to life.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YTQg6tG8noQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fXuS_EM_gt4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=88o72KbA5lQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AJ9lRvilINQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/DarkStar-One-Broken-Alliance/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/darkstar-one-broken-alliance/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/darkstar-one-broken-alliance"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":575,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Game Republic"],
			"synopsis":"An ambitious fantasy game set against the legends of Greco-Roman myth, this robust action-adventure title is based on the feature film remake of the classic Clash of the Titans. Set in the timeless grandeur of Greek mythology, Clash of the Titans immerses players into the epic battle for dominance between the human race and the powerful gods Hades and Zeus. Through vast landscapes of swamps, mountains and the underworld, two modes of play let players embody Perseus' adventure from the film, or take on original new bosses in fresh, dynamic adaptations of one of the greatest mythological stories ever told.<br><br>An unprecedented style of action-adventure game play will arm players with an ever-changing arsenal of weapons and powers. Players can journey solo or team up with friends to complete quests as they encounter a roster of legendary villains including Medusa and the sea monster known as The Kraken.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Apollo's Challenge Quest Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/05/28",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"This downloadable content will allow players to experience the following additional quests: \"Tyrant of the Swamp\", \"Two Headed Wolf\" and \"Sleeping Bull of the Labyrinth\", Obtain new subweapons and rare gift items by clearing these quests. A challenge from one of the 12 gods of Olympus, the sun god, Apollo! Defeat the mythical beasts from Greek mythology and rise to new heights of power! \"Tyrant of the Swamp\" and \"Two Headed Wolf\" are playable after completion of Main Quest 24 - \"Fall In!\" and \"Sleeping Bull of the Labyrinth\" are playable after completion of Main Quest 49 - \"Taking out the Trash\"."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Hades' Challenge Quest Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/06/23",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"This downloadable content will allow players to experience the following additional quests: \"White Horse of the Underworld\" and \"Absolute Defense\". Obtain new subweapons and rare gift items by clearing this quest. A challenge from one of the 12 gods of Olympus, the god of the underworld, Hades! Defeat the monsters that dwell in the depths of the underworld and rise to new heights of power! Both of these quests are playable after completion of Main Quest 49 - \"Taking out the Trash\"."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Zeus' Challenge Quest Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/07",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"This downloadable content will allow players to experience the following additional quests: \"Temple of the Gods\" and \"Man-eating Monster\". Obtain new subweapons and rare gift items by clearing this quest. A challenge from the king of the 12 gods of Olympus, Zeus! Defeat the monsters that protect the temple of Zeus and rise to new heights of power! Both of these quests are playable only after completion of all main quests in the game."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Athena's Request Quest Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/07/28",
				"type":4,
				"synopsis":"This downloadable content will allow players to experience the following additional quests: \"A Bird in Hand\" and \"Songs of Enchantment\". Obtain new subweapons and rare gift items by clearing this quest. A request has arrived from the goddess, Athena! Can Perseus defeat the monsters that attack his village and save the villagers and his family? Both of these quests are playable after completion of Main Quest 2 - \"Finding Tekla\"."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LP1M9Ec0Txw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hF_Ywlbn-X8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/976417-clash-of-the-titans/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/CLASH-OF-THE-TITANS/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/clash-of-the-titans/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/clash-of-the-titans"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Clash of the Titans Wiki",
				"url":"http://clash-of-the-titans.wikia.com/wiki/Clash_of_the_Titans_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":576,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Tiburon"],
			"synopsis":"Madden NFL 11 redefines the way you experience the game of football. It's simpler: From 350 plays down to 1, the all-new GameFlow system puts you in the helmet of an NFL quarterback to execute an authentic, situational game plan, one play at a time. It's quicker: 60 minute game times reduced to as little as 30 minutes; spend more time on the field and less in the playbook. full games, half the time. It's deeper: Madden NFL 11 is feature-rich including all-new 3-on-3 Online Team Play, improved animations, more intuitive controls, and Madden NFL Ultimate Team... all to the play-by-play of the most exciting voice in sports, Gus Johnson.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2x4gD9jaTTg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eOw4JCc1aZE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RMtgAF3zWWE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/988575-madden-nfl-11/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Madden-NFL-11/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/madden-nfl-11/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/madden-nfl-11"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":577,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Io-Interactive"],
			"synopsis":"After a simple job goes wrong, Kane and Lynch find themselves wanted by the entire Shanghai underworld. Lynch is living the good life as a henchman in Shanghai, where he has settled down with his girlfriend. He's involved in a big arms deal but needs help to make it happen. Kane is a wanderer, an ex-mercenary with family problems who needs to get away. Despite their differences, Lynch calls him for help. Once together, they set-off a chain of events over two days, as the deal falls apart and Kane and Lynch face the consequences the hard way.<br><br>Kane & Lynch 2: Dog Days is a raw and brutal crime shooter designed to take players on an even more intense story experience, following two of gaming's most disturbed criminals, through the gritty Shanghai underworld. Introducing a new visual experience, Kane & Lynch 2: Dog Days is inspired by documentary filmmakers and the user-generated era. Every aspect of the game has been designed to deliver a fresh perspective to the words 'intensity' and 'realism' in videogames.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Doggie Bag",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/31",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"Take on new heists and unlock new Achievement points with 2 never before seen Shanghai maps & 5 exclusive new weapons, all for Multiplayer & Arcade modes. New maps: Dockyard and High Rise provide more opprtunity to increase your wealth. Plus get the Radio Tower multiplayer map (available previously through pre-order offers). Arm yourself with 5 new weapons: DD 33, KL Viper, RTS, SMi 69, and the TOQ Model Four S."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Multiplayer Masks Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/31",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Conceal your identity and avoid revenge attacks with 8 costume masks stolen from a Chinese gift shop, for all Multiplayer modes and Arcade mode. You never want to be identified, especially if you are a traitor! (Previously available through pre-order)."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Alliance Weapon Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/08/31",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Increase your weapons arsenal with 7 powerful weapons for all Multiplayer modes and Arcade mode: the Doretta Silenced, Steele 870, TOQ SBR, Kaliningrad 47, PAC 10 silenced, N 77P Silenced and TOQ Elite. (Weapons previously available through pre-order)."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JsUEhe8Tshg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U4hn4YF6X84"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f02hHq49ja8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/979997-kane-and-lynch-2-dog-days/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Kane-and-Lynch-2-Dog-Days/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/kane-and-lynch-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/kane-lynch-2-dog-days"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":578,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["2K Czech"],
			"synopsis":"Born the son of a poor immigrant, Vito is a beaten down Italian American who is trying to secure his piece of the American Dream. Looking to escape the life of poverty that consumed his childhood, Vito is soon swayed by the lure of power and wealth that a life of Organized Crime can bring.<br><br>A petty criminal his whole life, Vito, along with his childhood friend, Joe, will descend into the world of Organized Crime. Together, they will work to prove themselves to the Mob as they try to make their names on the streets of a cold and unforgiving city.<br><br>Mafia 2 immerses players in the mob underworld of a fictitious late 1940's / early 1950's scenario. The game engages you in a cinematic Hollywood movie experience in a living, breathing city, fusing high octane gunplay with white knuckle driving and an engaging narrative.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Jimmy's Vendetta",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/21",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Meet Jimmy, in this new downloadable pack. A gun for hire, Jimmy helped clean up other people's messes - until he was betrayed by the people who hired him. Now it's payback time. Many new city based missions and new locales give you plenty of reasons to head back to Empire Bay. For more replay action, work to outrank your friends as you rise up the leaderboard. "
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Renegade Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Show off your inner renegade in this new DLC pack. Start with 2 new cars, one with the slick styling and tight handling of a small sports coupe and the other with the revved up engine of a 50s hot rod. Outfit Vito in 2 new suits including leather and lettermen's jackets to fit his renegade persona."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"War Hero Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The 40s wouldn't be complete without a war hero. Vito plays the role well in the War Hero DLC pack. Drive 2 military style vehicles and notice the superior handling in all weather conditions. Vito looks sharp in 2 new military inspired suits, including a full uniform and fatigues."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Vegas Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Get a taste of old school Vegas in this new DLC pack from Mafia II. Bring a taste of Vegas to Empire Bay as you cruise through the town in 2 new cars with smooth handling and timeless lines. Vito shows his Vegas style in 2 new suits."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Greaser Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"The Mafia II Greaser DLC pack is all about speed. These 2 new hot-rod speedsters will win you pink slips every time. Pair that with 2 new suits for Vito, one with leather jacket and heavy boots, the other a leather racing suit, and get ready to start your engines."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Joe's Adventure",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/23",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Play as Joe in this new add-on content. In this extension to the original story of Mafia II, Joe uncovers who had Vito sent to prison and what really went down with the Clemente family. In addition to the expanded story, players can explore new locations and get new cars and clothing in dozens of city-based quests. Plus, online leaderboards allow players to battle for the highest scores."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"All Trailers",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yblmO5jRh7Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JCRZICbhbkY"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/942955-mafia-ii/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Mafia-II/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mafia-ii/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mafia-ii"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Mafia Wiki",
				"url":"http://mafiagame.wikia.com/wiki/Mafia_II"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":579,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"Celebrating the 20th Anniversary of the franchise, NHL 11 aims to to raise the bar yet again for hockey fans. With a revolutionary real-time physics engine that brings an unprecedented amount of realism to the franchise, gameplay innovations like broken sticks and a revamped face-off system, as well as the addition of the Canadian Hockey League, NHL 11 promises to be the most complete hockey videogame ever created.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8UEqkKf67Hg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mG75fXcbJIk"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/991752-nhl-11/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/NHL-11/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/nhl-11/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/nhl-11"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":580,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Eugen Systems"],
			"synopsis":"R.U.S.E. is a one-of-a-kind real-time strategy game that allows players to bluff their enemies to lead their nation to victory, controlling the action using views that range seamlessly from the heart of the battlefield to the full theatre of war. Players will be plunged into the action thanks to the exclusive IRISZOOMTM Engine which offers an intuitive interface that allows for smooth, rapid transitions from a birds-eye view of the entire conflict, down into the heat of the battle and vice versa.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"The Manhattan Project Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/12/21",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The Manhattan Project Pack offers new challenges, including 3 exclusive multiplayer maps (Twilight of the Gods, Vesuvio and Guns 'n' Tulips), along with 2 additional multiplayer modes (Nuclear War and Total War). These modes will affect strategy and pace, allowing you to create nuclear cannons and benefit from accelerated technology evolution."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"The Chimera Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/01/18",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The Chimera Pack breathes new life into both multiplayer and solo skirmishes. First, players will be challenged in 3 new multiplayer maps, with a real change of scenery. Solo mode has not been forgotten, with 3 exclusive challenges. Bir Hakeim drives your army into the Libyan desert, where the Free French Forces resisted the Axis Advance in 1942. You will also play a part in a fight at Majaz al Bab as well as the Zapad operations."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"The Pack of The Rising Sun",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/15",
				"type":8,
				"synopsis":"The Pack of The Rising Sun gives you the opportunity to command the Japanese Army in solo and multiplayer modes. You will also make the most of 28 new units and factories in 3 exclusive operations dedicated to the Imperial Japanese Army (Gold for the Brave, Ostfriesland, and For Honour)"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5ohNzHWL7FI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ESm4AJ_EkB8"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uNUbaqGrf2s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zuvKFs-W55c"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/958986-ruse/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/RUSE/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/ruse/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/ruse"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"R.U.S.E. Wiki",
				"url":"http://ruse.wikia.com/wiki/R.U.S.E._Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":581,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Beenox"],
			"synopsis":"Spider-Man: Shattered Dimensions blends together the many alternate universes of the world-famous webslinger with four unique takes on Spider-Man's history in comics. In the game, Spider-Man attempts to retrieve a piece of a tablet that's been scattered across multiple parallel dimensions, and in doing so he crosses over to storylines famous to comic book aficionados as variant tellings (including The Amazing Spider-Man, Spider-Man 2099, Spider-Man Noir & Ultimate Spider-Man) of the Spider-Man mythology.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KX1W710uA3Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=90BmP93b1pQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3WEASiMUPV8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/991324-spider-man-shattered-dimensions/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Spider-Man-Shattered-Dimensions/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/spider-man-shattered-dimensions/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/spider-man-shattered-dimensions"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Spider-Man Wiki",
				"url":"http://spiderman.wikia.com/wiki/Spider-Man:_Shattered_Dimensions"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":582,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ubisoft Romania"],
			"synopsis":"Tom Clancy's H.A.W.X. 2 plunges fans into an explosive environment where they can become elite aerial soldiers in control of the world's most technologically advanced aircraft. The game will appeal to a wide array of gamers as players will have the chance to control exceptional pilots trained to use cutting edge technology in amazing aerial warfare missions.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"MIG Alley Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/09/29",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Go back in the time to relive the first all-out jet fighter dogfights. Fly two iconic aircraft battling for aerial supremacy in \"Mig Alley\" - the F-86 Sabre and the Mig-15 Fagot. Choose your era and create Team Battles with these planes, or fight other players in the intense battle of the new Trigger Happy mode. Plus, gain access to new bonus skins for the F-22 Raptor and the F-35B Lightning II."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Cold War Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/12",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Take to the skies in two famous aircraft that clashed in the Vietnam War: F-4E-Phantom II and Mig-21 Fishbed. Fight in a new Team Battle mission, Search and Destroy which take place in the Russian mountains, requiring careful manoeuvering when attacking ground targets or dogfighting. Also receive two extra skins for the Eurofighter Typhoon and A-10A Thunderbolt II."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Russian Power pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Unleash the power of the newest, most advanced jet fighter ever built in Russia: The Su T-50 (PAK FA). This fifth generation plane has all that it takes to compete with America's best advanced weapons, stealth technology and high maneuverability. You will also receive a bonus skin for Su-35BM and a new Team Battle mission - High Altitude Warfare. This mission will appeal to players who want fast dogfights and lots of player-versus-player action, with a less emphasis on player-versus-environment."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Bonus Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Fight against other players in Night Raid, a new Team Battle mission where one team attacks and the other defends a besieged city. Additionally, decorate your planes with two new skins, one for the F-15C Eagle and one for the F/A-18E Super Hornet. Content : . New Team Battle Mission: Night Raid . Bonus skin for F-15C Eagle . Bonus skin for F/A-18E Super Hornet"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tF0GrSZ13_Y"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mSFUTO12nrQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6zsZt2r6Tow"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pgpcIavrghg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rSzaHMuF5w8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/996044-tom-clancys-hawx-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Tom-Clancys-HAWX-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/hawx-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/tom-clancys-hawx-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"H.A.W.X. Wiki",
				"url":"http://hawx.wikia.com/wiki/Tom_Clancy's_H.A.W.X._2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":583,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Activision"],
			"synopsis":"Cabela's North American Adventures introduces fresh touches to the popular hunting franchise, including a custom gun builder that allows players the ability to create thousands of gun options with a variety of receivers, stocks, barrels, and scopes. The game also capitalizes on the popularity of hunting shows and online videos by adding a cameraman into gameplay -- to get compelling footage, hunters need to be at their best! And on Xbox 360, up to four players can hunt together co-operatively online.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0ITwa_ot30E"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YA-l8fwbGzI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=atvpaqDnB1M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=648DaHEJUlA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Cabelas-North-American-Adventures/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/cabelas-north-american-adventures/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/cabelas-north-american-adventures"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":584,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Super X Studios"],
			"synopsis":"Greg Hastings Paintball 2 introduces more than 10 single and multiplayer game modes each staged in all-new, paintball locations based on actual fields around the world. Seven single-player game modes challenge the most experienced \"ballers\" to hone their skills and then test them against up to 19 others in seven different multiplayer game types. Whether playing alone or against others, Greg Hastings Paintball 2 ups the ante with game-changing weather conditions and field hazards including rain, wind and fog. The game also features an improved map editor along with the hottest new gear and weapons. When things are at their bleakest, players can even use the all-new cheat meter that lets them avoid elimination by successfully wiping away paint splatter before they're caught.<br><br>Serious \"ballers\" can even become general manager of their own 10-player team composed of more than 100 professional and amateur paintball players. Gamers can trade players, issue commands, and use their earnings from the field to build each player's individual stats, so the overall team is that much more competitive. The better the team assembled, the more tournaments a player stands to win, providing him with added cash to buy new gear, players and skill upgrades.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qQdKFNE93aA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZfO1-CKZVB4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P_Jp1sBjxKw"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/988784-greg-hastings-paintball-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Greg-Hastings-Paintball-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/greg-hastings-paintball-2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":585,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Bungie Software"],
			"synopsis":"In Halo: Reach, players experience the fateful moments that forged the Halo legend. It's the story of Noble Team, a squad of heroic Spartan soldiers, and their final stand on planet Reach, humanity's last line of defense between the terrifying Covenant and Earth. This darker story is echoed by grittier visuals amid a backdrop of massive, awe-inspiring environments. Characters, enemies and environments are rendered in amazing detail by an all-new engine designed to deliver epic-scale encounters against the cunning and ruthless Covenant.<br><br>Once the campaign is over, the battle continues online with an unparalleled multiplayer experience that expands on the award-winning suite of features that helped define the Xbox LIVE experience.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Noble Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/30",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The fight for humanity rages on a galactic scale. From a frozen xeno-archaeology site harboring secrets millennia old to an orbital anchor defending the stars high above planet Reach - and to mysterious places far, far beyond - Bungie's Noble Map Pack injects three new explosive environments into the multiplayer battlefield, each designed to reinforce all of Halo: Reach's vital warfronts, from small scale engagements to massive Invasion battlegrounds."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Defiant Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/03/15",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"The fight for humanity's survival rages on in three brand-new battlefields: a giant orbital station high above the burning surface of the planet, inside the forest of a military wilderness-training facility, and wrapped in the remnants of a civilian mining facility. These awesome new environments comprise 2 multiplayer maps and a Firefight mission that deliver 3 new achievements and 150 gamerscore. Developed by 343 Industries and Certain Affinity."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Anniversary Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2011/11/15",
				"achievements":300,
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Celebrating ten years of Halo, the Anniversary Map Pack comprises seven of the most popular multiplayer maps in Halo history, beautifully reimagined in high definition for Halo: Reach (note that you must have Halo: Reach to play this map pack). Six classic competitive multiplayer maps and a new Firefight mission take you back to your favorite locations from early Halo games, now with the gameplay intensity of Halo: Reach. The Anniversary Map Pack includes seven new achievements and 250 gamerscore. Developed by 343 Industries and Certain Affinity."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Live Action Trailer - Deliver Hope",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gu8VDUDzxkM"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k9ez7iNjoVg"
			},
			{
				"type":"All Trailers",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7CXJXEHTT-s"
			},
			{
				"type":"Campaign Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JVuskwVQLfE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b3-HqL6Dyvo"
			},
			{
				"type":"Multiplayer Gameplay 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LKLbPONnJ9M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Firefight Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pd6S8dyIhms"
			},
			{
				"type":"Invasion Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7uAxrlRlxYI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/960512-halo-reach/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Halo-Reach/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/halo-reach/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/halo-reach"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Halo Nation",
				"url":"http://halo.wikia.com/wiki/Halo:_Reach"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Halopedia",
				"url":"http://www.halopedia.org/Halo:_Reach"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":586,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Krome Studios"],
			"synopsis":"In Legends of the Guardians: The Owls of Ga'Hoole - The Videogame, a young owlet named Soren arrives at the Great Ga'Hoole Tree and tells of his escape from the evil Pure Ones, revealing a new threat to the owl kingdoms. Players take on the role of Shard, a promising young Guardian, setting out on a secret mission to reveal the truth and uncover the sinister plans of the Pure Ones.<br><br>Kids will assemble an unlikely band of heroes as they take on the role of a Guardian, a winged warrior and protector of the owl world. As Shard, players take the fight against evil to the air, armed with battle claws and aided by trustworthy allies. Traveling through the owl kingdoms, fans will have a chance to experience the unique history and lands of Ga'Hoole in the heat of battle. Can you uncover the Pure One plot before it's too late?",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HRGWbH5KNPE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Legend-of-the-Guardians/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/legend-of-the-guardians-the-owls-of-gahoole/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/legend-of-the-guardians-the-owls-of-gahoole"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Ga'Hoole Wiki",
				"url":"http://guardiansofgahoole.wikia.com/wiki/Guardians_of_Ga'Hoole_Wiki"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":587,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["THQ"],
			"synopsis":"Friends and family will be squirming in their seats as they answer some of the game's silliest and most provocative questions in the new Truth or Lies video game.<br><br>Up to eight players can join in on this party game, as they offer up answers to more than 3,000 questions. Additionally, the Hot Seat mode will allow players to put other players on the spot and ask them any question that comes to mind. The gameplay will lead to revealing and hilarious situations among friends and family.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=siwt89Si1Zw"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T_ISw0pEm_M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Truth-or-Lies/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/truth-or-lies/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/truth-or-lies"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":588,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Codemasters Studios Birmingham"],
			"synopsis":"The first Formula One game to take advantage of high definition consoles and PC platforms, F1 2010 is the official game of the 2010 FIA Formula One World Championship and includes all of the official teams, drivers and circuits from the 2010 season. The game features the return of seven times Formula 1 Drivers' World Champion Michael Schumacher, the introduction of several new teams, and the brand new Korean International Circuit that host the 2010 Formula 1 Korean Grand Prix.<br><br>In F1 2010 gamers will take on the full, expanded grid in a variety of game modes including Grand Prix, Championship, Time Trial and an extensive, innovative Career mode. F1 2010 also features a highly advanced damage model, fully dynamic weather system and extensive competitive multiplayer options. The game was developed using the EGO Game Technology Platform, Codemasters' proprietary tech that powered the critically acclaimed, million-plus selling Colin McRae: DiRT 2 and Race Driver: GRID. The award-winning technology has been further developed to accurately recreate the unique aerodynamics and handling of 200MPH+ Formula 1 cars.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ixaGnxlRbA4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qoRCznoNqY4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8aKmx1fULrc"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/F1-2010/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/f1-2010/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/f1-2010"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":589,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Blue Castle Games"],
			"synopsis":"Several years have passed since the Wilamette incident, and Dead Rising 2 shifts the action from the everyday world of mid-West America to the glitz and glamour of Fortune City, America's latest and greatest entertainment playground. People flock to Fortune City from around the globe to escape from reality and the chance to win big and for some, this means competing in Terror is Reality.<br><br>Like millions of Americans, former national motocross champion Chuck Greene is gripped by the TV sensation that is Terror is Reality. Hosted by the flamboyant Tyrone King, Terror is Reality pits ordinary members of the public against an arena full of zombies with a simple challenge - kill more zombies than your opponents and stay alive with the winner collecting big money and the chance to come back and secure even greater prizes. So, what is it that has forced Chuck to come to Fortune City and risk his life in the modern day gladiatorial contest, is he trying to recapture the fame of his motocross days, does he have a reason to hate zombies, or is it simply the lure of big money?",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Skills Pack - Psycho",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/12",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Wearing this special costume gives Chuck all the shockingly disturbing abilites of a deranged homicidal psychopath! Actually, that's quite handy if you're surrounded by a horde of zombies. Some of the special abilites Chuck's costume-enhanced psyche affords him include better resistance to damage due to his deranged state, stronger attacks with some classic killing implements such as the chef knife and chainsaw, as well as truly sick new attacks for weapons loved by murderous maniacs everywhere, including the machete, mining pick and meat cleaver!"
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Skills Pack - Soldier",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/19",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Chuck becomes a battle-hardened soldier when he wears this costume. Mowing down zombies in a hail of bullets has never been more fun! These clothes give Chuck special abilities such as improved battle effectiveness when using firearms. Chuck also gains new attacks when using assault rifles. This pack is just what you need when you want to go on a bullet-fueled zombie killing spree!"
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Skills Pack - Sports Fan",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/26",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"This special costume brings out Chuck's inner sports fan! By wearing this costume, Chuck gains incredible sports fan powers, such as being able to drink as much alcohol as he wants without getting sick, gaining more health from food and winning more when gambling. Plus, attacks with sports-related items such as footballs and soccer balls become more powerful. Let's hear it for Chuck, and that Local Sports Team!"
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Skills Pack - Ninja",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"When Chuck wears this incredibly cool outfit, he gains the power of the legendary Japanese ninja! With this costume equipped, Chuck will be harder for zombies to grapple and can move through crowds of zombies easier. He will also gain new sword attacks, and throwing weapons (plates, nails, CDs, etc) fly farther and do more damage. Why? Because he is dressed like a ninja!"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uUdA2VVNY3w"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ju1FTmdU1FA"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/957985-dead-rising-2/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Dead-Rising-2/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/dead-rising-2/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/dead-rising-2"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Dead Rising Wiki",
				"url":"http://deadrising.wikia.com/wiki/Dead_Rising_2"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":590,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["EA Canada"],
			"synopsis":"Play on until the final whistle with the 2011 edition of EA's officially-licensed FIFA game series. FIFA Soccer 11 delivers a true soccer experience with authentic club and leagues licenses and gameplay refinements and innovations that combine to create the complete soccer simulation.<br><br>FIFA 11 reinvents player authenticity -- on and off the ball -- for every player and at every position on the pitch with Personality+, an all-new feature that sees individual abilities reflected in game, enabling clear differentiation for every player. With Personality+ a footballer's abilities on the pitch is mirrored authentically in game, creating individual personalities. Goalkeepers have also been injected with Personality+, so whether acrobatic or traditional, will dictate his style in game.<br><br>FIFA 11 also introduces new Pro Passing where pass accuracy is determined by a gamer's ability on the control pad, and player skill, situation and urgency on the pitch, yielding a deeply rewarding passing system. Plus, a series of new customization tools will enable fans to transform FIFA 11 in new and personally meaningful ways. Assign customized chants for every team and league and play music tracks from your existing library from within the game.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Live Season: Barclays Premier League",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/01",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Get weekly in game player updates for the Barclays league for the rest of the 2010-2011 season."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Live Season: Spanish Liga BBVA",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/01",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Get weekly in game player updates for the Spanish Liga BBVA for the rest of the 2010-2011 season."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Live Season: Italian Serie A",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/01",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Get weekly in game player updates for the Italian Serie A for the rest of the 2010-2011 season."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Live Season: German Bundesliga",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/01",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Get weekly in game player updates for the German Bundesliga for the rest of the 2010-2011 season."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Live Season: French Ligue 1",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/01",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Get weekly in game player updates for the French Ligue 1 for the rest of the 2010-2011 season."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Ultimate Team",
				"releaseDate":"2011/02/16",
				"type":7,
				"synopsis":"Build your own Ultimate Team with all your favorite football stars, choose to manage one or multiple squads & then compete in dynamically updated online tournaments."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H0jH7_cnnvs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_sBqAIqzIao"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/988949-fifa-soccer-11/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/FIFA-11/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/fifa-11/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/fifa-soccer-11"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":591,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Double Helix"],
			"synopsis":"In the future, the world is a changed place. Technology has advanced. Countries have merged into massive geopolitical blocks. But one thing, sadly, remains the same - humanity's appetite for war. When a terrorist attack destroys one of the U.C.S.'s prized orbital elevators, the military is mobilized to eliminate the threat. Dylan Ramsey, a young engineer, finds himself quickly caught in a swirl of destruction, conspiracies and crumbling alliances...<br><br>Front Mission Evolved brings the classic Front Mission franchise into an action-packed third-person shooter that gives players full control of a massive humanoid war machine -- the wanzer. Choose from dozens of weapons and parts, including weapons that can be equipped on both hands and shoulders, to customize your wanzer and blast your way to victory. When you think you're ready for a new challenge, join the ranks of online pilots for multiplayer battles.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Wanzer Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Smash the competition with a wanzer evolved from the Front Mission franchise's past Wildgoat and 1 brand-new type ISV-Prototype."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Wanzer Weapons Pack 1",
				"releaseDate":"2010/10/28",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Cut down the competition with these 3 new weapons - Machine Gun: Dark Hog, Shotgun: Blackstone, and Rifle: Sieger."
			},
			{
				"id":3,
				"name":"Wanzer Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Crush the competition with 2 wanzers from the Front Mission franchise - the Stork Mk. IV and Tatou."
			},
			{
				"id":4,
				"name":"Wanzer Weapons Pack 2",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/02",
				"type":2,
				"synopsis":"Blast your enemies with these 3 additional weapons - Bazooka: Rock Jack, Rocket Launcher: Wild Goose, and Missile Launcher: Goldias."
			},
			{
				"id":5,
				"name":"Last Stand",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/23",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"Endless swarms of the enemy are invading. Can you and your team hold them off? Multiplayer co-op mode."
			},
			{
				"id":6,
				"name":"Map Pack",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/23",
				"type":1,
				"synopsis":"2 new maps to conquer! Play all classic multiplayer modes on these maps."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JP28a84Fvjg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gOTnzRCH0pg"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/959895-front-mission-evolved/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Front-Mission-Evolved/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/front-mission-evolved/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/front-mission-evolved"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"front Mission Wiki",
				"url":"http://frontmission.wikia.com/wiki/Front_Mission_Evolved"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":592,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Neversoft Entertainment"],
			"synopsis":"Guitar Hero: Warriors of Rock breathes new life into gamers' current Guitar Hero music libraries providing literally hundreds of hours of replayability with the introduction of Quickplay+, which features 13 totally unique gameplay challenges for every on-disc track as well as most downloadable and importable songs from Guitar Hero World Tour forward.<br><br>Gamers will complete challenges such as Band Streak, High Score and Power Challenge, which allows players to choose any two warrior powers they have unlocked to try and earn ridiculously high scores, to rank up and unlock more rewards and content than ever before. All-new Challenge Leaderboards have been created in order to capture the outrageous scores that are capable with Quickplay+.<br><br>Guitar Hero: Warriors of Rock features more than 90 tracks that include guitar shredding hits from bands such as Black Sabbath, Megadeth and Slipknot and larger than life anthems from Queen, Muse and KISS. Additionally, Dave Mustaine of Megadeth wrote and recorded \"Sudden Death\", an original track for the game, which was inspired by Quest Mode's storyline. Along with original songs, the set list also includes special re-records by famous artists and tracks from bands that are making their music video game debut.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Downloadable tracks",
				"releaseDate":"2008/10/26",
				"type":9,
				"synopsis":"More than 100 tracks available for download at the marketplace"
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ht7Jn55kzUI"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8D6k7Pe2gFI"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/991401-guitar-hero-warriors-of-rock/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Guitar-Hero-Warriors-of-Rock/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/guitar-hero-warriors-of-rock/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/guitar-hero-warriors-of-rock"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Wikihero",
				"url":"http://guitarhero.wikia.com/wiki/Guitar_Hero:_Warriors_of_Rock"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":593,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Buka Entertainment", "Targem Games"],
			"synopsis":"Aliens have attacked Earth, killing millions in mere seconds. In a desperate attempt to retaliate, world leaders defended themselves with nuclear weapons. Now the aliens populate the planet, the world is a wasteland and the few remaining human survivors are relegated to dwelling in sewers, subways and basements to plot their revenge.<br><br>An action-packed third-person shooter, MorphX drops players into the middle of the fallout in Moscow, Russia. As part of the new resistance, players awaken in an alien laboratory with the option to enhance their stamina and health with Alien DNA, but at the cost of gradually turning into a monster. In an effort to fight the aliens and find an antidote to the mutation, players can choose to either use the Alien DNA to their advantage, or reject it and focus solely on collecting a variety of weapons to take down their enemies.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0m3g3r85edA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UG2Lit4EPF8"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/988437-morphx/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MorphX/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/morphx/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/morphx"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":594,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["The Sims Studio"],
			"synopsis":"In MySims SkyHeroes, players take to the sky to lead the resistance against Morcubus and his drone army and to stop his plans to take over the skyways.<br><br>Starting as an unknown pilot, players fight to become a celebrated hero as they defeat dangerous enemies in aerial combat, test their reflexes in fast-paced speed challenges, and take on massive enemy bosses that demand all their skills as a pilot to survive. As they progress, players build, customize and tune their aircraft to give them an edge in combat - upgrade wings for swifter maneuvers, switch out the engine for a speed boost, or change the paint job to camouflage the plane and avoid enemy fire.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g30yOOm7q-M"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4SFHQnqfj8I"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/MySims-SkyHeroes/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/mysims-sky-heroes/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/mysims-skyheroes"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"MySims Wiki",
				"url":"http://mysims.wikia.com/wiki/MySims_SkyHeroes"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":595,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Team Tachyon"],
			"synopsis":"Many years have passed since the world war inflicted catastrophic damage on the human race, leaving only a few survivors. In their new community Cocoon, life has been threatened by a black material called Erosion, creating a post-apocalyptic environment. Surviving humans recruit a militia to conquer the Erosion and set out to take down the evil, Living Tower. Arriving at the scene is the stalwart warrior Syd, whose only intentions are to destroy the Tower. He meets the beautiful and mysterious Filena as they both ascend to the top in their search for answers.<br><br>In this hyper-real action-shooter game, players experience Syd and Filena's adventurous ascent through a treacherous tower, presented in an art nouveau style world that is on the verge of becoming post-apocalyptic, which merges the beauty of organic motifs with technology and action-packed gameplay.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ob4oLHO6h64"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=no7eHbSHEHs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Quantum-Theory/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/quantum-theory"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":596,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Activision"],
			"synopsis":"Rapala Pro Bass Fishing pits players against real-life fishing pros on top freshwater lakes across North America - only the finest techniques and equipment will determine who is the best of the best.<br><br>For the first time ever in a fishing game, the competition is set up in a professional tournament structure and the action is presented as a live TV event with announcers (including Barry Brueland, the voice of InFisherman TV), live updates, competitive leader boards, analysis, and heart-pounding final weigh-ins. The competition gets tough as you fish through over 20 tournament events on your quest for the season trophy.<br><br>Equipped with an unequaled assortment of licensed boats, rods, lures, and apparel, players can fish by themselves, compete, or challenge friends in contests in simultaneous 2-player mode. There are over 50 of these contests, including challenges based on location, time, fish weight and accuracy of casts.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b1v46_TGVz4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_ju5l0mVPnY"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Rapala-Pro-Bass-Fishing/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/rapala-pro-bass-fishing/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/rapala-pro-bass-fishing-2010"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":597,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Extreme Sports"],
			"synopsis":"As the first skateboarding game in the best-selling Shaun White video game franchise, Shaun White Skateboarding will provide an innovative twist and fresh take on the skateboarding and action-sports genre.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HwMWmCn9jpg"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j-X07FT5UpQ"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 3",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zC30hAcjvwA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JLHBQTuVDI4"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Shaun-White-Skate/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/shaun-white-skateboarding/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/shaun-white-skateboarding"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":598,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["MercurySteam"],
			"synopsis":"It is the end of days and ungodly powers isolate the Earth. The worlds' alliance with the heavens has been threatened by a dark and malevolent force -- the mysterious Lords of Shadow. Across this shattered land, the souls of the dead wander unable to find peace, whilst creatures of evil wreak chaos and death upon the living.<br><br>Gabriel Belmont is a member of the Brotherhood of Light, an elite group of holy knights who protect and defend the innocent against the supernatural. His beloved wife was brutally murdered by the evil forces of darkness and her soul trapped for eternity. Neither living nor dead she realizes the horrific truth of what is at stake and guides Gabriel to his destiny -- and hopefully salvation for the world.<br><br>Castlevania: Lords of Shadow casts the player as the mysterious Gabriel. At its heart it is a vast third-person-viewed adventure, but combat and puzzle solving also play a major part in the main quest, while dark artifacts can be used to enhance Gabriel's powers.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Reverie",
				"releaseDate":"2010/04/19",
				"achievements":150,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"After the events of Castlevania: Lords of Shadow, Gabriel Belmont stands on the edge of an abyss contemplating his fate. In the darkest shadows of his mind, he hears her cry for help. Laura, the vampire child who had spared him during his quest, is in danger. Gabriel decides to repay his debt of honour to her and returns to the castle in order to offer his aid but comes face to face with his own terrible destiny."
			},
			{
				"id":2,
				"name":"Resurrection",
				"releaseDate":"2011/06/07",
				"achievements":120,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Follow up to Castlevania: Lords of Shadow \"Reverie\". Gabriel's fate and that of the Belmont clan is laid bare, as he battles the evil demon known only as \"The Forgotten One\". Imprisoned by the original founders of the brotherhood, this evil is now breaking free from its dimensional prison. Who will prevail? A demon who wishes to destroy mankind or a dark soul filled with furious rage, intent on revenge at any cost. Find out in Resurrection, the stunning finale to Castlevania: Lords of Shadow."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k-0M_AzQ3aE"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5G45MqKCVJE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/952493-castlevania-lords-of-shadow/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Castlevania-Lord-of-Shadows/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/castlevania-lords-of-shadow/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/castlevania-lords-of-shadow"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Castlevania Wiki",
				"url":"http://castlevania.wikia.com/wiki/Castlevania:_Lords_of_Shadow"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":599,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["4mm Games"],
			"synopsis":"Def Jam Rapstar is a music game based hip-hop music and culture. The game provides the ultimate emcee video game experience, and captures the essence of what Hip-Hop is all about: the Music, the Flow, the Battles, and of course... the Swagger. With a host of the greatest Hip Hop songs available at release, the game allows you to be the star: by rhyming, using your console camera, and uploading your video to the fully integrated Def Jam Rapstar community at www.defjamrapstar.com. Def Jam Rapstar also offers you the ability to freestyle over tracks by some of the hottest Hip Hop producers and upload your freestyle performances for the world to decide how good you really are.",
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f-fCN9V8oGA"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WStPcWGjTmk"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GWruzwcYj5Q"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Def-Jam-Rapstar/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/def-jam-rapstar/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/def-jam-rapstar"
			},
			{
				"type":"Wiki",
				"site":"Def Jam Wiki",
				"url":"http://def-jam-wrestling.wikia.com/wiki/Def_Jam_Rapstar"
			}]
		}
	},
	{
		"id":600,
		"details":
		{
			"developer":["Ninja Theory"],
			"synopsis":"More than 150 years in the future, the world has transformed into an unrecognizable state where all that remains are a dwindling human population and merciless robots left over from wars long past. In Enslaved, players take on the role of Monkey, a strong and brutish loner, and his AI partner Trip, a technologically savvy but sheltered young woman from a peaceful community. Both become captured by a mysterious slave ship, which are rumored to harvest people and take them out west never to return. As they each attempt to escape, Trip realizes quickly that Monkey, with his raw strength and power, is the only hope she has of making the perilous journey back home. She hacks into a slave headband to enslave Monkey and link them together - if she dies, he dies. Her journey has now become his.<br><br>Players must make sure both Monkey and Trip work together as they skillfully navigate through the world and survive against the dangerous enemy obstacles that lie in wait. Monkey will deftly wield his trusty staff weapon to attack and defend against enemies, using a combination of melee attacks, blocks and counters. He will also be able to perform spectacular takedown moves, allowing him to rip an enemy apart piece by piece, take its weapon for his own use or destroy it in one final blow.",
			"dlcs":[
			{
				"id":1,
				"name":"Pigsy's Perfect 10",
				"releaseDate":"2010/11/23",
				"achievements":250,
				"type":0,
				"synopsis":"Pigsy, the comical porcine character known for his one-line zingers and questionable hygiene, will finally get his time in the spotlight. The Titan Graveyard is a lonely place and Pigsy really needs some companionship. He dreams of the perfect woman and embarks on a mission to build one from scratch using scrap parts he finds around the junkyard. In addition to a new playable storyline, the DLC offers various modes of 3D which enhance the game's eye-popping visuals even further. Players can experience both the full main game as well as the new Pigsy story in 3D."
			}],
			"links":[
			{
				"type":"Trailer 1",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XnrOPv1Peno"
			},
			{
				"type":"Trailer 2",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NmfAORuigW0"
			},
			{
				"type":"Gameplay",
				"site":"YouTube",
				"url":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fUFnSCmnRAE"
			},
			{
				"type":"FAQs, walkthroughs and cheats",
				"site":"GameFAQs",
				"url":"http://www.gamefaqs.com/xbox360/975240-enslaved-odyssey-to-the-west/faqs"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement list",
				"site":"TrueAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.trueachievements.com/Enslaved-Odyssey-to-the-West/achievements.htm"
			},
			{
				"type":"Achievement guide",
				"site":"XboxAchievements",
				"url":"http://www.xboxachievements.com/game/enslaved/guide/"
			},
			{
				"type":"Reviews",
				"site":"Metacritic",
				"url":"http://www.metacritic.com/game/xbox-360/enslaved-odyssey-to-the-west"
			}]
		}
	}]
}